Episode 16
There's one thing I want to tell
you about the Blood Rage...
You don't know everything
there is to know.
Episode 16: Traces of the Dragon Emperor
There's actually a technique to raise
the purity of your dragon blood
and empower your bloodline,
while remaining unaffected by it.
But since it drains you heavily,
it uses a dragon blood serum.
But we only have enough for one person.
Do you know about the Nibelungen Plan?
It's something the School Board
has been plotting.
The most talented student will be
chosen to employ that technique.
Meanwhile, they also aim to eradicate
individuals with dangerous bloodlines.
You, for instance.
Or perhaps Lu Mingfei.
If this is a Gattuso family project,
the one they opt for will
definitely be Caesar.
Correct. But it means more
to you than it does to him.
For you, it's the only way to survive.
What do I do?
Prove yourself greater than Caesar.
Go to Shin and kill a Dragon
Emperor, just as Caesar did.
Understood.
Everyone should have an equal chance.
Make haste and prepare.
You leave in three hours.
Why are you forcing Finger to go?
He was originally an A-rank student.
He was wounded on a certain mission
and ended up in his current state.
Ten years ago, he was much like you.
He needs a chance to find himself again.
A knife?
It has the power to slay the Four Rulers.
A friend's family had an
alchemical weapon that shattered.
The fragments were used to create this.
Best of luck.
Thank you, Principal.
We'll leave in two hours.
I have prepared the weapons we need.
What's that?
A modified blowtorch.
We call it "Dragon's Breath."
Its chemical fuel is nitroglycerin,
and you can infuse it with mercury.
It can do some damage, but if you run
into a first generation dragon...
Well, you can use it as a flashlight.
This is a lighter?
Did you turn it into a bomb?
Anyone could do that.
So instead I gave it voice
capabilities and a speaker.
That's so cool!
Senpai, can I take it?
Of course. I assume you'll
want a bazooka too?
I'll pass.
I helped Chu Zihang,
but we're not friends.
Will you accept a gift from an enemy?
Or will you join the Student
Union and become my friend?
Sure. But as a spy.
Is that all right?
I'll consider it.
Caesar, I have something special for you.
The School Board told me to
give it to you personally.
Interesting. Want to see what's in it?
Sure.
A crossbow?
Philosopher's stone?
Pseudomatter. Crystallized fire element.
Specially refined.
Seems strong.
The Gattuso family is giving
you all the support it can.
Please slay the Dragon Emperor
of Earth and Mountains.
Are you from the clan?
I'm the Deputy Leader of
the Equipment Department.
If you run into a Dragon
Emperor, don't hesitate.
They won't give you time to think.
Senpai!
Can you give us some privacy?
We'll meet in two hours,
then leave for Shin immediately.
Okay, I'll bring Nono,
and I won't be late!
The photocopies of those
documents you requested.
The Lionheart Society had them.
That's all there is to know
about Blood Rage.
You should be able to interpret them.
You keep your promises.
Chu Zihang lets you handle these
things because he trusts you.
Aren't you betraying him
by giving this to me?
That's none of your business.
That was the deal, right?
If you supported him at the hearing,
I would give you these copies.
I've got other stuff to do. Goodbye.
Won't Chu Zihang hate you
when he finds out that someone
else can use Blood Rage?
He's just a selfish child who
can't take care of himself.
A selfish child?
Yes. A stubborn, selfish child.
He wants everyone else to save him.
You're going a little
too far to help him.
Me liking him and him liking
me are two separate things.
If I were you, I'd fight to win him.
Goodnight.
Thank you for flying with us.
The seats are so cramped.
It's a direct flight. Fourteen hours.
Get some rest, and you'll be
good to go when we land.
Always the perfect student.
I'm going to sleep.
Night.
I guess I'll hit the can.
Th-They're all...
Are you looking for your seat?
I'm sorry, everyone on this flight is...
I'm aware.
Those without dragon blood
cannot board this flight.
Everyone on board is a hybrid?
Then this plane...
...is a flying hybrid fortress.
What the hell?
Why are you being so stingy
if we're related?
Two drinks for the whole flight?
Give me all-you-can-drink!
Selling information on the Dragon Emperor
for 200,000 dollars
Phoenix
Direct Message
Message Sent
Whoa!
Look what I saw online!
It's supposed to be the
sky over Antarctica.
The dragons look like they're
escorting that private jet.
It's AI-generated. If it was real,
nobody would publish it.
Then...
Lu Mingfei! You're here too, huh?
Is that you, Tang? It's been forever!
We meet again!
These are my friends,
Finger and Chu Zihang.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks.
Are they dragonslayers too?
"Too"? Do you mean...
Yes. This is a charter flight, after all.
Passengers are checked before the
flight. They're all hybrids.
They're here to slay the dragon.
Do you need that many people?
Listen, mister, are you serious
about killing a dragon?
I'm not that arrogant.
It's a big event. I want to see
it for myself, or I'll regret it.
So I took time off and came
with some friends of mine.
We'll have a vacation, too.
Look, some people are
bringing their families.
So if you can't kill the dragon,
you just go on vacation?
We'll look for dragons while
we enjoy our vacation.
Great plan...
I think I've felt this presence before...
That's right! A tanker just ran
aground and sank five minutes ago.
Self driving again? You're so lazy.
Renewable energy stocks are
going to go through the roof!
So...
Looks like you're keeping busy here.
Don't touch me.
It won't kill you, will it?
Did you look at the documentation?
That bounty site that's
recruiting hunters?
I saw it. Whoever posted it is clever.
They've gathered hybrids
from all around the world.
In just the past week, three charter
flights came from An to Shin.
Over 1,000 hybrids are here in Shin.
Some of them have such weak bloodlines
that just getting close to the
Dragon Emperor will kill them.
They're coming not just from within
Shin, but around the world.
And that includes Finger von
Frings, Chu Zihang, and Lu...
I saw our little baby.
Which means we should have new
orders from the boss, right?
I got an email from the
boss three hours ago.
We're to make sure Lu Mingfei
personally slays the Dragon Emperor.
Not again...
How much time do we have to spend
looking out for that loser?
How lucky can one guy get?
Everybody wants to be his babysitter.
I don't know what the boss is thinking,
but orders are orders.
Lu Mingfei has to kill the Dragon Emperor,
and anyone else who sees the
Dragon Emperor has to die.
So the charter flights were cursed, huh?
Fine, I'll take them out, too.
But the problem is Lu Mingfei.
How does that loser
kill a Dragon Emperor?
I think it's doable.
He's got the Seven Deadly Sins.
They're capable of killing
any Dragon Emperor.
It's just a matter of
whether he can draw them.
Do we really have to do all
this to help that kid?
What's going through the boss's head?
Nothing, probably.
Lu Mingfei's a lucky boy.
Is he really happy to have
everyone helping him?
Nobody can give him happiness.
He's standing on the edge of loneliness.
And each time he's about to fall
into the abyss of sadness,
somebody reaches out and
offers a hand to stop him.
I've got this feeling...
That if someday he really does despair...
What'll happen?
He might turn into a demon.
Lots of data, no clues.
Can we really find the
Dragon Emperor like this?
Where'd Lu Mingfei go?
Net cafe.
He said he'd get in the
way if he gamed here.
We're relying on you.
They're a team of elites,
but we're just the unwanted stepchildren.
You're not using that phrase right.
A stepchild is a child
from a previous marriage.
Like me, for instance.
What are you fiddling with?
Aren't we here to slay dragons?
Shouldn't we go grab our gear
and hunt some dragons?
If "gear" means "cameras,"
then everybody's doing it for us.
They went straight to the tourist
spots from the airport.
There are many traces of dragons,
and both the geography and
buildings have dragon designs.
But the real information
we need is still hidden.
That's why I'm looking into seismic
data from the past few years.
Earthquakes went up by a
factor of ten this year.
I built an inference model
that might help us pinpoint
the epicenter where
the Dragon Emperor is.
Wow! I'm impressed!
A little hard to understand
for a humanities student, huh?
Am I in humanities?
I've been at the school nine years,
and I never knew!
So your theory is that the Dragon
Emperor is in a single place?
Any chance he's moving around?
Why would he?
Is he commuting to work?
Fair point.
He'd stay hidden and build his power.
He's planning on reviving at full
strength and wiping us all out.
But that data will help us
get one up on Caesar's team.
Maybe. There's a lot of stuff in
a city that can cause tremors.
And we don't have time
to examine every one.
Chu Zihang!
Xia Mi is here!
Come in!
Hello, Senpai!
What a mess...
So this is like a boys' dorm?
Wow, she's so cute!
Let your Senpai give you a hug!
I figured you'd be hungry,
so I brought you some snacks.
Wow! Local gourmet food?
Huh? Where's Lu?
He's off training.
We can split his share.
I'm local, so I bought these while
I was taking a side trip home.
I'm so happy I could cry!
That's our spy for you!
So your heart's always with us, huh?
Of course!
You're the most wonderful
guy of all, Finger!
Hey, Chu Zihang! Did you hear that?
My irresistible charm is giving us an
escape from eating just junk food!
Senpai, what's this?
Looking for the Dragon
Emperor using seismic data?
Yes. But there's too much
data for me to analyze.
Like waves on the surface while the
fish hides at the bottom of the lake.
When it fully awakens, it'll burst
through the water in dragon form.
But it'll be too late then.
So for now, it's in human form?
Correct.
Which is why it was able to destroy those
buildings without attracting suspicion.
But its power is limited like that.
It's the same as it was with
Dragon Emperor Norton.
It takes time to assume a dragon
body... Like hatching an egg, huh?
Okay, before that happens, why
don't you come eat with my family?
Why?
I told them how nice you've
been, and my parents said—
Hold it! You're introducing
him to your parents?
It was such a brief dream...
What does that mean?
Xia Mi, as you can see, I'm busy now.
I don't think I'll have time to go.
Tell them I said hi.
It's just a meal. It won't
take more than a few hours.
My brother wants to see you too.
He was shouting on the phone about
how much he wants to play with you.
That's why I'm asking you.
Don't say no.
When is it?
Tomorrow at noon. How does gyoza sound?
Okay.
Sorry, I'm busy.
I'd like to go with you,
but I won't have time.
Busy with what?
Visiting a museum.
Anyway, Miss Spy, where is Caesar now?
The antiques district, I think.
So you're Mr. Lin Fenglong, who
uses the name "Phoenix" online?
Mr. Caesar Gattuso?
So young.
I didn't come to drink tea.
I'll buy your information
on the dragon for $200,000.
I guess some hunters don't
mind spending money.
We'll both get what we want.
There's a certain spot on a
street not far from here...
During the days of the old dynasty,
they made gunpowder there.
Back then, it had another name.
"The Gunpowder Bureau."
The Gunpowder Bureau explosion
ranks among the top three in history.
It's said that all three were caused
by awakening Dragon Emperors.
Four hundred years ago...
A certain Dragon Emperor
revived in this city.
The one you're looking for.
This old book dates from the dynasty era.
It's made from mulberry bark
and dragon beard grass.
Records
of Strange
Disasters
It's written by an unknown author,
and contains more information about
the explosion than any other book.
It's the only one of
its kind in the world?
No, there are plenty of copies.
But the one you're holding is
quite different from the others.
It contains an extensive
section on geomancy.
Geomancy?
Feng Shui.
It explains in detail how
to find dragon veins.
And that's where you'll find the dragon.
Most addresses are the same today as
they were during the dynasty days.
But some names have changed.
As thanks for your purchase,
I'll give you a map from that era.
Is it part of your collection?
Nope. It was published by the Shin
Map Publishing company 20 years ago.
We have a deal.
Thank you for your business.
I'll tell you one thing.
I paid for this because it's real.
But if you've got some other game
you're playing, you'll regret it.
Will this do?
I told him what you asked me to.
You can hide, but it won't work.
His Yanling is "Wind Devil."
I'm more curious whether that book
has clues to the Dragon Emperor.
I assume so, but I've failed
to find it for years.
And there's more and more
of those small quakes.
As you people are assuming, the Dragon
Emperor is running out of patience.
Also, you still owe me another
payment of 2,500,000 dollars.
It's been paid.
But greed will invite your downfall.
What else could someone my age want?
I'm more curious, actually...
You bought that book from me
for five million dollars,
and then asked me to hand it to him.
You could have simply
given it to him yourself.
He doesn't want help.
He's in a rebellious phase.
But if he thinks he slew the
dragon emperor alone...
Won't he simply rebel more?
Even a proud bird will
someday return to the nest.
Close this shop and be gone.
I...
Don't try to tell me you're already dead.
You've been crossed off the list,
but your old friend Anjou has
been looking for you for years.
Mr. Friedrich von Ron.
Frost talks too much.
I hope you're the last person
to learn my name, Mr. Parsi.
There's no need to threaten me.
I won't be alive much longer anyway.
Appreciated.
Thank you, sir!
What was that about?
Two executors went missing in Shin.
These were their belongings.
Something might be useful.
Good luck, Detective Holmes.
History
July 28th - Bookmarks
Shin Year 207, July 4th,
Typhoon, Unknown Accident