Ow...
Only he can make our wish come true.
Yes.
But the young prodigy can at
least protect the hero, I'm sure.
Well, I lost that one.
I can't beat you anymore, Oliver.
Stop slacking off!
I know you're a lot stronger than this!
You used to be so much
better! What happened?
You're overestimating me.
That was all I've got.
Maybe I used to be stronger.
But you grew up to be stronger than me.
That's all there is to it.
I refuse to believe that!
I don't know what to tell you.
There's no way I can beat you.
You're a genius.
Just you wait.
I'll make you take this seriously.
No way.
I don't want to kill you.
Good work, Orhun.
Sion!
Too bad about losing, huh?
I didn't know you were here.
I guess I looked lame in front of you.
No, you looked really cool.
And, you know...
I know your real strength.
This is all the strength
I've got right now.
But that's...
Yeah.
This is the result of my heart
being too weak to endure them.
My strength, and the way
those grown-ups look at me...
But now Oliver's carrying
that heavy burden.
This is my fault.
So I'll have to help him...
I...
I won't let you be alone!
I'll be strong enough
to stand by your side!
Sion...
So that we can beat the **** together!
I'm a ****, just like you!
I'll always be with you!
Even if you go someplace far away,
I'll catch up to you!
So don't try to bear all
the burdens yourself.
O-Okay...
I'll do everything I
can to catch up to you.
And when I do, someday ****
I'll become a **** and we'll ***
walk side by side there together...
So for now, be my guide,
Orhun.
JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES, PARTY OF NONE
I'm sorry to come so
suddenly, Grandmaster.
The guild master for the continent's southern
regions has come to me in a hurry.
I assume it's a matter of import?
EPISODE 8: THE JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES
FIGHTS WITH EVERYONE
Three days ago, an adventurer defeated
the Black Dragon alone in a
region under my jurisdiction.
Finally?
The conquest of the southern
dungeon should resume, then.
But he must be suicidal,
challenging the Black Dragon alone.
I'm told that it was in
reaction to an emergency:
the Black Dragon appeared outside of its
normal habitat, the Floor 92 boss area.
Perhaps the vanishing of
the "west" had an effect.
So was it Oliver who defeated it, then?
No, it wasn't.
What?
But who else...
It couldn't have been Orhun Dura?
You know of Orhun?
Impossible.
What's going on?
If he had that kind of power,
he wouldn't have chosen
to defeat a Floor Boss.
Has he been acting unusual lately?
Not particularly.
So he hasn't returned
to his original state.
He's gained enough power to defeat
the Black Dragon some other way.
If anything else happens with
Orhun, tell me immediately.
Understood.
That's that.
What a waste of time.
Five top-level parties working together?
I didn't expect that.
It still ended the same as ever, though.
I'm just glad none of us were hurt.
What now, Sion?
Hm...
There won't be any powerful adventurers
showing up here at the Eastern
Great Dungeon for a while.
We should probably leave for a bit.
Why not come out already?
You have good eyes, Mistress Sion.
Let's hear what you want, Messenger.
I have a message from HQ.
Someone has appeared at the
Southern Great Dungeon
who's powerful enough to defeat
the Black Dragon alone.
A dragonslayer...
You are to make contact with him, and,
if you decide he's an enemy, kill him.
Someone that powerful, in the south?
HQ says it's likely he's
already sided with the Church.
I see.
Given the lack of information,
it's likely not Oliver.
I'd like to bring him over to our side.
We'll have to kill him
if he's with the Church, though.
Understood.
Thank you for the message.
I'll be going, then.
That magic's handy. It lets
him just appear and disappear.
As you heard,
we'll be heading to the Southern
Great Dungeon as soon as we're ready.
Roger that.
The south is Church territory,
just like this place.
We'll need to be careful.
Yeah.
I wonder how strong this dragonslayer is.
We'll know once we fight him.
I can't believe someone appeared in
the south who might be the same as me.
I don't want to get
involved with that place,
but I'm the only one
who can deal with this.
If he's the real deal, the south
might fall as quickly as the west.
And I have to stop that, no matter what...
I swore that I'd carry on
his will after he died,
and make this happen!
Orhun...
The person I loved most.
My feelings haven't changed.
They never will.
So...
I won't forget what happened
that day, either...
The day my heart froze over.
I'm sorry I can't fight with you...
I'll fight... even if I'm all alone.
I won't let anyone get in my way.
And I'll kill all those old men in the
Church who drove Orhun to his death.
No matter what it takes.
Dragonslayer...
If you're teaming up
with the Church,
I'll have to kill you.
Orhun's accomplishments are incredible.
He risked his life to protect our comrades
during the teaching
expedition the other day
by fighting the Black Dragon all alone.
Not only is he strong,
he has much knowledge that our clan lacks.
And in the Heroes Party,
he did all the management
and operations himself.
I wasn't expecting him
to be this laudatory.
In light of this,
I'd like to make him a lieutenant
in the Night Sky Silver Rabbits.
He can take the place of Albert, who died
fighting the Black Dragon last year.
Since this requires the approval of
two-thirds of the existing lieutenants,
I'd like to take a vote now.
Those in favor...
Sir, a moment.
Before the vote, I'd like to talk to him.
Orhun, we're glad to have you.
Our leader has recommended you.
Everyone expects great things of you.
But are you prepared to offer
your life for the clan?
If you become a lieutenant,
your decisions will change the
lives of many of our members.
To the clan's members,
the clan is everything.
Which is why we must do everything
we can to protect the clan,
and put its needs above all else.
I can understand that.
But...
I can't do that!
I swore a vow on that day
that I can never break.
I won't betray it...
I am...
not prepared to offer
my life for the clan.
What do you mean?
That statement not only makes you unfit to
be a lieutenant, but even a clan member.
In other words, you're not prepared to give
everything to the Night Sky Silver Rabbits.
So why is it you're here?
To protect those I care about.
I've had that resolve since
I decided to join the clan.
As a member of the Night
Sky Silver Rabbits,
I'll do everything I can
to protect my comrades!
Orhun...
So that no matter what horrible things
happen, I won't lose anything...
I'll become strong enough to protect those
I care about no matter what happens.
That's the vow I swore when
I became an adventurer.
And who are these people you care for?
I assume you mean not the clan
itself, but its members, then?
Yes. I'll protect them to the end,
no matter what happens.
Even at the cost of my life.
That is my answer.
I understand.
I'll take the vote, then.
Those in favor of making Orhun one
of our lieutenants, raise your hand.
You scared me for a moment then!
Sorry. That's just who I am.
Well, whatever.
Next, you get to meet Unit 1.
Everybody's looking forward to it.
Just a moment, Selma-cchi!
Selma-cchi?
I need to talk to our new lieutenant.
Oh, about that, right?
Orhun, this is Estella. She's with
our adventure management division.
Oh, we met at the meeting.
Sorry to bother you.
Are you good at teaching others,
mister new lieutenant?
There's someone you want
me to teach, you mean?
As I expected from the multi-talented
man who was in the Heroes Party!
I don't have to waste time explaining!
There's actually a new party
I'd like your help with.
Again?
We know you're up for it.
I'd like to ask you to do it, too.
But won't that interfere with Unit 1?
That's not something to worry about.
You'll have more free time than
you did at the Heroes Party.
We don't spend multiple days
going into the dungeon.
We ban going into the Great Dungeon
for more than three days at a time.
That's very generous.
That's fine, then.
Thanks!
They're really talented,
so you can expect great things.
Do you mean...
I'll send the materials over today.
Bye-bye!
He's finally here!
We've been waiting, Dragonslayer!
So this is the Night Sky Rabbits'
strongest party, Unit 1?
Don't get so nervous.
Yeah! We met once when we
all fought that dragon!
Or did Selma leave such a big impression
you forgot about all of us?
Of course not.
Well, we should introduce ourselves again.
As the oldest, I'll start.
I'm Rain Hugwell!
I'm twenty-four years old and a mage.
Come talk to big sister
if you need anything!
Big sister?
What? Are you saying they're small?
No, I think they're quite big.
Your clothes.
Okay! Okay!
My turn now!
My name's Lucretia Otis!
I'm an 18-year-old healer!
Call me Lucre!
Next is the happy-go-lucky Wil!
Don't introduce me like that!
I'm Wilkes Savery, the Defender.
I'm 20 years old.
Call me Wil.
And once again, I'm Selma Claudel.
The leader of this party
and an Enchanter.
Glad to have you.
Glad to be here.
These four are my new comrades...
It's your turn now, Orhun.
I'm Orhun Dura.
I'm 18 years old and a front-line attacker.
I'll do my best to catch up to all of you.
Glad to be here.
Lately, I've been in Albert's role.
So I'll be happy to give that job to you!
Got it. I'll do my best.
You don't need to be so formal, Orhun.
Um, but...
We're the same age and I don't
speak formally, so it's okay!
You should respect your elders more.
What's that about?
It's easier to communicate
if you're relaxed.
And don't call me happy-go-lucky!
It's true, though!
Well, if that's why...
And so...
Could we start by asking you how
you beat the Black Dragon?
Well...
You don't need to force
yourself to answer.
No, I think you need to share
information with your comrades.
A big reason I was able to defeat
it was two original spells.
Original...?
The first is called Impact.
It can raise the effects of equipment
or magic up to 100 times.
One hundred times?!
The second is a spell that
can be cast multiple times
to boost the effects of support
magic more than you can usually do.
How much?
Thirty-two times,
during the Black Dragon fight.
Thirty-two times?!
What? That's no fair!
But I can only use it on myself,
and the stress is so immense
that I can't fight for long with it.
The Black Dragon fight went
on longer than expected,
and it was really rough for me.
But Impact alone is a huge advantage.
If you're that strong, you could do
the other positions as well, right?
Actually, I can only use mid-ranked
magic no matter how much I try.
What? No way!
Even though you know enough about magic
to make your own original spells?
Yes. I don't know why.
I see...
Oh, but...
I can't use higher-ranked magic,
but I have my original spells.
I don't think I'm that useless...
You worked really hard, huh?
I hope you learn to use
higher-ranked magic someday!
Thanks, Rain!
I hope so too.
Hey, do you have a special ability?
I sure do.
Which means we've got three
people in Unit 1 who do.
Huh? Who else?
It's better that you see
down in the dungeon.
I'm planning on having us learn to work
together in the Great Dungeon tomorrow.
Agreed.
Okay! Let's have a welcome
party for Orhun, then!
Yeah.
But...
Got somewhere to be?
I actually lost my weapon
fighting the Black Dragon.
If we're going into the dungeon,
I need to buy a new one.
Really? You don't have a weapon?
It'll take days to get a new one!
Don't worry.
Mine's off-the-shelf, so I
can just go buy a new one.
Off-the-shelf?
It's not made-to-order?
It's been good enough so far,
and I can use my support magic to
make it strong and sharp enough...
Maybe, sure,
but you're a star member of the
Night Sky Rabbits starting today!
We can't let people see you using
a sword you bought from a store!
Huh?!
The Dragonslayer's using
an off-the-shelf sword?
That's right! So we want you
to make us a new one, Aran!
But... you're entrusting your
life to your sword, right?
I'm surprised you've survived this long.
I've been an Enchanter the past few years.
Weapons just aren't that important to me.
But...
When Rain got mad at me, I understood.
Now that I'm a part of the Night
Sky Silver Rabbits' Unit 1,
I've decided I need a weapon
worthy of my position.
Orhun...
Aran, would you make me a sword?
Of course. It'd be an honor.
He's a dedicated blacksmith
for the Rabbits,
and he's the best around!
I can guarantee its quality.
Don't flatter me.
But you know...
There's one problem.
Problem?
If we want to make a sword for Orhun,
it should be made of materials from the
deepest floors of the dungeon, right?
And I'm out of those.
I'll need you to get them for me.
Even though we're getting a sword
so he can go down into the dungeon?
Talk about putting the
cart before the horse...
Oh, that's fine.
I've got a lot of stuff
from the deepest levels.
Orhun, why do you have all this?
I got it all when I was in the
Heroes Party and never used them.
Wow! Wow!
Griffin claws! Manticore fangs!
And this black one is...
Is this...?
A scale from the Black Dragon I defeated.
That's right...
They all fought the
Black Dragon and lost...
and a party member died.
I've reopened that old wound...
I made a mistake.
Um... I'm sorry.
Wow!
You can make the strongest sword
ever with a Black Dragon scale!
It must really bother her, but she's
not letting it show for my sake...
Orhun, I'll use the Black Dragon
scale as the main ingredient,
so is there anything else you want?
Hmm...
We'll have that welcome
party some other time.
Sorry, Wil!
It's fine.
I can't wait to see the
Black Dragon sword!
Take your time and tell
him everything you want.
Okay!