I haven't been able to look her
in the eyes since then.
Are we gonna stay like this forever?
Hey!
Eiyu!
Here I come!
Whoa! Shorts!
Yo!
Don't "yo" me!
What was that about?!
What were you doing here alone,
all lost in thought?
I-It's nothing!
Sure.
Okay.
All right!
Let's go!
Hey! Stop! Wait!
Hey!
There you are, Shio.
Huh?
I need a word with you.
Wh-What's going on?
It's rare for you to stay after school.
Shio.
Something happened
between you and Eiyu, right?
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
What do you mean?
We're getting along as usual.
Don't try to hide it. It's so obvious!
You and Eiyu are acting
strange, smiling weird...
I don't know what happened, but
if this goes on, I'm gonna lose it!
I-I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful tomorrow.
Wha?
I-I didn't mean to...
Shio...
It's been bothering you that much?
Huh?
That kiss.
Th-That...
kiss.
A-A-A-Akarin! You knew about it?!
Of course I did.
I am your childhood friend, after all.
You're able to tell
those kinds of things, too?!
But when? Where?
Wh-What do you mean?
It happened right in front of me.
What? Really?
I didn't realize.
What do you mean? I was there, too!
Huh?! You were there?!
Right next to you!
stare
Right next to me?!
Seriously?!
Well, I don't blame you.
I don't remember how I got home
after that either.
I was too shocked.
S-Sorry...
So why are you two acting
so awkward and smiley?
That's because...
No! Did Shio and Eiyu...
I...
Akarin?
It's okay! You don't have to say it!
That must've been so hard... So painful!
You were rejected by Eiyu,
weren't you, Shio?
You couldn't handle the jealousy.
It's not fair that you
only kissed Haru-kun!
What?
You have feelings for me?
Gosh, Eiyu. He could've been
gentler, don't you think?
Huh?!
Gentler...
I-I don't know about that...
Oh, well.
But why are you being nice to me, Akarin?
It must not feel good knowing
that Eiyu and I um, ki—
You dummy!
We're childhood friends, aren't we?
You can always count on me!
Akarin!
Shio...
All right!
An extra-base hit on the first pitch!
I really am the best, aren't I?
Batting Cage
Hey, come bat it out!
When you're feeling down,
blast those feelings away with a crack!
Come on! Slowpoke!
Okay, okay.
Why do I have to do this?
Seriously? That's all you've got?
This isn't making me
feel better, you know.
Let's go.
I knew it.
You were rejected by Shio, weren't you?
Huh?!
What?!
Wh-What are you talking about?!
That's ridiculous!
Something's definitely been off
between you two recently.
You're imagining things!
I didn't do anything, and she's the one...
There you go again.
Hesitating and keeping things vague.
This is gonna turn out
exactly like I said.
You're gonna be rejected by everyone!
Shut up!
What the heck are you going on about?!
Mr. Hesitation's batting is weak, too!
That's why you can't even talk to Shio.
See? You missed!
Quit sulking already!
Just blast one out and feel awesome!
Damn it!
Come on! If you keep this up,
we'll eventually all grow apart!
We'll all... grow apart?
I won't let that happen.
They're all my very, very
precious... childhood friends!
Home Run
There ya go!
That's my Eiyu!
So? Are you feeling better?
Yeah.
About what happened...
I really want Eiyu to forget about it.
I want to tell him I just want us
to stay friends like before...
But the thought of being
rejected... scares me.
All these things were
in my head as time just passed.
And it's like I don't know
how to talk to Eiyu anymore.
I don't know...
Are things different now?
I don't know what to do.
I'm scared... I'm scared, Akarin.
Shio...
Snap out of it!
You two have made up
so many times before!
When you broke his toy...
When he ate your pudding
without your permission...
Why did you do that?! Give it back!
When you two weren't
talking after a fight...
Even when you two cried
like crazy that one time!
Akarin...
The bond we've built
together as childhood friends
can never be broken!
The bond... of childhood friends...
Right...
You're right.
You're exactly right, Akarin!
Of course I am!
Just because I kissed him...
It won't break our bond
as childhood friends!
That's right, it wo—
What?
Just because I kissed him...
I kissed him
"I kissed him"?
Akarin!
Thanks!
I'm gonna go talk to Eiyu!
I'm gonna tell him exactly how I feel!
Wait... What?
What do you mean...
you kissed him?!
I'm gonna beat you next time!
Haru.
Hey, thanks for today.
You were right. I was being
indecisive and worrying by myself.
What's with you all of a sudden?
I'm gonna go talk to Shio properly.
Good.
Wait there.
Huh?
What are you doing?
Here. As a thanks for today.
What?
Oh, come on. I'm not a kid anymore.
Whatever. Just open it.
Why are you being so pushy?
Hey! Lucky you!
Wait, is this...
Darn it! I'm just missing one!
How rare is it?!
I used to collect these a long time ago...
I can't believe you remembered.
Of course I remember.
I know what you like.
What?
You're one of my precious
childhood friends, too, Haru.
You idiot!
You're supposed to tell Shio that!
Shio
It's Shio!
Hello? Eiyu?
So, I...
I need to tell you...
Shio! Where are you right now?
What? I'm at school.
I need to talk to you about something!
Can you meet me...
Huh?
Hey, Shio? Hey!
What happened?!
I heard a loud sound
and the call dropped.
My call's not going through!
I... need to go.
I gotta go now!
Hey!
Wait!
Huh?
Use it! You're in a hurry, right?
Be careful!
Seriously, he hasn't changed at all.
Huh?
Wait...
Shio...
Shio!
Nobody came to my office today.
Nurse's Office
O-Okay.
She's not at school...
So she was on her way back home?
Shio... Where the heck are you?
Don't do this!
We can't leave things like this!
Shio
No Answer
Are you okay?
What happened?
No Answer
Jeez, Shio.
You can't do anything without me.
Oh, whatever!
No... This is my fault!
Who cares about a kiss?!
I'm such an idiot.
I should've told her how I really feel!
To me, Shio, you're my
precious... precious...
She's not home.
Damn it!
I should go back
and check all the spots again...
Eiyu!
Huh? Shio?
Over here!
Eiyu...
I...
Why...
Why are you in my room?
You didn't answer the door,
so I thought you were sleeping.
You never answered your phone!
Sorry! I got flustered...
And dropped my phone on the stairs.
Seriously... Don't scare me like that.
S-So, Eiyu...
There's...
There's something
I need to talk to you about.
What?
The thing is...
Wait, go back! That's dangerous!
About... the kiss...
We kissed...
But let's stay friends like before!
Don't make me worry. You dummy.
S-Sorry.
I want to be friends like before too.
You're...
My precious childhood friend.
That's the first time I've ever heard you
say something like that, Eiyu.
Ugh. Jeez. Shut up! Shut up!
Well, in any case...
I'm glad Shio's safe.
If you keep this up,
we'll eventually all grow apart!
We'll all... grow apart...
Yes.
Me too...
I want to, too...
I want to kiss him, too!
Up next is the first-year's running race!
Ready...
Set...
Minamo-san's fast!
She's fast and bi—
Gorgeous!
I finally got to tell him
what I couldn't say before.
We made up!
This is the start of
the best sports day ever!
It's Eiyu!
Maybe I'll cozy up to him
for the first time in a while!
Eiyu! Did you see that?
I got first place!
squeeze
Really?
Fwip
That's admirable! Impressive!
You're amazing, Shio!
H-Huh? Th-Thanks...
What's going on?
Your eyes are sparkling like crazy!
They're so pure-looking!
Sparkling? Oh, come on.
I've always been like this.
Well, I guess you could say that...
I had an epiphany.
An epiphany?
The sky's been this blue all this time!
Nature has always been so beautiful!
To make a young body
move with energy is...
such a wonderful thing!
I've come to realize all of this,
thanks to all of you...
My precious childhood friends!
Cringe
Wh-What's going on?
Wh-What happened?
Why are we all here?
When you got to kiss him!
Shio-chan, I brought some snacks for you.
Hey, Red Team! What do you
want from your enemy?
White Team
F-Forget about that!
This is an emergency! It's Eiyu!
Eiyu's become so gross!
What?
Sparkle! Sparkle! Sparkly shiny!
What the heck?
Ew!
You're right, that's gross.
Right?! Right?!
It's as if he's been released
from all the world's suffering.
Hey, what are you all doing over here?
Yeah...
Look at you, Runako, that's a nice camera.
Why don't we all take a picture?
Um... Okay.
Runako, you dummy.
All of us childhood friends
have to be in it together
or else it's pointless!
All right, smile!
Is this a family photo?!
Hey, what are you
trying to pull off, Eiyu?
Your face is making my skin crawl!
Akari...
Your face when
you're angry is so wonderful!
Wh-What?!
Whoops! Your headband is crooked.
Gosh, you're so silly.
G... Gr...
Are you okay? Your face is turning red.
Wh-Whatever!
Hey! Eiyu!
Whoa, Haru-kun?!
It's shock therapy!
Come on, wake up!
You have so much energy, Haru.
That means you're in good health,
and that's a wonderful thing.
Gross!
It's even worse now
with his face all swollen.
Oh no, what should we do?!
Huh?
Runako?
Squeeze!
It's not so bad.
Onii-chan's so nice, and we can
be all lovey-dovey like this.
This is the best!
Runako, you're just like a baby.
Runako! You!
Sh-She might be right.
Hey! You're the one
who said he was gross!
Well, it kind of just grew on me...
Me too, then.
H-Hey!
Th-Then...me too.
What the heck is happening here?!
Shio said she was able to make up with him...
And I'm guessing Eiyu got over
whatever was troubling him, too...
But why does he look
all refreshed like that?!
W-Well...
This is super gross and it makes
things even more annoying, but...
What if...this turns into
a rom-com kind of situation?
All right!
That's probably enough
snuggly time for now, huh?
What?!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
You're all so silly.
We're childhood friends
and we're acting so lovey-dovey.
What?!
You're one to talk!
The four of you mean the world to me.
What?
It would be weird
for childhood friends like us
to be in a rom-com situation, right?
What?!
Next is the pole-toppling game!
Well, I'm up next. Gotta go.
Participants, please gather
at the starting point!
H-Hey!
Wait!
Huh?
Did we all just...
Episode 11
Scared? Lost Something?
Let off Steam on Sports Day? Still Won't Start a Rom-Com
get rejected?!