It's warm.
It has a gentle aroma,
with a hint of sweetness.
Yum! What is this?
I've never tasted anything like it!
To the right of your mug is your plate.
There are fried eggs on it.
It's warm. I've had these before.
Next to the eggs are
some toasted sandwiches.
It's coarse... I've had these before too.
And further right is a bowl of salad.
Veggies? I know how this leaf tastes.
Did you get all that? Are you good?
I get where everything is now. Thanks.
I hope you like the taste.
Crispy. I like it.
I'm glad to hear that.
Hey, eggs! Creamy and yummy.
I like the sour sauce on the leaves.
I'm impressed.
I was born like this, so I'm used to it.
But you should chew some more.
Oh, right.
I don't need to hurry.
Nobody's gonna take my food.
I've had these before,
but never in this flavor.
It's all so good.
That was amazing.
You said you had amnesia,
but you know what your name is, right?
I do...
But I wanna know your names first.
Sure. I'll start, then.
I'm Flum. Nice to meet you.
Flum.
Flum, who saved me.
Do me now.
Where?
I'm Eterna, Flum's friend.
Eterna, Flum's friend.
My name is Milkit.
I'm Master's slave.
Slave?
That's naughty.
Wait, no, I swear it's not like that!
She didn't purchase me.
She took me in when I had nowhere to go.
She's letting me stay here too.
Huh...
You live together even though
you're not family?
Must be nice.
You can stay here for a while, too.
Huh? Can I really?
Of course.
But only once you've given us your name.
I'm Ink Wreathcraft.
Call me Ink!
WITHERING
BUDDING
BUDDING AND WITHERING
Huh?
A lost child?
Yeah. She says she has amnesia and
doesn't know where she came from.
If it means I can keep eating all this
yummy food, I wanna live here forever.
Flum did say you could stay,
but if you never go home,
your parents are going to worry.
I don't have any.
Were you living with relatives, then?
Hmm, I dunno.
An orphanage, then?
Dunno. I don't remember.
Sounds mighty fishy to me.
If she doesn't wanna say,
she prob'ly ran away from home.
No, don't jump to conclusions yet.
But it's clear she doesn't
wanna go home, right?
Has there been any news about a girl
going missing from an orphanage?
Not from any Church orphanage, at least.
Right, Ed?
Right.
There's been no word from the West
District one or any of the others.
I see.
Anyway, do you want us to take
that girl in to our orphanage?
Good idea. It'd make her easier
to find for anyone lookin'.
What do you say, Flum?
Er...
If Ink escaped from
a Church research facility,
handing her over to Church people
might just get her sent right back.
And then...
No, it's fine.
Ink seems to have taken a liking to me,
and I'm worried about her.
I'll ask around some more.
Are you sure?
If you ever need help,
we'll always be here.
Hey!
It's the least we can do after
everything you've done for Sara.
Jeez.
Thank you. I'll be counting on you.
You got it!
I'll ask around when I get back
to the Central church, too.
GUILD
A job request to search
for a missing girl?
Yep. Has anything like that come in?
Let me see.
If I can find someone looking for her,
I should be able to figure out
where she came from.
Nope, nothing.
What? Not even in East or Central?
Who knows?
Can you check if a request like that
has come in anywhere?
Hey, don't poke your head in.
Please look into it, Y'lla!
I'm begging you!
What's gotten into you?
Okay, how about you do this
for me, and I'll look into it?
What's that? A request to guard a shop?
Yep.
Mr. Big-Fish-Small-Pond and his bottom-
feeders are making a mess of things.
Big fish?
Come on in, Mister Kahnis.
Cheers.
I'm gonna follow you, Mister Kahnis.
He's got power and influence
in all sorts of places.
You got that right.
I always thought Dein was no good.
Now, now. He was a pathetic loser
who called himself A-Rank,
but I'd say he did as well as he could.
Okay, but he couldn't
have done it without you.
You were the one
who pulled all the strings!
Say it louder!
Nah, Dein did his best.
Keyword being "did."
Up high!
Kahnis!
Y-You mean them?
Yep. That's them.
Mr. Big-Fish-Small-Pond
and his bottom-feeders.
Ah, Dein's flunkies?
Thugs, the lot of them.
They wagged their tails for Dein,
but the moment he goes
missing, look at them.
You still don't know where Dein ended up?
Nope. I heard they found some of his
men dead at their hideout, though.
You sound unaffected.
Weren't you on the same team?
That's what it takes to survive
in West District.
Anyway, I hear you're living
in a nice house now.
How'd you pull that off?
Oh, at first—
Well, if you've got an address now,
better update your license.
Sheesh!
I thought you were just another slave.
Way to prove me wrong.
I mean, the house came
as a surprise to me, too.
ADVENTURER LICENSE APPLICATION
No, not like that.
Fill this part out.
What?
I didn't expect you to come over to help.
Hey, it speeds up the process.
Now I see what your full outfit's like.
Problem?
What a short skirt!
I'd like to make a job request.
Of course. How can we help?
I want you to look for a runaway child.
All done with laundry!
Thank you for helping, Ink.
No problem. It was fun.
It smells like the sun.
You're all sweaty, Ink.
Let's take a bath and freshen up.
You went to bed without one
last night, too.
Brr!
Okay!
I'm back.
Something smells good.
Welcome home, Flum.
The bath felt great.
Hey, those pajamas...
Did you go with her, Eterna?
Yep. Her magic gave us
unlimited hot water.
Good for you, Ink.
Master.
Welcome home, Master.
I'm back, Milkit.
Huh? Did the air turn all sweet?
Bingo.
Flum and Milkit
are getting all handsy in secret.
That's naughty.
D-Don't tell Ink that, Eterna!
She'll misunderstand!
Besides, you're one to talk!
Right, Milkit?
Naughty.
I never thought
I'd get told off by Milkit.
My Milkit has a mouth on her!
Is this Ink?
The name's Sara. I'm a nun.
She comes here from Central to hang out.
Every night after work for dinner.
Deadbeat. Freeloader.
I show my gratitude, okay?!
I just can't live without
Miss Milkit's yummy cookin'!
NAME: CANDY BOAR STEW
Tonight, we have candy boar stew.
That's bleedin' good!
Seconds, please!
S-Sure.
That's the last of 'em, Milkit.
Thank you, Master.
So, where is it?
Right, that.
I can't eat no more...
Ink.
Here. Present for you.
Huh? What is this?
What do you think?
Super cute!
Do you like this outfit, Ink?
It has a ribbon. I like ribbons.
Good to hear.
It suits your energetic personality.
It does.
This place is so warm.
Did you know there's
a major artery in the thigh?
The sword technique she used released
blood into the body from the blade's tip.
Her Genocide Arts not only caused pain
but also rendered the target immobile.
You realize what will happen if you
don't stop the bleeding, don't you?
Now, where is Dein?
Fine... I'll talk!
D-Dein is...
Dein's a strong man who can
even take on the Church!
Unlike Dein, Kahnis has actual power!
Can you people stop bringing your
quarrels here each and every day?
Dein...
Dein is a strong man!
Not in front of my store.
You're hurting my business.
Yeah. You're being a bother to the store.
Take this elsewhere.
Th-The slave girl?
That's all you've got two-on-one?
And weren't you two having a falling-out?
Anybody else want to come at me?
Okay, dismissed.
Thank you. You really saved my behind.
No problem. Glad I could help.
Hey, Badras! I found Dein!
Say what?
Is it true?
Yeah, well...
S-Slave girl?!
Where did you see Dein?
H-He was kneeling in prayer in the church.
Really?
Yeah. He's become
an Origin follower for real.
Dein, of all people?
I don't believe it.
Dein wants to live so bad,
he's willing to become a Church lapdog?
He choose survival over honor.
Connect.
Resonate.
The wisdom we accumulate
will rise above us,
a great spiral connecting us to God.
We want to be linked.
Connect.
Let's connect.
Resonate.
We want to be linked.
The wisdom we accumulate
will rise above us,
Let's connect.
a great spiral connecting us to God.
We want to be linked.
Let's connect.
Quiet!
Shut your mouth!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Did he repent his sins
and convert to Originism?
Connect! Resonate!
No way.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
He's gotta be plotting something.
Who's there?
Sheesh.
Were you really planning
to go out there alone?
Ottilie!
With the Church backing Dein now,
you should avoid
messing with him carelessly.
What? The soldiers who went after Dein?
Yes. They became a mix of corpses
so grotesque you couldn't tell
royal army soldier from Dein lackey.
I've never heard anything like it.
The Church pulled strings
to get a gag order issued.
It was swept under the rug.
Surely not even the Church
is capable of that?
At this point, His Majesty is
but a puppet of the Church.
No...
They've been making more and more
ominous moves lately.
We must reveal their true colors
to the public at once.
How can you be so strong
in such a grim situation?
Do you even have to ask?
It's all for milady's sake.
You risked your life to protect that
blind girl the other day too, remember?
That was heroic of you.
You have my respect.
I just couldn't abandon her there.
Besides...
All I want is to live
an ordinary life with Milkit.
She's dear to you, is she?
Yes.
Let us both fight for the ones we love.
L-Let's!
I'll be taking my leave now.
I think I'll be able to come back
with good news before long.
Ottilie...
That tickles, Ink!
Sorry. It wasn't on purpose.
Hey, I know you meant that!
Stop it, Sara!
Milkit, I'll set the table.
Thank you, Master.
Something smells really nice!
Sit tight. Your hair's still wet.
But dinner is calling me!
Once your hair is dry. Just sit tight.
Ink sucked all my youth away.
Huh?
Thank you for the food.
That was delicious.
I'm stuffed.
You'll be the greatest wife
in the world, Milkit.
Wife, you say?
I'd be happier serving you
my cooking, Master.
Will you marry me, then?
Marry you...
I-I'll go do the dishes.
You two are so close,
Miss Flum and Miss Milkit.
I hope Sister Maria's doing well.
Ink, your lively nature is the only
thing you have going for you.
You're utterly useless.
You good-for-nothing!
Are you okay, Ink?
What's wrong?
I...
I'm unneeded.
Ink,
nobody in this world is unneeded.
If anyone ever says you are,
I'll kick their ass.
Me too.
I'll wash them away without a trace.
Same here. We're all on your side, Ink.
Right.
Why? We've only just met.
Because we're friends already.
Damn, Sara stole my line.
Friends...
Yep, friends.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
Milkit.
You don't need the medicine anymore.
Right.
Here I go.
Okay.
Sorry. I shouldn't have
done that so suddenly.
We match.
Those words took Flum's deep mental scars—
the thorns stuck in her heart
like countless swords—
and reversed them all.
Yeah.
You and I are the same.
Milkit, I want you
to stay by my side always.
Yes. I feel the same way.
I want to stay by your side, Master.
SOLITUDE AND FAMILY