Yay!
I always wanted to ride in one of these!
You're getting too wound up, Shiek.
We're on our way to
help Cecilia, you know.
You just had to tag along...
What? You were gonna leave me behind?
Damn it! It was supposed
to be just me and Cecilia!
I'm sorry to drag you two
along on my business.
What's wrong?
I think... I'm a bit motion-sick...
Should we take a break?
Oh, then drink this.
It's an infusion made from
a secret pixie recipe!
Thank you so much.
I think I feel better.
Oh, good!
See? I'm pretty useful, right?
G-Get off me!
To be honest, I'm relieved
that you're both with me.
Sure! You can count on me!
You can count on me, too!
I said get off me!
For crying out loud...
I heard they had been
attacked by bandits...
This looks pretty bad.
Well, well!
I never expected Lady
Cecilia to come to our aid.
And... who are these two?
My friends. They're here to help me.
They're skilled at healing,
so don't worry about a thing.
Hello.
Ah, that is reassuring.
Thank you so much!
Take care of yourself, now.
Cecilia's really giving it her all.
Look at her, trying her hardest.
Take care.
Mr. Yoki.
Isn't Lady Cecilia a wonderful person?
Yes.
Right?! Isn't she?!
Still, the fact that no one was
killed is kind of a silver lining.
Yes, the bandits suddenly turned and fled.
They fled?
Someone showed up out of
nowhere and cut them down.
Infighting?
Next, please!
Cecilia...
Cecilia, maybe you should
take a little break?
No, I'm all right.
Holy Bell.
It's okay! She's only asleep.
Do you have a place where she can rest?
Ah, she's awake.
You know what I'm about to say, don't you?
I'm sorry I used magic to put
you to sleep without warning.
It's not right to ignore
someone's own will.
But it's not good to overdo it, either.
If you'd kept healing like that,
you would've knocked yourself out.
Yes, you're right.
But please don't ever do that again, okay?
I promise.
We finished treating the
villagers, so don't worry.
Yoki...
Thank you.
So cute!
Aw, nah...
Come on in!
Ah, Lady Cecilia. Are you feeling better?
I'm sorry I worried you.
Not at all. I'm sorry to bring
this up when you're exhausted,
but there's a little girl named Teal
living on the outskirts of town.
Could I trouble you to take a look at her?
Did the bandits hurt her, too?
No, thankfully, she was not attacked.
But Teal has been sickly since she was
born, and she's always stuck in bed.
I'm worried about her.
Understood.
Could you tell me where she is?
Excuse me.
Come in.
Who might you be?
I'm sorry to drop in unannounced.
My name is Cecilia.
This is Yoki, and this is Shiek.
The village headman asked us to come.
The headma—
Shiek, you're up.
Right.
Take this medicine.
Don't worry.
Despite how he looks,
Shiek knows his stuff.
What?! Captain, what was
that about how I look?!
I think I feel a little bit better.
That's great!
Thank you for giving me
this amazing medicine.
This must be the guardian
deity's divine protection.
Guardian deity?
You don't know him?
He's the statue of the god
on the outskirts of town!
A statue of...
...a god?
The day the bandits came,
I suddenly grew sleepy on my way
home from taking him an offering,
so I escaped their attack!
Wasn't that just coincidence?
That's not all! When I
was seven years old...
Just when I thought it was all over...
the guardian deity saved my life!
What could it be if not
his divine protection?
Intense sleepiness and black lightning?
Dark magic?
Yoki, this sounds a bit suspicious.
It isn't suspicious at all!
One look at him, and you'll understand!
Uh, this is...
...obviously...
He's so wonderful!
A demon statue?
I won't allow anyone to
belittle the guardian de—
Teal!
I'm sorry we pushed you so hard.
Why don't I take you home?
You know, it looks just like...
the gargoyles in the Demon King's castle.
It really is a gargoyle! Shiek!
Huh?
Right here!
Captain, what should we do with him?
Man, you're quick.
Hey, can you speak?
If you want to kill me, do it!
'Kay!
Wait, wait, wait.
I just want to talk to him.
You haven't come to kill me?
You're the one who attacked us first.
I apologize.
I heard that you knew what I was,
and then something about
the Demon King's castle.
We're sorry, too.
But how did a gargoyle like you become
this village's guardian deity?
I was originally made to
guard a certain temple,
but long ago, I was stolen
from it by bandits.
Then they attacked this village,
so I brought down divine
punishment upon them.
The villagers have been calling me
their guardian deity ever since.
Only that little girl still
comes to see me, though.
Teal?
Yes.
Nearly every day since I saved
her from those monsters,
she has been cleaning this
little shrine for me.
When I learned that bandits
attacked again yesterday,
I kept her safe.
I see.
So you don't mean the
humans any harm, then?
Not at all. I only live here.
I have no intention of involving
myself with the humans in any way.
Guess there's no problem, then.
Sorry to bother you. Shiek, got a sec?
What is it, Captain?
I need to talk to you.
Going back to the inn first
because he was sleepy...
Shiek is just adorable, isn't he?
He's still a kid, after all.
Though the truth is that
I sent him back myself.
Now it's just the two of us!
Is something the matter?
Oh, no! Nothing at all!
I mean, uh...
I was wondering if it's okay
to just let that gargoyle be.
It does seem like a problem that
there's a monster in the village...
but he doesn't seem to be
bothering the villagers.
Yeah.
Seems like he's kept to
himself the whole time,
so I think it'll be fine.
Shall we put the matter on hold for now?
Sure.
C-Crap! What do I do?
I'm out of stuff to talk about!
Cecilia!
Er, um... watch your step.
R-Right!
Walking around at night
is dangerous, y'know.
Yeah...
Thank you.
It's the bandits!
Take all the money and food you can find!
Stop right there.
We will not allow any further evil acts!
Who the hell are you brats?
You're up, Shiek.
Okay, here I go.
What?!
You little...
He's strong...
He isn't my subordinate for nothing.
Well, I'd better get
in on this fight, too.
I'll back you up.
Storm Blow!
Who's next?
Yoki! You saved me!
Not a problem.
Is that...
From the guardian deity's shrine?
Shiek, head over there.
Got it!
Get over yourselves!
You think two little
brats can take us alone?!
I could handle the likes of you by myself.
Here I go.
Hyper Storm!
Well, they're taken care of.
Shiek isn't back yet?
It would seem not.
Guardian deity! Hang in there!
Shiek!
Ah. The celebrity appears at last.
Who the hell is he?
He's Miller, the hero
of the Gallis Empire!
A hero? There are other
ones besides yours?
Th-The battle's not over yet...
Shiek, don't push yourself too hard.
What happened?
He came up from behind while the
gargoyle was protecting Teal, and...
I... tried to protect them, but...
You piece of...
What kind of moron defends a gargoyle?
Hold it!
What? Don't we need to kill the monster?
Stop. He's only protecting Teal.
Then I'll slice the brat
in two along with him.
Like hell you will!
My magic was erased?!
You can't! Please, fall back!
You're no match for him!
His weapon is a man-made
magic sword called Magic Eater.
It absorbs magic!
You heard her. So back off!
Guardian deity!
Please stop this!
If you harm a citizen of
Clariness, it'll lead to war!
War sounds great. I'd love that.
I can hardly enjoy killing when
the world's at peace, can I?
But in a war, I can kill all I want.
Isn't that right, my good lady?
You have no pride as a hero, do you?
We can't let this guy go free.
Magic won't work on me, you know.
Are you sure?
Pretty pathetic, for all your bluster.
This is just a little greeting.
I told you, magic won't work on me!
Why don't you try using a weapon?
Unfortunately, magic is all I can use.
Idiot!
Not enough!
It's no use! No use! No use!
This is bad.
If the boy uses up all his magic, he'll
be up against the wall instantly.
Yoki!
Okay, then, how about this?
Oh?
Blazing Plasma!
He's so powerful...
It can't be... Even the highest-ranking
magic doesn't work.
Is that all you know how to do?
I'm just about to get serious.
Go on, keep flailing!
Your magic capacity is
impressive for a human,
but the moment it runs out, you're dead!
No!
That might have worked
on anyone else but me!
It's just a man-made magic sword.
Looks like there's only
so much it can absorb.
This is the end of you.
Just how much magic do you have?!
Storm Blow!
Angering me was a big mistake!
This is as far as your
arrogance will take you!
Die!
No!
What are you—
Thank goodness... I kept you safe...
Teal!
Well, that was pretty fun.
Getting yourself killed to defend
a demon was just brilliant!
Shut up. I won't let
you get away with this.
You sure? They're all gonna
die if you don't protect them!
Damn it!
He got away.
I'm a fool!
I let myself think everything would work
out as long as I had overpowered magic!
What is... that form?
Yoki...
A demon?
Perfect timing. I'm
really pissed right now.
A demon hunt sounds like fun.
What?!
Damn it! What the hell are you?!
You robbed one of my men
of his arm and wings.
Your many evil deeds
warrant certain death.
Tsk! You're that gargoyle's master, huh?
The Demon King was defeated!
How is there still such
a powerful demon around?!
I'm not done.
Die, damn you!
What are you gonna do to m—
I get it. Killing is
so much fun, isn't it?
Yoki...
You are not worth killing.
If you're lucky, you might make
it back to your country.
Screw you!
You're gonna regret
humiliating me like this!
Yoki!
How's everyone?
They're all safe and sleeping.
Oh, good.
You're bleeding!
Oh, this? I'm fine.
I just ripped out my own horns.
You're not fine at all!
Welcome back.
Thanks.
You want to go to Minerva?
Please!
I want to look for a way to heal
the guardian deity's wounds!
Healing magic can't
heal wounds like these.
But maybe in Minerva...
That's true, but monsters
can't enter Minerva.
In that case, I have a good idea.
I changed his appearance with earth magic!
Now he doesn't look like a monster!
T-True...
Anyone recommended by Cecilia is
welcome to work in this mansion.
I'm good at cleaning!
I'd also like to put this
statue in the mansion.
No.
Aww!
I can't put something with
such poor taste in this house.
Take it back.
B-But...
The guardian deity!