I'm Anna Akechi!
Mikuru started school today!
Legendary Pre-Kit charms from an old book!
I went to deliver an umbrella and new
Pre-Kit to Mikuru at school, but...
I shouldn't bother Mikuru.
Nijee turned the beloved school
swallow statue into Hannindas.
We were out of step,
and Pochitan saved us.
But we lost the Makoto Jewels.
Pochitan!
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
Jett-senpai!
It's Pochitan, she's...
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
A brilliant inspiration
rinto hirameku
I'm sure we'll find it
We're Precure, after all
kitto mitsukeru
datte Precure
It's calling to us
watashitachi wo yondeiru
Where's the truth?
What will we discover?
shinjitsu wa doko?
hakken wa nani?
One mystery after another
nazo ga nazo wo yondeiru
Gather the pieces
From now to the past and future
Puzzle wo atsume
genzai kara kako, mirai e
Like evidence
Something shining across time
shouko mitai ni
toki wo koe kagayaku mono
How? How? Is it a trick?
nande? nande? Trick kana?
Why? Why? We'll face it
naze? naze? tachimukau
Look and feel
Figure out the secret
mitsumete kanjite
himitsu wo tokiakasu no
One brave step will lead to a miracle
yuuki no ippo ga kiseki made michibiku
The answer?!
Found when you notice the unnoticed
kotae!?
Kizuitenai mono ni kizuita toki
It's destiny, it's love
Whispered in a tiny voice
unmei ne tte daisuki yo tte
chicchana koe
Let's walk that road together!
issho ni aruite ikou!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
A brilliant inspiration
rinto hirameku
The jewel key connects us
Opening the link moving forward
Jewel no kagi ga tsunagaru
tsugi e no kizuna hiraku yo
Hey, us being born and having met
Is a wonderful mystery
nee umareta koto
meguri aeta koto no shinpi
Go on! Star Detective Precure!
susume! Meitantei Precure!
Miraculous Pre-Kit Mirror Loupe!
She's drinking her milk, so don't worry.
You two have a drink, too.
When Pochitan started glowing,
this glowed too...?
I need to investigate this further.
Sorry.
I meant to give it to you, but I couldn't.
Where's Nijee? Why isn't he back?
He even got two Makoto Jewels!
That's, like, totally bogus.
Cure Arcana Shadow.
Go fetch Nijee.
Lie lie, sir!
Mikuru?
I'm going to get the Makoto Jewels back.
-Me too!
-You stay with Pochitan.
I still hadn't figured out
how to carry it.
But then you helped me!
Hanninda!
I'll turn it into swallows,
and transport it easily!
It's my fault!
It's just as my fortune-telling said.
You're here.
Why didn't you come back?
Did you get lost?
Of course not!
Then why?
I want a more beautiful conclusion
for myself.
I'm actually a very greedy thief.
What are you going to do?
Defeat the Precures.
Just like I told Maestro Usonoir!
I have no choice.
I'll do it with grace!
You came back to look for evidence.
Just as I expected.
I've been waiting, Detective.
Nijee!
Oh! Calm down, baby!
I've just come to invite you
to a fabulous show!
You'll be able to see the Makoto Jewels,
by which I mean two swallows.
What?
The venue will be the town's
beautiful beach, Nijigahama.
Isn't it romantic?
Wait!
I'll be waiting for you there, baby!
Still nothing.
No matter how I look into it,
I still can't figure it out.
Where's Mikuru?
She went to look for the Makoto Jewels.
Tsk. Leaving you and Pochitan behind.
It's... It's my fault.
Because I couldn't talk to Mikuru.
Anna?
She was laughing with her friends.
It was a side of her I didn't know.
That's why...
Mikuru has a world I know nothing about.
We only just met, so it's not surprising.
I didn't want to be a bother.
I thought I'd investigate alone.
And then we fought.
It's all reversed!
Huh?
It's like you and Mikuru
have switched places.
You're thinking too much about Mikuru
and now you can't act, right?
That's like Mikuru.
While Mikuru ran off on her own.
That's just like you.
It means you're influencing each other.
Even though you just met.
I can hardly believe it.
I told you I only believe
what I see, right?
It has been a short time,
but I've seen you two, and I know.
You are a fated, no, a miraculous pair.
Jett-senpai...
Pochi?
Pochitan...
Leave Pochitan with me!
Go and find Mikuru.
Together you're
Star Detective Precures, right?
Jett-senpai...
Pochi.
Okay!
I'll be back!
Open!
Pre-Kit Voice Memo!
Anna?
Mikuru! Where are you?
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
I'm on my way to the beach!
Nijee told me to go there.
I'll go too!
What about Pochitan?
Don't worry, Jett-senpai has her!
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
I'll be right there!
Why did you call her here?
The sea...
I see.
She figured out my strategy?
What's going on?
By the way, this will be a secret show,
not visible to Maestro Usonoir.
I'll defeat the Precures,
and take two Makoto Jewels back with me.
Surprise!
Do as you like.
Just hurry up and finish it.
That's what I plan to do anyway.
I've been waiting, Precure.
-Mikuru!
-Anna!
Oh? The baby fairy isn't with you.
That suits me just fine.
Hanninda!
Open!
Jewel Cure Watch!
Precure! Wake-up Time!
3! Discover!
6! And face one another!
9! We are the miraculous duo!
Spin Around!
And finish off cutely!
Gold-star closing the case on any mystery!
Star Detective Cure Answer!
Jumping towards smiles
with layered reasoning!
Star Detective Cure Mystique!
Star Detective Precure!
I'll show you my answer!
Go! Hanninda!
Hanninda!
Han!
Nin!
So that's Nijee's plan.
Huh?
If you can't fly, you'll lose
your footing above the sea.
But these swallows fly freely!
Now what'll you do?
What?
They're good.
They made platforms?
Counterattack!
Answer Attack!
Hanninda!
Mystique Reflection!
Da!
Return the Makoto Jewels!
Give back the swallow statue!
The show has just begun!
Han! Nin! Da!
Hanninda!
Are you sensing the Makoto Jewels?
You need to rest!
Fine, fine! I'll take you to them.
Everyone is so high-maintenance! Sheesh!
The Pre-Kit Mirror Loupes!
You want me to bring them?
This is what working together looks like!
Hanninda!
Looks like rain again.
It's as if the sky
is reflecting your hearts.
I came to give you an umbrella.
What?
Then I saw you with your friends.
I didn't want to bother you.
But it made me realize...
In this time, in this world,
I'm all alone.
That's why I investigated on my own.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
You're right.
You came to 1999 by yourself...
It must be lonely.
You must've felt anxious.
But then...
I...
I also acted on my own.
I'm sorry.
Mystique.
Hanninda!
It's about time for this show to end!
Precures!
Time for your entrance?
Baby fairy.
But I won't let you on stage!
Hanninda!
What's that?
You wanted to deliver these, right?
To Anna and Mikuru!
Leave this to me! Go! Pochitan!
Star Detective Precures
have fairy friends who support them.
They stand close to them,
and always watch over them.
Is Pochitan working hard to become theirs?
To become Answer
and Mystique's fairy friend!
I won't let you get in their way!
Bring it on!
Answer.
Mystique.
It's reversed.
Huh?
Jett-senpai said that.
We've swapped places since then.
Take a single step
and the answer will follow!
You taught me that.
A single step of courage
becomes the answer!
What?
Mystique.
You said I must be lonely and anxious
since I came to 1999.
But I'm okay now!
She came to 1999?
After all, I have you in my heart!
Yeah! And I have you in my heart.
We are...
not alone!
Alone or together, I don't care!
I have no future...
unless I defeat you!
Together with Mystique!
The Makoto Jewels!
The swallow statue!
We'll get them all back!
Not just two! The three of us!
Open!
Pre-Kit Mirror Loupe!
Pochitan!
Makoto Jewel!
Look.
Feel.
Solve the mystery!
This is our answer!
Precure! Flying Spectrum!
CUREtto Case Closed!
Hanninda!
Pochi Pochi Cure Cure!
Let's go back.
Pochitan, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Hey! Is everyone okay?
Jett-senpai!
Would you look at that,
a proper fairy friend.
Your role is finished.
-Maestro Usonoir.
-You may go.
-Down into the trap room.
M-Maestro Usonoir.
P-Please, wait.
I have some valuable intel.
O-One of the Precures, Cure Answer,
said she "came to 1999."
What?
I think she came from another time.
A Precure who came from another time?
That's not written in the Tome of Mirages.
It can't be...
I got in touch with my sister!
She said she was asleep
and missed the call!
It was midnight in London, after all.
It was just like you said!
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
Thank you very much!
I'm glad Keiko is alright, too!
And the swallow statue is back in place!
-The ghost issue, too.
-Gold-star case closed!
My candy!
Take it out!
Give it back!
Hey, c'mon!
Pochitan! Come down!
(NaNaNaNa why? Why? WHY?
NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER?!)
(NaNaNaNa naze? naze? WHY?
NaNaNaNa nazo? nazo! ANSWER?!)
Connect the dots, oh? Oh my!
ten to ten musundara ara? ara!
Could it be a "gold-star case closed!"?
Could it?
"hanamaru kaiketsu!" kana? kana?
Reasoning turns around riddles
Twists and turns, reverse
suiri to nazo wa uragaeshi
niten santen gyakuten
Even words and behavior are traps? Traps!
Don't just believe them! No!
kotoba ya shigusa sae wana? wana!
unomi ni shite wa dame! dame!
Pay attention, think and then
Take the first step!
yoku mite, kangaete, sorekara
fumidasu no yo ippo!
When I see someone in trouble
I immediately want to help
komatteiru hito mitara
sugu ni tasuketai
Cause I wanna, wanna do something
So I go running off
datte nantoka nantoka nantoka shitakute
kakedashiteiru
Na Na Na mystery! Mystery!
Na Na Na nazo! nazo!
Solving mysteries
Is what a Star Detective does
nazo wo toku no ga meitantei
See through lies and find truth
Find the answer for a smile
uso ka makoto ka mikiwamete
egao no kotae mitsukeru
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 100
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 100 bai
Working together, we can figure it out
Friends are a true miracle
chikara awasete norikoeru
tomo wa kiseki no katamari
Let's go! Star Detective
iku yo! Meitantei
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 1,000
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 1,000 bai
Hand in hand with my friends
Until everything's solved!
tomodachi to te ni te wo totte
banjikaiketsu suru made!
We're Precure, after all
(NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER!)
DATTE Precure
(NaNaNaNa naze? nazo! ANSWER!)
I can't wait to go to school with you!
Me too!
Huh? The door won't open?
We need a key to get out?
Mikuru! It's detective time!
Star Detective Precure!
"Yikes! The School is a Maze?"
That mystery! CUREtto Case Closed!