You look good in anything
'cause you're so pretty, Big Sis Shikoku!
Cute!
Braids are nice!
Buns look great!
Glasses suit you, too!
What are you two doing?
Eight Thunder Gods
Rairen
Big Sis Shikoku was in a bad mood,
so I'm cheering her up!
Eight Thunder Gods
Kuusetsu
Are you still angry because one of
the pests managed to land a punch on you?
Yes, but she said it happened
because she had to suppress her powers
to sneak inside of the barrier.
Yeah, well... it still pissed me off.
I learned two things.
Humans can muster up
a surprising amount of power
depending on their emotional state.
You had best remember that.
So that there aren't
any embarrassing failures.
Nobody can hold a candle to me!
In strength or in beauty!
I'm perfect!
Are the traits of the prey she consumed
showing in her personality?
You're still just a hatchling, Kuusetsu.
Quit your bragging!
Huh?
What was that about a hatchling?
Oh, so she can change forms.
Cool, isn't it?
She's already insanely strong.
You mentioned learning two things?
Right.
I may be a god,
but I'm far from forgiving.
Clearly.
Hone your skills
until it's time for battle, Kuusetsu.
Only one god left until
the Eight Thunder Gods are complete.
I shall continue my research beautifully!
'Cause as you know, my special ability
lets me become infinitely strong!
And I'll wipe out the Demon Defense Force
all by myself!
Mune ga shizunde mirai kanjirenaku nattari
Toki ga tomatte mou owatta tte kanjitari
Fusagikonde hanasenakute
Jiwari kokoro no kasa ga hiraita
Soredemo tsuyogatte ikiteta
Nagusamete nante iwanai
Tsuyoku natte mae o mitetainda
Dakedo yowasa ga oshitsubusu
Kimi ni atte sekai afurete hikari ataetekuretari
Sukoshi datte kibou nakatta boku ga waraetetanda
Nanigenai kaiwa de zutto egao ataetekuretari
Arigatou tte terete warau kara iwanai yo
Dakedo omotteru yo
Kono saki mae muite ikeru kana?
Hikari yo, boku ni
A New Azuma
Episode 5
This is such an... indecent reward...
Huh?!
Do go on.
The reward for using Slave, hm?
I-it'll be over in just a minute.
Can't you go wait over there?
It's not as simple as that.
Why not?!
If you must reward him,
you ought to do it properly!
Even if the reward is a kiss,
focus on more than just his mouth.
Incorporate your hands.
Show your appreciation.
Don't get greedy.
Be sure to pace yourself.
They're adorable.
That takes care of the appetizers.
All that's left is the main dish.
Look, they found each other!
I want you to show me your power, Himari.
Sunset
Sol-Piercing Lance
Sunset.
A retractable spear.
Himari told me all about it.
It looks strong, plain and simple.
But I can counter it
with my "Heaven" form!
Heavenward!
Ah, that's how you defeated Homare.
And I'll take you down, too!
Do it, Yuuki!
How can she swing it so fast?!
She's in a different league than Homare!
We're in danger this close!
Yuuki!
He doesn't have enough experience
to fight me in that form.
Yuuki?!
Yuuki!
You allowed somebody else
to protect you again.
Is that it, Himari?
The extent of your power.
If Slave is your only means of combat,
Commander Uzen has it covered.
You can spin your spear to block,
but the blast will hit you!
Pathetic!
I can control my spear's output.
That was 10 percent of my power.
As a second-in-command,
you ought to require at least 30 percent,
Himari.
Hmm...
Guess that's it for the Banquet.
I-is that...
It's now or never.
Hold on, Himari! I'm coming!
Damn it, Maia!
You blacked out the moment
you saw Himari was in trouble.
Hey! Let me go, now!
You're staying right there.
This is for the Azumas.
Not even Yachiho can save you.
Well? What will you do?
I'll catch her at close range!
I'm also enhanced by my ability
while my spear is drawn.
Your hand-to-hand combat won't work.
We're done here.
A pitiful display for a second-in-command.
The 7th Squadron and Commander Uzen
must be nothing to write home about.
Me?
Second-in-command of the 7th Squadron?
I've been watching you
ever since you joined the 7th Squadron.
I have full confidence in you.
It's just...
I ran away from home,
so if you appoint me...
the Azumas...
There's a chance that the 9th Squadron
will think less of you.
So what?
I'm choosing you, Himari.
Himari?
S-sorry!
An Azuma ought to do better than this!
The Azuma Family doesn't need you!
Commander.
Thank you very much!
You're making me cry, too.
And here I thought my tears
had all dried up.
You earned the job with your tenacity!
Be proud of yourself!
Yes, ma'am!
This isn't the Himari I know.
What you just said... Take it back.
I won't let anyone talk bad
about the commander.
I said it because you're weak, Himari.
If it upsets you,
then make me take it back.
Learning!
Character Info
*Commander*
Yakumo Ezo
Mato Destruction Power
Is that...
Commander Ezo's Night Storm?!
That's your...
She copied Ame-no-Mitori?!
It isn't as accurate,
but it's suitable for battle.
This ability...
It's Homare's Python!
Golden Hour!
I'll say it one more time: Take it back.
Does something about Himari seem strange?
She's losing her cool.
A subconscious awakening on account
of her rage and the high-stakes situation.
Man, this is getting good!
Nobody gets to insult the commander!
I take back what I said
about Commander Uzen.
So come at me with everything you've got!
That's right!
My commander...
She's...
the best...
there is.
Looks like you're already at your limit.
But you showed me, Himari.
Your potential.
Well done, Himari.
Had you interfered,
we would have never known.
From now on,
don't forget to take care of yourself.
Maia had teamed up with Fubuki,
and Yachiho had participated
to support Himari.
The pair conceded,
and the Azuma Banquet came to a close.
Fubuki became the next matriarch.
So in this game,
when the gauge is maxed out,
you get to use a super special ability!
You can turn the tables
with a single move!
You're very knowledgeable, Shikoku.
Playing that electronic thing again?
We're sampling human pastimes.
Before we destroy 'em.
Yes, well, put it away.
Things are about to get busy for us.
Gotcha!
Going somewhere, Big Sis Shikoku?
To bring the eighth Thunder God to life.
It's about time!
I'm getting awfully hungry.
Can you consume a third person?
Yup!
I like eating the ones with abilities!
'Cause that's how
they turn into my abilities.
And the two inside me
are going to love having a new friend!
I'm amazed that you can make room
every time you're hungry.
But absolutely no ugly prey allowed!
Kinda sucks that she adopts
their personalities, though.
Should we attack the Demon Defense Force
and abduct one of them?
Let's avoid the Demon Defense Force
until all eight of us are here.
In fact... I have a brilliant idea.
Big Sis Shikoku! Such a pretty smile!
I kept my mouth shut
'cause it would've killed the mood,
but I got the healing stuff locked down.
You used two commanders' abilities
in a row?!
That's incredible!
Yeah, but I can't recreate it now.
Golden Hour! Golden Hour!
That pose isn't cool enough, Himari!
Like this! See?
I thought I'd finally mastered Learning,
but if not, then...
Be patient, Himari.
If it's a compatibility problem,
we'll solve it with training!
I agree with Commander Uzen.
You discovered your strength,
and that's enough for now.
Work on figuring out
how to develop its potential.
You've grown into a fine Azuma!
It's a little late for that.
So go and have a bunch of children
for the family's sake!
What?
I mean, you already have a man right here!
If you like, I can give a lecture
on how to conceive,
and I'll even let him sit in on it!
Oh, uh... W-wait a minute.
How about it?
That's okay, I...
There it is. Overbearing old bag.
Once she starts talking,
there's no stopping her.
Mother.
What?
Would you kindly shut up?
Come again?
Fubuki?
We have you to thank for
making our household stronger than ever.
However...
A performance-based system
encourages relentless competition,
even amongst the children,
and promotes familial conflict.
The children aren't being brought up
with a healthy mindset anymore.
Furthermore,
a matriarch who acts high and mighty
while cosplaying as
an ordinary member of the family
because it requires less effort
is not indicative
of a functional organization!
I would ask that you refrain
from wandering about outside
in a school uniform!
You need to grow up!
Then again,
I suppose I can overlook that part.
Who the hell do you think-
I am the head of the Azuma Family now.
You would've effortlessly countered
an attack like that
back in your
Supreme Commander days, Mother.
You're getting careless.
If you can't keep up with the times,
I will dispose of you.
Fubuki, you bitch.
You got stronger.
From here on out,
I'm in charge of the household.
Fine, suit yourself.
I will.
An Azuma should be powerful.
That principle will remain,
and I will create a new family.
From now on,
let's try and get along better.
Uh, okay...
Homare and Yumina.
I'm going to retrain you
from the inside out.
Lovingly, of course.
Blegh!
Commander Izumo, I look forward
to our long-lasting friendship.
Oh, same here!
Commander Uzen, I owe you an apology.
You were trying to rile up Himari.
But if you do think so little of me,
I'll prove you wrong anytime.
I have you to thank
for training Himari well.
The Azuma Family
will remember this kindness.
Don't go anywhere, you two.
Huh?
Let's brush up on your ability.
Hitting the ground running
with her new matriarch role.
You're on!
Cipher, cipher
Watashi o nozoku hitorikiri
Kaitentaishou loop shiten ne
Saiten bakari de tsukareta wa
Seikoutaiken doko ittanda?
Doko? Nee
Hattentojou panic sunzen
Ontei bakari o awaseru wa
Rinsen taisei jirettai ne
Glass no kutsu wa mou
Saitei sa
Konna no wa mou yameyou yo
Meishoubu no yokan
Kimi ni wakaru ka?
Cipher, cipher
Watashi o nozoku hitorikiri
Only you no taikendan
Inu ni nacchimae yo
Cipher, cipher
Mero sugiru kamo sono kusari
Sensenkyoukyou nonfiction
Hikiwakerannai ne
Daioujou
Watashi o nozoku no dare?
CHECK OUT
So this is where the humans live.
Late Summer Slave
Episode 7
Next time, Episode 7: "Late Summer Slave"
And here is today's bonus.
Wh-wh-what?!
Wow, our mom is badass!
I think this one would suit you, Himari.
What's that supposed to mean?!