Kaya.
Daddy.
Oh, hello. Wasn't Nana-san supposed
to pick Kaya-chan up today?
Yes, well...
It seems her mother
passed away last night.
What?
She did?
Hello. You've reached
Hanamugi Kindergarten.
Oh, good evening.
Chie-sensei?
Yes, she is. I'll put her on the phone.
Please wait a moment.
Kaya-chan's aunt is on the phone.
Hello. This is Hasumi speaking.
It's me, Nana.
Nana-san. Sorry for your loss.
Ext.
Select
Hold
Chie-sensei, I need to talk to you
about something.
What is it?
It's complicated, so I'd prefer
to discuss it in person.
Please come to the main house
of the Ebisumori family.
What?
What?!
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 11: Mommy's House Isn't Scary
Origami
Manabi-ya\h\h\h\h\hCrayons
And this one.
Oh, I drew that!
Yup. I really love this drawing
you did, Kaya-chan.
So I thought it'd make your grandma
happy if she could see it, too.
At her grave?
Mm-hmm.
That's the story we're going with,
right, Nana-san?
That's right.
Her father was exhausted,
so I told him I'd keep her for the day
to visit her grandmother's grave.
I'm sleeping all day,
— Shizuo
But that's an excuse.
Which means we're going there
for a different reason.
We're here.
So this is...
Ebisumori
The main house of the Ebisumori family.
The Ebisumori family. Where
Kaya-chan's mother grew up.
Okay, but...
What are you guys doing here?!
It concerns Kaya-sama.
There's no way I'd miss it.
It concerns Osamu-kun.
There's no way I'd sit this one out.
We're at a sacred site, Master.
More like a forbidden zone.
What's with these guys?
Are you sure you want them here?
I get Namu-san,
but Mob-san's a complete outsider.
Look who's talking.
It seems they also have
a history with Kaya.
Look what I made, Mobuo.
W-Well, I guess that's true.
Do you like it?
You're so talented.
I need all the help I can get right now.
Help?
That's convenient.
So now you're turning to an outsider?
Did seeing the way your mother died
strike fear in you?
Master.
Ebisumori Mutsu...
was murdered. Isn't that right?
Stop! There's a child in the room.
It seems you're still as sharp as ever.
Taking that into account as well,
I invited you here to share everything.
About the past and about what's to come.
This way, please.
Kaya-chan, why don't you go play
jump rope in the yard while we talk?
Okay!
Take care out there.
Um, is there anyone else here
besides you, Nana-san?
No. It's just me here.
Although there were a lot of comings
and goings when my mother was in charge.
Exorcists aren't exactly
popular these days.
The current head is a shabby psychic who
can't even fake it like the previous one.
Hey, don't be so rude—
He's right. I don't have the kind of power
my mother or Kaya does.
The best I can do is a basic exorcism.
What? Really?
But that's fine.
Because in this day and age, no one has a
need for such dubious people as psychics.
Still, even if we're no longer needed,
we can't simply be done with either.
What's left here are the
remnants of such an occupation.
Snap! Snap!
This is urgent.
So I will tell you everything
about the forbidden ritual
used to bring back the shrine maiden:
"Curse Gestation."
It was never meant to come to light.
Curse Gestation.
That's the method she mentioned
for intentionally producing psychics.
Curse Gestation requires one thing
above all else: a pregnant woman.
The ritual is performed by
the Ebisumori woman herself.
The father doesn't matter.
Nor does the fetus's sex.
Whatever it was originally, sorcery will
turn it into a vessel of a shrine maiden.
However, there's something that is
required for the transformation to occur.
What is it?
The umbilical cord.
The cord attached to the naval.
It was believed the shrine maiden's power
lay in the umbilical cord,
so the mother ingests the cord itself.
I see! Perhaps it was inspired
by customs like eating the placenta?
In the end, the theory was proved correct.
The fetus altered by Curse Gestation
was said to grow stronger
the longer it remained in the womb.
I was born prematurely,
so my time in the womb was very short.
That's why my transformation
was very minimal.
That is how I became a shabby psychic.
Makes sense.
Basically, you're just
a weaker version of Mutsu.
And there's nothing you can do against
the curse on the Ebisumori family.
What a joke. I don't know
where you picked up that grudge,
but you should clean up your own mess.
What do you mean? What curse?
Ebisumori Mutsu didn't die from illness,
and certainly not from old age.
She was cursed by another human being
who bears a grudge against the Ebisumoris.
Wh-What makes you say that?
That day, I went to see
Ebisumori Mutsu about something.
But she suddenly died
right in front of me.
That, in itself, doesn't matter to me.
If anything, I felt liberated.
I thought I might even get
to throw a jab at her after she died.
But her spirit didn't appear
right after her death.
But how? That's impossible!
Even when a person dies, their spirit
doesn't vanish the moment they die!
That's why Kyoko...
That's right. It wouldn't have
happened in a natural death.
The only explanation
is a human-cast curse.
Members of the Ebisumori family
are cursed by someone
who holds a deep grudge
against the family.
And you know who that is, don't you...
Ebisumori Nana?
You're absolutely right, Ebisumori Namu.
Let every curse
be laid upon
Ebisumori Mutsu
That's...
Let every curse
be laid upon
Ebisumori Nana
like what was written
inside Kaya-chan's talisman.
Mine was just a novelty for a child.
But what my mother had was real.
Let every curse be laid
upon Ebisumori Mutsu
She died in my place.
The one cursing us
in order to wipe us out...
is none other...
than my little sister.
Kaya's mother.
Ebisumori Mirai.
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Little Sisters Aren't Scary?
Kaya-chan's mother is the one...
...who killed Mutsu-san?
H-Hold on a second!
Crafting a curse strong enough
to kill someone isn't so simple.
Nana
Mirai
And Kaya-sama's mother
was born an ordinary person.
There's no way—
She can.
Because...
Every younger sister
born into the Ebisumori family
are destined to bear cursed objects.
Cursed objects?
At times, they wipe out targets with ease.
Other times, they generate vast wealth
when that power is sold.
They are the core of the curse.
The reason the Ebisumori family
has grown so large,
and can live comfortably
even as the spiritual trade declines
Ebisumori
is largely because of those cursed objects
rather than the shrine maidens.
And that's what's inside
Kaya-chan's mother?
Yes, she is pregnant with a cursed object.
That doesn't add up, though.
If that's the case, the Ebisumoris
would cherish the younger sisters.
They should be treated well.
Why would one bear a grudge?
Allow me to explain from the beginning.
Huh?
Who's she?
You have a big tummy.
Is there a baby inside?
Like I said earlier,
in Curse Gestation, the fetus grows
stronger the longer it's in the womb.
The child born has no human form,
and the broken vessel
constantly releases curses.
The thing devours the mother's life
and tears through the womb to be born.
It's a cursed infantlike being that brings
death to the one the mother wished for.
Hiruko-no-kami. The Leech Child.
In their attempt to create shrine maidens
with greater power,
Hiruko-no-kami emerged
from that desire,
ultimately sealing
the Ebisumori family's fate.
The younger sisters
were called "Ohara-sama"
and brainwashed to bear cursed objects,
sacrificing their lives
in times of crisis.
And the last person
to become an "Ohara-sama"
was this woman: Ebisumori Yoshie.
My mother's younger sister.
Oh, I remember her.
Yes, I showed you a photo before.
She's the woman in this picture.
Aunt Yoshie took great care of us.
She was cheerful and kind.
Mirai especially looked up
to our aunt like a real mother,
since she didn't get
much attention from our mother.
Yoshi-chan!
Oh. Hi, Nana-chan and Mirai-chan.
Your tummy's so big! Can I touch it?
No, Mirai!
Why not?
B-Because Mom said you're not supposed
to touch Ohara-sama's baby.
I don't know anything about that!
Nobody tells me anything!
Don't make such grim faces, you two.
I'm sure the baby will
be happier if you smile.
You can touch my tummy. Just be gentle.
Yay!
Wow.
Unlike me, who, as the shrine maiden,
already knew about the Ohara-sama,
Mirai never knew the truth about
what happened to Aunt Yoshie in the end.
Or that's what I thought.
Right up until that moment.
I'm sure she's uncovered the truth
about the Ebisumori family.
She's spending the day with your older sister
So Kaya's at the house.
The Ebisumori Family Isn't Scary?
Look, Nana-chan!
Huh?
Look what I found. Isn't it cute?
Mom!
Since birth, my mother and sister
could see things I couldn't.
No, no, no! It's my little bunny!
Most of the time, a possessed object
can be disposed of in a ritual fire.
Remember that, Nana.
Okay.
I couldn't understand a word
of what they were talking about.
Mirai-chan.
What's the matter?
Did you have a fight with Nana-chan?
Or was it with your mother?
Both!
Oh, bummer.
Well, that can't be helped.
Nana-chan and your mother
are shrine maidens, after all.
Shrine maidens?
A shrine maiden's power is special,
and they do a lot for the family.
The reason we can live so peacefully
without hardship is all thanks to them.
But she burned my stuffed animal.
Oh, you're still hung up on that, huh?
Then...
How about I give you something better?
Chicke-Men
Rockin'
delish
Umashibo
Seaside
Grill\h\h
Gumi Tree
Neri Neri Neri-ne
Mix until fluffy
Chicke-Men
Rockin'
delish
Umashibo
Seaside
Grill\h\h
Gumi Tree
Neri Neri Neri-ne
Mix until fluffy
Chicke-Men
Rockin'
delish
Umashibo
Seaside
Grill\h\h
Gumi Tree
Neri Neri Neri-ne
Mix until fluffy
Wow, really?
Just don't tell your mom
and Nana-chan, okay?
Do you want some, too, Yoshi-chan?
Thanks, but I'm staying away
from snacks for the baby.
You're a good mom.
Right?
Aunt Yoshie felt more like a mother to me
than my own mother,
and I was a little jealous of the baby
she was about to give birth to.
Funeral of
Ebisumori Yoshie-sama
My mother said she died
in a car accident.
Where's the baby?
It's not here anymore.
Take that!
Begone, evil spirits!
Wh-What was that for?
Oh, c'mon. It's what
your family always does.
Namah Samanta. Om Kili Kili!
Bam!
I've never done anything like that!
Liar.
My parents say your family's nothing but
a bunch of fake psychics running a scam.
You don't want to go to school?
Bullied again, I see.
I'll talk to the school,
so don't let them get to you.
But you don't make Nana go!
So I don't want to go to school, either.
The Curse of Ebisumori Mirai!
Her target is K-kun
from
Class 3!
Photo Order Form
Ebisumori Mirai
Curse
Begone,
evil
spirits
We're sisters, after all.
Mirai.
Don't make things so difficult for Mom.
She's doing what's best for you.
What's best for me?
I'm the only one forced
to go out of the house
and left to deal with whatever
outsiders want to say or do to me!
No one in this family helps me!
And you say that's what's best for me?!
Mirai—
That's right.
Why only me?
What's so different about me
compared to Nana?
You're not a shrine maiden.
Mirai!
Don't, Nana.
Leave her be.
Infant and Early
Childhood Health
New Edition
Childcare Studies
So for our next class,
we'll be using your Maternal and
Child Health Notebook for reference.
Please bring either
the original or a copy.
Hey, that's her, right?
The girl everyone calls
the "Cult Princess"?
Hey, not so loud.
She'll actually take you out.
Maternal and Child Health Notebook?
I doubt she kept such a thing.
Ebisumori
Maybe she has Nana's.
Hmm, this is the only
place I can think of.
Huh?
Mother's name:
Ebisumori Yoshie
Child's name:
Municipality:
These are...
Yoshi-chan.
This picture. I couldn't find it anywhere,
but it was kept in here.
I've been all by myself in this world
ever since you left us, Yoshi-chan.
Maternal and
Child Health Notebook
Huh? Is this Yoshi-chan's notebook?
Facility or
Provider Name
eaten it when I had the chance...
That's my only regret.
But I need to help
the baby grow,
so Mommy's gonna
do her best
Doctor’s Notes
(Rest, Leave from Work etc)
Weight
Additional Tests
(Including Hemoglobin)
Blood Type Test
I'm staying away from snacks for the baby.
You're a good mom.
Oh, Yoshi-chan.
Record
Questions to Ask
If you have bleeding, your water breaks, or feel strong tightening
in your abdomen, see a doctor immediately.
Unlike normal childbirth, I hear it happens in an instant, so there's no pain or suffering.
I used to think a lot about the afterlife, but my sister said she would guide me as the shrine maiden.
"Unlike normal childbirth,
I hear it happens in an instant,
so there's no pain or suffering."
"I used to think a lot
about the afterlife,
Questions to Ask
If you have bleeding, your water breaks, or feel strong tightening
in your abdomen, see a doctor immediately.
Unlike normal childbirth, I hear it happens in an instant, so there's no pain or suffering.
I used to think a lot about the afterlife, but my sister said she would guide me as the shrine maiden.
So I'm not worried.
but my sister said she would
guide me as the shrine maiden."
"So I'm not worried."
I've spent my life being protected by my sister.
But the day I can finally serve her and the Ebisumori family is almost here.
"I've spent my life being
protected by my sister."
"But the day I can finally serve her
and the Ebisumori family is almost here."
It's been moving a lot inside my belly
lately. I can feel the power to destroy
our enemy growing stronger.
"It's been moving a lot
inside my belly lately."
"I can feel the power to destroy
our enemy growing stronger."
What?
What is this?
Looks like my sister hasn't properly educated Mirai-chan.
"Looks like my sister hasn't
properly educated Mirai-chan."
I can feel my face going pale.
"It seems she doesn't
understand the difference
It seems she doesn't understand the difference
between shrine maidens and Ohara-sama.
between shrine maidens and Ohara-sama."
My instincts are raising the alarm.
It seems she doesn't understand the difference
between shrine maidens and Ohara-sama.
If Mirai-chan doesn't get educated, the one
who'll have a hard time later will be
Nana-chan as the shrine maiden
"If Mirai-chan doesn't get educated,
Nana-chan, as the shrine maiden,
is the one who'll have a hard time later."
Don't read any more.
It seems she doesn't understand the difference
between shrine maidens and Ohara-sama.
If Mirai-chan doesn't get educated, the one
who'll have a hard time later will be
Nana-chan as the shrine maiden.
It's Mirai-chan's life, after all.
"It's Mirai-chan's life, after all."
"We should make sure it ends
in a way she can accept."
It seems she doesn't understand the difference
between shrine maidens and Ohara-sama.
If Mirai-chan doesn't get educated, the one
who'll have a hard time later will be
Nana-chan as the shrine maiden.
It's Mirai-chan's life, after all.
We should make sure it ends in a way
Or else...
I'll leave in this notebook the things Mirai-chan
needs to know as the next Ohara-sama.
May she honorably fulfill her duty
as an Ohara-sama.
"I'll leave in this notebook
the things Mirai-chan needs to know
as the next Ohara-sama."
"May she fulfill her duty
as an Ohara-sama honorably."
Mirai-chan.
Ohara-sama's Role
"Mirai-chan will probably be the one
who uses my umbilical cord."
No!
Yoshi-chan didn't die in a car accident.
Yoshi-chan had to die...
for the Ebisumori shrine maiden.
Why didn't I realize it sooner?
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka
In this family, only the eldest daughter
with special powers is considered human.
The rest are just eggs meant to give birth
to monsters and be broken whenever.
It's a twisted family
that thinks nothing of its own kin.
Maternal and
Child Health Notebook
Ebisumori Yoshie
You can't just leave!
At least talk to Mom about it first.
As if!
You know she'll never
allow me to leave, Nana!
I was...
never treated like a human
in this house. Not even once!
The Ebisumori family
should never have existed.
It's nearly time.
We can't stay here anymore.
We can't fail this one.
Sato Mirai
Sato-san, let's get you on an IV.
No way...
Oh, no!
Someone! It's an emergency!