Wrong.
Assassinate?
Play dead?
Wrong.
It's "don't fight homicidal maniacs."
I don't understand.
I've killed people during games.
Isn't that enough for the rest of society
to consider me a homicidal maniac?
These games are built around survival,
not killing, as the win condition.
That's why we've become
specialized in only that.
But homicidal maniacs are different.
They're playing a different game.
Whatever you do, don't fight them.
What if I'm forced to fight one?
What if it's the only way to win?
What do I do then?
Training is over.
Figure the rest out yourself.
It was probably Hakushi's
so-called "homicidal maniac"
who threw the pine cone,
but that would mean
she'd been targeting her.
Impossible. She'd never
make a mistake like that.
But there was no other
plausible explanation.
No. That doesn't matter.
What I should be focusing
on right now is...
my own survival.
A-chan?
What will happen to me
if I don't become a swan?
What?
A duck...
If I'm still a duck when I grow up...
what should I do?
What do you think you should do?
Huh? Me?
If I'm still a duck?
But I like ducks more than swans.
Really?
Then you'll be fine
even if you stay a duck.
Even if I don't become a swan...
Even if I can't do anything about it...
Still... That's exactly why...
All I can do is fight back.
It will soon be 5 PM on day one.
It is time for everyone to go home.
No matter how far it went,
the sun never got closer.
Instead, as it gradually grew
smaller and farther,
the sun said...
"You are a grey nightjar.
I see. That must be
quite difficult for you.
Fly tonight,
and ask the stars for a favor.
After all, you are not a daytime bird."
Moegi-san.
It will soon be 5 PM on day one.
Good. You're still alive.
It is time for everyone to go home.
There's a serial killer among the rabbits,
so no one can focus on the game.
You're not leaving, are you?
No.
I felt hopeless by myself.
I'm glad I ran into you.
The situation has become difficult,
but let's survive together.
Okay.
So, I know it's a lot to ask,
but may I make a request?
I don't have any weapons right now.
If you can afford to
spare anything, then...
Sure.
Thank you.
One shot will do, right?
It is now 5 PM.
The gates will open again
at 6 AM tomorrow.
It is now 5 PM.
The gates will open again
at 6 AM tomorrow.
I ran into a rabbit.
She was like a ghost.
What?
Their experience levels
were too different.
No matter what I tried to do,
the ghost was always one step ahead.
At this rate...
I thought if I killed my parents...
If I could just kill my parents,
then I could be like Kyara-san.
I knew that a grey nightjar
could never become a whale.
That's not...
That's just not...
I love you.
Apparently, that was how Moegi
interpreted her exhalation.
I love you.
Because it was something
she'd never received before,
she didn't understand
exactly what it was, but...
I love you.
That warmth
was her final remaining reason to live.
Even if a grey nightjar
can't reach that star,
I...
I will keep fighting.
I refuse to lose here.
Because I am Kyara-san's student!
My nerves burned with pain.
I think I took another blow
to my shoulder and stomach,
but I couldn't tell where anymore.
I didn't even understand why
the ghost woman made that face,
but apparently, it was over.
It meant I didn't have to
pretend to be strong anymore.
I haven't felt this way
since I killed my parents.
Wait, what?
How did the grey nightjar end up?
It couldn't become a star, and then...
Whatever. I'll have Kyara-san
read it to me again.
In any case, until my very
last breath, I, Moegi...
until my very last breath...
cried tears of frustration.
And so, the grey nightjar's
star continued to burn.
It kept burning and burning and burning.
It's still burning to this day.
It was inconsequential.
She lacked talent.
That was the only way to put it.
Apparently, she was the
homicidal maniac's student,
but she surely lacked potential.
Even if we'd repeated the
same events a hundred times,
that stump would've lost every time.
But still, she saw it.
Her face as she died.
She poured all of her being into
reaching for it and still failed.
How could she compensate a loser
who'd lived the best she could
but whose efforts didn't pay off?
Yuki couldn't begin
to guess what that was,
and she couldn't begin
to sympathize if asked,
but there was still something there.
It was different from Yuki's
feelings of "just because."
By continuing to play these games
and live in this world,
there was something she could achieve.
And Yuki killed that.
Someone living "just because"...
No, a practical ghost who
wasn't even really alive...
depending on her innate talent.
Hakushi had taught her how
to emotionally prepare herself.
Take a couple of slow breaths.
But not even that technique
could clear her mind.
No matter how many times she breathed,
nothing changed.
Eventually, even the beating
of her own heart
felt strange to Yuki.
A part of her couldn't accept
that the stump had died
while she still lived.
If she encountered the homicidal
maniac in that state, she'd die.
Still, her legs didn't stop walking.
How do I have legs
when I'm not a ghost?
Isn't that incredible?
Welcome home.