Causes of death are many and varied.
Old age, suicide, illness...
But the cause of death that scares the
most people in this day and age...
...is death by fire.
I...
took damage this heavy?
You did well, Ogun!
You too, Hinawa!
I'm sorry!
Given that I had to avoid hitting Ogun,
I couldn't finish him with one shot!
A-An Insect!
Yu!
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Episode 18
"Incantation of Destruction"
What's that noise?
The battle has begun outside.
We should hurry, too.
Yeah.
Since I'm finally here at my legacy,
I'd like to take a good look around,
but I don't think we
have that kind of time.
Vul, do you know what the key is?
There's no doubt that it's the starter
that kicks off the Great Cataclysm.
And there's that string of numbers.
This technology is incredible.
Yeah, it is, but from what I can see,
this area is all just support
systems for the generator.
Looking at the data from the
Tabernacle on the continent,
the hole for the key should
be in the core section.
But according to the
map we got from Joker,
Amaterasu's structure is
a lot more complicated.
Careful you don't get lost, okay?
Don't get separated from us, Arthur-san!
There is no need to have
such worries for a knight.
Stare...
Arthur!
Arthur-san!
Whoa! Hey! It's pitch black!
Are you serious? It's completely broken.
I can't believe something that
Vulcan built could break.
Should I use my flames for light?
No, it's too enclosed here.
It'd be bad if any combustible
gases caught fire.
The core isn't far from here.
I'll take the lead.
Use the lights on our fireproof
suits as markers and stay close.
Understood.
All right. Let's go.
According to the map,
it's just up ahead...
on the other side of these doors.
There isn't any power, is there?
How are we gonna open them?
Those doors look pretty big.
This, here. Yu.
Yes, sir.
I made sure to bring it.
The Ultra External Battery!
All right. Now they'll open!
This is the core my ancestor
built for Amaterasu.
Thank you for opening that for me.
Feeler!
Everyone is guarding the entrance!
How did you get in here?!
Insects can creep in from anywhere
before you even realize it, right?
Arthur, I'll leave him to you!
The rest of us will support...
What? Where did he go?!
Did Arthur-san get separated from us?
Come on, are you serious?
This is a will o' the wisp.
Where have Vulcan and the
others disappeared to?
I see. Companions abducted
by the Demon King.
An abyssal dungeon.
This must be a rescue event!
As a knight, it was naïve of me
to attempt to skip a rescue event
in order to battle Dragon King Dracon.
The Knight King, Arthur Boyle,
shall overcome this trial without fail!
Vulcan, what do we do?
Arthur isn't here. We just
have to handle it ourselves!
Are you okay, Yu?
Yes! I am feeling very grateful!
To you, Vulcan, and to Lisa-san
for saving me back then, of course!
But also to Shinra-san and
Arthur-san, to the sister,
and to everyone in the 8th
who looked after me.
I know that I'm alive now
thanks to all of you!
There's all the doctors and nurses
who performed procedures on me, too!
This world is just overflowing
with so much love!
I was able to realize that once more
thanks to the wound that sent
me to the brink of death!
Thank you so much, Giovanni-san!
Thank you for shooting me!
Okay. Now stand back.
Yes, sir.
It is I who wishes to express gratitude.
For over 250 years, you've kept it safe.
Our key to Amaterasu, that is.
That's my ancestor's key!
Then do you know what this is?
Yeah. I have a guess as to what's inside.
It's pi, right?
Indeed it is.
In ancient times, the Evangelist implanted
pi as the incantation of destruction.
Incantation?
Humanity has continued to chant
this incantation of destruction.
And now that the image of that
destruction has been established,
the computation of pi is finally complete.
The computation of pi
is complete? You idiot.
Pi continues infinitely.
It can't be completed!
That was true before the
previous Great Cataclysm.
Whether it's then or now,
it doesn't affect pi!
Didn't you see the moon
and stars in the night sky?
The physical laws of
this world have changed.
Just as the last Great Cataclysm turned
human combustion into a mainstream event,
pi has now become completable.
And now that pi has been solved,
humanity is finally straining to
reach the end of its evolution.
The end?
There is a theory that the end of an
organism's evolution is destruction,
and that theory is correct.
While striving for the destruction
that lies at the end of evolution,
humanity has conjured an
image of a wish for death.
That image is the Great Cataclysm,
as well as their goal
to return to the flames
and to go home to the sun!
Why the sun?
How are dying and the sun related?
Long ago, the star that we
now refer to as the sun
saw the essence of its image transform
to conform with destruction,
and it became a star of flames.
This planet, in the
coming Great Cataclysm,
will become a second sun!
All of the human pillars
who have disappeared
are now in Adolla, fulfilling their roles.
It can't be. I don't believe it!
The moon has that face now.
Right now, we don't
know what might happen.
Licht. Licht!
Vulcan-kun, I heard everything.
What he said is very difficult to believe,
but considering everything the
8th has investigated up to now,
it's hard to definitively call it a lie!
We've got our hands full
with the situation out here,
but we'll find a way to head to you!
You have to hold out until then!
Now, this lecture is over.
I have work to do.
Get out of my way!
I won't let you!
Vulcan's ancestor built Amaterasu!
I won't let you use it as
a weapon of destruction!
You won't let me?
What a ridiculous thing to say.
From the beginning,
Amaterasu was built to trigger the Great
Cataclysm as a destructive device!
Then why did my ancestor hide the key?
Two hundred and fifty years ago,
your Joseph family participated in the
construction of Amaterasu with us.
"With us"? Just who are you?
During the construction of Amaterasu,
there was a team that would later
lead the founding members of Haijima.
My ancestors were engineers on
that team alongside you Josephs.
My ancestors as well as yours were
in charge of the power source.
However, you Josephs...
Amaterasu
Wh...
Who's
there...
Hel...
Amaterasu
Help...
me...
Foolishly, he put a lock
on Amaterasu's true powers,
sealing them away.
Which is why my family has continued
to monitor the Joseph family
while waiting for the right time to come.
Monitor?
You turned Gramps and my old man
into Infernals and killed them!
They were fools who turned their
backs on the will of Adolla.
I merely granted them the
release of the flames.
You...
You monster!
I granted you the power of my research,
yet you foolishly choose to turn on me?!
Lisa!
Are you okay?
Somehow, yeah.
What's going on with that body of his?
It's all Insects.
All of that writhing black...
It's all a mass of Insects.
Fire Force
Chapter 3
It's all right. I'm here with you.
He's using some kind of power
to control the Insects, right?
I have a plan.
We'll get through this together.
Yu! That thing I asked for!
Yes, sir!
Found it!
Feeler!
Do you remember, Feeler?
V-Vulcan!
Lisa! Put your tentacles through here!
How absurd.
We've researched how to deal with Insects!
Insects use organs that humans
don't have to see the flow
of magnetic fields
and act based on them!
What?
Wh-What is this?!
We used Lisa's ability to disrupt the
magnetic fields and disperse the Insects.
So that's your real body.
How pathetic.
Me? Pathetic?
I will strike and strike
and strike a stone bridge
because I am too cautious
to cross it otherwise.
Your finish is too weak, Vulcan.
As a reward for what you've done for me,
I shall give you the gift
of terror in return.
A-An Insect!
Yu!
It can't be!
Captain! What was that?
This is an emergency!
Bring the line of defense
back and send aid inside!
Go! I will handle this alone!
Counting on you!
Hang in there, Vulcan!
You...
will not pass!
Out of the way!
If that door is blocked...
So you've finally realized it?
The ones who have been
delayed here aren't us.
Maki-san, what was that?
I made them after getting support
for materials from Haijima.
They're a new style of barrel.
Before, when he used Velocity
Rampage, he'd only get one shot.
But with these barrels...
She's been hearing it
ever since she was born!
Humanity's despair!
Connected to Adolla,
she continued to observe
it until she broke down!
Humanity's filthy, dark, deep psyches
packed tightly together into
the collective unconscious!
She's heard it ever since she
was a child who should've cried
and been coddled by her mama!
Do you think she wants to keep
living a life like that?!
I will trigger the Great Cataclysm...
and I will free Haumea from this hell!
The Great Cataclysm will
purify this planet!
It will end this hell!
Yu!
No... Please, stop it!
Vulcan-kun. Vulcan-kun!
Yu...
What's happened? Please respond!
Vulcan-kun!
Yu was persistent in coming to
the workshop over and over again.
Every time, he smiled and asked
me to make him my apprentice.
And he always held his toy
like it was precious to him.
I always thought he must be some
well-born boy who came by for a laugh.
But one day, when I went into
town to do some shopping...
I found Yu on the street,
wrapped in a blanket.
When I asked, he said his
parents had died in a fire.
After losing everyone,
the thing that had supported him
was that junky toy that
he'd carried so carefully.
That's why Yu wanted to become an
engineer who could make things from junk,
and why he'd come to my workshop.
I'd already decided
I wasn't taking apprentices.
So I brought Yu in as
a member of my family.
I still remember
how Yu smiled in that moment.
After a while, Lisa showed up, too,
and it was the three
of us living together.
As their older brother, I swore that
I'd protect Yu and Lisa, no matter what.
Yay!
I was only an engineer in a tiny workshop,
but I was going to make them happy!
Vulcan-kun!
An Insect got Yu.
What?
I can't let Yu turn into
an Infernal like this!
Help him, Licht! I need knowledge!
Is there some method besides magnetic
fields that can control the Insects?
Leave it to me! That's why I'm here!
Are you listening, Vulcan-kun?
Methods by which Insects
control their fellows...
Given your circumstances,
there are two possibilities!
The first is to use the magnetic fields
that you disrupted to control
their sense of direction.
The other is the specific,
unique dance of the honeybees!
It's highly likely that Doctor Giovanni is
using that dance to control the Insects!
Please stop the individual
bug that is dancing!
Lisa!
I understand.
I'll never forgive him.
We're stopping him, no matter what!
Whatever it takes,
I'm gonna slaughter him!
Lisa!
He modified a type of Insect so that
it wouldn't be affected by magnetism,
and now it's dancing to control
the rest of the swarm?
No. He's cautious enough to repeatedly
strike a stone bridge before crossing.
I can't imagine he'd use an Insect with
greater chances of irregularities arising.
He's an engineer, too.
He wouldn't have used Insects.
To control them,
he'd have built Insect mechs!
If it's a mech, then its heat source
and movement should be different!
In this giant swarm of Insects,
I will find the mechs that
are controlling them all!
Where? Where are they?
Vulcan!
Not yet!
There!
Lisa! There are seven of them!
Vul!
I marked them!
Let's end this!
Leave it to me!
I crushed all the mechs!
All that's left...
is Giovanni!
Help... Help me...
Help...
Yu!
Yu?
I'm right here, Vulcan.
Yu...
Your finish is weak, Vulcan.
I used an Insect to make
my way into his body.
The solution to pi is here.
It's time to compare answers.
The Great Cataclysm is about to begin.
To Be Continued
Fire Force Chapter 3
Now, let's move forward...
Next Time
toward the end of this tale.
Despair is nothing special.
Despair doesn't suit us in the 8th!
Next time, "Those Who Fight Back."
Episode 19
Those Who Fight Back
Return to the great flame of fire. Látom.