I've come to invite you
to play in Candle Woods.
Are you ready to go?
Yes.
Please take me there now.
This is a story about a deranged world.
I'll be back.
Good morning.
That outfit doesn't suit you at all.
Same to you.
It's been three months
since we were last together.
Has it been that long?
How are you doing?
You haven't picked up any
odd injuries, have you?
No. I'm doing well.
There are so many of them.
Probably mostly beginners.
Not so. Most are regulars.
What?
We'll probably start six hours from now.
We have a lot of time.
Let's go for a walk.
I'll wait here.
That wasn't a request.
How many games is this?
This is my sixth or seventh or eighth.
I haven't reached ten yet.
How many times have I told you?
After completing a game—
Record what happened.
What does it matter? I'm doing well.
What about you?
Have you completed 99 games?
I'm still only at 96.
I haven't played since the pool.
You're taking your time.
With four more to go,
I want to be careful.
What's that?
Why is it so beat-up?
It's the explainer.
We thought there might
be an item hidden in it.
Won't you get in trouble
with the game runners?
I would've left a turtle or wolf alone,
but it's a raccoon dog.
And it's acceptable to break raccoon dogs?
Rabbits beat raccoon dogs,
like in "Kachi-Kachi Mountain."
Kachi-Kachi...?
You haven't heard of it?
I have.
I see.
We're playing hide-and-seek this time.
If we rabbits survive for a week, we win.
A stump wins if they kill
at least five rabbits.
The raccoon dog didn't mention it,
but the stumps were probably
given some kind of equipment.
Rabbits and stumps.
It's an odd combination.
You don't know that story, either?
I do. I know that one. Really.
"The Rabbit and the Stump," right? Yeah.
You're a smart student.
You know, rabbits...
are killed by stumps.
I'll be back.
Um...
Good morning...
Hello.
I'm Moegi.
Nice to meet you.
What does she mean by that?
Who knows?
Um, am I the last one?
What is it this time?
An escape game? A survival game?
Was there a rules explanation?
Huh?
Was there?
What? I don't know.
Is this everyone's first time?
Do you not know why you're here?
Um...
Moegi-san, you're a veteran, right?
Do you know what this is?
Players—rather, the stump team.
Welcome to Candle Woods.
Arm yourselves.
You will be hunting rabbits.
You're drinking that?
Will you be going the whole week
without eating or drinking?
There must be food stored somewhere.
I've never played such a
large-scale game before.
Are you nervous?
I feel like I always do.
I'm surprised this many idiots are willing
to risk their lives for a few million.
You're one to talk.
Maybe we are idiots.
Why do you play these games?
I...
Why do I play?
Don't ask me.
Ninety-nine games, huh?
There's no trophy or cash prize, right?
Nope. It'd just be the new record.
Actually, there's no
guarantee it would be.
I've just heard 98 consecutive
wins is the record.
I can't believe you're
counting on a rumor.
You'll understand eventually.
Let's come up with a strategy.
Against ranged weapons,
we'll split up and take it slow.
Against melee weapons...
Slacking off?
Sumiyaka-san.
You're as unfriendly as ever, huh?
And you feel terrible to hug.
You should eat better food.
You're making good money.
Shouldn't you be over there?
Nothing for a mere 29-game
veteran to do over there.
The rabbits' leader is a 95-game veteran.
We could sleep through this game and win.
She's really amazing, isn't she?
What? Amazing doesn't
begin to describe her.
Do you have any idea what
the odds are of beating 95 games?
Avoid acting on your own.
Always act and strike in
groups of at least three.
Is it one in 95?
Idiot.
I calculated it once.
The survival rate is 70%.
Multiply that 95 times,
and you get one in 500 trillion.
What?
Do the math once you're home.
No one on Earth can compare to her.
Your mentor is humanity's
greatest genius of all time.
You'd better give her
the respect she deserves.
There's no need to push ourselves.
We'll steal our opponents' weapons
and build up our strength.
I do.
Do you?
Yeah, that's right.
I'm gonna go.
Okay.
Kill her.
This is practice.
I want all of you to kill her.
What's your name?
Your player name.
It's Kabane.
Kabane-san. Kill her.
B-But she's still alive.
Yes, she is. So kill her.
Twice per person—that's the quota.
Stab through to at least
the center of the blade.
Ideally, aim for a vital point.
Why aren't you picking it up?
But, um... th-the order...
What?
Wh-Why am I first?
It's not fair unless we decide
with rock-paper-scissors—
It doesn't matter who's first!
I'm saying you'll all die
unless you stab her!
We're not just hunting
rabbits in this game.
We're trying to kill each other.
It's kill or be killed!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry. Please don't be angry.
If a stump dies, that leaves
more spots for survivors.
So the rabbits will try to kill us, too.
Unless you shape up,
they'll take your weapons and kill you.
It doesn't just affect you, either.
It'll be a huge loss for the whole team.
For all of us to survive,
we need your help.
Don't hesitate.
I'm quitting.
I didn't know it was like this.
I'll drop out, so please forgive me.
Please.
Please. Please. Please.
Please...
Ah.
Ah?
What's your name?
Next.
Moegi-san.
What?
What should we do now?
Grab all the weapons and
make sure everyone is armed.
I'll come up with a strategy.
Don't come in.
Her head felt heavy.
I considered putting a hole in it
to make it lighter for her.
But I thought she'd done well this time.
She deserves credit for that.
A strong player who
doesn't care how she looks.
I know she would've done the same.
She deserves credit for acting that
way for the last half hour or so.
Because that was her goal.
Eventually, she'd be able to
act that way all the time.
Moegi was willing to give
her life to achieve that goal.
A strong player who doesn't hesitate.
A strong person who
doesn't care how she looks.
She'd keep coming back from the dead
until she achieved it.