Episode 11
Guys, do you really think this will work?
I gave up a cushy job
to come here, you know!
Xiao, just follow orders
from the higher-ups.
No complaining.
This is obviously a trap.
What kind of idiot would fall for it?
Ha! If you ask me,
Biyou Village is full of idiots.
Who do you think came up
with this terrible idea?
It's not Chairman Zhao's style!
Who else could it be?
Who was closest to Ma back in the village?
Such an obvious scheme!
The Bastard is bullying honest people!
Father!
What's wrong, this early in the morning?
Bai, what happened?
The Company captured Brother Qing!
They took him to some "secret bunker,"
and said they need info on
a guy called Ma Xianhong.
Why did you come forward?
Aren't you afraid...
I feel guilty.
I don't want to have nightmares anymore.
I can confirm that they
really don't know anything.
I can't bring myself to
harm these kids any longer.
In five days, if they still
haven't revealed anything,
they'll be crippled and
permanently imprisoned here.
I've already told you the
location of this secret bunker.
I want to at least let
the outside world know
what's happening here.
What should I ask?
How's this guy been doing lately?
This answer isn't even worth reading.
The Company really knows
how to cause trouble.
Sir, we have no idea
what's going on either.
Look, you were fine for
the first two days, right?
If you don't mind me asking,
why did you flip over our mattress?
Miss, why are you interrogating me?
This is getting ridiculous!
Day after day! Can't a guy
get a good night's sleep?
How annoying!
Is this guy crazy?
Master Wang...
Sorry.
Whoa! Finally showing your face, huh!
You guys have the nerve to say sorry?
I've been ignoring you day after day,
and you just keep pushing!
Have you no shame? When will this end?
Tell me, what exactly do you want?
Master Wang, you've repeatedly
refused Master Kui's invitations,
so we have no choice!
Master Kui told us to follow you,
so we can only obey...
Chen Jinkui?
Fine, I'm tired of this too.
I'll give you a place.
Tell him to come,
alone!
There are only three days left
until the so-called execution day.
Come to think of it,
the company really went all out,
giving up an entire secret
bunker just for Ma Xianhong.
How could that be?
I heard something happened to the
Company's first secret bunker
and it was later abandoned.
This must be that one.
Not bad, Zhang Chulan.
Huh?
First you toy with that silly girl,
now you've even lured the
Heavenly Master's disciple to your side.
Hey, Brother Guan Er!
The way you put it...
"Lure" is such an ugly word.
Oh, by the way, Zhang, did you know?
They found that baldy, Liu Mingyuan.
He was dead. It was suicide.
We checked with guys in the Northeast,
turns out he was some kind of folk shaman.
Not very skilled, not famous either.
People who knew him didn't
remember him for his abilities,
but for his unshakable drug addiction.
What are you thinking about?
Huh?
Right, tell everyone about how
you came up with this clever scheme.
Scheme? Me?
Well, it was like this.
We all had our own tasks back then.
I was in charge of chatting with Ma,
and you guys dealt with him too.
Describe Ma.
The kid's got potential.
He's just a bit extreme.
Too stubborn.
A brat who thinks too highly of himself.
Paranoid, arrogant, loves splitting hairs.
Thank you.
I've spent the most time with him,
so I've noticed some other things.
You're all right,
but have you noticed that
this guy also has a strong sense
of justice and responsibility?
And he has another very important trait:
frankness!
These traits of his make me think
there's a subtle mismatch
between him and his rescuer.
The killer was willing to eliminate
Company personnel to save him,
which suggests that Ma is
very important to the killer.
Ma kept a low profile in Biyou Village,
but he welcomed everyone
without hiding himself.
This guy doesn't like hiding.
But what about the killer?
Ma's close associates and
his escorts are all dead,
which must be for the sake of hiding.
I see.
Not hiding versus hiding.
You're going to exploit this
to emphasize their differences.
So I had the Yaoxing Society and
Xiaozhan spread the news that
all these people suffered unjust
persecution because of him.
I don't believe someone who would
turn against the Company for Chen Duo
would remain indifferent.
As soon as he gets this news,
he'll definitely make a move.
In theory, it makes sense,
but your scheme is too obvious.
Would he fall for this?
And how can you guarantee that
he'll come here once he hears the news?
There's a possibility!
I tampered with the information.
Once Ma receives it,
it should be a huge shock to him!
Someone's coming.
You didn't actually hit
the jackpot, did you, kid?
Why are they here?
That's Master Jiekong and his
senior disciple, Monk Baowen!
Master Jiekong, what brings you here?
You're all from the Company, right?
Don't you all know why I'm here?
With your years of experience,
can't you see through the tricks here?
Although Chairman Zhao has already
explained that this is a fabrication,
I was still worried
and had to come and see for myself.
You're just afraid
Chairman Zhao was fooling you.
What kind of reputation
does our Company have?
Who's the old monk?
You don't even know who he is?
One of the Ten Elders, Master Jiekong.
He hails from Shaolin and later
became the abbot of Lingyin Temple.
Master said he was once a
formidable warrior monk,
though for some reason,
all his skills were crippled.
Master, if you're worried,
shall I take you inside for a look around?
Much obliged.
Who is this murderous-looking
Master Baowen targeting?
Or have we been disrespectful in some way?
Baowen!
Master, seeing this beast...
I can't help myself!
Master, you're still so full of vigor?
Xiao Zizai!
Brother! Long time no see!
Master!
Where is justice?
A disciple strikes his master!
Master!
Master! I wasn't paying attention!
My life is so miserable!
We all take on disciples,
but look at Zhang Zhiwei's disciples.
Including the late Master Liang,
each of his ten
disciples outshines the last.
Oh, right, now it should be nine.
And now look at you bunch of miscreants.
Master! It was my mistake...
I... I won't fight anymore!
The way you are now,
how are you any different from Baojing?
Master, shall we go inside
and take a look?
Okay, let's go.
You see, Master?
I didn't deceive you, did I?
This place is abandoned.
There's nothing here.
Ah, this puts my mind at ease.
The Company must have its reasons.
I was just being meddlesome.
No problem! No problem!
We'll take our leave now.
Baojing, have you kept our agreement?
Yes.
Self-defense and exorcising demons.
Beyond that, I haven't
killed anyone since.
Well, that's very good.
But my inner demons have
never truly gone away.
Master, I'm afraid that
one day I'll still lose control
and harm innocent people.
As long as you haven't given up
on yourself, that's what matters.
Remember, if one day you truly
succumb to your inner demons,
and intend to slaughter the innocent,
kill me!
I will remember.
Chulan!
Yes?
Those two kids wandering in
the mountains since yesterday,
are we really going to ignore them?
No need, there's no need for
you to get involved, Xiao.
Ignore them.
They won't cause us any trouble.
Brother, Zhang Chulan's trip this time
doesn't seem related to finding
clues about Wu Gensheng.
Should we keep watching?
Let's stay and see what actually happens.
Today is the Company's
so-called execution day.
I'm also curious about
what the Company is up to.
The execution day has passed.
In the end, he didn't come.
No matter how stupid Ma Xianhong is,
he wouldn't fall for a trap like this.
Thanks to this mission,
we've had a few days of peace.
Still, thanks to you, Bastard.
How's it going?
I've heard that the Part Timers
have all returned to
their respective regions.
Is it reliable?
I can't confirm it,
and I can't dig any deeper.
It's obvious that Zhao suspects
someone on the board.
You just need to keep
watching Ma Xianhong!
Sister...
Is this why you made me rest?
Sister, do you think I'm an idiot?
Would I fall for such an obvious trap?
That's good.
Xianhong.
Didn't we agree...
not to do anything stupid?
Sister...
I'm sorry.
I know this is almost certainly a trap.
But even if there's a one
in ten thousand chance...
If the Shanggenqi Mutants are
persecuted because of me,
I have a duty to seek justice for them!
If the Shanggenqi Mutants
really were harmed,
wouldn't it be better to get revenge on
the Company after we've achieved our goal?
Think about why you've worked so
hard to get where you are today!
Once the Cultivation Furnace is complete,
your lost memories can be recovered.
Think about which is more important!
Sister...
To be honest, I'm a bit disappointed.
After all this time,
you still don't know what
truly matters to me the most.
To me, living with peace of
mind is the most important.
If I don't check
on the Shanggenqi Mutants,
I won't have peace of mind!
Xianhong, then let me tell you this too.
If you go, you definitely won't find
the peace of mind you're looking for!
Trust me!
Trust me! You must trust me!
In this world, nothing is
certain except life and death.
It's trying to understand and judge these
uncertainties that's causing your unease!
Leave it to me.
Stop judging.
Stop thinking.
Leave it all to me!
Let me teach you what to do!
This is your path to peace of mind!
Sister!
Did... you know that I've been
having terrifying thoughts lately?
I... I didn't dare tell you.
I hate it!
I hate these thoughts!
But they just won't leave my mind!
Oh?
I've been thinking...
why should I trust you?
Come on! Tell me!
Why should I trust you?
Sister...
What is this?
Your hand... is it more than just red?
Father!
Why did you wait until today
to teach me something this powerful?
You're my son, not my enemy.
I hesitated repeatedly
before teaching you today!
Do you know how outsiders
view our Wuhou Clan?
Mysterious!
Not just that, but also
complicated and flashy!
Today I'll tell you why our Wuhou
Clan's cultivation is so complex.
You talk about learning this and that,
learning one thing after another,
but when will it ever end?
Our lives are finite,
but knowledge is infinite.
Pursuing the infinite with
the finite is a perilous thing.
We master these arts
solely to strengthen our bodies and minds.
In the end, we must master ourselves!
Its principles and application defy
the Wuhou Clan's traditional complexity.
They're simple, straightforward,
yet extremely dangerous!
The spirit of the upper dantian,
the energy of the middle dantian,
the essence of the lower dantian.
Use these Three Treasures
as fuel to ignite!
Ignite the flame of life itself!
You want to use something you
can't even master to deal with me?
Come! If you're so skilled,
ignite it and show me!
Impossible. We couldn't
even succeed together!
How could you possibly ignite it alone?!
Fortune and misfortune are intertwined.
So this is how it works.
It's because those
ultimate skills were too terrifying
that the excessive reverence for
the Samadhi Fire had disappeared.
It's because you've become a slave to the
Eight Secret Arts that I've been freed!
With your meager cultivation,
can you even control the Samadhi Fire?
Even if you could,
I roam freely within this inner realm.
Can you even burn me?
Hey, am I crazy or are you stupid?
You haven't forgotten what our
Samadhi Fire is for, have you?
This fire, fueled by the Three Treasures,
doesn't burn firewood or earth or stone.
It specifically burns the souls
of all beings in the world.
Run! Run far, run fast.
I was planning to burn
this place down anyway.
You bastard!
This Samadhi Fire can't even
compare to the Eight Secret Arts!
You know that!
I know. Of course I know.
That's why I can't
tolerate you any longer!
Stop! Stop!
Stop burning!
Ah, Qing! You're awake.
Did you make it through?
Zhuge Qing!
Zhang Chulan has come to the Company.
He's looking for you.
Looking for me?
It's good news.