It's been three days since the festival...
I want to watch the fireworks
with just you, Eiyu!
Me too. I want to watch
the fireworks with just you, Eiyu!
But so far... nothing has happened.
Shio
Festival Time!
Let's meet at 6 o'clock!
Roger
I'm confused.
Weren't we about to start a rom-com?!
What happened?!
What about the legend of love?
Where?! Where did it all go?!
Onii-chan!
Huh?
Here you go!
Thanks.
You really don't mind paying?
I can pay you back
with my allowance later.
Used up his allowance at the festival...
Don't worry about it!
I couldn't make the festival,
but I'm so happy I get to go on a date
with you today, Onii-chan!
A date, huh?
Thanks for your generosity.
You seem kinda down.
Did something happen at the festival?
Well...
Nothing really happened...
But it turns out I was the only one
looking forward to...
There's no way my life would
turn into some rom-com, right?
It will.
Huh?
So sweet!
I don't know what happened,
but it's always been one for me.
It's always been a rom-com.
Huh?
It's always been a rom-com for me.
Hey! Your heart just jumped, didn't it?
Wha—?!
What are you talking about?
Don't tease me like that.
Man, that startled me.
I'll go get the food,
so wait there, Onii-chan!
Jeez! Why is everyone
messing with me right now?
Looks like you're getting
all the attention, as usual.
Huh?
Um...
I-I think you must be
mistaking me for someone else.
Huh?
It's okay! These are shorts!
Well, see ya later, Eiyu!
Huh? Why does she know my nickname?
Onii-chan, do you know her?
No, I don't think so...
Eiyu...
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
You're late!
School starts today, you know!
I know that!
Shio, let's just leave him behind!
Did you know a new cosmetics shop
opened in the station building?
They're my childhood friends.
Oh, really?
Wanna go check it out?
Summer break's over, and we're
back to the same old routine.
Yeah, let's go! When's a good time?
As expected, you can't be in a rom-com
with your childhood friends.
This is totally a rom-com!
It's you again!
Look at you, Eiyu!
Walking with two beauties in the morning?
I'm so jealous! Come here!
What happened to the cutie
from last time, huh?
SQUEEZE
Squish, squish, squish, squish!
Hey, let go of him!
Which "cutie"?
It was Runako.
Runako?
You're telling me that was Runako?
Y-Yeah...
Yup.
You're Shio and Akari.
You all look completely different!
Man, it feels so nostalgic
when all four of us are together!
Right?
Huh?
Well then!
Later!
Who was that?
Beats me.
Is it true, Sakai?
You're seeing three girls at once?!
What?
What are you talking about?!
Don't play dumb!
You're already messing around
with both of your childhood friends!
I hear you're involved
with a girl in junior high, too!
Where did you hear this?
Oh? What a funny rumor.
I'm letting that idiot
mess around with me?
And he's seeing two other girls
at the same time?
That's hilarious.
Whose dreaming up
these funny stories?
Gosh!
What's with those rumors?!
Hinata Haru-san from
the P.E. department, huh?
She's a rising first-year track star
and pretty popular in class.
Seems like the rumors spread
after she talked about us.
BLAH
WHAAAT!!
That tan girl!
It's those girls, right?
I wonder why...
He's seeing three girls at once, right?
But it seems like she knows us.
Yeah, that's crazy.
I don't know her!
Fine, then.
I'll go set her straight!
Eiyu!
U-Um...
Is H-Hinata-san here?
Haru? She's probably having
lunch at the clubroom.
He acts all high-and-mighty with us...
Thank you very much.
I appreciate your help.
Now I'm worried.
She's here, huh?
Yes?
Um...
Do you have a moment?
Oh! Hold on a sec!
Whoa!
S-Sorry!
Oh, it's just you, Eiyu.
Huh?
Let me change real quick. Just wait there.
O-Okay!
Okay, come in.
E-Excuse... me?!
Ouch...
S-Sorry!
Um... So... I'm here because...
Huh?
You know you're being super rude, right?
It's fine.
But why are you acting
all distant like that?
We're friends, aren't we?
Friends? I don't know about that...
What?
No way...
You don't remember me?
I wonder if Eiyu's okay.
Should we go check in?
Good idea.
I can't say he's the most experienced
when it comes to talking to girls.
But he's totally fine with us!
Track and Field Club
S-Seriously?
Is that true?!
It's true.
Then Eiyu...
Wanna try touching them?
What the heck are you doing?!
What?!
You said you were going to
set her straight!
What do you think
you're doing right now?!
You can't do that! It's a crime!
Ah, no... I tripped is all.
But forget that!
This is Haru!
Haru from Nishi Elementary!
What?
From Nishi Elementary...?
Come on! Is that it?
It's getting late!
It's time to go home!
Onii-chan!
This is the final round!
Just one more!
All right! You're weak, Eiyu!
Darn it!
Losers get what they get!
Haru was the kid who was athletic
and sassy, but really fun to be around.
We'd always run around
until the sun went down.
Brace yourself!
Don't make it too painful, Haru-kun!
I remember Haru as my
childhood friend who's a boy.
No way...
Haru-kun was...
A girl this whole time?!
No wonder. It all makes sense now.
Back in first semester,
I tried saying hey and was ignored.
Hey!
Huh?
Really? Sorry!
On top of that...
I always thought you were a perv
since you'd always invite me to
go pee or go take a bath together.
Wait...
Weren't you referring to yourself as
a boy back then, um, Haru-san...?
Don't be so formal, just call me Haru!
Well, I grew up with a lot of brothers,
so I was probably copying them.
Why do you keep looking away?
Is it because now that
you know I'm a girl,
you're thinking of me differently?
No, um...
So sad!
I always thought you were my friend!
What? No...
You're all flustered!
How are you so adorable?
What?
This girl...
I-It's not like that.
I was just a little surprised, that's all.
Right, right. I get it, I get it!
H-Haru-kun!
So...
A-Anyway...
We need to talk.
Huh?
Seriously?! That's the rumor?
I only said I was jealous since Eiyu's
hanging out with three beautiful girls.
I'll make sure to correct them.
But seriously.
Aren't you all a thing?
Huh? Why would you...
Well, you're always together.
I'm sure a lot of people think
you're with either Shio or Akari.
It's not like that...
Hmm, okay.
Yeah... right?
You can't be in a rom-com
with your childhood friends...
What a relief.
See ya, Haru-kun.
Let's hang out next time!
'Kay!
What did she mean by, "What a relief"?
What a relief.
Nobody's cheating on anyone.
No, that can't be.
Hey, Eiyu.
Wanna go to that park after school
where we used to play?
Huh? Sure.
We can invite Shio and Akari, too.
Wait!
I want it to be just the two of us.
She's still not here?
Why does she want to meet with me alone?
No, no, no!
This is Haru we're talking about!
Why am I getting nervous?
Boo!
You!
What a great reaction!
You're early too, dude!
I'm the one riding a bike.
What? I didn't have any other plans.
So, wanna get started?
Get started on what?
Wait!
Huh?
One-on-one, of course!
Come on!
Show me what you've got!
Is your body the only thing
that developed?!
Seriously? You just wanted
to play basketball?
Well, of course!
But yeah, what a relief!
I'm glad you all weren't a thing!
Huh? Why?
Because if you all were...
We couldn't do this
with just the two of us.
Gotcha!
Dang, you almost had it, too.
Sh-Shut up!
I'm just rusty!
I could've scored if I tried.
Here!
Then, give me all you've got!
Back then, you'd get physical
just to steal the ball.
But what the heck happened, Haru?
You suddenly stopped
coming to the park.
We were all waiting for you every day!
My bad, I just got really busy.
You know!
And you got into
the same high school as us!
Why didn't you tell us?!
You're the ones who didn't
even realize I'm a girl!
Haru hasn't changed.
Always messing with me.
She's definitely Haru!
I'm not losing no matter what!
First to three wins!
I won!
So soft... smells nice...
But it's Haru!
All right! Losers get what they get.
What? We never agreed on that!
Come on, this is how we always did it!
What should it be?
Huh? Isn't it always the forehead flick?
Can I ask you a question instead?
Huh?
So, I actually heard about you guys
going to the fireworks festival.
Shio and Akari confessed
their love for you, right?
But you're acting like
nothing happened...
Eiyu!
Who are you gonna choose?
What are you talking about, Haru?
Sure, it may have looked that way to you.
Sorry to disappoint you.
But...
You do see them that way, right?
As more than friends?
What? Not at all.
Come on, I can tell.
I'm your childhood friend, too.
Oh yeah, you were on a date
with Runako, too.
What's that about?
What?!
Just spill it, Eiyu!
Don't you wanna start a rom-com
with your childhood friends?
That's stupid!
There's no way I could see my
childhood friends as more than a friend!
Eiyu, do you remember?
When we graffitied
that wall in our neighborhood?
Hey!
You brats!
When we got caught...
You're mistaken! It's the opposite!
We were actually cleaning this wall!
You told the most obvious lie.
You totally have that same look now.
Just admit it!
I-I'm really not interested.
Liar!
Enough of this crap. Let's go home.
Then fight me!
If you win, I won't bother you
about it ever again.
But if I win, you have to
tell me everything.
Huh? That's not fair.
There's no way I'd agree to that.
Come on, please!
I'm so curious!
Aren't we friends?
Come on, come on, come on!
Jeez, cut the whining!
All right, all right!
But only under this condition!
I'll only take you up on it
if it's you-know-what.
Sure thing.
The current standing is eighty rounds,
80 Rounds
37 Wins
38 Losses
thirty-seven wins,
thirty-eight losses, five ties
5 Ties
and sure, I'm behind in wins...
But since then, I haven't stopped training
even while brushing my teeth
and taking baths...
Do you think you can beat me?
You shouldn't talk smack
until you've won.
Let's go!
Daruma-san! Daruma-san!
It's time for the stare-down!
Laugh and you lose!
Na-na-na!
You haven't gotten rusty at this, huh?
You too...
Then!
What about this?!
What the heck is that face?!
Told you, I've been training!
Behold!
This is the new face
I came up with just last week!
What? Last week?
You've been training even
as a high-schooler?
Shoot, I can't let that get me!
But...
My steel mask hardened by childhood
friends isn't going to break easily!
Come to think of it,
I remember Shio asking about this.
I wonder if Eiyu likes someone.
Yeah.
It's time to come clean. Don't you think?
Y-You're being unfair, Haru!
Akari's been quietly
admiring you all along, too.
Y-You mean glaring?
Runako's always said she likes you, too.
She's like a little sister!
Why are you so stubborn about this?
Back atcha. Why do you
want to know so badly?
What do you mean? That's obvious.
I want to cheer you on!
You're my dear childhood friend!
Haru...
What the heck is that face?
That's not fair! Gosh!
It's my normal face.
I lost.
Okay. I trust you, Eiyu.
I do...
I do think of them
as more than friends.
Are you sure? I lost the bet.
Yeah, you're a c-close
friend of mine, Haru.
Yeah? Really? Ooh!
And? And?
What exactly do you like about them?
Shut up!
This is so embarrassing.
I dunno!
I'm not even sure if I'm really in love.
I feel stupid seeing them
as more than friends
when I don't know how they feel about me.
I see.
You're so cute.
But what a complicated situation.
I'll ask them for you!
What?
I'll be the one to support
you guys' love life!
All right, let's go!
Episode 9
An Unfamiliar Girl Who's Your "Guy Friend"?
But if You Laugh, It Still Won't Start a Rom-Com
Hey! Hold up, wait!
Just stay out of it!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
Ready?
Great to have you back, Haru-kun!
We went all out today
to celebrate our reunion!
Wow. Thanks so much!
I'm still shocked that you're a girl.
Plus, you're cute and
have an amazing figure!
Stop it!
You two are really cute, too.
Oh yeah. How about Runako?
Where's Runako?
Runako's...
I don't have to worry about Haru... right?
Listen! Please stay out of this!
What? You embarrassed?
I can get them to open up
about their feelings naturally.
I said you don't have to do that!
We settled things with a pizza bun...
Delish!
Delish
Oh yeah!
I was wondering, Shio and Akari...
Huh?
What is it?
What do you two think about Eiyu?
Idiot!