Shinra... disappeared?
Iris?
Commander?
Everything is going according to plan.
We will also go to the pillars.
Yona, I'll leave the rest to you.
Until the day of destruction, then.
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Episode 17
"At the Center of the World"
Shinra Kusakabe.
A holy child of virgin birth.
In the fire twelve years ago,
had he disappeared like his
mother and younger brother,
he might have become just a legend.
But left above ground, he was made
to bear the name of parent-killer.
Instead of a hero of legend,
he was forced to live as a devil.
Devil! Devil! Devil!
And now, with the image of the devil who
killed Raffles being projected everywhere,
the budding hero has
been thoroughly crushed.
All that remains is to
offer the key to Amaterasu.
This planet will become a flaming star.
There is no savior.
Humanity's hero has disappeared.
There's a blackout across
the whole Tokyo Empire!
Are the comms still up?
What's going on?
Captain Pan!
There's a message from the fire station!
Infernals are appearing in huge numbers!
I'm docking your pay.
Why? I defeated the Titan, didn't I?
What kind of boss forgives a subordinate
who lets their work be stolen from them?
I think I really will change jobs.
That conversation is over.
More importantly, I received an
urgent message from headquarters.
What is it this time?
For unknown reasons,
Amaterasu has ceased functioning.
And Nataku Son, whom the research
department was looking after,
has apparently vanished.
Nataku-kun is gone?
That's bad.
He is a precious weakling
worthy of tormenting.
For now, we're heading
back to headquarters.
Hurry up and start the car.
Flying would be faster.
My suit would get dirty.
Think of a way to get
me there quickly by car.
Understood.
It's no good. I can't
find either one of them.
They might be hiding somewhere.
Shinra's a pillar, so that's one thing,
but why is Iris gone, too?
The reason is simple.
Sister Iris must be the final pillar,
the eighth one.
Then that flame earlier really was...
And at Fuchu, when Dragon's
attack was blocked...
The sister did that?
And...
this blackout probably happened because
the first pillar's disappearance caused
Amaterasu to stop functioning.
If so, Shinra-kun, the sister, and the
pillars vanishing must be connected.
The question is, where have they all gone?
Adolla.
You're...
They went to Adolla. Every second counts.
The Great Cataclysm has
entered the final phase.
We don't have time to argue here.
Why would we trust you?!
You show up out of nowhere
and say all this?!
Captain Huo Yan lost his
right arm to your arrows!
And there's Lieutenant Rekka, too!
Now, when the fate of the
world hangs in the balance,
what is the worth of one arm?
This is not the time for such grievances.
You little—
What is it that you know?
Arrow.
If my brother can become
this world's hero,
then the Great Cataclysm
may yet be stopped.
If that fails, all of the pillars
will likely disappear to Adolla.
Commander, if I lose you, then my duty...
Listen to me, Arrow.
Do not abandon hope.
As long as my brother exists,
the endpoint of humanity's
collective unconscious
is not death.
Yes, sir!
Just as the fourth and eighth
pillar have disappeared,
the third pillar vanished, too.
Protecting Commander Sho
Kusakabe is my mission.
But what can we do
under these conditions?
Hope still remains.
We merely need to stop the switch
that triggers the Great Cataclysm.
Where is this switch?
I have a guess as to where
the switch might be.
"Amaterasu"
Amaterasu.
Right?
Giovanni was looking for
the key to Amaterasu.
It must be connected somehow.
Don't try anything funny.
You won't find any vulnerabilities.
What did you say earlier?
"Don't abandon hope."
Those are good words.
They're the commander's words.
Sho-kun's words, huh?
As long as this world still exists,
we won't give up hope.
Is that...
It's the 8th's Matchbox.
Where are you headed in such a hurry?
Ogun of the 4th! This is an emergency!
Ogun!
Arthur!
We're on our way to Amaterasu!
You come, too!
That's a super blunt invitation.
Did you see the number of
Infernals on your way here?
There were quite a lot of them.
What could be more important
than laying Infernals to rest?
The White Clad are attacking
my castle, Camelot.
To lay the final preparations
for the Great Cataclysm,
the White Clad will attack Amaterasu.
So they've finally made it this far, huh?
Is Shinra okay? I heard he'd disappeared.
He'll come back, right?
Yes. He's already overcome his devil.
Whether it's from Adolla or
somewhere else, he'll come back.
Devil, huh? Makes me
remember the old days.
The old days?
When we were at the training academy.
Next!
Yes, sir!
I'm Shinra Kusakabe!
After becoming a fire soldier,
I want to become a hero!
Next!
Hey, Shinra!
Oh, you're the knight.
Arthur-kun!
Arthur, you're a knight?
Indeed, I am.
That's amazing!
If we're ever in a pinch,
come and protect us, okay?
I shall always hasten to your side!
That's a promise, okay?
Isn't Arthur-kun adorable?
I totally get it!
I wish I could keep him as a pet.
You seem to already be
popular with the girls.
Well, I am a knight.
What's this? Are you two
getting along already?
You're...
the new student who's top in both
the written and the practical,
Ogun Montgomery.
Well, in the tests, anyway. My personal
grades have nothing to do with anything.
Fire soldiers work as a team, right?
He's the ideal fire soldier!
And on that team, we need people
like you, who aim to become heroes.
And he doesn't forget to follow
up on supporting guys like us!
Ogun! Could it be that you're a good guy?
Well, I'm no villain. Let's be friends!
Yeah! Glad to!
Did you hear the rumors?
WHISPER
They aren't just rumors.
Apparently, they're true!
WHISPER
He's a devil who killed his parents.
Hey.
WHISPER
He's smiling. That's freaky.
Shinra, you okay?
Oh, Ogun.
Don't let it get to you.
You don't believe the rumors?
Then did you really...
I-I didn't! Back then, I...
You didn't do it, right?
I wouldn't doubt a friend because
of some ridiculous rumors.
BOOM
Besides, we may end up
assigned to the same company.
GRIN
So you are a devil after all?
What'd you just say?!
Arthur knows, and he's saying that anyway.
But you really should
stop grinning like that.
I can't help it. It's a habit.
Weirdo.
We're gonna bring Shinra back.
We've arrived.
This is my castle.
Vul!
Lisa! Yu! You got here fast!
You two came?
I called them here for backup.
It doesn't look like the
White Clad are here yet.
They will definitely come to use the key.
I'll finally learn if I was right about
the mystery of the white feather arrows
we saw in the Tabernacle on the continent!
All right! Let's get in there.
Hang on! This area is off-limits!
What are you doing?
We've come to inspect Amaterasu!
We haven't heard anything about that!
Maki.
Yes, sir.
Don't come any closer, or...
You're the ones they're
looking for! Company 8!
Spider net.
Sorry about this.
Hey! Is the 8th always
doing stuff like this?
It's never been quite this blatant before,
but I think that vibe
has always been there.
This is the only entrance into Amaterasu.
All right. We'll fight our
defensive battle here.
Vulcan, you take care of
the inside of Amaterasu.
Right.
Lisa, Yu!
We're finally heading into
my ancestor's legacy!
Yes, sir!
We don't know what may happen inside.
Arthur, accompany Vulcan and
the others as their guard.
Guarding the party is a knight's duty.
I accept the mission!
Vulcan, this castle was built
by your ancestors, wasn't it?
That's right. Amaterasu is
no weapon of destruction.
I won't let them start
the Great Cataclysm.
Let's go!
Captain, what do you plan to do?
Today, it's vital that we don't
allow the enemy near Amaterasu.
If they get inside, it's all over.
We'll intercept them here!
A head-on collision?
That's right.
Since we were branded rebels,
we've had to restrain ourselves.
We're itching for a fight,
and look at this situation!
We're gonna save the world
with everything we've got!
As soon as we spot the enemy,
Arrow and I will begin shooting.
If there's a chance for close combat,
Tamaki and I will intercept.
I'll make use of my mobility
to disrupt enemy formations.
I'm on offense. I'll hunt
down one of the big guns.
They're here.
We'll stop the Great Cataclysm
and bring Iris and Kusakabe back!
Begin operations!
Yes, sir!
Fire Force
Chapter 3
The Fire Force? Why are they here?
This isn't what we were told.
But it's within expectations, isn't it?
Don't react to every little thing.
We have as many pawns
as we could ever need.
It seems we're already surrounded.
Let's do this, Arrow!
Don't let them get close!
I could say the same to you!
"Velocity Control"
"Acceleration"
"Cluster Arrow"
You're pretty good.
So are you.
Tamaki! Take care of the Infernals
that made it through the barrage!
Got it!
Come, come...
Great Fiery Infernals.
Great Fiery Infernals
For Infernals to be that big...
Just how many people's
lives did you toy with?!
It's so tough!
Tamaki and I will handle
the regular Infernals!
Lieutenant, you two handle
the big Infernals!
You traitor!
Your opponent here is me!
Counter.
BAM BAM BAM BAM BAM
What?
Rush doesn't leave you any
openings to use Counter!
Most of my punches didn't
feel like they landed.
That Rush was like a storm.
I took a few hits there.
Ogun! You okay?!
Yes, sir!
I will stop Charon here!
We won't let you trigger
the Great Cataclysm!
The Great Cataclysm will happen!
No matter how many people you may
have, I won't let you interfere!
THMP THMP
THMP
I have a duty and responsibility to
protect the citizens of the empire!
THMP
THMP THMP
What duty?
There is no such thing!
Stomp!
The responsibility springs from
the previous Great Cataclysm!
Clap!
SNAP
Crap! Your whole body is a bomb?!
To help... To save...
It sounds good, but for people who
feel like just living is torment,
this world is hell itself.
There is salvation in destruction, too!
And that's why you're
gonna blow it all away?!
The immigrants living
in Tokyo right now
were brought here by my ancestors.
I cannot abandon those people!
My ancestor was a ship captain.
During the last Great Cataclysm,
he allowed everyone on board,
regardless of race and social status.
When the Great Cataclysm made the route
rough and the passengers grew afraid,
my ancestor sang reggae songs of love.
He gave them courage and a sense
of safety as they crossed the sea.
He let aboard the future
Raffles I and many others,
and he brought them here, to Tokyo!
I became a fire soldier
to take responsibility
for protecting all those
people he brought here!
I have a duty to protect
those people to the very end!
Flamy Ink!
Let's get this party started!
Charon will absorb this
attack and counter-attack.
Why would you assume that
I have to take your first strike?
CREAK
CRACKLE
That's one.
Which one of you is next?
Ogun!
No human exists that can
defeat that invincible man!
Anyone'll do. Come at me.
It's still me.
I can still fight!
The impact of my punches
gets completely swallowed!
Counter?
He can't absorb and release
stored-up energy at the same time!
I'll counter this Counter!
There!
If it's just a regular strike,
I can maintain my absorption
and attack at the same time.
He's too powerful.
How can I stop a monster like him?
If one can't stop 'em,
then stop 'em with two!
That's why team sports are fun!
And any team Ogun joins is bound to win.
Hey, Shinra!
S-Seriously?
Ogun.
You should come play basketball, too!
If Kusakabe's joining in, I'm going home.
I think I'm done for today, too.
Me, too. I'm not playing with a devil.
You're up next, Shinra.
Damn it, I can't stop you.
Looks like I have the
advantage in basketball.
Can't help it when we're
playing one-on-one.
And it's not like basketball is meant
to be played one-on-one anyway.
I guess.
We're a team.
If one can't stop 'em,
then stop 'em with two!
Is that why you make yourself trust me?
What?
Ow!
Anyone should be able to tell!
You're not that kind of guy!
You still have time to turn the tables!
Let's keep playing!
It's no use.
You have no chance of winning.
I...
will not give up.
You're so battered, you can't even stand.
You're just using the flames plastered
on your body to force yourself upright.
You have no strength left.
If you'd just kept quiet, you probably
would've lived to the day of destruction.
I am not alone.
Fire soldiers are a team.
What?
If you can't stop 'em alone,
you stop 'em with two.
It's an ironclad rule
among fire soldiers.
The 8th are battle-hardened veterans.
They'd never let this chance slip away!
To Be Continued
Fire Force Chapter 3
And this planet, with the coming Great
Cataclysm, will become a second sun!
Next Time
As your big brother, I vowed that I would
protect you two, no matter what.
Next time, "Incantation of Destruction."
Episode 18
Incantation of Destruction
Return to the great flame of fire. Látom.