Látom.
The little saint girl closed
her beautiful eyes...
until the arrival of the appointed day.
She closed off the light and
accepted God's revelations.
In the darkness, as she
sought the light...
she felt humanity's darkest
emotions rush inside her.
Hate Futility Despair Regret Malice Humiliation Fear Desire
Indolence Desire Futility Despair Humiliation Fear Hate Regret Malice
Hate
Deceit
Nothingness
Cunning
Evil
Humiliation
Desire
Despair
Hate
Futility
Regret
Depravity
Indolence
The little saint girl closed her eyes
and endured it all.
She opened her eyes...
and she understood.
Her eyes looked at Earth...
at the planet's unconscious.
The saint's innocent eyes
opened and shed a single tear.
It was for the sake of the devoted warrior
who had given everything for the saint.
And then,
she gave praise to the light
that lay beyond her long wait.
Those eyes, so full of compassion
and grief, took in everything.
Even the brothers who
could control time
were so captivated by the saint's
compassion that they lost time.
O brothers of destiny...
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Episode 23
"Despair Saintess"
Come, Inca, Sumire.
Bye, Shinra.
Inca!
At last this day has come. Thank you.
What have you done?
How could you do that to your comrades?!
Death is the true salvation.
You just decided that on your own!
There's no way death saves anyone!
My brother is right.
But it is gods that can
justify such contradictions.
She has taken in all of humanity's
collective unconscious.
The history of all the deities
humanity has dreamed up...
She's taken all of it in.
The way Haumea is in this moment,
she could be called a god.
Evangelist, you decided
to show yourself, huh?
The Evangelist is humanity's
collective unconscious given form.
And the collective unconscious
is made up of the unconscious
desires shared by all of humanity.
So the Evangelist is truly
an entity that embodies all the things
humanity secretly wishes for.
The despair that we saw
before we came here...
That is the Evangelist's true form.
All of that?
It's just as you say.
As a saint, I have received the
collective unconscious all this time.
And I have learned the
answers to the questions,
"What is the Evangelist?"
Hate Futility Despair Regret Malice Humiliation Fear Desire
Indolence Desire Futility Despair Humiliation Fear Hate Regret Malice
and "What is the unconscious?"
The endpoint of imagination.
Humanity wishes for the extinction
that lies at the end of evolution.
Gods did not give birth to humans.
Humans birthed gods from despair.
And it is those very gods
who birth new despair.
And so...
what are gods, exactly?
The Great Sol.
Yes, indeed.
Religion.
Friends.
Information.
Science.
Art.
Culture.
Family.
Anything that offers salvation
to that person will do.
However...
as the other side to that salvation,
humanity's history holds...
War.
Massacres.
Accidents.
Disasters.
Illness.
After sustaining so many heavy blows,
a tremendous amount of despair was born.
And from that great despair,
a great deal was learned.
Ethics.
Values.
Medicine.
Technology.
And law, too.
Civilization advanced,
and the value of each
individual soul increased.
We successfully distanced
ourselves from death.
Humanity attained safety.
But did we really?
The safer we became,
the stronger our salvation grew...
the more we feared death,
the stronger the fear
in our hearts grew,
and the stronger that despair grew, too.
And then what do you think happened?
The Great Cataclysm.
When humans are confronted with danger,
they are saved. That is the current norm.
The stronger salvation grows,
the stronger despair grows.
As a fire soldier, you must
understand this better than I.
Shinra.
Young savior.
To end the chain of
salvation and despair...
Can you give any means of
relief other than death?
Is anyone there?
I'm coming to save you now!
Thank you, but...
It's all right! Don't give up!
Everyone, please stay
calm and come this way!
Don't stop!
Is your footing all right?
I'm sorry.
My eyesight may be bad, but you look
like you're glowing, Mr. Fire Soldier.
That's so that no one loses hope.
Let's give it our best shot.
There are a ton of people on the
surface who don't want to die!
That's why my fire soldier comrades
continue fighting, even now!
Death can't be the only salvation!
It's not possible for everyone
to be wishing for death!
On the surface, that's likely true.
But what about deep in
their unconscious minds?
Your theories have nothing to do with it!
My friends are out there saving people's
lives, and as long as they exist,
I will not give up hope!
Brother, time is stopped.
You can move, can't you, brother?
Of course I can. I'm your big brother!
Let's end this!
For our friends!
Did you do something?
The only ones who can move within
stopped time are me and my brother.
Haumea didn't move at all,
but our attacks didn't hit her.
What did you do, Haumea?
I haven't done anything.
I exist here, and this is where I was.
Indeed, just like the despair
that has always existed here.
Cut the crap! What did you do?!
Is it Inca's ability?
The souls of the other
Pillars are also with me.
Of course, that also
includes Sumire's soul.
It's no use.
Karma has predetermined
that you cannot touch me.
What's that supposed to mean?
That's not possible!
Quit screwing with me!
Brother, don't act rashly!
No matter what you may do,
you are fated to face despair.
Damn it! What am I supposed to do?
Calm yourself.
Brother, you must not let
yourself be swallowed by rage.
Your despair or death would serve as the
trigger for the destruction of the world.
Anger is the greatest ingredient
for summoning death and despair.
How the Great Cataclysm ends
is up to you, the Hero.
The saint has nothing to do with it.
So if I don't die...
and I don't let anger swallow me up...
I fight for the sake of others!
And I will stop Haumea!
The death and karma that
are laid out for us...
We'll transcend them!
For the sake... of my friends...
Has saying that allowed you to
protect those who are dear to you?
What?
What do you mean?
You said that it's impossible for
death to be the only salvation,
but people who value human life, who seek
solace and aid, have also chosen death.
Look at this.
The support that allowed humanity's
revival and prosperity: Amaterasu.
They could even be called the support
for all human life, and they, too...
after experiencing the cycle
of salvation and despair...
have accepted it.
FIDGET
Power Cobra
I-It can't be...
Fire Force
Chapter 3
They, too...
accepted the offer of death
that I extended to them.
Don't twist things for
your own convenience!
You killed them, Haumea!
What will you do with that?
Will you kill me?
Yeah! That's right!
I'll kill you and break this stupid chain!
So you do understand, then.
Death is the only salvation.
How dare you kill the sister?!
No!
Brother! You'll only be doing
what the Evangelist wants!
Sho...
Shinra, you have always been motivated
by the rage of revenge, haven't you?
That rage at having your
family stolen from you
will not be assuaged by
anything other than my death.
Brother, you must not get angry.
Look at me!
I am right here.
Sister...
Stay calm.
I know you can do this.
It wasn't just for revenge.
You've fought all this time
to protect people's lives.
And this fight isn't for revenge, either.
You're fighting to protect people!
For the friends who are still here...
Flames of rage can only be extinguished
by the death of those who caused them.
Brother!
Revenge will turn me into a devil.
I... am not a devil.
I am a fire soldier.
But you were able to become a hero
thanks to the flames of your revenge.
I fight for people, for human life.
And was it really that sense of justice,
which feels so good on the ears,
that allowed you to come this far?
You kill your Infernals, right?
No, brother! Don't listen to her!
It's all right.
Sho, I'm not angry at all.
You're terrible at lying, Shinra.
I am fighting for everyone!
Brother!
You won't be able to
protect yourself like that.
Your death will complete the Great
Cataclysm and save all of humanity.
Sho!
Brother, it's not a problem.
Not a problem? That can't be true!
Such a futile gesture.
This karma of despair can only
be resolved through death.
Why do you fight it?
Haumea, you...
If you let anger consume
you, the world ends!
Brother, you and the 8th have
fought to protect this world.
We can't allow it to end here!
Everyone in the 8th.
Captain Obi.
They all supported me.
That's how I got this far.
I'm not a devil! I'm a hero!
I fight to protect the
citizens' lives and property!
It's no use. Karma cannot be defied.
That doesn't seem to be true.
Just now, your hair moved!
If it's impossible for us to do anything,
her hair shouldn't have moved.
Is the future still in flux?
The unconsciousness's conclusion
isn't set on death yet!
A gentle breeze that stirs my hair
isn't enough to change anything.
No! The flap of a butterfly's wings can
turn into a giant storm with time.
We don't know what a gentle
breeze could turn into!
That's why the Evangelist is afraid
of me, a guy who's like a puff of air.
There is no fear. We have
accepted everything.
That's not true!
Brother!
Look down at the surface.
The last flames of despair
are trying to wake.
Licht, the fires in this area
seem to have all been put out.
In that case, please go
and check the condition
of the living facilities
near the shelters.
Will do.
Did something happen, Captain?
No, I just came to see how
things are going over here.
Right.
Licht! The evacuation shelter...
Is something wrong?
No, the captain is here...
but why would the captain come
back to guide the evacuation?
Captain! We've completed
the evacuations here.
Good work. There's just
one job left to do.
Oh! Captain!
Evacuation of this area should
be complete soon, too!
Really? Good work.
All that's left is to
believe in Shinra and wait!
Yes, sir!
Huh?
It can't be.
Don't!
The light has been lost.
No! Brother!
Now, the world will be saved.
This is already...
Captain!
Kayoko-san!
Iris...
Shinra...
Joker!
It looks like it's already too late!
It seems that Shinra has
been consumed by rage...
and humanity's future is no more.
Yeah. I saw it, too.
Are you going to let things
end this way, Shinra?
It can't be. It's not possible.
It's time to drink!
Huh?
Waka, this is an emergency.
If we don't evacuate everyone
in town to higher ground...
This planet has nowhere left to run to.
All we can do now is believe in Shinra.
Time to drink! Get some booze ready!
If you can't drink alcohol,
just drink whatever you want!
Now that the world's come to this,
even I can't save all of you!
I'm sorry!
No need to apologize, Beni!
It's fine! Just fine! Right, everyone?
Still, I'm gonna make sure
none of you are ever left alone!
I'll follow you all to the next world!
Let's enjoy the show!
Let's hear it for the King of Fun!
Even the moon looks like it's laughing!
Here's the booze!
That's the King of Fun for you!
Beni! Beni! Beni! Beni! Beni!
Konro, you want one?
You're drinking, right?
You cleared away the fears of
everyone in Asakusa in a flash.
You've become quite the smart,
thoughtful man, Benimaru.
If it wasn't for Asakusa, I'd just have
been a born monster, wreathed in flames.
It's all thanks to you and
the old captain. Thank you.
Now, how about the two of us go
and see the old captain again?
At last, this moment has come.
The teachings of the Holy Sol Temple,
planting the image of returning to
the sun within humanity's ideas,
has made this destruction
proceed smoothly.
The birth of a second sun...
Now I, too, can return
to Adolla's flames.
To Be Continued
Fire Force Chapter 3
Next Time
Even if everyone in the world despairs,
you are the one person
who must not give up!
Brother... are you really sure about this?
Next time, "Answer."
Episode 24
Answer
Return to the great flame of fire. Látom.