Ninety-eight... ninety-nine...
One hundred!
I-I can't keep going.
Two hundred three! Two hundred four!
Two hundred five!
Two hundred six! Two hundred seven!
You all right?
Y-Yeah...
Dammit, it still hurts! Shit!
Guess I oughta work on my baseline
before transforming into a combatant, huh?
How the hell are you two
so strong, anyway?
It's obviously because...
we train every day.
Like, every day? How long
have you been livin' like this?
I couldn't give you an exact date,
but it's been over ten years.
Ten...?!
You wanted to join Shocker, right?
Didn't you train for it?
Well, that was more part
of the gangster routine.
You guys are way more serious about this
than I ever was about joining Shocker.
Well, Shocker is destined to be
defeated by the Riders, after all.
Yeah. The training would've gone to waste.
What the hell was that?!
- Thanks for the food.
I'm amazed you two
don't get sick of this stuff.
I'd kill for some real meat.
You're a needy one, aren't you?
Meat, huh...
Well, there are options.
Seriously?! Where are they?
A living chicken?
If you can bring this bird down,
we'll have chicken hotpot tonight.
Didn't they do this in Rocky?
This bird looks like
he's seen better days.
Not sure he'd taste good
even if I caught him.
You'll understand once you get started.
Get to it, then.
I've always wanted to try this,
to be honest.
It's supposed to be great reflex
and lower body training.
Get a move on.
You sure this isn't too easy?
You'd think so, right?
But for the record,
I've never been able to catch him.
Gotcha.
Ow! Whoa!
Ow, ow, ow!
That hurts!
Yow, knock it off! Are you kidding me?!
What the hell?! Wait a sec!
It's trying to kill me!
Make it stop!
This really is a good way to train
your reflexes and lower body.
Isn't it, though?
No!
D-Damn.
A gangster, getting his ass
handed to him by a rooster...
Are you gonna be okay? You seem to be
running a fever from all those scratches.
I'll manage.
I feel like that bird taught me a lesson.
What lesson?
That I'm a small fry.
The kind of wimp who can't
even take down a rooster!
Looking back, all I've done for
the past 44 years was... survive.
Never had any hopes.
Just learnin' how to give up.
And in the end, I couldn't even protect
the men who'd dedicated themselves to me.
I've got nothing now.
I don't have anything, either.
Likewise.
But you two do!
Something that's crucial to really living!
Right in here!
And that's what I'm missing.
I dunno how to put it into words, though.
H-Hey!
Are you really going out
in that condition?
Right now, I'm like a frog who's
been half-swallowed by a snake,
but hasn't realized it yet.
So, where are you going?
To train myself to death.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm weak! Weak! Weak! Weak!
I'm supposed to be their aniki?!
And a gangster?!
What a load of shit...
No wonder I can't even beat a bird!
I'm gonna work at it
until I find what I'm missing.
He said he was gonna train
until he dies, but...
It's been three hours,
and he still hasn't come back.
You all right?!
He's foaming at the mouth.
O-One hundred ninety-seven...
one hundred ninety-eight...
One hundred... ninety...
I-I ain't done yet!
Dammit. I'm not gonna...
I'm not gonna stop
until I get where I'm going!
He's looking better lately.
Yeah.
Hey.
Wanna do some light sparring?
Sure.
Keep it light, okay?
I'll try to.
He's pretty fast.
But!
Gotcha!
That was a good one!
Yeah!
Couldn't see it coming, could you?
I guess.
This punch...
Will be how I take down the bird!
Not Shocker?
This is it.
I can't believe Shocker's
sponsoring an event like this.
Let's go.
I've been meaning to ask, Yukarisu...
What's with that outfit?
This is how all men look
to me, except you!
So, I'm sure no one will notice!
Let's go.
Is this gonna work?
Th-The show will begin in ten minutes.
Roger Wilco!
See what I meant?
It's the perfect disguise!
Come on!
We're sorry about the wait, everyone!
We're proud to announce that
the 10th Jewel Night Combat Girls Cup...
is now underway!
Now, let's introduce our teams!
First up, the winners of Group A...
Team Air Master!
Next, the winners of Group B...
Team Ayakashi Leader!
The championship match
will be between gamers
who made it through
some fierce qualifiers!
What kind of white-hot competition
will we see here tonight?
I can't wait to find out!
And I've heard a rumor...
that the winners of this tournament...
will have their whole lives change!
I wonder how, though...
Maybe the prize money?
It's more than that, I bet!
But let's ask someone who'd know...
Our previous winner, BlackTights203!
A combatant?!
Someone's looking sharp
in all that black!
Very cool!
What do you have to say?
Has there been any change in your life
since you won the last tournament?
Oh, definitely.
Ever since he shared his power with me,
I've felt more joy in life
than ever before.
Who's he talking about?
That is amazing!
Joy in your life, huh?
Yes!
When I used to walk around town,
I'd end up prey for petty thugs!
Oh, that sounds awful!
But now, I just clobber them
and send them running!
Wow!
Thanks to this tournament,
I've won every fight I've gotten into since.
And you have the power
he gave you to thank for that.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Are the rest of you satisfied
with who you are right now?
This world is so unfair... Haven't you
ever wished you could just tear it down?!
What is he talking about?
I'm not sure what the deal is here.
Well, you don't have to worry any longer!
Now that you're here, you'll obtain
enough power to stand up to anyone!
You can use it against
anyone you don't like...
And crush them all!
Let's make this world...
one that belongs to us!
And now to introduce our
super-duper VIP guest!
The tournament's sponsor...
Morio Koda-sama!
It's him!
The Bat Man!
Welcome, you foolish humans.
You find yourselves despairing at
how asinine your society has become,
and seek to immerse yourselves
in this fantasy world as a result.
But is that really enough?
You can't run from reality, y'know!
Nothing will ever change if you do that.
I'm going to give you power.
Join Shocker and together
we will rule the world!
This is bad news, right?
Let's get out of here.
The sooner, the better.
Huh?
The doors won't open!
Are we trapped in here?!
EMERGENCY EXIT
There!
Ow, ow...
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
Thanks for the hel...
Wait, you're...
Puunyan from the Little Busters!
I've always been a fan of yours!
But what are you doing in a—
Join Shocker now, and each and
every one of you will get a girlfriend.
And...
They'll all be idols!
Come on, boys!
We're joining Shocker!
Th-This is...
What do we do, Mitsuba?!
Well, well.
I thought I sensed a Shocker combatant.
Looks like there's a rat
crashing our party.
Say...
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
This ain't no ordinary rooster, is it?
Very observant.
It's a Shamo, a type of bird
raised for cockfighting.
I figured.
He's a legendary champion in the
underground world of cockfighting,
and in human terms, he'd be 120 years old.
He's been enjoying
his retirement out here.
That don't explain
how he got here, though.
My grandma used to breed
roosters for fighting.
That explains it...
And why he's as intense
as a martial arts master.
All right, if you're ready...
Then
begin!
He's coming out the gate at full throttle!
And he's as fast as ever!
But I can actually follow his moves now!
Gotta keep my eyes on him...
watch how he moves, keep defending,
and wait for the perfect opening!
Build up my strength like in
an old-fashioned catapult...
This is it!
.44 Magnum!
The Shocker combatant wins.
The name's Nakao!
Nakao wins!
Hell yeah!
I didn't think you'd actually pull it off.
I was getting ready to go next.
You guys are unbelievable.
Th-That's impressive.
I guess... it's a tie then?
Thank you for your guidance!
Don't let it bother you.
How exactly?!
That stray cat's been out
to get him for a while now.
Always lurking around
outside his enclosure...
Master Shamo...
That's the nature of combat.
He pried my eyes open
after a life of lethargy.
Looking back now,
I always thought I was on my own.
But I always had the boys with me.
Ito. Ishige. Sato.
The three of you were,
without a doubt, my brothers.
I'm sorry it took so long
for me to realize it.
Master Shamo... thank you for everything!
I'm going to take down Shocker
for the sake of my brothers!
Granted, I'm not the star of this act,
so I'll probably die in the process...
But I'm ready for what comes next.
I'm gonna go train.
Just lightly enough that it
doesn't slow down the others.
I've had a pretty simple life...
But I wouldn't complain.
Whoa!
You ran all the way
into the damn mountains.
This works out nicely.
I was...
I WAS CRAVING A BATTLE WITH SHOCKER
...cravyeeeng...
...a battle with Shocker!
Bring it on, then.
NEXT EPISODE
BECOMING
THE ULTIMATE
MONSTER
BECOMING THE ULTIMATE MONSTER
ILLUSTRATION BY: AYARAGI HIROSHI