Will...
I'll always be by your side.
Will!
Rosty! Rosty!
Rosty!
Ice Faction Aide-de-Camp
Sarissa Alfeld
Lightning Faction Aide-de-Camp
Guilford Zurgas
Lord Zeo!
And where are you planning on going, Zeo?
Cariot Incindia Wiseman
That's obvious, isn't it? The battlefield.
Crying and wailing,
dying pathetically by the wayside...
Every last one of them is useless!
But...
The most useless of all...
Zeo Thorzeus Reinbolt
are us for sitting here
and watching them die!
Lord Aaron has already explained.
If we, the Magia Vander, fall,
the Great Barrier will vanish.
Aaron Masterias Oldking
In that event, there is but one outcome.
The Celestial Host will utterly
destroy this world, reducing it to ash.
Cowardly flames...
At the moment, even we are at
a disadvantage against those things.
We should at least wait until
our magical energy has recovered.
You ought to be more conscious of
your position as a Magia Vander, Zeo.
I'm always telling you that, aren't I?
Now, come back and take your seat.
You want me to be more conscious?
In that case, screw this.
You can keep your feeble Wand title.
I told you to get back here.
If you don't, it will become necessary
to pin you in place by force.
Go ahead and try it.
Elf Faction Aide-de-Camp
Lefiya Viridis
This may turn into
a disgraceful spectacle.
What would you like to do, Lady Ellenor?
This is preposterous.
Ellenor Ljos Alf
I shall remain a spectator.
After all, this is the mages' land.
There is one of our
kindred at the academy.
Elf Faction Aide-de-Camp
Filvis Challia
What would you have us do?
Go.
Understood.
The battle above ground
is already desperate.
And the Magia Vander just
aren't in step with each other.
If things continue this way...
What? Wait...
Lady Elfaria?
Elfaria Albis Serfort
Rescind your order.
We're wasting time.
You will not change my mind.
Stand down, Elfaria.
I'm going to save those
who are dear to me, including Will.
If you get in my way,
I will knock you down as well.
L-L-Lady... Lady Elfaria?!
Episode 15
One Single Magic Spell
The Devander's arrival has spelled
the collapse of our front line.
Rigarden Magical Academy Professor
Workner Norgram
And the surviving Dinoboroses
are starting to drive back our mages.
Even the dwarves can't keep
this situation in check.
This boy is our last and only hope.
...can't.
I can't protect anything.
I can't save anything.
I can't do anything!
It's just like it was back then.
This is no different than when
they took Elfie away!
Is it because I can't use magic?
Because I can't use magic, I can't
protect Elfie, or Rosty, or anyone else!
It's all because I'm just a laggard!
All of it! Everything!
It's all because of that!
Will, calm down!
Professor Workner.
Why am I...
Why is it just me?!
Why am I the only one who can't use magic?
Will! Pull yourself together!
Will!
Yo.
That brat reeks.
He's even more of a pain than the dwarves.
That's what his stench is telling me.
I'll kill you both at once.
Thank you, Colette!
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Lihanna Owenzaus
Colette, what are you doing?
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Colette Loire
Just now, that was...
Familiar
Kiki
Kiki!
Kiki, are you all right?
It can't be... Just now, was that Will?
Please, Kiki! Take me to Will!
Sion?
You guys figure out
what to do about all this!
Rigarden Magical Academy
Julius Reinberg
H-Hey!
Julius, make some doubles of yourself!
Huh?
Julius, hurry!
What?!
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Wignall Lindor
Hurry up and do it, Julius!
Aren't they ready yet, Julius?
Julius!
The whole lot of you! Stop treating me
like I'm at your convenience!
That silly Marze
seems to be quite excited.
A chorus of screams
in a monsters' march...
This delightful melody
will continue forever!
Oh, how I'd love to go
hunt some adorable heads.
But unfortunately, today
my job is to be the conductor.
Now, you should be on your way, too.
This is bad.
It's headed for the tower.
Don't let it get near Central Flos,
the heart of the city!
That monster is capable
of killing the Magia Vander!
Clairie Serah
Serah!
Launch a suicide attack, dwarves!
Make for the city center!
Destroy that mage slayer the Devander
is using by any means necessary!
You can't be serious!
My people are already battered and ragged
from serving as shields for your kind!
Donnan and the others have fallen!
And you're telling us to go die?!
Gina
Yes, I am!
Rigarden Magical Academy Professor
Edward Serfence
For the sake of the capital!
To protect the children!
Give your lives, dwarves!
Gina!
Saeva Fulminas!
You... Why did you do that?
We're up against an enemy
impervious to magic, so right now...
my life is worth
far less than any of yours.
That's all.
I will pay the same price.
So please, lay down your lives!
Men!
Gather our brothers!
We make for the city center!
Frubas Julier!
Wait, Colette!
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Sion Ulster
Don't run off alone!
But if we don't hurry, Will could be...
That laggard!
He's always jerking us around!
Stear Viola!
Loire Sique!
Now, of all times?!
Colette!
The western front line has fallen!
The high mage units in the
northeast have been wiped out!
The Dinoboroses can't be stopped!
Send all civilians south!
Organo's team, the lightning faction,
are holding the enemy at bay!
All units, keep fighting!
I repeat! Everyone out there,
resist to the bitter end!
Resist to the bitter end?
That's gonna be impossible.
I wonder where Colette ended up.
I would've liked to see
her one last time...
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Rose Prehnite
but it looks like things
might be too far gone for that.
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Mike Maius
Everyone, head south!
Just follow the streets,
and you'll get there in no time!
Hurry!
I've shouted too much.
My throat can't take anymore.
We can't go this way!
Where are we supposed to go?
Go south!
Ignis Rooks!
Lyril!
Hurry up! We're getting out of here!
But... But what about...
He saved us, and we're the ones
who get away?! That's just...
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Lyril Mars
Gordon Vally
Quit it with the heroics
when your knees are knocking!
Ulverre.
P-Professor Eliza?
Transport the wounded.
Rigarden Magical Academy Professor
Eliza Nosferat
You will not pathetically flee.
This is aid that only you can provide!
Leave here to me and go!
Y-Yes, professor!
They're a handful.
But...
they are my darling students, after all.
Emma!
What are you doing?
We need to get away from here already!
This girl...
She said she has a much
younger brother back home.
She said she was finally
going to see him.
And now... It's too cruel!
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Emma Klever
This is just too cruel!
Edward is injured!
And we've lost touch with Workner!
Clairie, give us a situation report!
Clairie, respond!
Fires in the developments keep spreading!
We can't guide the residents to evacuate!
The situation couldn't be worse.
Rigarden Magical Academy Headmistress
Caldron Anouve
It's taking all we have just
to defend the civilians.
Someone please come and help!
East is taking heavy damage!
We can't turn the enemy back.
Requesting backup!
The Devander is still alive and well!
And the horde of Dinoboroses
is headed for the city center!
I-It's no good! We can't stop them!
Thanks to the dwarves, we've been able
to whittle away at the mage slayers.
My arm! My arm is...
But we can't stop the Devander.
Reinforcements!
Please send reinforcements!
That's the heart
of the dilemma on every front.
Wizard's Tower Watcher
Iris Churchill
We can't hold them off any longer!
Someone! Anyone, please!
We can't scrape together
enough of a fighting force!
With only a few of the dwarves left, the
best we can hope for is to die honorably.
The southwest sector can't
take any more! What should we—
H-Help us!
At this rate, the tower will fall.
What can we do?
The enemy is...
Who is that?!
What's wrong?
Please, give me a situation report!
What's happened?!
Iris, how's the sword?
What?
Y-You're...
Where is the sword right now?
Yellow Mud Wand
Rose Prehnite
Race: Rhizanth   Age: 16   Height: 159 cm
Birthday: 3rd of Ahzomoon
Likes: Meat soup, curry, beef stew, Colette
Dislikes: Annoying adults
Wants to Protect: Colette Loire
Deepest Dungeon Floor Reached: 8th
Equipment: Yellow Mud wand
Skills: Up to intermediate earth magic;
Plenus Witch
An earth mage in the same academic year as Will
and the others. Colette Loire's roommate.
Easily talented and capable enough to ascend to
the tower, but she hides it. If she's ever discovered,
Lihanna would swiftly fall into a deep depression.
Approached Colette on her grandfather's orders,
but at this point she's changed from "an observation
target" to "a friend dearer than any other."
Devander
A notorious monster from floor 40.
Though their overall numbers are small, they appear in the dungeon every few years.
Their ilk have killed Magia Vander of previous generations, and their strength
surpasses even that of a floor keeper.
The tower has determined them to be worth 4,444 credits.
That guy... He's pretty good.
Imagine being in that situation and
trying to return a killing blow.
But I hit deep.
This is the end for him.
Where am I?
The city. The west side.
It appears we crashed.
It was all I could do... to protect you.
Professor... Workner...
Will, I'm sorry.
The only thing I can do now...
is depend on you.
You're the only one...
But since it's you, I just know...
you can save this city.
I can't.
I can't, Professor Workner.
I let Rosty die. And now you,
Professor Workner...
Someone's always saving me.
I can't protect the people
who matter to me!
I can't change a thing.
A sword can't overturn
the order of the world!
I'm not...
Someone like me who can't
even use magic isn't...
Will, as your teacher...
I've been lying to you.
You...
You can use magic.
It'll show everyone that there's hope.
One single magic... spell...
Wait. Please, wait!
Don't die, Professor Workner!
Please tell me! What is my magic?!
Even the tiniest bit of gumption
and a light that can pierce anything...
An argent light.
You're... Mister Finn.
He's all right.
Once his pulse kicks in,
he'll breathe again.
What?
What's more important right now is you.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and get on your feet.
The stage has already
been set for you, hasn't it?
An argent light?
No, before that...
What's this about a bit of gumption?
When you heard the word "magic," did you
think you'd be wielding flames or wind?
You know that isn't possible!
He was talking about where
your willpower comes from.
You could even call it your emotions...
or a type of self-suggestion.
You raise your voice. You shout.
And you stir yourself to action.
It's a tremendous roar that turns
the unreal into reality.
But that's...
A childish trick like that
won't help me save everyone!
Something like that is just...
Stop spouting such foolishness!
It's the most important
thing of all, isn't it?
Those who cannot transform themselves
will never change the world!
And that's exactly what
you're aiming to accomplish!
Remember your roots.
Take back your origins.
The lock has already been opened.
Now, take up your sword!
Let's set out on a journey.
Over the hill of darkness...
to pass beyond the false sky!
You already know the answer!
What is the name of the magic
that lives in your heart?
Cry out and bring it into being!
What is the name of your spell?!
Courage!
Limiter Off.
Now, unsheathe your sword!
Are we... saved?
What just happened?
Just now, that...
It can't be.
What is happening?
This is...
That light is vanquishing
the monsters one after another.
Halcon!
Sion!
Run, Sion!
I can't... run.
I won't!
If it were him, he'd never run away!
That coward...
who's braver than anyone!
I can do this, too!
I will not let him beat me!
You have it all wrong, Sion.
I was jealous. I was bitter.
I was desperate.
I've been chasing all of you
all this time.
I'm just a pathetic wretch.
Which is why, from now on...
I will be like a lone sword!
Mageblade: Wis
Wistoria: Wand and Sword
Next time on Wistoria: Wand and Sword,
episode 16, "And the Story Begins."
Episode 16
And the Story Begins