Excuse me, you dropped this.
Sorry...
Namie-chan...
Why?
Satoru-kun?
Why didn't you come that day?
Because...
I waited for so long...
I mean I... I also wanted to...
Namie-chan!
Satoru-kun!
Hey, Goddess!
Oh? What are you doing?
Let us hold one another, Namie-chan!
Let us hold one another, Satoru-kun!
Now, we must hold one another!
Now...
Um... is this a trap?
No.
This time I thought I
would be more "dere."
Now...
What's gotten into you?!
When one has been a reincarnation
goddess for so long,
they sometimes get a sudden desire to
feel another's touch: a fit, if you will.
A fit?!
Now...
Hold me close.
My Ribdiculous Reincarnation
Here you go.
What's this?
A yellowtail fish.
It's great wrapped in kombu.
Don't wrap me in kombu.
Hold me tight and close.
I'll tighten my necktie!
Don't do that.
Candy Fair
Buy one participating sweet
Get one
Free!
Close the register...
Don't do that.
Have some rice porridge.
Don't end our meal with that.
I like to end my
meal with udon noodles.
Oh no!
I didn't do enough research!
What's wrong?
This is what you wanted, right?
Now, hold me tight.
What's wrong?
I'm sure I could have a
lot of fun right now...
But...
I'm scared of what comes after!
I won't deny that you should be.
I really wish you would!
Don't worry.
Afterwards, the overwhelming
humiliation and regret I feel
will make me kill you until you forget.
This is getting worse than "scary"!
I need to reincarnate, fast!
What did you get?
Vegetable
Vegetable!
Yes, a world where you are an edible
vegetable is a terrifying thought.
Great. That keeps us on theme.
Um, what's going on here?
Hold me before you reincarnate.
I think I'll...
pass!
I feel... lonely...
I'm back!
And of course, you return.
Is your fit over?
Yes. I apologize for making you worry.
It's not over.
Now, let's hear your report.
I'll stick it in myself!
Shine!
I wanted to be the one to stick it in.
Maybe some other time.
I was the tomato hero!
A very ripe tomato, I see.
I rose up to fight the Demon
King who threatened the world!
The time is ripe!
Yes, it is.
I will be the tomato that saves the world!
I will!
You were aggressive from
the start this time.
But I was just a single tomato.
So I started by gathering allies!
Twinkle twinkle!
Hey, won't anyone come with
me to beat the Demon King?
Big Sky Veggies
Hello? Anybody?
But nobody answered!
You were a vegetable, after all.
Hello? Anybody?
Who's there? Who's there?
I shouted as loudly as I could, but only
the old man on guard duty heard me.
This is just a horror story.
My wife! It's my dead wife!
So I got the old man to join my party...
Stop.
How?
Well, you know...
I'm a lovable guy!
Share some of that love with me.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no...
But having an old guy in the party was
bad from a visual design standpoint...
Hot Old Man Magic!
Hot Old Man Onion!
That's a brutal thing to do to someone.
And that was the birth of Onion Warrior!
O-Onion! Onion!
His special ability was making people cry.
I'm from Awaji!
I'm sure he wanted to cry
about what happened to him.
And that onion is...
Here!
I'm from Awaji!
You brought him back as a gift?
Is he edible?
Our first enemy was the cook!
I'm from Awaji! I'm from Awaji!
I'd say I'm surprised,
but somehow I'm really not.
Hold it, you!
Run!
I'll cook you, boil you,
throw you in a pot!
Oops!
The security guard!
Oh, boo!
Hot Old Man Eggplant Magic!
I quickly sealed his soul
inside the nearest vegetable.
Chef!
This time, you were the enemy of humanity.
I'm sure he never imagined that he'd
be the one to end up on the menu.
And that eggplant...
is right here!
Another gift.
And only half of him?
Anyway, I'll skip the details, but...
Cilantro Knight!
Cilantro Knight
Strength
Deliciousness
Nutritional Value
Some like him, some don't
Cucumber Samurai!
Cucumber Samurai
Strength
Deliciousness
Nutritional Value
Great with miso, milord
And Cabbage Gladiator...
Cabbage Gladiator
Strength
Deliciousness
Nutritional Value
Friend to caterpillars
all joined my party!
The party seems unbalanced, job-wise.
Just so you know, all these vegetables
were once my party members!
Are they edible?
Are you sure they're edible?
And did you really need such a big party?
Hoy, hoy, hoy, hoy!
Vegetables, hey!
Hoy, hoy, hoy, hoy! Vegetables, hey!
Hoy, hoy, hoy, hoy!
Vegetables, hey!
Cucumber!
In death, a cucumber I remain!
Cabbage!
Cilantro!
A lot of my companions got
eaten and died on the way,
so I had no choice but to recruit more.
You don't have to be a monster
to eat some veggies you
find on the roadside.
In the end, by the time I made
it to the Demon King's castle,
there were only four of us left.
If anything, I'm shocked
you made it there.
My party consisted of...
Onion Warrior!
I'm from Awaji!
I'm shocked the security guard
actually made it that far.
Tofu Martial Artist, who joined halfway.
It feels like he'd crumble
apart if you hit him.
And finally...
Evil Dragon God Bahalmetia!
That one, I did not see coming.
It explains how you made it to the
Demon King's castle, at least.
By the way,
Evil Dragon God Bahalmetia
was actually the weakest
member of the party!
Weaker than the onion who was
once a night security guard?
Evil Dragon God Bahalmetia's level was...
72.
And Onion Warrior was Level 98!
I'm from Awaji!
By the way, the max level
for that world was 99!
I see the night security
guy was an XP grinder.
Tofu Martial Artist was 92.
And you?
872.
You added a limit-breaking option
when I wasn't looking, didn't you?
Well, even if a vegetable hits the
level cap, it's still a vegetable.
Can you explain why a Level 98 onion
was stronger than the
Evil Dragon God, then?
The last battle with the Demon King,
Potato Warrior, was about to begin!
Another warrior.
To think the friendly guy we met at
the bar was actually the Demon King!
Bar
No Demons
Even I didn't see that coming!
No, that is clearly the Demon King.
Hot Old Man Magic!
The real surprise for me was that
you met the Demon King at a bar,
became his friend, then ripped out his
soul and sealed it inside a vegetable.
I'll get you for this!
Demon King Potato Warrior
unleashed his wrath on me.
I'm sure he was very upset about
being turned into a vegetable.
No, he was mad that I gave
Evil Dragon God Bahalmetia
treats until he joined my side.
You got him to join your
party by giving him treats?
By the way, his favorite
treat was eggplant!
Is that where the cook went?
He's also not a big eater.
And thus we solve the mystery
of the half-eaten eggplant.
Toma-toma-toma-toma-tomato!
Demon King Potatotia's blade
sliced through space-time itself!
Was that, by chance, his real name?
Also, I can see the staff through
the hole ripped in space-time.
Tofu Martial Artist risked
his life to stop the blade.
It cuts space-time but not tofu.
And so the poor little
caterpillar became a star!
Farewell, Cabbage.
You were delicious.
Onion Knight told a sad story to make
the Demon King cry, which blinded him.
I don't think that's how onions
are supposed to make you cry.
And then Evil Dragon God
Bahalmetia burned everything to ash!
Stop putting actual powerful
things in the story. It's weird.
Take... this!
Vegetable
Reincarnation Section
Video Production
With that,
the Demon King was defeated,
and peace returned to the land.
But since they didn't want the hero
to rot, they planted me in a field,
and I'm still cultivated to this day
under the brand name "Hero Tomato!"
Hence why there's no
tomato in the gift box.
Yes, that's right.
Looks like your fit is over, huh?
I do feel like I've calmed down.
Okay, I'll use these
veggies to make curry.
Yes.
Let us hold one another in our
arms while we peel onions.
It wasn't over!
I always want to annihilate
myself after these fits.
Um...
Is it safe to come out?
My fit is over.
Let me try getting close to make sure!
Even if you immediately resurrect,
it's still creepy to see you come back
without changing your expression at all.
I learned a way to not feel pain!
Kids these days are barely even human.
Oh, it's almost time for
another reincarnation!
You've started saying it yourself, huh?
The Lock on a Treasure Chest
The lock on a treasure chest!
Inorganic this time, I see.
That's my specialty!
I'll give you credit for your optimism.
Let's give you your options.
Let's add the usual shock trap...
Denied.
Shock Trap
Shock Tr
Shock
Sho
Sh
What?!
How am I supposed to fight, then?
Why are you fighting, again?
Gloom...
Locks are about defense, not offense.
Act like it.
I'll do my best to bring back what's
in the treasure chest as a gift!
Just die already...
It won't open.
I'm...
back!
I can't open the door to the
safe where I keep all the snacks
I don't want you eating.
Please open it.
That's so cold!
This is our big reunion!
It's open.
Your time as a lock paid off.
I could open the door to your heart, too!
All it takes is a smile...!
Let's hear your report.
I became the lock on the treasure
chest at the holy temple!
You look pretty cheap.
I cost 20 yen to make!
That seems too cheap.
Since that's hard to understand,
if we depict me as a human...
I look like this.
As for the key, it was in the next room.
It was made out of pure gold
and decorated with jewels!
So that's where the money went.
I'm curious what was inside the chest.
The Demon King!
The Demon King was inside the chest.
So that's what it was.
How'd they get him in the box?
They folded him six times
and stuffed him in!
He must've died when he
was folded six times.
It was a guy named Demon King Spacious!
Having Plenty of Room
No nominative determinism here, I see.
In the distant past, Demon King
Spacious tried to destroy the world!
The humans shall serve beneath my seas!
What's this?!
Curse you!
I set it so I would be
the lock on his chest!
You were getting greedy, for a lock.
I'll get you for this...
I'll get you for this! No matter what!
He spent every day raging at
the god who sealed him away!
You sold the game I lent you online!
You said you'd only eat a bite of
my ice cream, and you ate it all!
Who does that?!
I'll forgive you for sowing the seeds of
eternal war between demons and humanity.
But I'll never forgive
you for putting lemon
on my chicken wings without asking first!
This god sounds like a real asshole.
I felt so bad for poor Demon King
Spacious that I talked to him one day.
I know it sucks, but eat
something good and forget it.
I especially recommend
delicious sockeye salmon.
Who the hell are you?!
How dare a mere lock speak
to me, the Demon King!
Know your place!
A mere Demon King was being rude to me,
so I hit him with a spell that
sprayed him with lemon juice.
Lemon Juice!
Lemon! Ahh!
My eyes! My eyes!
You were brutal as a lock, too.
Stop it! Stop pouring lemon juice on me!
What's this liquid?
An ominous portent!
This is definitely ominous!
I also hit him with a spell that
filled the box with vegetable oil,
Vegetable Oil
perfect for crispy tempura!
Were you trying to cook?
Grr!
Demon King Spacious was a fish monster,
so this caused him to awaken.
It was oil, not water, though.
And the priests decided he was
dangerous and put up another barrier.
Be quelled!
Damn you, Demon King!
It was a barrier that made oil burn...
Ahh! H-Hot!
This is...
Too ominous!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
What's wrong?
Some guy appeared, holding the key.
Okay, let's open 'er up.
Who's this guy?
The key's huge! Wait, wait, wait!
Lemon!
Key!
I'll make you pay...
None may treat a god like this.
So the guy was the god?
Even sealed, you resist a god?
The Demon King is truly evil!
I shall end your life myself!
Holy Sword of Banishing Evil!
Annihilate this wicked soul!
He got serious.
Vegetable oil!
God!
Corn oil!
Olive oil!
The Holy Sword of Banishing Evil...
You asshole! You! Asshole!
That's so evil!
And then he got shocked.
I thought I took that off the option list.
The treasure chest itself
had it as an option.
The treasure chest was
reincarnated too, huh?
And down went the god.
Demon King Spacious went down too.
He got shocked too, huh?
And so the hero defeated
Demon King Spacious.
The treasure chest was the hero, huh?
The treasure chest was
kind of a jerk, huh?
He beat not just the Demon
King, but the god, too.
And you were just as responsible.
Since both the god and the
Demon King were gone,
the seeds of discord between the
demons and humans were gone,
and the world became peaceful on its own.
That's a nice ending.
Hero
A hero robot?
He had a transformation fetish.
But the guy brought an end
to my job as a lock...
Lock on a Treasure Chest
Reincarnation Section
Video Production
Koji Kumeta
I didn't get to do anything.
I think you did a lot, for a lock.
Oh, as a gift I brought what
was in the treasure chest...
Go put it back.
What? A great Demon King wants to
transform into something like that?
Yes, that's right.