There's no other way.
Riderman!
What does he think he's doing?
That's hilarious!
What's that?
Swing Arm!
Let's go, Yukarisu!
I can't believe what we just saw.
I never thought Shocker would be
bold enough to pull a move like that.
What now, Mitsuba?
I've got an idea!
Bring it on, then.
He's...
You're a lot slower than my master was.
My 44 years...
of worthless life...
I'm loading all of it into this fist!
Have a taste!
.44 Magnum!
It worked!
I did it, Master!
Hey!
What? Is it morning already?
I caught a female combatant!
Who in the world is this?!
What's she doing here?!
I beat her on my own!
That doesn't answer who she is!
Were there any other Shocker
members with her?!
What? Shocker?!
What is Shocker doing here?!
I saw your match yesterday!
It was brutal, Miou-san!
Thanks.
Another one-round KO!
You've been undefeated since your debut!
You're seriously the strongest!
Look, the other girl was just too weak.
I'm really looking forward
to your next match!
Wait, you're a pro wrestler, right?
Now, what was your name again?
I think she's Thunder Raiko.
Oh, right, Raiko-san!
Are you on your way home from a match?
Hope your trip back isn't too long.
The name's Miou, and I'm
a mixed martial artist.
Ever heard of me?
I'm pretty sure I could take you.
I mean, pro wrestling in this day and age?
You're just traveling to the boonies,
putting on a little show...
It's basically a cheap circus.
Oh, look at that.
You wanna go? Right now?
Because I'm ready to go. Let's do it.
Easy there. I don't think this
is the right time or place.
Why? You chicken?
Ow!
Come and get some, "strongest."
PRO WRESTLER AND MIOU IN A STREET FIGHT
PRO WRESTLER CHALLENGES MIOU
CAN PRO WRESTLING BEAT MMA?
MIOU EXPRESSES  CONFIDENCE.
Miou! Miou! Miou!
When we first met,
you said you were stronger.
Yeah? Because that's the truth.
We fight for real.
Pro wrestlers are just actors.
And you think that makes you stronger?
Sure do.
There's an old rule in pro wrestling.
Anyone who spouts that kind of crap,
whether they're an amateur
or a seasoned pro,
gets their ass kicked. Hard.
You're the only one crazy
enough to believe that!
Looks like you're all talk, after all!
You can't even fight back!
Hey, is this gonna be
another KO in the first round?
Miou is so damn strong!
Mitsuharu Misawa, one of the all-time
greats in wrestling, said something once...
"MMA fighters have it easy. They're
encouraged to win as fast as possible."
You get what he meant?
Why the hell would I?
You people fight once
every three or four months.
pro wrestlers can have over
a hundred matches in a year.
Seeing the difference yet?
What the hell...?
She won't budge!
And then there's something
the inspiration for my ring name,
Jushin Thunder Liger, said...
"Pro wrestlers are superhuman!"
A Double Arm Suplex?!
In an MMA match?!
You think this is a joke?
She sent me flying with a body check?
I'm about to show you a pro wrestler's...
full power!
Shinya Hashimoto's overhand chop!
Something to remember...
The only person who can withstand
a pro-wrestler's offense
is another pro wrestler!
Genichiro Tenryu's powerbomb!
Oh, hell, is she for real?!
Here it comes...
Kenta Kobashi's...
Moonsault press!
One! Two! Three!
Raiko, we don't do pinfalls around here!
I know. That was for the crowd.
Pro wrestlers don't win on their own.
They win with the crowd!
Jumbo Tsuruta's...
And then...
Riki Choshu's Scorpion Deathlock!
Raiko! Raiko! Raiko! Raiko! Raiko!
And that's enough to satisfy you?
Who are you?!
As talented as you are,
society doesn't recognize your gifts.
Don't you want to show them
what they're missing?
Why don't we change the world together?
I will make you...
part of Shocker.
A monster!
With your potential, I could have
made you a monster right away.
Instead, I'll make you into a combatant
and oversee your development myself.
And in time...
I'll make you into the ultimate monster.
There it is.
No one should be around at this hour.
Are we seriously breaking in?
They've gotta have crazy security.
Leave it to me.
Okay, here we go.
There was some unexpected interference,
but it went smoothly enough.
Who the hell were they, though?
I'm sure it's fine.
There's no way they can disrupt our plan.
The event was a huge hit on social media!
I guess you're right.
Th-This is...
I guess rich people really are sickos.
Talk about gross.
Are they... drinking his blood?
I'd actually heard rumors about
Bat Man's blood being special,
and that drinking it makes you stronger.
Still nasty, though!
NEWS FLASH
Now that's an ad.
I've got high expectations
for the show at the dome.
We are so grateful, Master Bat Man!
We worked really hard, y'know?
Please, praise us more!
The Tokyo Central Dome?
Is it gonna be a repeat of today?
But in an arena like that...
it's on a totally different scale!
Let's see what else we can find out.
I can't believe a vegetable-only
hotpot could be so delicious!
All I seasoned it with was salt.
But you added love
as a secret ingredient, right?
I already told you I didn't!
Why couldn't I beat these
middle-aged idiots?
T-Transform!
Y-You're awake?!
Now, hang on a second!
Why?! She looks ready for a fight!
You oughta settle down, too! Please!
I asked this before too, but you're
Thunder Raiko, the pro wrestler, right?
Yeah.
I knew it!
I've seen plenty of pro wrestling
and loved it, but...
That fight you had with Miou?
That fight... hit me harder
than anything else in my life!
I was sobbing when you locked
in that Scorpion Deathlock!
Th-Thank you.
Pro wrestlers fight more for
the audience than themselves.
So if you really enjoyed
my match that much...
I couldn't be happier.
Squee.
W-Want something to eat?
S-Sure.
It's good.
Isn't it?! Because there's love in it!
I thought you said there wasn't—
I put some in yours, especially!
And there's plenty more!
I'll kill you after I finish.
Th-Then...
Well, come get us when you're done.
Where are you going?! Don't run!
We're going to train.
Who the hell are these guys?
Who are you people—
Kamen Rider!
V3!
I get it, I get it!
Mind if I join you?
You don't need to ask permission.
You're free to train however you like.
Three hundred thirty-one!
Three hundred thirty-two!
Three hundred thirty-three!
Here you go.
Th-Thank you.
One hundred fifty-eight!
One hundred fifty-nine!
One hundred sixty!
Don't kill us, okay?
I might. Unintentionally.
One thousand five hundred twenty-one!
One thousand five hundred twenty-two!
How many punches are we throwing?!
Ten thousand!
One thousand five hundred twenty-three!
T-Ten thousand?!
One thousand five hundred twenty-four!
We actually punched ten thousand times...
I feel like I could collapse.
Y-You hung in there really well!
Good job!
Really good...
I like Thunder Raiko.
Hell, I'm in love with her.
I see. You're a moron.
She still wants to kill us.
I love you!
I love you, Thunder Raiko!
A romantic confession to Shocker
first thing in the morning.
I knew he was a moron.
I've never been in a relationship
in my entire life!
But I'm trying to take my life
more seriously from now on!
Until I die fighting Shocker...
I'll live! And live!
And live the hell out of my life!
I'm part of Shocker, remember?!
It doesn't matter if you're in Shocker...
You... Wh-What are you babbling about?
I'm saying, I like you!
I love you!
I-I used to never say stuff like this...
But please, let me share my feelings.
It's like I've been struck by
lightning...
And the lightning
is you!
I... I...
I'll make you into the ultimate monster.
I am...
BECOMING THE ULTIMATE MONSTER
Becoming the ultimate monster!
A-And I...
love you!
Let my feelings reach her!
.44 Magnum!
Sh-She's strong.
I think we may have ended up
helping our enemy.
I-I love you...
Shut up!
I love you! I love you!
I love...
I love you. I really do.
The way I feel about you...
is totally love!
Fine.
I-I'll try to keep this short, then.
Ba-bump...
You're too damn old!
It's never gonna happen! Ever!
I-I'll leave it at that for today!
N-Next time you die!
No!
The Shocker combatant just ran away.
She received a desperate love confession
from some middle-aged guy.
That's probably scary, even for Shocker.
NEXT EPISODE
SHOCKER IS
ON THE MOVE
SHOCKER IS ON THE MOVE
ILLUSTRATION BY: KEN NAGASAKI