Why did I decide to play?
Because I didn't care about living,
dying, or anything else anymore.
Riko.
What do you think about the self?
How much of this world
do you think is yourself?
They say lilies are poisonous.
If the seeds I plant bloom,
and their poison kills someone,
then I killed them.
That's how I see it.
I give them life.
I guide them.
I give them purpose.
If there were someone like that,
wouldn't you consider their acts my doing?
Couldn't you say they are basically me?
Riko.
Since you are hollow,
I will give you a mission.
Mishiro-san?
I brought her.
Good work.
We have enough tags, don't we?
Yes. One for you, too.
Exit without me.
It's not her.
I'll go see for myself.
Hey. You seem well.
Will you spare me this time, Mishiro?
What a disgrace.
What a disgrace. What a disgrace.
What a disgrace!
What a disgrace! What a disgrace!
The score had to be settled
much more dramatically.
I'd risen from rock bottom,
and she'd seem more
divinely possessed than ever.
We'd throw all our strength at each other,
and in the end, I would win.
That's how it had to be.
Forty.
I've played forty games,
and none of them were easy.
I used every trick I knew
to keep my broken body going
and never stopped looking forward,
all so I could fight her again.
How dare she show up looking like this?
Quit skulking around.
You can't be serious!
Do you have any idea how I felt?
Why do you look so miserable?
You're just like how I used to be.
After losing to you,
I started by addressing my weaknesses.
I rejected everything about my old self.
Do you have any idea
what it took to get here?
Look.
Look! Look!
I... I...
I didn't come this far to see this woman.
I thought that maybe
I could keep doing this.
I'll probably die eventually
if I keep playing,
but then I'll just become an actual ghost.
That was fine with me.
But now...
What about now?
I was ready to die anytime.
Now that I'd entered this world,
I didn't care about that.
I never cared before I entered.
Mishiro.
An inferior player who lost to me once
and pitifully bowed her head to me.
Now she'd tripped me up, and it was over.
Why?
I didn't want to die like this.
Why did Mishiro...
Oh, right. I'm frustrated, too.
Die.
Die! Die!
I don't want to die. I don't
want to die. I don't want to die.
I refuse to die!
I will give you your first mission.
Mishiro-san...
Pale skin.
A lifeless face.
Mishiro-san...
Exuding death from her entire being.
She's like a ghost.
Mishiro-san!
Riko.
When she defeats me,
you must take my place.
That's right. I'm a vessel.
Wait.
Mishiro-san gave me an order.
I'm supposed to kill you.
Do it, then.
Did Mishiro-san say anything about me?
What did Mishiro-san say?
Huh?
Say something!
Oh, I get it.
You ran away from Mishiro-san.
Right?
Didn't you?!
They're right about the
Wall of Thirty being a curse.
It was a shit game,
and I played like shit.
I had no shot at winning.
I was covered in wounds,
and she was a fully metal killing machine.
I only won because of luck.
Pure luck, as though I was spending
several months' worth of luck at once.
Where are you going? You'll die.
Oh.
Oh, right. Of course.
That's a less painful death.
Shouldn't you be stopping me?
If I kill myself,
will her purpose be fulfilled?
Riko.
Wait. Wait!
Riko. Riko. Riko.
Don't go! Don't go! Don't go!
Please don't go!
Riko.
Riko, thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
They were washed down the drain.
Congratulations on
completing your thirtieth game.
That leaves 69 more to go.
I have a question.
What is it?
I woke up last this time.
You always do.
Was that a penalty?
You were caused needless
anxiety this time.
Don't worry.
I won't allow it to happen again.
What do you mean?
All I can say is we support you girls
from the bottoms of our hearts.
The way you sacrifice everything to win.
Your soul-rending desperation.
There are many people in this
world who want those things.
Kiritani.
Ochiba.
Funabara.
Hagakure.
Shizukawa.
Warabi.
Karin.
Mizunoto.
Amon.
Sugiyama.
Hiwada.
Azuma.
Riko.
I'm glad I met her.
I wish time would stop.
Because right now,
I'm more beautiful than anyone.
So warm.
So warm...
Good game.