Princess, time for some torture!
For today's torture, we have a hamster!
A hamster?
This isn't good, Ex!
I love hamsters.
Don't beat me to the punch!
It's true, though.
I love hamsters.
Their adorable faces...
Their plump tushies...
And most of all, how tiny they are!
Such lovable, yet fragile animals...
I bet they'd die if they
were up against a lion.
Most animals would.
Looks like this one's in the bag!
Come on out!
Hamungous the hellbeast hamster!
It's huge.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Huh? What?
A lukewarm reception?
Hamungous is a hellbeast hamster who's
a star in the Demon World.
Even His Majesty is a Hamungous fan!
So intimidating...
Hamsters' eyes are huge
when they're this size!
I mean, well...
It's kind of scary.
That hurts.
You can talk?
Hellbeast hamsters can talk.
Krall.
Unfortunately, I won't
be giving in today.
I'm sorry that I won't be confessing.
Why are you apologizing for that?
Really? Too bad.
Let's get going, Hamungous.
Please wait!
Krall put her trust in me
by bringing me along for this torture.
She's helped me out so much.
I don't want her torture
to end in failure because of me!
Hamungous!
Please give me a chance!
Oh? A chance, you say?
Do you have a trick up
your sleeve to make me fold?
Yes! I can make a mean pepper steak!
Wh-What?!
Pro hamsters are usually signed
to a talent agency.
Hamungous, on the other hand...
first blew up on social media and became
a top pro hamster while staying freelance!
Freelance
Pro Hamster
Hamungous
A pro hamster?
You can go pro as a hamster?
Nothing I hear or see makes any sense,
so my brain can't keep up!
That smells amazing!
It looks pretty authentic.
Yep.
Before making it big, Hamungous worked
at a Chinese restaurant!
And I hear all the ingredients
were carefully selected.
I can't wait!
Order up.
Time to dig in!
It's delicious!
You betcha!
The rice is complimentary!
And comes with unlimited refills!
Awesome!
"So much for the hamster part,"
Ex silently thought to himself.
The princess
confessed
What?!
Is this true?
Indeed.
I-I don't believe it.
Hamungous was here for today's torture?
Wish I could've been there.
I thought you would say that.
What?
You don't mean...
I had them take the time to stop by.
Here's Hamungous!
Hell yes!
Oh, you got a photo with Hamungous?
Are you jealous?
Hamungous took part in today's torture.
Oh?
You should show Maomao-chan tomorrow.
She might get mad and say,
"Not fair, Papa!"
The next day.
The Hell-Lord got yelled at.
Resume
Furigana: \h\h\h\h\hHamungous Starham
Name:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hHamungous Starham
Birthday:\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h8/7
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Yes! I can make a mean pepper steak!
Princess, for today's torture...
You're up against me!
I-Is that...
That's right.
One of the items
from my Hellblade collection:
Shishio, the Flaming Longsword!
Shishio, the Flaming Longsword
Packing enough heat
to melt through shields and armor,
this prized sword was the favorite
of the departed god of destruction, Kyna!
I'll be using this to make you surrender.
Stop, you fiend!
What are you going to do
to Her Highness with that?!
Fried rice!
Krall told me that the princess
gave in yesterday to pepper steak.
Oh, so that really didn't
count as the hamster?
Today's torture is fried rice made
with Shishio's supernatural heat!
Will you be able to withstand
its devastating power?
Looks good...
But rest assured, Ex!
Two days in a row of Chinese food
is too heavy, even for me.
If it was a light Japanese meal,
I would have been in danger.
Right now, rather than Your Highness,
I'm worried that the god of destruction
may be rolling in his grave right now,
seeing his favorite sword
used to make fried rice.
The heat is what makes
or breaks fried rice!
High temperature is what
separates the rice granules,
leading to perfectly delicious...
Ah.
The wok melted.
Packs enough heat to melt shields!
Why don't you ask Torture for help
with the cooking?
No way!
Tor-chan's doing desk work today,
writing up a report for her business trip.
That's why she asked me
to handle this torture.
If I make her help with the torture,
she won't finish her report...
And she'll have to work overtime!
We can't have that.
That means the victor
of today's torture is Your Highness!
Makes sense.
V for victory!
Wait! Please wait, Princess!
You're skilled enough to wield
the legendary sacred blade Ex!
Oh?
You'd be able to handle this Hellblade...
and keep the temperature
under control, wouldn't you?!
I'm begging you!
Please help me make this fried rice!
And why would we ever work with you?!
Isn't that right, Your Highness?
You swallowed your pride and pleaded
with your enemy to attain your goal.
You've got moxie!
Your Highness?!
Let's make that fried rice together!
Thank you, Princess!
She's hopeless.
So this is Shishio's power...
This is nothing!
Princess...
I am the Princess and Commander
of the Imperial Third Legion!
I will never bow down
to a mere Hellblade!
Obey me! Shishio, the Flaming Longsword!
Yeah, that looks good in terms of heat.
Okay, now's your chance!
Y-Yes!
I can smell a masterpiece cooking!
Maintain a steady temperature!
Speed is what makes or breaks fried rice!
Shake that wok real good!
Keep the rice moving!
Finish it up by sprinkling
in some scallions!
All done!
Fried rice with juicy shrimp!
My body's craving something greasy!
What?
Weren't you in the mood
for a light Japanese meal?
Well? Did it come out good?
I surrender!
Yes!
After you held your own
against the Hellblade?!
The princess
confessed
Is Gilga-chan fine on her own?
Perhaps I should go and...
m 0 0 l 200 0 200 60 0 60
Incoming message
From: Gilga
Sub: Got a secret out of her
In the language of flowers,
turmeric means, "The sight of
you intoxicates me."
It seems she succeeded
in learning a secret.
Good work, Gilga-chan.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Peschutz Manor
What?!
What did you just say, Kon-chan?
What?
Peschutz Manor Maid
Kon Konko
Master said...
It's about Vanilla-chan's tortures.
She's been having trouble getting
the princess to surrender as planned.
She must be feeling dejected.
There must be...
a surefire torture method we
can come up with for her.
After hearing that,
I simply gave you my suggestion.
S-Still, a torture so
terrifying and cruel...
No...
It's possible that I misheard you.
Kon-chan, could you
repeat what you just said?
Of course.
Jumping stairs.
First, two people stand on the first step
of a staircase, and proceed to jump down.
If they succeed, then
next is the second step.
Then after that comes the
third step, fourth step...
This continues until one person is too
scared to jump and is declared the loser.
That's way too dangerous!
It's what all the younger grade schoolers
play until the teachers ban it!
The forbidden game!
Forbidden?
What's wrong with that?
Master.
House Peschutz is said to be the most
ruthlessly brutal clan in the Hellhorde.
That may be true...
But wouldn't Vanilla-chan
be in danger as well?
It's far from dangerous.
Miss Vanilla is sure to
reign victorious with this torture.
You can't be serious!
Have you forgotten?
With the wings on her waist...
Miss Vanilla can fly for
a brief period of time!
You're right!
It's more like reducing her
speed falling than flying, really.
I see. With this...
Vanilla-chan can be the surefire winner!
That's right.
There's no room for Miss Vanilla to lose!
Unless the princess that she faces...
has an extremely strong lower body!
A merciless and infallible torture
befitting the Peschutz name.
The perfect torture!
Unless the princess has
an extremely strong lower body!
I'll go suggest the idea
to Vanilla-chan right away!
Papa.
Vanilla-chan.
Are you all right?
You looked a bit gloomy.
Yeah.
My tortures haven't worked out lately,
which means I can't fail next time.
So I was trying to come up
with a surefire torture method.
I-In that case...
And just now, I had the idea
for the best torture ever!
Just you wait, Papa!
I'll definitely win next time!
This torture...
I hope the princess likes it.
Oh yeah, Papa.
What did you want?
No...
It's nothing.
I'm sure the princess will love it.
Yeah!
Since I, the daughter of the noble House
of Peschutz, came up with this torture!
Time for your torture, Princess!
I, the daughter of the House of Peschutz,
have devised the perfect torture for you!
Vanilla-chan, you seem different today.
We'll need to brace ourselves.
Nothing will have you ready for this one.
Today's torture is utterly flawless!
Mama and Papa said it was great!
And I picked a really
cute gift bag for it.
You're sure to surrender
completely, Princess!
Even I had to admire its sheer perfection
next to my pillow just before I slept!
Sheer perfection?
Just what does this torture entail?!
Wouldn't you like to know?
Why don't I show you right now?
Take this!
Here's your torture for today!
I left the torture next to my pillow...
What?
W-Wait, Princess!
I'll go grab it right now!
Vanilla-chan!
It was the perfect torture, too...
I worked so hard late into the night...
Now that's what I call merciless!
What a wonderful torture
that lives up to the Peschutz name!
That's my Vanilla-chan!
After all the praise I got
from Mama and Papa...
Sorry to make you carry me like this.
You need a chaperone in order
to leave the castle.
Don't sweat it.
Thanks for coming along.
Found her! Vanilla-chan!
I knew it! Vanilla-chan's crying!
It's okay!
The torture hasn't failed yet!
If I run to grab it
and head back, I can make it!
You can do it, Vanilla!
Is Vanilla-chan's house far from here?
'Tis about a ten-minute
walk from Hellholm.
I wouldn't call it far.
I see.
Should we head back and wait, then?
Yes, let's do that.
Princess!
Once again, it's time for your torture!
Let's see it, then.
Let's test this perfect torture of yours!
Here's your torture for today!
Whoa, what's this?
This gift bag's so cute!
Open it up.
What could it be?
A teddy bear!
Wait, don't tell me that it's...
Sewn by hand.
What?!
Surrendering's not enough for this!
Thanks, Vanilla-chan!
Yeah.
Today's inquisitor, Vanilla Peschutz,
successfully made the princess yield.
I'd expect no less from Aliotto's girl.
She can't resist her
diabolical Peschutz blood.
Well said!
As for the information she obtained...
It seems the princess's little sister
sleeps with a stuffed animal every night.
I approve!
Wow, I really like how this looks.
And it feels great to the touch.
The price... seems reasonable!
I'll go grab you a new one.
It's my first time in here,
but it turned out to be a great shop.
That comes out to 34,200 yen.
Eh?
My purchase yesterday turned out
to cost more than I thought.
I mean, I like the color...
And the material is nice...
But 30,000 yen for a completely
normal-looking sweatshirt...
I was too embarrassed to say,
"Actually, never mind" at the register...
No, there's no point in moping like this!
This doesn't change the fact
that it's a nice piece of clothing!
I'll go out today wearing this!
The material is thin and light,
yet I'm so warm with this one layer alone!
And it feels so nice on my body.
I never knew...
Good quality fabric... really is good!
I feel like there's more
bounce in my step today.
Fashion's about more than just the price,
but I still feel a sense of exhilaration.
At this very moment...
I'm wearing some nice clothes!
Oh yes, this hotel...
I believe they have a café.
It always seemed too upscale
for me to go inside,
but I feel like I can work up
the courage now!
Seeing as how I'm wearing nice clothes!
This is great!
Today was a fun day
full of new experiences.
I never saw the point in buying
expensive casual clothes before...
But it turned out to have its merits.
I learned something new today.
It's always good to approach things
with an open mind.
I'll buy the clothes I like best
going forward, regardless of the price...
Let's take good care of this sweatshirt.