Wait, you got a search request
for a runaway?
Really?
Yep. That very day, right after you left.
A gaudy lady showed up
wanting us to find a runaway girl.
So who was it?
Satils Francois.
You know Shoppe Francois
in the East District?
She's the owner.
But if Ink was from a wealthy family,
would she really run away dressed
like she'd escaped an orphanage?
JOB REQUEST
SEARCH FOR MISSING CHILD
Be thankful I found someone to take
that runaway girl off your hands.
Thanks, Y'lla.
By the way, why's it
so quiet in here today?
Well, you're the only one who's showed up.
Really? That's unusual.
Because none of the others returned.
From where?
Haven't you heard?
Dein and Kahnis had a duel yesterday.
I had no idea. Who won?
Dein, apparently.
Why apparently?
Kahnis and his hangers-on never came back.
Only Dein.
So he won by default.
Only Dein remained,
and none of the others returned?
What does that even mean?
No entry past this point.
If you want to get to the
other side, take a detour.
Can't you let us through?
I'm just trying to visit
my brother on the other side.
Forget about it!
Nobody can go through here.
But why?
Is there something in there
you don't want us to see?
Ugh, what's that stench?
Something smells rotten.
Gotta be a corpse or something.
Master?
Milkit.
I'm happy this fits me just right!
Great.
I got a similar one for Sara too, but...
She's not coming today either?
She must be busy with Church work.
Oh...
I'm worried about her.
REALITY
TRUTH
TRUTH AND REALITY
I'm looking for a girl named Sara.
She should be here.
Wait...
You know her?
Did something happen to her?
Where is she?
Sara was excommunicated yesterday.
On orders from the pope.
She was banished as a demon-worshiper.
Obviously, that's a lie. It's all a sham.
Sara would never do anything of the sort.
But I don't know where she is.
She'll be put on trial at this rate.
Please tell me you're okay, Sara...
Um, I'd like to meet Ed and Jonny.
Those two aren't here anymore.
They were transferred out
yesterday morning.
Yesterday?
That's so sudden.
I bet they were disappeared.
Ed... Jonny...
Sara...
Where did you all go?
Sara got excommunicated,
and Ed and Jonny were transferred?
What's going on here?
Oh, I bet Ottilie knows something.
Huh?
Ottilie isn't here right now.
If anything, I'd like to ask you
if you know where she went.
Even you don't know, General Henriette?
The royal army does not enjoy
the trust of His Majesty.
Rather, even the Lieutenant General
can be erased without hesitation
if she is adjudged
to have defied the Church.
Ottilie was saying she wanted
to unmask the real Church.
I asked her to.
The responsibility is all mine.
She said something when I met her last.
I think I'll be able to come back
with good news before long.
She probably had a lead of some sort.
How reckless of her.
She's never changed. Not then, not now.
She always clung to me like my own shadow.
She even trained in the sword
when it wasn't her forte.
If I hadn't been general,
I could've responded to her feelings.
Sara and Ottilie both suspected
the Church of wrongdoing.
And knowing Ed and Jonny, they would've
done anything to protect Sara.
Ultimately, I dragged them all
into this mess.
It's all my fault, huh?
Master... Master...
Master!
Are you all right?
Milkit...
They're all gone...
and it's all my fault.
I'm so awful.
I'm sorry, Milkit.
I'm such a useless master.
Before Milkit even thought to comfort her,
her body was already moving.
Milkit?
Milkit...
You've done nothing wrong.
Milkit... But...
Ottilie, Sara, Ed, and Jonny—
people who were good to me—
all got taken out by the Church.
And Dein's probably involved in it all.
He really has it out for me.
They all got targeted because of me.
I can't go on anymore.
Sorry... I'm so sorry, Milkit.
Sorry I'm such a useless master.
Master.
I never knew that cooking
was such a joyful thing.
Nor did I know that doing the dishes,
the laundry, and shopping could be so fun.
Only after I met you did everything
in my life take on a whole new light.
You are the one who gave me everything.
I wouldn't be rid of the
toxin marring my face,
I wouldn't have come to love this brand,
and I wouldn't be here right now
if it weren't for you.
You are my hero, Master!
So please, don't call yourself useless.
Okay... Thank you,
Milkit.
Not just Sara, but Ottilie too?
I think they learned something about
the Church they weren't supposed to,
and that was why...
No, stop! I have to get a grip!
This Satils woman who's looking for Ink
might be connected to the Church.
I have to keep Ink safe.
PAELLA
BROCCOLI AND TOMATO SALAD
Say, Flum. Is Sara not
joining us tonight either?
Ink...
Don't you think it's about time
you told us the truth?
But I have amnesia—
We already know that's a lie.
Please don't lie to us anymore, Ink.
When I went to the Guild today,
I found that someone who claims to be your
parent has a search request out for you.
No way! Mother would never look for me!
Mother? Is that what you call Satils?
Are you okay, Milkit?
P-Pardon me.
I'm fine. I'm sorry.
Ink, tell us about this "Mother."
If I tell them anything,
I'll be sent back there.
I don't want to go back.
I'll get scolded real bad.
After all, I left without permission.
No...
No!
I want to stay here!
I want to stay with them!
At least tell us about
your medicine, then.
I told you, I'm not taking any.
Ink has a heart defect.
She needs medicine,
but I've never seen her take any.
If she's run out, her life's in danger.
Mother told me to take it every day.
This is the first time
I've gone so long without taking it,
but nothing's wrong with me, Eterna.
That's good.
Thanks for telling us, Ink.
Aren't you going to scold me?
Nope. I'd rather respect your wishes.
Sorry, Eterna.
I'm sorry I lied.
Ink told us everything after that.
You're part of a family of seven,
you're ten years old,
and you have four younger,
non-blood-related siblings?
Yup.
Were all of you made to take that drug?
No. I was told only I needed it,
because I'm first-generation.
"First-generation"?
Yup. The rest can all talk to Papa.
Did they not let you see him?
No. They didn't let any of us.
But the others can hear his voice.
Telepathy?
They probably came to hear
a voice as their powers grew.
It wasn't just a hallucination?
Yeah. They were all mean to me
because I couldn't hear it.
Well, I only realized recently
that they were being mean to me.
Because Flum, Eterna, Milkit, and Sara...
You're all so nice and warm.
I mean it. I was the only one
they never took outside.
So this is my first time being outside
and meeting people other than my family.
Ink, thanks for telling us.
It must've been painful.
It's okay.
Hey, is it my fault that Sara's gone away?
Will she come back
now that I've told the truth?
Yeah, she'll be back.
Thanks, Ink.
Thank goodness.
Okay, let's eat.
Yeah!
By the way, Ink, why "Mother" and "Papa"?
Is that not what people out here say?
It's usually either Mama and Papa
or Mother and Father.
That, or we use names.
I don't know Mother's name,
but I do know Papa's.
He's called Origin.
Origin...
Assuming the supernatural being
called Origin really did exist,
why was it targeting her?
PAY F0R Y0UR SINS FLUM APRIC0T
FLUM APRICOT
Flum was besieged
by a fear of the unknown.
Oh, Eterna? Having trouble sleeping?
I was double-checking what to do
if worst comes to worst.
Is this about Ink?
Ink's heart isn't beating.
Huh?
Hey, Sheitoom.
I haven't seen Neigass around
these past few days.
She visiting the kingdom again?
Yes, that's right.
She just got back from there.
How devoted can you be?
She must've found
something of value there.
I can't wait to see
what she brings back this time.
Then I guess I'll go play with them
a bit before she gets back.
The heroes' party?
I hear another one left them.
Huh? Who?
The taciturn knight.
Gadhio? Is that true?
Come on, there's only four of them now.
Her heart isn't beating?
All I can do is leave
Ink in Eterna's hands.
Ed and Jonny? Yeah, I saw them running
toward the bridge. Seemed in a real hurry.
Right. They were with that blonde nun.
Yeah, I got there late,
and nobody was there.
It reeked of flesh
somethin' awful, though.
Sara and those two came here?
So they got mixed up in Dein's duel?
Hmm?
Is this...
Clearly signs of a battle, right?
Oh, you're Mr. Leitch's little sister.
Yep, Welcy.
Are you looking for Sara?
Do you know anything?
Everyone who went to watch the duel
went missing all of a sudden.
Something big must've gone down for sure.
Look, the ground's been scratched up.
Yeah, and even the walls.
All slashes of different
depths and widths...
Meaning they weren't caused
by the same blade.
Somebody must've used magic.
At the very least, it wasn't Sara.
She fights with a mace.
What kind of battle could've caused this?
I came here thinking I might
find a lead on the Church,
but I don't think I'll find anything else.
Oh, yeah. You said you were trying to find
who was smuggling herbs to the Church.
Yeah. I was able to identify the culprit.
Who was it?
Satils Francois.
Huh?
Got no evidence to back it up yet, though.
Anyway, I should go.
The lady calling herself Ink's parent
has connections to the Church?
Yeah.
So, Eterna...
I want you to teach me magic.
Well, that came out of nowhere.
If she finds out where Ink is,
she'll come to take her back.
Who knows what she's plotting?
I want the power to protect Milkit
and all of you with my own hands.
Flum. Magic is all about visualization.
Create a clear vision in your mind
and project it onto the matter before you.
Picture it...
Then you need only say the words
that come naturally to mind.
I'm beat.
Milkit.
Let's go shopping now
so that Flum can rest.
Right.
Heya.
Long time no see,
mummy girl.
Dein.
So this is Dein?
Yeah. And wow.
Didn't think I'd find you
cheating on your master
with the hero Eterna Rinebow
of all people.
Shut your mouth, scumbag.
Why are you here?
Don't you want to know
the secret behind the children?
The children?
That girl Ink and her ilk, of course.
They're monsters. Got those dark
crystals embedded right in 'em.
You're housing one hell of a calamity!
Master! It's an emergency!
Miss Eterna...
E-Eterna?
She's under attack by eyeballs—
Wow, you're sopping wet! What happened?
Um...
You'll catch a cold!
Give me a sec. Where are the towels...
Huh?
Milkit? Why'd you turn off the lights?
Huh? Milkit?
Milkit?
Where are you?
Milkit!
Why? What's going on?!
She was just here!
Milkit!
Where'd you go?
Milkit?
Where are you?
Milkit!
Where did you go?
I'm home.
Huh?
Ink?
No... No...
No!
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
DEIN AND FLUM