Hello? This is Nishino.
This is the To-Ou Medical
University Hospital.
Your family member, Tsuyoshi Nishino-san,
has been hospitalized.
What?
He's currently being examined
and treated here at the hospital.
But we're calling to ask that a
family member come to the hospital
so we can explain the patient's condition
and discuss future treatment options.
Emergency Entrance
Nishino-san!
Sir! Can you hear me?
You're in the hospital.
Everything will be all right.
Kashiwagi. Do you know him?
Yes.
Please put me on your team, Sensei.
Emergency Entrance
Um, I'm Mizuho Nishino.
I received a call saying my
father's been hospitalized here.
Emergency Room Reception
Please wait a moment.
Mizuho!
Shin!
Thank goodness I caught you
before the surgery.
Shin, how's my dad?
He's stable.
He'll be better once
we perform the surgery.
Okay...
It's okay. Don't worry.
I was added to the treatment team
and will be there during the operation.
You will?
Why do you think I became
a doctor in the first place?
Shin!
I entrust my father to you.
I've worked relentlessly since that day.
I'm not who I was back then.
Now... I can help her.
I'm not letting Mizuho go
through those feelings again.
Mom... Please save Dad...
Airu
Incoming call...
Airu? Why are you calling so suddenly?
I heard from Syugo! Is your dad okay?
He's in surgery right now...
I'm waiting for them to finish.
Mizuho... How are you doing?
I'm sorry I can't be by your side.
It's okay.
I'm feeling relieved
just hearing your voice.
Thank you.
I should have delayed my return to London.
Wait.
Are you alone right now?
Yeah...
I was so frazzled... I was only
able to contact Syugo about this.
I see...
Then what about Shin?
You're at Shin's hospital, right?
I am. Shin's able to be in the
operating room with my dad.
Is that so? Then that's a relief.
Huh?
We of all people know
how great Shin-chan is.
Right?
It's gonna be okay. Don't worry.
Yeah. You're right.
I'll have faith and wait.
Thanks, Airu.
Yup.
Hm?
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Syugo
I contacted Kizuki, too.
But he hasn't responded.
He might be at practice.
I contacted Kizuki, too.
But he hasn't responded.
He might be at practice.
Ugh. That swimming-obsessed idiot.
Do your best, Shin-chan.
I leave the rest to you.
Yes.
Good work, Kashiwagi.
Thank you very much!
Thank god.
He'll be okay...
I'm so glad that he'll be okay.
Shin!
I came to tell you
that the surgery's complete.
It's a success.
Thank goodness...
He's still asleep from the anesthesia.
But he should be awake
by tomorrow afternoon.
Okay.
He'll be better in no time.
Yeah.
Thank you for saving my dad.
Mizuho. Do you have some time?
Hm?
I... There's something
I need to tell you.
Kizuki
Incoming call...
Emergency Entrance
Kizuki!
I'm sorry I couldn't come sooner.
I just heard the voicemail
Syugo left me...
You came all the way to the hospital
after hearing that?
Yeah. I was worried about you.
You could have at least
used an umbrella...
But thanks.
So... How's your dad?
His heart surgery was successful.
We just need to monitor him
for the next few days.
There's no need to worry now.
I see. I'm glad.
As expected of you, Shin.
Yeah.
I'm sure my dad would be surprised to
hear that Shin took part in his surgery.
Are you going home, Mizuho?
I can take you.
Oh. I was thinking of staying by Dad's
side until he regains consciousness.
Then I can stay with you.
Only family members can be in the ICU.
I'll drop Mizuho off at her house later.
You should go home.
You'll catch a cold if you stay like that.
Nishino-san.
Yes?
Sorry to interrupt you.
There're a few things we need to explain
regarding your father's
hospitalization paperwork.
Thank you for that. I'll be right there.
Thanks for coming, Kizuki.
My dad and I will be fine now.
Okay.
Let me know if there's
anything I can help you with.
I'll see you later, Mizuho.
Uh-huh. Thanks again, Shin.
I'm glad Mizuho's not crying.
You just don't know about it.
I'm leaving Mizuho
and her dad in your care.
Yeah.
Kizuki. I'd never let Mizuho cry.
Nor would I ever make her worry.
I'll use my own ways to make her happy.
Yeah. But...
I won't lose to you when it comes
to wanting Mizuho to be happy.
Jeez... Sorry to worry you two.
This isn't a laughing matter, Dad!
You really scared us!
Sorry, sorry.
We'll check on you
for two to three weeks.
If nothing else arises,
you can be released.
Thanks, Shin-kun.
Never thought I'd see the day
you'd be the one to save me.
Shin was very dependable, you know?
Oh, that's right.
I'm going to call everyone real quick.
Okay.
Sir.
Hm?
Do you remember what
I told you in the past?
What?
I'm a doctor, just like I said I'd be.
Uh...?
If I become a doctor in the future...
Can I propose to Mizuho?
Shin-kun?!
Well then, please rest up
for the next few days.
How can I rest up after that?
Hey.
Hm?
I need to tell you something, Shin.
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Everything okay at work?
Yeah. Anyway, here.
Oh! A fruit sandwich!
They're not the ones
from the Enoki store, though.
You haven't eaten anything
since yesterday, right?
You'll get carsick if you don't eat.
Thanks, Shin!
Don't mind if I do!
Yummy!
This is just what I needed
for my weary bones.
You're exaggerating.
Kashiwagi-sensei!
Are you going home already?
Sensei! Who's this?
Your girlfriend?
What?! No!
Shin-sensei is my boyfriend!
Right? Sensei?
Whatever you say.
I know you feel better,
but don't run around too much.
Aw, but...
A paper airplane?
This one won't fly at all.
That's why I'm making it fly by running.
Sorry, Mizuho.
Can you wait a little bit longer?
What?
I'm going to teach them
how to make a paper airplane.
Wow!
Sensei! Me next!
You'll get your turn.
Aw. It fell almost instantly again.
Shin's paper airplane flies the farthest.
What makes it any different from ours?
It's gotta be something with his brain.
You guys are folding it wrong.
I wish all of ours
could fly far together.
All right, fine.
I'll show you how it's done.
Mizuho, come here.
Lucky us!
Thanks, Shin!
Thanks!
Pay attention.
Use the center fold line to fold
the left and right sides symmetrically.
Then you raise the angle
of the wings up a little.
I did it!
Okay. Let's fly them all together!
'Kay!
All together!
Wow!
We did it!
Nice!
Back then, I thought all of us
could fly anywhere together forever.
But...
Whoa! Cool!
The things you do don't change
even when you're an adult, Shin.
What was that?
Even if we fly them at the same time,
they each end up going
in different directions.
In the past, I clearly knew
what path I wanted to take.
I had no worries.
But I can't say the same
now that I'm an adult.
Did something happen?
Now's the time to choose
what I'm going to specialize in.
The more things I know,
the more possibilities I can see.
No matter what path you take,
I'm sure you'll do fine, Shin.
I'll be cheering you on.
Yeah. Thanks.
Wow, way to go, Shin-chan.
Yeah. Shin seemed really
confident last night.
Well, of course he is.
He's handsome, a doctor,
and on top of that,
he saved Mizuho's dad's life.
You, on the other hand, are a nobody.
You're an unemployed swimmer.
Any normal girl wouldn't choose you.
Can't you say one good thing about me?
Well... How about this?
The fact you can tackle things
straight on without a thought.
I feel like that's not a compliment.
It's totally a compliment.
Well, just do your best, buddy.
Yeah. I'll contact you again later.
Kizuki... Hurry up and open your eyes.
Okay!
I lost to that straightforward
personality of yours.
I wonder if that's everything?
This too, Mizuho.
I brought things that could
be useful for the bathroom.
Thanks. You're a great help!
Then let's get going.
Uh-huh.
A photo?
I'm sure your dad will like that.
Yup. He won't be lonely
if Mom's with him.
Sorry to keep you.
Oh. Do you remember that card?
Nope.
I bet you got rid of yours.
I don't know about that.
That's an illustration card
I made for the Ao High festival.
You helped me a ton
during those times, too.
Because you worked so hard, we were
able to make precious memories.
I'm really grateful for that.
We all worked hard for that.
I suppose.
Let's get going, Mizuho.
Okay.
So pretty...
Seeing the ocean really calms me.
Yeah.
I've been thinking a lot
about you lately, Shin.
I wanted to thank you properly.
Not just about my dad, but also
how you've supported me all this time.
Shin, I...
That card.
What?
Even to this day, it's displayed
in my locker at the hospital.
That day, being in the classroom
with you, Mizuho...
Hey, Shin.
Let's remember this moment forever.
September 18th. 5:20 PM.
Shin and I were in an Ao High classroom.
Hold onto that card
as a reminder of today.
Yeah.
That's a precious memory of mine.
I didn't think you'd cherish it so much.
When we were students,
I watched over you and your studies.
At first, I thought it was just something
for my own satisfaction. But...
I'm glad I went to Ao High.
You're amazing, Shin.
You actually became student
council president, too.
You said it yourself:
"Shin would be
the student council president."
Oh!
Is that from when we all
celebrated getting into Ao High?
The bows on Ao High's
uniforms were so cute!
Are you joining the swim club, Kizuki?
Yup. What'll you do, Shin?
Huh? Me? Hmm...
What about student council president?
Ooh, right! Nice one, Mizuho.
I don't have time for that.
There you go again with that.
You're such a boring guy.
C'mon! Live a little!
Mizuho, Kizuki!
Hold onto Shin's legs!
Roger that!
Alley oop!
What are you guys doing?
We're soaked!
That's what I'm talking about!
Now this is adolescence!
Sorry, Shin.
I'm just happy that
I could be with you again.
I'm sorry for back then.
You'd just been rejected
from your #1 choice school,
yet I said I was so happy.
Don't worry about it.
Plus, I wasn't rejected.
What?
I wanted to be with you and everyone
else. So I pretended I failed.
No way! You turned down
the Seikai High School?!
My life's always been
guided by you, Mizuho.
By me?
When you lost your mother...
You looked like you
were in so much pain...
I didn't want you to make
that face ever again.
I wanted to be someone who could save
the lives of the people in your life.
I didn't realize... Even though
I've been by your side this whole time.
I can do anything for you.
Remember what I told you when
we went on that gondola together?
I've already set my heart
on being with you.
So when you're ready too, tell me.
Yeah. I was really surprised.
Even when I knew about
Kizuki's feelings for you...
And when you two started dating...
I've decided to go out with Kizuki.
I couldn't give up on you, Mizuho.
I can't imagine a life without you.
I love you, Mizuho.
I live for you, and want to
keep living for you.
I want to be happy with you.
Will you marry me?
Translation:
Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Karen Bildsoe
Mariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
S Bilyeu
Michelle Tymon
# 24 Anyway, I'm Falling in Love with You.