'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Curry Mix
All right, then.
Let's begin making the torture implement.
Yes! I'm ready to learn!
Form a claw with your left hand.
Cut the carrots
into one-centimeter rounds.
Say, Sakura-chan.
Yes?
Have you considered applying to become
a pain-private in the near future?
What?!
Your training period's about to end,
so I think it's the perfect time.
I'm not a demon, so do
I stand any chance of getting in?
Most certainly.
I've seen all of the hard
work you've been putting in.
Me, an inquisitor...
There's no need to fret so much.
To become a pain-private, simply submit
the form with all the required fields.
Oh, that said...
The application requires that you write
down a torture you're proficient in.
What will you choose?
Anything in particular you fancy?
Actually...
There's one torture I wanted to try.
Oh? What is it?
Senpai, do you have
some free time tomorrow?
Tomorrow?
I'd like to give it a shot
before I fill everything out...
Or well, I want you to take
a look at my torture...
I want you to be my first torture victim!
'Twould be an honor!
Sakura's
Apartment
All my life, I've done nothing
but obey orders.
I never gave any thought
as to what I wanted.
The only thing I knew was assassination,
and all I could do was make people suffer.
I never imagined I could be cut out
to entertain them through torture.
However...
after learning about torture from Senpai,
she made me realize all the
different things I was capable of doing.
Take a good look, Senpai...
at what I've chosen
for the first time, all by myself.
My first torture.
Senpai, it's time for your torture!
My street performance torture...
Please enjoy it!
Where'd that apple come from?
What?!
She's keeping the apple in the air by
throwing the knives she's juggling at it,
while peeling it at the same time?!
S...
Sakura-chan, that was amazing!
Huh?
Wait... Surely not...
You were still saving your best trick?!
Hah!
Wow!
Senpai! What'd you think of my torture?
That was incredible, Sakura-chan.
It was so thrilling,
I almost forgot it was torture!
I really enjoyed it!
Thanks a lot!
Sakura's pain-private
application
Was submitted
Princess...
Your torture's been canceled.
Huh?
What's the meaning of this?
Remember our conversation the other day ?
Oh, yeah.
What animals do you like
that haven't shown up in a torture yet?
Penguins!
So I asked a penguin I know to come all
the way here for today's torture...
Hellbeast Penguin
But we've been having
a nasty heatwave in Hellholm,
so he can't make it.
Hellbeast penguins don't
do well in the heat.
Poor thing!
That's a shame, but
the penguin's health comes first.
Thanks, Princess.
Your Highness, you like penguins
as well as hamsters?
Yeah.
The way they waddle.
Their cute, round eyes.
Their gentle faces.
I fell in love with them at a penguin show
I saw at the aquarium as a kid.
Penguins!
Penguin Show
Seeing them shuffle to and fro.
Cheering them on when they mess up.
Get up! You can do it!
Their laid-back attitudes.
Pick yourself back up!
So adorable.
Penjamin couldn't make it, but he's
the Northern Demon World Aquarium's star!
Oh, wow.
The cream of the crop, huh?
I'll have him come some
other time when it's cooler.
Yeah!
I can't wait to meet him!
Hold your horses!
Some other time?
You can't be serious, ladies.
The hellbeast penguin, Penjamin...
is right here, baby!
What? Penjamin?!
Sorry I'm a teensy bit late.
You're covered in sweat!
You came all this way in this heat?
No heat's gonna stop me
from helping out my buddy Krall!
Penjamin!
Alrighty, Krall.
We can't keep our
audience waiting any longer.
Time to look alive.
Let's get this penguin show on the road!
The Penjamin Show
First up, we have this trick!
A-one, a-two, a-three!
And next is this!
Hup, hup, hup!
But there's more!
Now it's time for the grand finale!
Penjamin!
Are you okay?
Don't push yourself like this!
Shaddup!
You expect me to stop in
the middle of a show?!
If I die here on stage, then so be it!
Penjamin...
Here I go!
Take a good gander!
Penjamin's going for the hurdle jump!
Hah!
Yeah!
You did it!
That was amazing, Penjamin!
How do you like them apples?!
The Penjamin Show
What'd you think of Penjamin's
penguin show, Princess?
Not what I expected, really.
But she felt bad
So she confessed
anyway
Penjamin!
Oh, is that you, Hamungous?
How's it going?
I heard you were here,
so I came to take a look.
I forgot the two of you were pals.
Yeah.
We worked at the same Chinese restaurant
before we got our big break.
You haven't gotten rusty?
Perish the thought!
Try some of my pepper steak for yourself!
Here you are!
Looks great!
Oh, not too shabby.
Please try some, Penjamin!
You know I can't eat pepper steak,
on account of being a penguin and all.
Oh, that's right.
You can have both plates then, Krall.
Eh?
It looks good, but two whole plates?!
How about I show off
some of my skills, too?
Hooray!
You're still the master
of making fried rice, Penjamin!
There we go!
That looks amazing!
That's all of it!
It was delicious, but I'm stuffed!
But you know...
Oh, right.
You can't eat fried rice,
being a hamster and all.
T-Time to chow down...
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Man, I'm bored.
Why don't you work out, then?
Ugh, what a pain.
You say that now...
Don't come crying when you get a flabby
belly after all that eating and sleeping.
Little Princess.
Master Mama!
Huh? Are you feeling down?
You're walking with
a heavier gait than usual.
Impressive, Little Princess.
You noticed that?
I am Commander of the
Imperial Third Legion.
I can easily glean information
from the sound of someone's footsteps.
Oh, that's amazing.
I wish she could've seen
Her Highness just moments ago.
Truth be told...
This morning, I broke my favorite mug,
and it's been one small mistake
after another at work.
Today's just not my day.
Oh, I've had days like those.
So I'm taking off work early today...
and going on an adventure!
An adventure?
An adventure where I go down the streets
I always pass by but have never taken
to see where all of those turns lead me.
Wow, sounds like fun!
Care to join me?
Yeah, I'll go!
It's lit a fire in her heart?!
The water's so clear.
It sure is.
There's a paddy field nearby.
Is that what this irrigation canal's for?
Ah! I see it!
Oh, it went your way!
Huh? Wait, where?
Right next to you!
I don't see it at all!
It's a little warm today,
so I bet that feels great.
Yeah.
Oh, right there!
Okay, it's ours!
Awesome, we got it!
Did you catch something?
A crab!
Oh, very nice.
You can find crabs here?
Yeah.
Ricefish as well.
Wow!
Catch you later!
Bye-bye!
What a pretty bird.
So cute!
Little Princess, do you like birds?
Yeah.
But it's not like
I know what they're called.
So I usually try not to mention it.
You don't have to be an expert
to say you like something.
Liking things isn't a competition.
Yeah, you're right.
I like birds!
What a funny-looking staircase.
You said it!
Let's climb to the top!
Climb, climb!
We sure have walked a lot.
This has been fun.
Yeah.
That reminds me
that I was feeling down today.
All this fun on my adventure
with Little Princess made me forget.
Master Mama!
I haven't been tortured yet today,
and I forgot to get permission to go out,
so I let Torture know where I was.
Right, since you're a prisoner.
And Torture just told me about a place
with great tea around here!
She said I can go visit it!
Oh?
That's awesome.
Oh, my.
Gonna check it out now!
What an adorable bird.
The Next Day
An experimental spell went haywire...
turning the princess into a bird!
Surrend!
You fiend! What's the meaning of this?!
Return Her Highness
to her old self at once!
I'm terribly sorry.
We're looking into it now
but have yet to determine the cause.
Say it ain't so...
It breaks my heart
to see Her Highness like this.
Surrend! Surrend!
It must be a terrible
inconvenience being stuck like that.
Unable to even talk properly...
She can't reveal any secrets like this,
so maybe this is better for the empire.
No, don't think like that, Ex!
There's no way that Her Highness
is better off this way!
Why is she a bird, anyway?!
I really don't have an answer for that.
Perhaps because she's fond of birds?
I see...
Surrend.
No, that can't be it!
And wait, Her Highness likes birds?
That's news to me!
It seems she mentioned it during
her adventure with Giant yesterday.
She even sent me a photo of a cute bird.
What?
Was I the only one who wasn't told?
Maybe Her Highness really
is better off this way...
Surrend! Surrend!
Here's some food
for the time being, Princess.
I'm not sure what you can eat,
so here are some nuts I've ground up.
Surrend.
Surrend, surrend.
She's eating it!
What a relief. Do you like it?
Surrend! Surrend!
She's practically a pet now.
The vast majority of polar
bears are left-handed.
No way! She's folding even in this state?
Why is she giving in as a bird?
Did Her Highness retain full sentience?
No, she can hardly be considered aware
and is acting mostly by instinct.
She's surrendering by instinct?!
This is bad!
She could turn into an endless
surrender machine at this rate!
Fear not, Ex.
I won't report any information
gained outside of a torture session.
Going by the book!
Our top priority right
now should be the princess.
Thank goodness Torture is our inquisitor!
I wanna eat something sweet.
You could learn a thing
from her, Your Highness!
Something sweet?
What kind of sweet food can a bird eat?
Gâteau au chocolat.
She's got a big attitude for a bird
with no sentience.
I'm sorry, Princess.
A bird's digestive system cannot
process gâteau au chocolat.
Surrend?!
Surrend! Surrend! Surrend!
I can prepare it for you
when you've returned to your old body.
Surrend!
What's going on? Could it be?
Her craving for gâteau au chocolat...
has broken the spell and
is returning her to her original self?!
Her gluttony knows no bounds!
Not quite!
Surrend!
Biblical levels of gluttony!
I see...
Since it was her desire to eat
that broke the spell...
Only her body returned to normal.
So she could have a digestive system
that can process gâteau au chocolat.
Which means that if I offer her food
that a bird's head cannot eat...
That's it, Torture!
Your Highness!
Surrend?
Here's a tasty rice cracker.
You won't be able to eat this
with a bird's mouth.
Surrend?!
Surrend!
You did it!
It worked!
A smartphone emoji!
Let's just wait for
the Hellhorde to figure it out.
I suppose.
Surrend!
Demon World Ristorante e Caffè
Sayizatso
Hell-Lord Pharmacy
Prescriptions Filled Here
I'm sorry to keep you so late
with all my questions, Senpai.
Think nothing of it.
In return, I'll have
you treat me to dinner.
But of course!
Oh right, Senpai. Did you know?
Everyone says the spot-the-difference
puzzle in this kids' menu is really hard.
Oh, is that right?
Still, it's just a kids' menu.
I'm sure a grown-up
could solve it in no time.
Oh! Here it is.
Let's see here.
Torture Spot-the-Difference
Find
the 10
differences!
Torture Spot-the-Difference
Find
the 10
differences!
What if we end up finishing it
before our food arrives?
Torture Spot-the-Difference
Find
the 10
differences!
Torture Spot-the-Difference
Find
the 10
differences!
Thanks for waiting!
Your squid ink spaghetti
and Hamburg steak set.
Torture Spot-the-Difference
Find
the 10
differences!
Torture Spot-the-Difference
Find
the 10
differences!
Torture Spot-the-Difference
Find
the 10
differences!
Torture Spot-the-Difference
Find
the 10
differences!
Here! The hilt of the sword is longer!
You're right!
It's so conspicuous,
yet I didn't notice it at all!
The last one! I can't find
the last one for the life of me!
Let's look it up online.
Hold it, Sakura-chan!
Let me look a little longer.
That's right.
Senpai always gives her full effort.
That attitude is what's
behind those flawless tortures of hers.
Despite her experience,
she never phones it in for a torture.
She always tackles it
with the utmost sincerity.
That's the Senpai I admire!
I'll see it through to the end with you!
Huh?
Thanks, Sakura-chan.
Demon World Ristorante e Caffè
Sayizatso
Hell-Lord Pharmacy
Prescriptions Filled Here
Just before closing time, Torture
and Sakura found all of the differences.