EPISODE 09: THE JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES
HAS A BAD FEELING
Come on, get seated.
The meeting's about to start.
I can't believe I get to go
dungeon-delving with my comrades again...
I can't betray everyone's
expectations for me,
after they've let me join them.
About today's plans...
The Adventure Management Division has
asked us to collect Noxious Sheep pelts.
We'll be practicing our
teamwork on Floor 86...
I'll make sure we all get to Floor 94,
so we're equal with the Heroes Party!
We will begin our exploration of Floor 86!
It's the lower floors
of the Great Dungeon,
but the scenery's so nice
it makes you want to relax.
Every floor above us is
just caves, after all.
One of the great things about reaching
the lower floors is the different
scenery you can enjoy.
No letting your guard down.
Our goal is the Noxious Sheep,
but there's lots of tough
Earth Dragons down here too.
Once again, our major goal here
is to see how we work with Orhun.
Glad to have you here, Orhun.
Yeah, glad to be here.
Wil's job will be to keep
the monsters' attention.
Rain will attack from the rear with magic.
Roger that!
Lucre, join the attack, but make sure
you've got healing magic ready to go.
Okay!
I'll keep everyone buffed
and give the orders.
And Orhun, you stay at
the front as an attacker.
Got it.
You can probably defeat all
the monsters yourself, Orhun.
Maybe we'll actually be slowing you down.
Orhun, if it's easier for you to just
fight on your own, I'm okay with that.
I'm a part of this party.
You can give me orders.
If Orhun's off on his own, we can't
learn to work with him, right?
That's right.
Sorry.
Don't space out on us, Boss.
That's not like you, Selma.
Watch out!
Orhun!
This attack...
An Earth Dragon.
I don't see it.
We have to find it, first.
Leave it to me.
I've got Magic Tracking!
Magic Tracking?
It's her special ability.
She can follow traces of
magic to locate her foe.
Found it!
Flash!
My turn, then.
Watch me, Orhun!
Yeah... It's better that you
see our strength for yourself.
Rain, prepare to attack.
Magic Up!
Hah-yah!
Well? Is that all you've got?
I'll fire off the big guns
to celebrate Orhun's arrival!
Explode!
That was fast.
Right?
Well, Orhun?
I'm surprised.
You work together incredibly well.
You're being so polite again.
I was just so impressed.
I'm surprised that he didn't just
block the attack, he canceled it.
That double blade is a weapon
that barely anyone can use, too.
And the way she was able to construct
a special-rank skill like
Explode at that speed...
It would've taken most
casters twice as long.
And Lucre's Magic Tracking
is amazing, too.
The hardest part of any dungeon
dive is finding the monsters.
You could say it's
indispensable for a party.
And Selma's leadership abilities
bring them together.
They're an ideal party.
Why are you staring at me?
I was just thinking how
impressive you and Unit 1 are.
Aw, we're not that special...
Selma's blushing!
Lucre!
Looks like we woke up
some sleeping kiddos.
Two of them, huh?
Perfect. Let's practice our teamwork.
Let's go, Orhun.
Yeah.
Wh-What's wrong?
Rock Arrow!
A Hiding Turtle?
Good catch, Orhun.
This is bad. We're trapped between
it and the Earth Dragons.
Hiding Turtles have tough
shells, but move slow.
Rain, Lucre, you handle it.
Roger!
Wil, Orhun, take down the Earth Dragons!
Don't worry about what's behind you!
Got it!
Her decisions and orders came fast.
She's somebody you can trust.
Leave it to me!
Go around to the side, Orhun.
Selma?
This is my special ability, Telepathy.
I can communicate from a distance.
What? That's incredibly useful!
Th-Thank you...
Target the Earth Dragons' blind spot!
Buff yourself how you want.
I'll let you decide.
Roger!
Wil, keep them distracted!
I know that, Boss!
Stop calling me that!
Rain, how's it looking?
It's just a turtle with a tough shell.
We're fine. Leave it to us.
Selma's special ability is incredible.
It's what I wanted most of all
when I was in the Heroes Party.
Strength Up!
Technical Up!
Sharpness Up!
I'm in position!
Match the timing with Wil!
Five seconds until attack.
Four, three, two...
Orhun, go for it!
Impact!
So that's "Impact"?
It's amazing!
It's because you lured them
into position for me. Thanks.
How's the Hiding Turtle?
Wrapping up!
Mjölnir!
Ice Javelin!
Good work, everyone.
We're done.
Orhun, that was pretty good for
your first time working with us.
It was great.
It's been forever since
fighting was this easy for me.
Easier than when you were
in the Heroes Party?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm so glad I was able to join you.
That makes us happy.
I'm happy too.
We're all helping each other.
That's normal for a party, but...
I'd almost forgotten
how much fun it was...
You're amazing, too!
That "Impact" spell was amazing!
I've never seen anyone cut clean
through two Earth Dragons before!
Thanks.
Orhun, may I ask a question?
Sure.
From your perspective,
are we ready for Floor 92?
Yes, of course.
Because you're here?
No.
I think you could defeat the
Black Dragon without me.
Really?
I mean it.
Your strength is enough
to make me believe that.
Thank you.
We've worked as hard as we
could for the past year...
But we didn't know if it
had amounted to anything.
But hearing it from the dragonslayer
makes me believe it!
They've probably practiced incredibly
hard since losing Albert.
I'm sure that they're strong enough
now to beat the Black Dragon.
But the Black Dragon is strong.
Incredibly strong.
Seeing its strength during the teaching
expedition reminded me of that.
I don't want to lose anyone else.
I don't want any more deaths.
So please, fight with us.
We want your help.
Of course.
I'm a part of Unit 1 too.
Defeating the Black Dragon
is Unit 1's long-held wish.
And I swore I'd protect my comrades
to the end no matter what.
Right?
Thank you, Orhun.
Okay, all that's left is
to hunt some Noxious Sheep!
Let's finish it up and go home.
Yeah!
The air on the surface smells so good!
How many Noxious Sheep
did we end up killing?
Nine in total, I think.
Orhun did a great job
of collecting the pelts,
so the mission was a success.
You did a great job on that, Orhun!
Thanks!
Lucre couldn't do it that cleanly.
You'd do it even worse than me!
I can do it a million
times better than you.
Selma, I'm supposed to go see the
Adventure Management Division tomorrow.
Could you tell me where it is later?
What? Did you want me
to go with you, then?
Would you?
I need to report the
mission's success, too.
If you're free in the morning,
let's meet up and go.
Now then, Orhun!
Welcome to the Night Sky
Silver Rabbits' Unit 1!
Cheers!
Thanks, everyone.
No, thank you.
After you defeated the Black Dragon,
any number of places would want you.
I'm grateful you came to us.
We need to do our best so
he doesn't regret it, huh?
Regret it? No way...
I had such fun in the
dungeon with this party.
I want to continue helping everyone.
That makes me so happy!
I'm also glad that you're a lot easier
to talk to than I thought you'd be!
Hey! Why are you crying?!
Because I was a little worried
I wouldn't get along with Orhun!
So I'm really happy!
I was actually really nervous, too!
I wasn't sure I'd be able to
support you from the rear...
Me too!
If I couldn't work with you on the front
lines, I figured we'd be in trouble!
Aw, so all of us were worried?
You guys should've said something!
I was really nervous!
Well, you'd be nervous if you thought
you were the only one, right?
But you know, I bet Selma was
the most nervous of us all.
Yeah, you're right.
She'd taken a big interest
in Orhun, after all.
Wh-What are you saying?
Don't even bother to try and hide it.
She was a little too interested,
actually. So maybe...
A-As leader, I just
wanted to make sure he felt
comfortable here as soon as possible.
That's all. Right?
Yeah. I had a great time thanks to you.
I'm so glad you're the leader.
G-Good then.
The Boss gulped down her drink!
Hey, Selma!
Drink! Drink!
Hey, another round!
The Old Man always said regrets
come with any decision.
But right now I don't
regret joining this clan.
I just need to do my best
for my precious comrades.
Selma, are you okay?
Um...
You know...
You're such a handsome man, Orhun.
Stop joking around.
I'm serious.
Oh no...
If she gets close to me
with that expression...
It's impossible to play it cool!
You're wide open!
Selma, you're drunk!
I'm not drunk!
That's what drunk people say!
Orhun!
Yes?
Why not? You know, I...
I've been waiting for
this day for so long!
You're not getting away until morning.
Until morning?!
What are you doing?
Rain! Can you calm Selma down?
Okay, sure thing.
Let me join in.
Her too?!
Oh? You're trying to say I'm
not serious enough yet, huh?
That just made it even worse!
Orhun's super-popular!
A girl on each arm! Nice!
Help me, you two!
Now, now.
You're the star of the show today.
No matter what happens, we won't look.
Or we'll look, but we won't say anything!
I don't care whether or not
you look, just save me!
Her breasts...
Her breath...
It's so soft and warm...
What should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
Orhun...
It's all over...
I didn't want to have to do this, but...
Induce Sleep!
Whew...
Thank you, Selma.
It's been a long time since
I've had this much fun.
Sister's late...
I heard she was going into
the dungeon with Orhun.
But she can't still be
down there at this hour.
What is she doing?
Sister?
It's me.
Sorry to come at this hour...
Orhun's coming back at
this time of night? Why?
Is he here to see me?
No way...
I'm dressed like this...
What should I do? I'm embarrassed...
Sorry. Could you open the door?
Okay! Coming!
Hello...
What's going on here?
I can't believe my sister's coming
home in the morning, carried by Orhun!
I mean, it's night, but still.
Um, Sophia?
Orhun, when did your relationship
with my sister become like that?
"Like that?"
No! There's nothing between me and Selma!
Sorry for the misunderstanding.
She drank too much and passed out,
so I brought her home.
Is that so?
I was surprised.
I'm sorry.
My sister never gets this drunk.
She must've had a lot of fun today.
Orhun...
A lot of fun.
Sister, wake up!
Not yet...
Sister!
Sophia?
If you're awake, then why not climb down?
You're bothering Orhun, you know.
Sophia?!
You're going to tell me
what happened, right?
So you drank too much at
Orhun's welcome party?
Yes. I'm sorry.
He was smiling as he left,
but the way you were acting
must've really bothered him.
Yes. I'm sorry.
I feel really bad about it.
Oh, fine.
You've been really busy and under
a lot of stress lately, right?
You can finally relax now
that Orhun's here, I guess.
So you let yourself have
a bit too much fun, right?
I get it.
You'll forgive me?
There's nothing for me to forgive.
It's a little upsetting, but...
It's not right to get mad at you
because of these feelings...
But you know, be careful
from now on, okay?
No causing trouble for other people, okay?
Sophia!
She's such an angel!
No causing trouble for other people, okay?
Is my little sister an angel from heaven?
I'm so lucky to have an
angel for a little sister...
Is it worth crying over?!
You're exaggerating.
Sophia smiles so much
more than she used to.
And I don't think it's because of me.
It's because of Orhun.
I hate to admit it, but...
It feels so good...
Sophia's right.
I feel a little more relaxed.
It's thanks to Orhun.
But I still can't believe
he carried me home...
He must be exasperated with me.
I embarrassed myself so badly.
And in front of Sophia.
I need to be careful from now on
or Sophia will misunderstand again.
I should be supportive of my little
sister's first love, I'm sure.
As a good sister.
Why am I thinking about this stuff?
It's like I'm trying to convince myself.
But you know, I bet Selma was
the most nervous of us all.
Was I? Because of Orhun?
Wait, that's impossible!
It's true that I like him as a person.
And I look up to him as an adventurer.
But there's nothing more to it than that.
I don't... think there is...
I...
You know...
You're such a handsome man, Orhun.
Is that how I really feel?
No, no way.
Sheesh...
It's hard to focus.
Good morning, Selma.
Did I keep you waiting?
No... I'm sorry.
About yesterday. I feel really bad.
Well, you'd been drinking.
It's fine.
Let's both forget it.
Yeah.
Let's focus on the future.