I don't mind.
I'll let myself...
be a sacrifice for you.
In my place, please...
continue living to your heart's content.
And...
take the Magecraft society
that took everything from our clan...
and pulverize them!
Papa... Mama...
Oh, you have quite an interesting way
of putting up a struggle.
An Einzbern...
homunculus?
Why are you here?
My wounds...
Wha...
Here.
This is your Master, see?
You should hurry up and make the pact.
Good boy.
The path—
Self-sacrificial Magecraft...
wasn't uncommon back in my day.
But at the least,
make sacrificing yourself look fun.
Okay?
Th-This woman is...
not...
Wh-Wh-Who in the world are you—
Don't worry.
I may look like this,
but I like humans, okay?
Now that I'm here...
all of you humanity...
will be properly dominated!
Livestock to Deficit.
It seems you didn't attend
the scheduled report last night.
I was assaulted by Assassin
immediately after the summoning,
and I was passed out.
Oh, the one that assaulted
the police station.
I'm surprised you survived it.
Saber happened to be
there, and he saved me.
What?
He proposed a ceasefire afterward...
and I accepted.
The same goes for Assassin.
Then while you look into
more intel about them...
suggest a united front
to deal with the King of Heroes...
and the Lancer who is in line with him.
Humph.
Saber already...
seems to have formed
an alliance with that Lancer.
By the way, did you figure out
who your Heroic Spirit was?
Yes.
My Servant is—
Watch out.
Assassin is keeping watch behind you.
Chaplin.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Can you repeat that?
A Lancer. Charlie Chaplin.
That's the Servant I summoned.
I'll be asking him about his Noble
Phantasm among other things later.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
You're fine now. I don't
sense her anymore.
Why didn't you take spirit form
if you knew she was there?
Didn't I tell you?
We are nothing more than Shadows.
Only you, the Watcher's
Master, can see us.
Tell me stuff like that sooner, would you?
Hmm?
That look on your face... Are you angry?
You're such an easy read.
Anyway, my boy...
Chaplin, huh?
Why a comedian of all people?
He was the first to come to my mind
as someone of greatness.
Can I come in?
Who is it?
Classical comedy is your thing.
That's unexpected.
I've watched comedy multiple times
and appreciate it.
But I've never laughed
from the bottom of my heart.
Hey, you can come in!
Were you able to sleep
at least a little bit?
Yeah.
You were a lifesaver by
letting us use the room.
Thanks to that, Ayaka is feeling good now.
Um...
What's your name?
My name is Sigma.
I'm one of the Masters
of the Holy Grail War.
Did you figure out anything
about the case of that curse?
Nothing on that end yet.
However, I had a report that Halri Vorzak
is with an Einzbern homunculus...
and is heading toward
the industrial district.
Industrial district, huh?
Is she planning to make contact
with the demon from the Scladio Family?
So, is that the captain of the Argo?
What do you mean?
It's likely because we're connected
by Magical Energy paths,
but your memories are encroaching into me.
A noble-looking brat was mouthing off
fantasies about an ideal
nation atop a boat.
Hah!
Someone speaking flights of fancy
of that nature must be him.
A senseless man.
Why did a great hero like you
become an oarsman for him?
Indeed, he is a pitiful king
hell-bent on his desires,
and he was a king that
spoke of idiotic dreams.
However...
that is exactly why he is my friend.
I will not allow you...
someone who did not board that ship,
to mock him so lightheartedly.
I see. I understand now.
I won't apologize, but I promise
I will never bring up this topic again.
Mr. Cordelion!
What's wrong?
It's Ei... nzb...
...'s homonc... is her...
What does an Einzbern doll want with me?
Oh, dear.
You're covered in so much mud.
You're already halfway out the door
from your humanity?
Then, you wouldn't mind if I killed you...
together with that twisted
Heroic Spirit there, right?
Is that what the Einzberns want?
Einzberns? You mean the people
who created this container?
I was so lucky!
This container hardly had
any soul formed in it,
so I was able to possess it so easily.
It's as if it was created for
the purpose of being a vessel for a god.
A vessel for a god?
Are you saying that...
you are a god or something?
That's right!
A goddess, that is!
What're you doing?
You really have no manners.
You tried to shoot a god dead.
Self-proclaimed goddess,
why have you trampled into our base?
Oh, this is a Holy Grail War, right?
It's only natural to eradicate enemy
forces that don't strike your fancy.
Though, I'm neither Master nor Servant!
Th-The space is being transformed
into a labyrinth!
Oh! You finally deployed
your bounded field?
You're really taking your time here.
No, this is how it was meant to be used.
N-No way!
To be able to deploy a bounded field
on such a giant workshop...
and then transform it
into an underworld...
That's a composite artwork
of the Scladio Family.
It will be rather difficult...
even for an adept Mage
to get out of there.
Hmm, I see!
You can tell whoever made this
must be an unpleasant personality.
Was it on your order
that she came here, Halri Vorzak?
I-I...
I am...
Papa!
Mama!
We came here at Ms. Philia's suggestion.
I merely tagged along.
I see. So, that thing is called "Philia."
What is that thing?
The person who saved my life.
Stymphalian Birds?
I see. Not bad.
Ms. Philia!
Looking the other way?
Such confidence.
Hmm?
Oh, what a good little one.
Now, Halri!
You're the Master,
so hurry up and give your orders.
Huh?
I'm asking you. Who is your enemy?
If you let it be,
it will kill off everyone
other than you and me. Is that okay?
The enemy is...
this magical workshop!
Tear it down to pieces...
Berserker!
What is that?
Ms. Halri...
What in the world...
did you summon?
This is Ayaka.
My Master... she is not,
but she's my partner.
Nice to meet you... Sigma.
Yeah.
Oh...
I assume it'd be too much to ask
to introduce me to your Servant.
He called it "Chaplin."
Chaplin as in...
There was a movie at the
music club yesterday!
I definitely would like an introduction!
He says that actors are
to be seen in movies,
so he doesn't show himself in person.
I see.
I can agree to that.
You can?
He was contacting someone.
Who is the mastermind
pulling your strings?
Answer me!
Hold on!
What will you do, my boy?
I'm a mercenary, and I
was contacting my client.
What?
I can't say any further.
But...
I'd be in trouble if you kept
probing around, so please stop that.
So honest! What an interesting fellow!
You're one to say that.
All right, how about this?
Would you like to form
an alliance with us, as well?
I can't share that much about myself,
so I think it'll be difficult
to earn your trust.
Therefore, I wouldn't mind agreeing
if it's a ceasefire.
Hmm...
Oh well, I guess that's okay!
Have you lost your mind?
It's not okay?
I...
decided, as well.
That, at the least, I
will try to trust Saber.
So, now, I will for you, as well.
Hey, Saber.
Is it possible for me to connect
the... path... was it... with this person?
Yeah, leave that to me!
My gratitude.
That girl's got a surprising
amount of gusto.
And that king, too.
Be careful.
Well, I think with that,
we have no objections.
It may be only for a short while,
but nice to work with you...
Sigma.
Destroy the workshop, huh?
You dodged that one pretty well.
You don't tell it directly to kill?
Oh, it's not like I dodged it...
I'm not blaming you for anything, okay?
I mean, Halri, if you were a kid
who would say "Kill people" so easily...
you'd no longer be human—
Now, you should run for it.
If we're not careful in how we kill them,
mud will splatter everywhere.
So, we have to be careful
how we get rid of them.
No way! You're kidding!
This is amazing, Halri!
She was only brought in so we'd
have enough people, but she
summoned something amazing!
But... this scene is almost over.
Well then, I'm going to
give the order, okay?
I will have you cleanly wrap up
that battle between those monsters!
That's an order I'd like to refuse
even if you used a Command Spell on me.
We finally have all the actors,
but if the folks above
Faldeus make their move,
this perfect stage would be ruined,
don't you think?
So... you'll head out there for me, right?
You want me to stop this?
Great! This is the best!
This is the best, me!
I mean, Halri, if you were a kid
who would say "Kill people" so easily...
you'd no longer be human—
You'd be categorized as a Mage,
so you wouldn't be worth
keeping alive anymore.
I don't care if you suck away
all of my Magical Energy!
So, please!
Please, destroy it!
Destroy everything!
What the Mages created!
All of it!
Everything!
Halri Vorzak...
What the hell did you summon?
You think I'd easily disclose information
about a Servant?
You either give me the info or order it
to commit suicide with a Command Spell.
If you do that, I'll end you
without unnecessary pain.
I see how it's not
"I'll at least spare you your life."
I don't think you're such a foolish Mage
to believe in such nonsense.
Me, a Mage, huh?
All right.
I order you with a Command Spell!
Berserker!
With all the strength you have,
take this city and—
I pay tribute...
Grand Illusion!
This is...
deceiving the texture of the world?
How could they...
Hello there.
A lot of new faces here.
What's the meaning of this, Caster?
All in all,
it's so that the Holy Grail War
continues safe and sound.
Don't worry.
I am on your side.
I'm allies with humans.
I'm allies with gods.
I'm allies with Mages.
So, I, to make sure all of
that doesn't get lost...
only came here to prolong the fun.
Why don't we strike a deal right now?
With me...
whom a foulmouthed crowd
called a "demon"...
long ago.
What is going on here?
Just what did you do?
It's just an illusion!
Besides, the people who
were fighting there
suddenly seem to have reconciled.
Isn't that strange?
Is it the power of love?
Isn't it such a wonderful thing? Love!
You can physically touch
and use the workshop...
but in about five more days,
the world will notice
and it will collapse!
So, I trust you to do
the cover-up work in the meanwhile!
Mr. Black, what is that?
It looks like there was
a fire out in the city.
Who's there?
I'm Jester Karture.
Nice to meet you...
Tsubaki.
Livestock to Thorn.
Please send several members
of the squadron to watch over Deficit.
Why surveillance on Sigma?
I just remembered
that Mages are not to be trusted.
Besides,
it troubles me that he's pretending
to be an actor as it doesn't suit him.
It looks like that guy Faldeus
is sending Thorn over here.
You really aren't trusted one bit, my boy.
"Suggest a united front," huh?
My objectives are restful
sleep and stable meals.
Huh?
I'll give you information.
This Holy Grail War has been set up
by the United States government.
My client is one who
sides with the States.
One of the masterminds.
U-United States government?
Mastermind?
This Holy Grail War has
13 sets of Masters and Servants.
Hold it! Wait up!
Can you go in order, slowly?
My client is the type that wipes out
allies once they're no longer of any use.
So, I want to have a connection
with you guys, as well.
You're using us as insurance?
I don't mind if you think of it that way.
You don't have to trust me.
I will be utilizing you,
so you should utilize me, as well.
All right. I get it.
I will trust you.
EPISODE 7