Eyes on you! We are F/ACE!
Hewwo to all my E/YES out there!
It's me! Everyone's happy, pretty angel,
Natsuki Ishibashi!
So what're we doing on the show today?
Natsuki Ishibashi's
Counseling
Room
It's Natsuki's Counseling Room!
Natsuki's Counseling Room
And today's assistant angel is...
Thanks for having me.
It's Ouri!
I look forward to helping you out today.
Natsuki Ishibashi's
Counseling
Room
Now, the E/YES that
need our help today is...
First, a high schooler from Tokyo
named Ookmi Ookguchi-san.
High School Student
From Tokyo
Ookmi Ookguchi-san
Okay, cut!
You okay?
I'm so sorry about that. I'm okay.
Okay, let's continue.
Yes.
"I have a crush on someone,
but that person likes someone else.
Should I just go for broke?"
I think what you're feeling right now
is very precious, Ookmi-chan.
It might be fine to go for broke
and let it end there, too.
But if you don't want that,
maybe you don't actually have to break?
Of course, you can't just
not do anything, though.
Talk to them a lot
and make them notice you!
Do you have any advice to offer, Ouri?
Right...
As Natsuki-kun said,
you need to not give up
and make sure this person notices you.
Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
Smooth as ever, I escort you
And this voice, seducing you
Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
I am your ace darlin'
Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
Please Please
Whisper just to me, call my name
You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
Hey, girl
Look this way!
I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
So take my hand and let's roll
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
It's a spell that makes your heart race
We can't go back
You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
Sweetie honey
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
Morning!
Asuka
As you all know, Tanaka-sensei is going on
parental leave, so for the time being,
Asuka Inoue
Yellow Spring
I'm being promoted
from assistant to class teacher.
For real?!
I'm Asuka Inoue.
Assu's gonna be our teacher!
I look forward to learning together.
I'm so happy!
Assu!
Call me "Sensei"!
Isn't this exciting?
Yup, yup.
Sometimes, he would talk
about Japanese history.
Inoue-sensei.
She's a new teacher who started
working at our school this year,
In this case, "sometimes"
is similar to "used to" and...
and while she's usually nice...
Takahashi-kun! You forgot your
homework again, didn't you?
You get early remedial classes
for a week from tomorrow.
What?! That's too harsh!
She's harsh towards slackers.
That's not harsh at all!
Thank goodness I did my homework.
If you don't want remedial classes,
then do your homework.
If I end up with remedial classes,
it'll affect my job.
Yes, ma'am...
Okay, see you tomorrow!
Today's another day to work
so I can support my oshi.
Ah, Inoue-sensei?
That's...
A mini towel that's exclusive
to F/ACE fan club members!
Whoops.
Kinoshita-san...?
Same oshi?
Same oshi DNI??
Do we have the same oshi? Is she DNI?
Tamon Oshi
Red
I'm red.
Natsuki Oshi
Yellow
I'm yellow.
Natsuki!
Tamon-kun!
Man, I had no idea you were
one of the E/YES, Kinoshita-san.
Tamon-kun sure is popular.
I'm sorry I'm so basic.
No, I totally get it.
Everyone loves that face
even if they're not a Tamon stan.
So you're a Natsuki oshi, Sensei?
Yes, I am.
He's just so cute!
And he always says whatever's on his mind.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Food Report Time
This sorta sucks!
Thanks.
Though people call him a selfish brat
because of that, too.
But he's trying his best,
believe it or not.
Oh, I'm almost out of detergent,
so I should buy some.
Let's see, where is it...
Ooh! The lip tints that
Natsuki-kun's producing.
Produced by Natsuki Ishibashi
Lip Tints
He's a great speaker,
and he's even making products.
He's so multi-talented.
I want one, but I don't know what to get.
I've never actually done my makeup,
Kinoshita-san?
Natsuki-kun?!
I knew it was you!
You were at the training camp.
Are you gonna buy that?
You've got a good eye!
Oh, this is...
Hmm...
Wait, what? He's so close!
And his eyes are huge!
Yellow spring.
Huh?
Just like me.
Peach would look great on you.
Oh, actually...
Ta-dah! I actually have
some samples with me.
So let's try it on!
Huh? Wait.
We'll just put this on and...
go a little overboard on the upper lip...
Huh? What? Uh... Um...
and done!
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle!
You look so cute!
I knew it'd look great on you!
You can keep that one,
so if you like it,
try out the other ones, too.
Bye, now!
Natsuki-kun's just like how he is on TV.
Thank goodness he's nice and friendly.
His sense of personal space
needs work, though.
I look forward to working
with you again today.
Good evening...
Huh? Gloomyhara-san?!
I-I'm sorry. I was just surprised.
Was the lip tint weird?!
Right. No way a hardcore fan with zero sex
appeal would look good with makeup on.
He's avoiding me so hard.
What if he thinks I put on makeup
just to get his attention?!
Tamon-kun...
Okay, yeah.
Marry me, please, please, please,
please, please, please, please...
I'm disappointed in you.
I just told him that
I'm no more than his housekeeper.
I don't want him thinking I'm getting
my priorities mixed up after all!
Pardon me!
Please stay away from me!
I mean...
maybe it's better he keeps his distance
rather than get awkwardly clingy.
Gloomyhara-san doesn't
understand the risks sometimes.
So... I want to be something to you, too.
Please stop! Don't look at me!
You've got the wrong idea,
Gloomyhara-san!
I wasn't trying to get your attention
or anything with this lip tint!
I'm not trying to get you to like me,
but it hurts to have you dislike me...
I realized that just now!
Th-There's no way
I could ever dislike you.
Your lips... were so shiny...
Huh?
You looked like a mature woman,
so I got nervous...
You've made the heads of countless
mature women explode.
What are you even saying?
Um... so the lip tint is weird, right?
What? It looks really good on you.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Huh?
Huh?!
Huh
Is this on purpose or
does he not even realize it?
Oh... but I think I'm getting used to it.
I coincidentally ran into Natsuki-kun
at the drugstore earlier,
and he put this on me for some reason.
Natsuki-kun should be busy today, though.
Huh?
You might know this already,
but some of F/ACE's songs
are written by Natsuki-kun.
And tomorrow's the deadline
for a new song.
He was supposed to be holed up
in his apartment today.
Huh? But I just...
Hey, have you seen Natsuki?
Keito-kun.
Earlier, outside.
Tch. Damn it. He ran away again.
Huh?
He skips out on rehearsals,
doesn't finish his work,
and doesn't pay people back!
He can't keep getting away with this!
You two look for him, too!
Find him and drag his ass back here!
Y-Yes, sir!
Man, my head is killin' me.
I drank too much last night.
I don't wanna work.
Big winner!
We wandered around the city at night
trying to find Natsuki-kun.
Damn it.
Did you find him?!
He wasn't over here.
Tch...
I found Natsuki-kun.
When we finally found him...
Um...
Who is this? More importantly...
His room's so messy.
Enough is enough, Natsuki.
Huh?! Natsuki-kun?!
Tee-hee!
Sparkle!
When I met him at the drugstore,
I'm fairly certain his eyes
were at least twice as big!
Why the hell do I gotta
write the songs anyway?
We'd be better off gettin'
some pro to do it. This sucks.
Don't drink alcohol
when I'm trying to lecture you!
Shiraishi-san sees your talent—
She just doesn't have
the budget to oursource.
Shameless, I tell ya.
Just shut up and get to work!
Nope. I don't like you.
Is that how you talk to someone
who lent you money?!
Get to work, you stupid smoking addict!
I'm sorry you had to see that.
I'm honestly used to it.
So even Natsuki-kun did
have a B-side after all.
Natsuki-kun...
He's just a slightly heavy smoker
who loves alcohol and pachinko.
He's not a bad person...
I don't think. I'm sure of it.
Well, now I'm worried.
I'm sorry that you ended up getting
caught up in our group troubles again.
Please don't worry about it.
But is everything okay?
Since we got you involved,
I'll explain the situation.
This could happen again, after all.
Situation?
You see, we're getting our own
flagship show next year and...
Keito-kun!
Awawawawawawawawawa
Kinoshita-san jumped for joy so hard
that she went through the ceiling!
Oh, no. what do I do?! What do I do?!
Were you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Can I continue?
Yes.
Natsuki's supposed to write
the theme song for that show.
So we get to hear another
song Natsuki-kun wrote!
But Natsuki-kun isn't motivated at all.
Huh?
He usually never shows up when
we rehearse on our own either...
But we've all been worried about
his total lack of motivation lately.
Our first flagship show...
All the E/YES have been waiting for this,
so we want to do our best.
But with Natsuki-kun being
in the funk that he's in...
Usually, such a big gap in drive
among members wouldn't be tolerated,
but he's always been hard to deal with.
Hey.
I need to use the john.
Tch. Fine.
H-He's naked!
My eyes!
Put on some damn clothes.
Hey, there ain't any A/C in that room.
Then go to the bathroom already!
Were you thinkin'
that my face looks different?
Ack!
No, I, um...
If I go like this and...
Ta-dah!
Wow.
So, yeah. It ain't no plastic surgery.
I just don't do it outside work
'cause it wears my eyes out.
Th-That's impressive.
I'mma go take that piss now.
Don't say "piss".
Natsuki-kun.
What?
Oh, um, it's nothing...
Whatever.
Another problem with
F/ACE not getting along?
Tokyo Municipal Hanagatani High School
Okay, here's the big announcement!
The lottery results for what Class 2-A
will do at the cultural fair is...
Cultural Fair Project Application
Food Stall
a food stall!
Sweet!
Yay!
So today, we'd like to come up with
menu ideas and decide everyone's roles.
Let's all do the cooking!
Utage's really good at cooking.
Totally. Let's sign up
for the kitchen team.
Hey, hey!
Okay, we'll have you in charge
of the kitchen, Kinoshita-san.
Kinoshita will get it done.
Huh? Me?!
Let's do our best together.
She's too perfect!
I've never taken on a
leadership position in my life.
Is this going to work?
Before I met Tamon-kun,
I was just living the plain life.
But since I've been chosen,
I need to do my best.
Because I'm the leader!
Hey, Kinoshita-san!
You seemed a bit down.
Inoue-sensei...
Their new official group shot didn't
capture Natsuki's good looks at all,
so I'm devastated.
I was just wondering what to do for
the food stall at the cultural festival.
Ah, I see. Hm...
Oh! This is totally cliché,
but how about takoyaki?
That's a great idea.
I'm gonna jot that down.
Actually, my family runs a takoyaki place.
Our best seller was the cheese yaki.
We put cheese in instead of octopus.
Huh?
Is that even takoyaki anymore?
Though it sounds delicious.
My parents put it on the menu
for a friend of mine who was broke.
But in the end, all the students
in the neighborhood loved it.
It's cheap to make, and cheese
does go with everything.
Yeah, so I definitely recommend it.
Don't half-ass this.
You're never motivated, so if you lose
your talent, what are you left with?
If you don't want to bring down
F/ACE's value, rewrite this song.
What?
I'm sorry I got in your line of sight
without permission.
But is everything okay?
Oh, you mean about the new show?
In the end, if I'm not
able to write the song,
I'm sure they'll just hire someone else
or just use one of our old songs.
Huh?
Our show ain't goin' down
just because of this, so don't worry.
That's not it...
I'm worried about you, Natsuki-kun.
Usually, you can do it all.
You've never had such a hard time
with anything like this before.
It's nothin'.
I'm just not in the mood.
You know what the show's
gonna be about, don't ya?
Youth! Challenges!
Movin' people to tears!
Honestly, I don't like any of that stuff.
I understand that a little.
You know...
I thought you only ever cared
about yourself, but...
I guess you're payin' attention after all.
Also, you've changed a bit recently.
Did somethin' change with yer mindset?
My mindset?
If there is something...
It might be because of a certain someone.
Uh-huh...
Tamon
I'm so sorry!
I'm not here for me, but I started
rambling about myself!
I'm not sure why, but I sorta feel
a bit more motivated now.
Huh?
Thanks for carin' 'bout me.
I'll give it a shot.
So, yes...
Apparently, he'll give it a shot.
Really? That's great!
Kinoshita-san.
Yes?
About what you said the other day...
About how it'd hurt if I disliked you...
What exactly did you mean by that?
It's exactly how it sounds!
Nobody wants to be disliked
or be seen as a disappointment!
It's just general human nature!
Oh, look at the time!
I'm going to clean the bathtub!
In truth... It's not just
general human nature.
Back then, I didn't just want
Gloomyhara-san to not hate me...
I actually wanted him
to genuinely like me.
That's a very dangerous train of thought!
I must kill it before it takes root!
Kinoshita-sa...aaaaaaaah!
I-I'm so sorry! How could I do this
to a national treasure?!
Don't change the subject.
I know what I heard.
Wh-What could you
possibly be talking about?
Say that line again.
My ear! Oh my god, my ear!
I am meant to revere you, Tamon-kun!
I can never blaspheme you
with my true thoughts again!
That goes against my dignity!
I'd rather bite my tongue and die
than say something like that again.
It's embarrassing just remembering it,
so please stop.
Well, it made me really happy.
You finally let go of your reasoning
and told me how you really feel.
And that's exactly why I shouldn't!
I want to hear it again.
A-As I said, I'd rather
bite my tongue and die
than say something like that again!
Then, Kinoshita-san...
This is...
Did you say something like that...
just to play with my heart?
His dark side?!
I'd like to hear that again.
Or...
Can you not die
for a piece of trash like me?
Utage Kinoshita. Dead at six****.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Utage
Kinoshita
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Dead at
What?!
Natsuki disappeared again?!
Find him immediately and bring him back!
Yum!
Everyone loves mochi and cheese!
We've gotta thank Assu.
She even lent us a takoyaki maker.
I don't really understand myself.
And gave us recipe advice.
I just want Tamon to live
a healthy and happy life.
I was just content with
cheering him on from the shadows.
But there's something else inside me
now that wasn't there before.
Let's let Assu try them out, too.
Right, Utage?
That's for sure.
Hello? Utage?
That's for sure, but...
Are you listening?
Stop fantasizing while you're eating!
I'm listening! I'm totally listening!
Sensei, right? I'll go get her!
Damn it! Come back here!
Huh?
Give yourself up, you creeper!
Sensei! Are you okay?!
Kinoshita-san! Could you call 110?
Hey, wait a sec! Listen to me!
I captured him without thinking.
So OP.
Wait, damn it!
It's me, Asuka!
Natsuki?!
What's going on?!
Did he just call her "Asuka"?!
Um... Do you two know each other?
Yeah, sorta...
No, we don't.
Huh?!
I've never seen this unfamiliar
person ever in my life.
Uh, all of Gen Z knows about F/ACE.
Nope, never heard of them.
I dropped my smartphone
into a lake ten years ago.
Even if this is
the first time they've met...
At least put some effort into those lies.
Isn't Sensei Natsuki-kun's fan?
Welp, gotta get back to work.
Anyway, Kinoshita-san, I'mma head back.
Huh?!
Try a little harder!
Sure you wanna be a teacher who leaves
her student with a supposed creeper?!
Come on, Asuka!
So you two know each other... right?
That's one way to put it.
She's my ex-girlfriend.
Ex-girlfriend...?
Ex-girlfriend...
Ex-girlfriend
Ex-girlfriend?!
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michelle Tymon
\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza\h
\h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
\hTranslation Check:
Alicia Ashby
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
Uh huh...
Na na na...
I wonder what the world
would look like without you
When I look back,
you've always been by my side
Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
A speedboat sails across the endless skies
An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
Like a wilted flower coming back to life
A light that shines
Through the impossibly dark night
(Light of your soul)
I wanted to grasp it
(I love you so)
So I strived for it
Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom