The Hellhorde and Imperial Army have been
locked in battle for many years.
Led by their grand inquisitor,
Torture Tortura,
the Hellhorde's elite inflict
their torture on a daily basis.
She faces fierce beasts, flames,
unknown devices and spells,
yet the princess does not give in.
She would never give in.
She would never let the words,
"I surrender!" leave her lips so readily.
Meanwhile, the princess's former friend,
the assassin Sakura Heartrock,
fails to assassinate the Hell-Lord,
and sets off on a new path.
'Tis time for torture, Princess...
is what I'd usually say, but...
we have Hellholm Pre-School joining us
today for Bring a Kid to Work Day.
Bring a Kid to Work Day?!
Are you going to make
these children torture me?!
All together now!
Princess!
Thanks a lot for having us today!
You're all raring to go!
I hope I have enough secrets for you all.
Your Highness?
Listen, Ex.
Thinking about it, I give in to
Maomao-chan when she's by herself,
so I never stood a chance
against so many of them.
Stop with the calm self-evaluation.
Today, we'll show you a torture
we practiced very hard!
We hope that you enjoy it!
Sure!
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
The kids from Hellholm Pre-School
will be performing on handbells.
A-one, a-two...
Thank you for listening!
The princess
confessed
It seems that the first word
that the princess ever spoke was "bread."
Maomao-chan's first word was "Mama."
On that note, I hear today's torture...
was a spectacular handbell performance
put on by Maomao-chan and her friends.
That's correct.
And? Where's the video?
What? A video?
We didn't receive a video,
so I don't believe it was recorded.
What?!
I-It can't be...
You mean I can't see
Maomao-chan playing handbells?
Your Majesty?!
Your Majesty!
The Hell-Lord passed away.
No, he's not dead.
However, the shock of missing
Princess Maomao-chan playing handbells
has made him inconsolable.
Papa's in a funk.
He's so bummed out,
his horns are drooping.
My apologies for not recording a video.
You were just busy
doing your job, Torture.
Anyway, to cheer Go-chan up,
we'll ask the Hellholm Pre-School kids
to put on another handbell show!
I see.
The Hell-Lord's wife
calls him "Go-chan."
The other preschoolers
have agreed to help us out.
But a normal performance would be boring,
so we'll make it a surprise.
I call it...
Operation: Handbell Flash Mob!!
Operation: Handbell Flash Mob!
First, we'll get a secret
out of the princess as usual,
Papa
Kanadge
and have Kanadge report it.
When suddenly, Kanadge...
Kanadge
We've failed to extract a secret
from the princess.
Or so he says!
Huh?!
Which alarms Papa!
The torture has failed?
Is Torture not feeling
like herself, either?
And then!
Upbeat music starts
playing out of nowhere!
What? Is that music I hear?
Kanadge
Kanadge starts dancing along to the beat!
Woo-hoo
In come the preschoolers
and their guardians!
What in the world?
What's going on?
And then the handbell show!
Let us begin the handbell performance.
A-one, a-two...
Papa
Papa's moved to tears!
Thank you for listening!
That was incredible!
The Hell-Lord cheered up
Lulune had always wanted to
try her hand at a flash mob.
And she believes that it's not
a flash mob unless there's dancing.
Is it okay if I go out for the night?
It's dangerous to go out at night!
Is it some kind of event?
You see, they're holding
a festival tonight.
I was thinking of inviting a friend.
Say no more!
Go enjoy yourselves!
Yeah!
She should be done with
today's torture right about now.
I didn't make it very clear last time,
but I'll invite her properly today.
I get to go to the festival
with you, Vanilla-chan?
I'm so happy!
The princess is sure
to be overcome with joy!
I even got some allowance money.
I can't wait.
We've delivered our report
to the grand inquisitor!
That means we're done with you.
Damn it...
Your Highness, get a hold of yourself!
Looks like the torture's just ended.
Princess—
Oh yeah, Princess-chan.
There's a festival tonight.
Wanna come with us?
What? Really?
Yeah, I'm down!
Awesome!
That's great!
What food do you think they'll sell?
I hope there's shaved ice.
Sounds good! And takoyaki's a must!
That's always tasty!
Right. I forgot the princess is popular.
Makes sense that someone else
would invite her.
I messed up.
I should have called her
to ask beforehand.
That'd be the right move.
I always mess up...
Papa. Mama.
I'm sure they'd be sad
if they knew how I felt right now.
My phone!
Oh, Vanilla-chan!
All of us are about to
head out to the festival.
Want to join us?
Yes!
Everything looks so good.
Delish!
So hot!
Hey there!
Almost!
Too bad.
What a shame.
I know what color I want,
but it looks hard to get.
Leave it to me!
As the daughter of the
noble House of Peschutz,
I'm great at water balloon fishing.
You're amazing, Vanilla-chan!
I'm back!
You're back?
Welcome home.
Have fun at the festival?
Yeah! I had a great time!
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Shooting Gallery
Princess-chan, time for some torture!
Today's torture is a shooting gallery.
Each prize has a point
value based on its size.
Shooting Gallery
Guy running
the stall
1 point
3 points
5 points
You'll each get five rounds,
and whoever gets more points wins.
A shooting gallery?
I've never been great with guns.
That's information we already have!
What?!
By the way, I'm really good.
That look of confidence
on Youki's face...
We're in trouble, Your Highness!
Yeah. This won't be an easy fight.
Okay. I'll be going first.
Behold my superb sharpshooting technique!
Hah!
Hmph!
There!
Bam!
One plus three makes four points.
Pretty normal.
Not very impressive.
What?
You're the festival hero if you manage
to win two prizes at the shooting gallery!
Shooting Gallery
Next! You're up, Princess-chan.
Sure.
Okay, I'll set my sights on that plushie.
Whoops...
Didn't even get close.
Looks like an easy win for me.
She grazed it!
Almost.
Still, I have the hang of it now.
H-How'd you land a hit so easily?
Huh?
I worked out the trajectory from
where the first bullet hit,
and fine-tuned my aim a bit.
What?
Last night at the shooting gallery
was just child's play.
Now that it's a showdown,
Princess-chan's in serious mode.
No more taking advantage of weaknesses
when it's what they do for a living!
We're talking about Princess-chan here.
She might really get it on her next shot.
But too bad.
The five-point prizes
are actually clamped in place!
I figured she'd aim for
the big prizes based on her personality,
and used that to plant a trap.
And even if Princess-chan gets
suspicious and tries to check...
The clamps are set up to release
with the press of a button.
With the button on the
pole facing the stall owner.
If he releases them before she
can check, she'll never find out.
Yes, the shooting gallery
owner is in on it, too.
Well, actually...
he's Vanilla, disguised using magic!
Too bad, Princess-chan.
The moment you agreed
to this shooting gallery torture,
your fate was already decided!
Your Highness.
Instead of going for the five-pointer,
wouldn't it be safer to go
for the three and one-pointers?
What?
Uh oh!
Those plushies look heavy,
so they might not fall even with a hit.
No.
Shoot to break its balance
with the center of gravity in mind,
and it has a chance of falling over.
Why are you so insistent on that one?
Stop being stubborn
and aim for safer ways to win!
Still...
That plushie's a character
that Vanilla-chan likes.
I thought she'd be happy
if I won it for her.
Princess!
I was scared for a minute, but I'm saved!
Princess-chan's going for the plushie!
It's no use, Princess-chan.
Even if you land a bull's-eye,
that plushie will never fall!
So long as Vanilla doesn't
press the release button!
Huh?
Did I just hear a beep from
the button being pressed?
Vanilla? Did you press it?
Vanilla?
Why are you making goo-goo eyes
at Princess-chan?
The princess won
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
A Hit in the Demon World
Loose-Lipz
A character who's a hit in the demon world
Loves to talk and has its mouth sewn shut
I'm so happy that I managed
to find a four-leaf clover.
Now I can torture the princess with this!
That's...
I believe she recently
became a pain-private.
Sakura.
It looks like something's bothering her.
Maybe I should ask her about it.
I've never talked
to her in private, though.
I'm too nervous to do it.
Time to run away.
If it was the princess,
I'm sure she'd say something.
Sakura.
What's with the long face?
You're...
Shall I, Vanilla Peschutz, daughter of
the noble House of Peschutz, lend an ear?
I managed to talk to her!
Vanilla-senpai...
Please listen to me.
I'll finally be performing
my first torture next week.
But I'm worried because I'm not sure
if my torture will be good enough.
Huh? Senpai?
Can you hear me?
Vanilla-senpai?
Vanilla-senpai? Senpai? Senpai?
Senpai?!
Hooray! Yay!
Since I skipped grades in school,
everyone around me's always been older.
I've never been called "Senpai" before!
I'm so happy!
I understand!
As your senpai, I'll help
you come up with tortures!
Since I'm your senpai and all!
Really? You mean it?
First, show me what you can do, Sakura.
Yes.
I used to be an assassin,
so I've got good hand dexterity.
I can take a Rubik's Cube...
hit it with pebbles from afar...
and solve all six sides.
I have good stamina as well.
I can run fifty kilometers
in around two hours.
I speak nine languages
so I can go undercover.
My engineering knowledge means
I can assemble a car from its parts.
Also, my taste buds have been trained,
allowing me to figure out
the ingredients by trying a dish.
That's about it.
That's more than enough.
What?
I don't have any advice to give.
You should have no problems
performing any torture.
What?!
To be honest, I have some
ideas for torture techniques to try.
But I'm worried that my torture target
won't be able to appreciate them.
I have no self-confidence.
Vanilla-senpai, you're always
so cool and full of confidence.
Cool and full of confidence?!
Thanks.
Don't tell anyone else...
but I lack self-confidence as well.
What?
I always get nervous before torture,
and a lot of times,
I want to cry because I mess up.
But...
Recently, I managed to make a f-friend...
She's always really cool.
Seeing her makes me want to try hard.
Instead of running away
because I lack confidence...
I decided to challenge myself
to gain the confidence I lack!
Vanilla-senpai...
Thank you.
I'll challenge myself, too!
I'll give it a shot and
see what I can do!
Yeah! Let's both give it our all!
Give it your all!
Oh right, Princess.
Next week, our new recruit will be
performing her first torture.
What? The recruit you keep talking about?
What kind of torture will it be?
I can't wait for next week.
It still makes me nervous!
I wasn't told so that I could
focus on my own torture...
but I wonder what my
torture target is like.
No point dwelling on it, I guess.
Time to give it my all!