I get why you're fixated on Kaya-chan.
Student Guidance Record (Instructional Notes)
Sato
Kaya
Born
April 2020
Female
Objective
(Developmental support)
Behave energetically and experience fulfillment
Actively move her body and willingly engage in
\hphysical activities
Develop habits and attitudes for healthy and safe
\hliving, and act with kindness
Enjoy her kindergarten life and experience the
\hfulfillment of acting independently
Form bonds with familiar people, strengthen relationships,
and enjoy working together through creativity and coop-
eration, developing affection and trust
Develop desirable habits and attitudes for social
\hlife
Become comfortable with her surroundings and
develop interest and curiosity through interaction
with nature
Actively engage with her surroundings, enjoy
making discoveries and reflecting, and applying
what she learned to everyday life
Create opportunities for her to
plan her own activities and daily
routines, work cooperatively
with friends and foster independ-
ence and cooperation
By engaging in proactive acti-
vities, she can learn to express
her idesa and thoughts, and
develop empathy through
social interactions
Engage with different peers, learn
fundamental rules for living in
a group and enjoy her kinder-
garten activities
By opening up to her teachers
and peers and communicat-
ing her thoughts verbally
repeatedly, she develops the
ability to express herself
openly within a healthy
relationship
At the time of enrollment,
she did not cry, but showed
no response to the teacher
and was observed waiting
for their guardian at the
entrance throughout
the day.
— While not displaying
oppositional behavior,
she appeared highly tense
and tended to avoid eye
contact with others.
— In contrast, she shows
strong motor skills, is
excellent at origami to a
level noted by those around
her, along with a high
level of concentration.
— Literacy skills were
also highly developed,
with a solid understanding
of hiragana and numbers
evident from the time
of enrollment.
Kaya-sama and her family
But if you owe her so much, isn't that
all the more reason not stalk her?
And for several years,
I had no idea how she was doing.
But a few months ago,
while doing occult-related work,
I received info about
a really creepy house.
After some investigation,
I found out it was Kaya-sama's house.
And...
there is "something"...
inside it.
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 4: Lost Kids Aren't Scary
There is "something" inside that house?
Hearing that just scares me.
Why now, of all times?
Home Visit Schedule
Chie-sensei.
Oh, you're Kaya-chan's father.
Hi. I'll go get Kaya-chan now.
Thank you in advance
for tomorrow's home visit.
Same to you. I look forward
to discussing things.
See you tomorrow.
This is a public safety announcement.
An eight-year-old girl has been missing
since around 3:30pm today.
She is 95cm tall
and has black hair in braids.
She is wearing a floral-patterned shirt,
a white skirt, and black sneakers.
If you have any information,
please contact the nearest police station.
What is it saying?
An elementary school girl
has gone missing.
Oh, there was an announcement
this morning about a missing man.
An eight-year-old girl has been missing
since around 3:30pm today.
Kaya, we need to be
careful, too, okay?
Okay.
She is 95cm tall
and has black hair in braids.
She was wearing a floral-patterned shirt,
a white skirt, and black sneakers.
Hi there.
Are you okay? Are you lost?
If you have any information,
please contact the nearest police station.
P-Please help me!
I can't make it back to my house!
You're okay now.
This little girl is my daughter.
The three of us can go
to the police together.
Then, you'll be home in no time.
N-No!
I can't go home yet.
Huh?
I'm not supposed to go home!
Uh, hey, little girl!
What got into her all of a sudden?
Go away!
No!
It keeps following me.
What if it follows me to my house?
No...
What do I do?
Missing person
Oh, found you.
You scared me.
You're that girl from earlier.
Oh, you're here, too?
"Too"?
No!
Help me...
Did you beat it?
It's saying something.
Ew.
"It's dark."
Huh?
It's dark. It's cold. It hurts.
Let me out. I want to go home.
"It's cold. It hurts. Let me out.
I want to go home."
That's what it said.
It wanted... to go home?
Kaya!
Didn't I say you'd get lost
if you run off by—
Oh, I was worried about you, too.
Are you okay?
Let's go to the police station
together. Okay?
Okay.
The eight-year-old girl who was reported
missing today has been found safe.
I was worried sick!
I'm so glad you're okay.
Mommy. I have something to tell you.
Thank you for your cooperation.
It said, "Thank you."
It's about that girl from earlier.
Thank goodness.
This is a public safety announcement.
The 82-year-old man who had been missing
for several days has been found.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Dolls Aren't Scary
Wow!
So many toys.
Wowzers!
How did you end up with these toys?
A kindergarten I know closed down.
They were throwing everything out,
so I took them so they
wouldn't go to waste.
Ah, here we go again with
your "What a waste" mindset.
What a waste
Some are in better shape than others.
Let's set them aside and sort them
out when the kids have left.
Roger.
Okay. We'll play with these
starting tomorrow.
Who wants to play outside?
Me!
Let's go.
Okay!
Maybe we shouldn't.
What if we get caught?
We're not playing with them.
We're just looking.
I hope we don't get in trouble.
Ew, look at this one.
I bet it'll get thrown away.
Huh?
Hey, what are you doing, Nacchi?
It'll be sad if she gets thrown away.
So I'm gonna save her.
No.
Ack.
Kaya-chan.
W-We didn't do anything bad.
You can't take it.
We're not!
We're just kidding. Right, Nacchi?
Hey, Nacchi!
Where are you going?
You'll be safe here.
What are you doing? You were scared
about getting in trouble, remember?
Nobody will know.
No one uses this room.
Huh? Your sleeve's all ripped, Nacchi.
Oh, it is. Maybe you
caught it on something.
Takamatsu
\h\hNatsuki
Sensei!
Nacchi's cutting her hair with scissors!
Why did you do that?
Because I thought
it'd be better shorter.
Hey, stop that, Nacchi.
Don't you think Nacchi's
starting to look like that doll?
Stop. The hair thing was a surprise,
but it was just a coincidence.
Sensei! Something's wrong with Nacchi!
What are you doing?
Don't do that! That'll hurt!
I'm fine.
I just lost a tooth, that's all.
Something's totally wrong with her!
The doll! We gotta get rid of that doll!
Huh? It's gone.
Where'd it go?
You're being bad.
N-Nacchi...
You were going to be mean
to the baby, weren't you?
Don't be a meanie.
Don't be a meanie. Don't be a meanie.
It's all the doll's fault!
Go away!
Huh?
Kaya-chan?
This is why I said no.
Stop!
Ow.
Huh? Kaya-chan?
What's that dirty doll?
But wait, where am I?
You're back to normal, Nacchi!
We were so scared!
What's going on?
Huh? I'm missing a tooth! But why?
I don't like babies.
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Home Visits Aren't Scary?
I'm starting to get nervous.
There is "something" inside it.
Nope! Nuh-uh! Don't think weird thoughts.
This is my first home visit.
I need to get it together.
Huh?
Oh, Chie-sensei.
What are you doing here?
Your home visit is today, Kaya-chan.
Home visit?
I'm going to chat to
your mommy and daddy.
Huh?
My mommy and daddy?
That's right. I'm a bit nervous
because of, uh, well, everything.
But I hope I can chat to your mommy
about lots of things.
No.
Huh?
You can't talk to my mommy.
Kaya-chan?
Mommy... My mommy is...
Not like everyone else's—
Kaya.
That's Kaya-chan's mother?
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Hasumi Chie,
and I look after the middle-year class.
I've come for a home visit
and to discuss childcare matters.
Yes, I'm looking forward
to speaking with you.
Come on in, Chie-sensei.
Oh, Kaya-chan's father.
Thank you for having me.
Mom, are you sure
you don't need to lie down?
You shouldn't push yourself.
I'll try not to take up
too much of your time.
How's Kaya-chan doing at home?
Oh, you're so funny.
How is she at school?
She can be like that, yeah.
But she explains herself when
we listen to what she has to say.
We'll keep a close eye on her
to make sure that doesn't happen.
In fact, she's been
making friends recently.
So I don't think there's
anything to worry about.
Thank you for your time today.
Chie-sensei.
Huh?
Ugh, what are you doing here?
Today was your home visit, right?
You know about that?
So how'd it go?
Notice anything strange?
Excuse me?
Not really. It was a normal home.
Maybe you were given
the wrong information.
Th-That can't be right!
I was scared witless
and couldn't cross the threshold!
What's scary is your attempt
to trespass on their property!
I-In that case...
Huh?
Well, would you at least tell me
what you found out?
Of course not! That's personal
information and it's private!
Schedule
Huh?
Aw, man. I must have forgotten
my pen at Kaya-chan's place.
Then, how was Kaya-sama?
Did you notice anything unusual about her?
Kaya-chan? Not really.
Oh. Actually, she said
something odd in her front yard.
Chie-sensei. You forgot something.
Oh, Kaya-chan's mother.
Thank you so much! I was just about
to go back to your place and get it.
It... It can't be...
I appreciate it.
Not at all. I'm thankful
you were still nearby.
I'm so clumsy.
I'm glad we were able
to have our chat today.
Kaya's a difficult child, so I'm sure
we'll have a lot of things to deal with.
Oh, not at all. She's a very nice girl.
I'm sure she'll be
a wonderful big sister.
What's your problem?
Here's fine. If you've got something
to say, just spit it out already.
I gotta get back to the kindergarten.
Chie-sensei, how did
Kaya-sama's mother seem to you?
Huh? She looked like a sweet mom.
She's even expecting a child.
Yes, indeed. Her mother is pregnant.
But what's inside her
is possibly a specter.
What?
When I saw her...
I'm glad we were able
to have our chat today.
Kaya's a difficult child...
Oh, not at all. She's a very nice girl.
I'm sure she'll be
a wonderful big sister.
Kaya-chan's mother
is pregnant with a specter?
You can't talk to my mommy.
My mommy is not like everyone else's.
What are you talking about?
You shouldn't joke about things like that.
It's something even I've never seen.
Despite being obviously possessed,
she exhibited none of the erratic behavior
typically seen in possessed people.
Which can only mean
the unborn child is the host.
To the specter, the mother
serves as a living shield.
All things considered,
both physically and emotionally,
it's completely impervious to Kaya-sama.
D-Does that mean things'll have to stay
the way they are until she gives birth?
Or more importantly...
Is the child she's going
to give birth to...
even human?
I don't like babies.
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
People with psychic powers and
those without perceive people differently.
For example, someone with
strong powers like Kaya-chan
would see her mother as a specter,
while someone with no powers
would see her as a normal woman.
Someone like Mob-san,
who has some powers,
would see her and
the specter overlapping.
In other words, there's no way of knowing
how you look through someone else's eyes.