It was all pointless.
It's not pointless!
I know you don't really want to quit!
What about you?
You gave up your dreams to write manga
and ended up an office worker.
Hmm...
The character writing's
still a little weak.
Hello?
How are you doing, Mi-chan?
Oh, it's just you, Dad.
What do you mean, "Oh"?
You're making your dad sad!
Sorry, sorry.
I was just working, so...
But it's so late.
Are you overdoing it?
Are you eating decent meals?
I'm sure editing is no easy job.
Especially with scary superiors or
manga writers who are hard to work with—
You're choking!
Calm down, and slow your words a bit.
Man, I've been coughing a lot lately.
Maybe I'm getting old.
Yes, yes.
So? Why did you call me?
Well, I don't really have
a reason or anything...
Oh, that's right.
Have you heard, Mi-chan?
Heard what?
About Kizuki-kun.
What about him?
I heard from his mom that...
He quit his job.
What?
From: Mitsuman Swimming School
Subject: Inquiring about an interview.
Koigahama City
Happe Park (Kugenuma Exercise Park)
Thanks so much for scheduling
this appointment, Nishino-san.
Your work can be more convincing
when you go out and do some research!
Yeah!
Thank you for this opportunity.
I'll show you around.
This place hasn't changed...
Have you known
about this place for a while?
This is the place my childhood
friend used to swim.
Is that so?
I heard from his mom that...
Right this way.
Whoa.
What a big pool.
The athlete you'll be
interviewing is over there.
Thank you very much.
Why?
Mizuho?
Yes, something like that.
This is great research material.
I'm glad to hear that.
Hazawa-san?
Oh, I'm sorry.
But you know...
I took a long hiatus from swimming,
so my information could be a bit outdated.
Is that so?
It's because of my shoulder injury.
Because of that, I had to completely
step away from swimming at one point.
In desperation, I ended up pushing away
the people who supported me.
But I've made the decision
to stop running away.
And now I'm back.
I even quit my job.
Kizuki...
He did that so he could
go back to swimming.
That's a very serious commitment.
Did you have any doubts?
I did.
I know it's a reckless challenge.
But...
I want...
A specific person to see me again.
Well, his shoulder isn't
in tiptop shape just yet!
I'll heal. I guarantee it.
Don't slow down!
So cool!
Kizuki really shines when he's swimming.
You're regaining your strength.
Thank you for everything today.
I was able to get some great references.
Don't mention it.
As long as it can help
create something amazing.
Thanks to Hazawa-san, I think I have
a solid idea for the main character.
I'm glad to hear that.
Is... Is something wrong?
Is Hazawa-san that childhood
friend you mentioned earlier?
The one who swam.
What?!
I was right!
Are you a psychic, Kawaguchi-san?!
So you didn't know that
he's been swimming again.
Yes...
He should have told me.
So he's your adolescence.
What?!
That's not...
Mizuho!
Kizuki?
I wanted to see you.
What?
Nishino-san.
Right now, I... have all
these ideas in my head!
I'm going home to work on a draft!
Oh, uh, all right.
I'll be heading out first!
Sorry, Mizuho!
What?
I kept running away
for the past three years.
And I selfishly hurt you.
I'm really sorry!
It surprised me, you know?
Because I didn't think I'd see you here.
Are you still mad?
I'm mad. At myself.
I didn't try to understand you at all.
I can't believe I told you "Don't give up"
when you were suffering so much.
All I could say was "Are you okay?"
and kept cornering you.
You're wrong!
Because you encouraged me back then,
I was able to come back again.
Kizuki...
Mizuho. I...
I'm going to aim to be
a swimming athlete once more.
I don't know if I can ever
achieve my peak condition again.
But I want to take back the things I lost.
Both swimming and you, Mizuho.
Kizuki...
I'm going to make you fall
for me again. I swear it.
I'm going to take a stand once more!
I'm going to take
a stand once more!
I can see that the interview
was useful, but...
Why?!
Senpai. You're being so loud.
Oh, sorry.
It's been bugging me so much
that I lost my composure.
Then how about you help me out
a bit for a change of pace?
What?
Here, take a look.
Let me see.
Wait, is this...?
I'm stuck on what to do next.
The two characters are about to confess.
Let's go out.
Shin...
But Shin, you...
Let me see if I still like you, Mizuho.
I want to take back the things I lost.
Both swimming and you, Mizuho.
Kizuki...
I'm going to make you fall
for me again. I swear it.
I need to think these things through, too.
Is something still bugging you?
Hey, Sakura.
Yes?
What would you do in this case?
What if...
Nishino-san!
You have a visitor
waiting over at reception.
Oh, thank you.
But I don't think
I have any appointments.
Hmm...
They said their name is Kashiwagi-san.
What?! Kashiwagi?
Yeah. Apparently, he's quite a looker.
He's hot?!
What's your relationship with this guy?
Ah! Mizuho!
Kai! What are you doing here?
I came to see you, Mizuho.
So?
Wanna quit your job and marry me?
What a handsome high schooler.
Marriage? How cute!
Why's it always Nishino-senpai!
No way I'm doing that, idiot.
Kai as a
kid
Shin's younger brother
Just marry me already
and come live with us!
You're so childish on the inside
after all this time.
Hey, are there manga artists here?
There are not!
Wait.
What about school, Kai?
About that...
I'm visiting colleges for
their open houses today.
So, here.
Take this to my workaholic brother.
What? To Shin? Why?
He's out sick with a cold right now.
So Mom made me bring all those things.
But I'm busy applying to schools
and it'd be bad for me to catch a cold.
Which is why I'm leaving it to you!
W-Wait, Kai!
You can't just dump this on me.
Why?
Why would it bother you?
Because...
Did something happen
between you and Shin?
N-Nothing like that...
Huh...
If this is something that
makes you drag on like this,
you should just choose me already!
Ugh...
If nothing's up, then
you can pass it on to him.
Then I'm leaving it to you!
Hey!
Nishino
Mizuho!
Oh. Shin!
Perfect timing.
Let's reschedule today's plans
for another day.
What?
Kizuki had an asthma attack.
Relay that to the others, okay?
I'm going to check on Kizuki!
Ah...
Mizuho... What am I to you?
What is it?
So loud...
Mizuho?
What's wrong?
Did you fight with Kizuki?
Shin...
Congrats on making it
into To-Ou University!
I'm so happy for you!
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
Shin-chan!
I'm so happy for you!
Congrats! I believed in you!
You're amazing! You studious nerd!
Thanks, everyone.
You've worked so hard for this.
Congrats!
Everyone Got Accepted Into College!
(Airu got into technical school)
Oh. I fell asleep.
There's never going to be a day
when Mizuho needs me.
Thank you to all the
athletes and individuals
involved in today's swimming competition.
The competition
has ended successfully and...
Those two look happy.
Shin-chan...
You'd better show up to the next lecture!
You'll lose your credits if you don't!
Kuroda
Even if I don't do my best...
Mizuho would be happy.
But...
During the fireworks festival...
Kizuki showed up.
What?
He said he came to see me.
Even though Kizuki and I
ended things a long time ago.
Mizuho just won't let me give up.
Mizuho?
Oh, sorry. Did I wake you up?
You came.
Yeah.
You still have a fever, Shin.
Are you okay?
I just took some medicine.
It should kick in soon.
In that case, you should keep sleeping.
Okay.
Um...
I put some stuff from Kai in your fridge.
I'll head out now...
Don't leave.
I've been jealous this whole time.
Whenever Kizuki was sick,
he was able to keep you to himself.
Shin...
Hey. Have you been keeping
in touch with Kizuki?
I'm going to make you fall
for me again. I swear it.
Yeah.
I won't forgive him.
I won't forgive him for hurting you.
To: Shin
Kai gave me some
side dishes from your mom.
They're in the fridge for you.
Get well soon.
From: Mizuho
Shin?!
I'm not letting you go anywhere, Mizuho.
Mizuho...
Stay by my side.
What's up with you, Shin?!
This isn't like you at all!
Huh?
Shin?
He still has a fever.
Mizuho...
Nishino-san?
Kuroda-sensei...
Oh. Thank you for the other day.
Ah. This is...
I brought some things from
Shin's mom. That's all!
So, um...
I-I'll take my leave now!
Please wait.
Can I ask you something?
Nishino-san...
What does Kashiwagi...
What does Kashiwagi mean to you exactly?
What?
Shin's... my childhood friend.
It's not fair.
Huh?
That's not fair!
Don't you realize it?
That Kashiwagi doesn't see you that way?
Holding onto those feelings for so long...
It's really painful.
I can't keep seeing Kashiwagi like this.
I-I...
I'm sorry.
I'm just being jealous.
Please forget about this.
# 22 Something I've Been Meaning to Say