It's finally time for Osaka High's
school festival!
School Festival
You listening, punks?!
Give this all you've got!
Yes, sir!
It's like everyone's going
to war or something.
Well, yeah.
I was intimidated by it all
as a first-year too,
but our school festival is hot stuff.
This is new for the first-years,
so pay attention.
Osaka's school festival
lasts for three days.
Day one features athletic events.
Day two hosts festival activities indoors.
And on day three, we open
the campus to outside guests.
So to boil it all down,
we're basically jamming together
our field day and cultural festival.
That sounds like a ton of fun.
But this is the important part!
Our festival pits the dorms
against each other for the grand title!
The dorms compete against each other?!
As you are all aware, our school splits
each grade level into three classes.
Said classes are then assigned to dorms.
Dorm 1
In Dorm 1, we have students
focused on sports.
Dorm 3
In Dorm 3, we have students
focused on the arts.
Dorm 2
And our dorm, Dorm 2, has a mix
of students from sports and the arts.
The overall winner is determined
by how many points each dorm gets.
Don't forget that this is riding
on each one of you individually!
Oh, and I forgot something important.
The winning dorm gets special
privileges as their reward.
Special privileges?
For example, special meals
in the dining hall.
Special meals?!
Rumor has it they get a full-course
French dinner once a month.
Really?
Additionally, the class who earns the
most points will be named the MVPs...
and score a cash prize.
Cash prize!
All right, if they weren't
fired up after all that,
we wouldn't stand a chance of winning.
The team leader for each dorm
will be the RA, so me.
Let's keep our eyes on the prize and—
It's not gonna happen, Dorm 2 dwellers!
This year, Dorm 1 is taking that prize!
Yeah!
The annoying crew showed up.
Oh, you're awake now.
Who is that?
If it isn't the karate chump.
Who're you calling a karate chump?!
That's Tennoji Megumi, Dorm 1's RA.
He's also the captain
of our monstrous karate team.
Nanba Minami!
Looks like the time to settle
our score has finally come!
Victory shall be ours!
Yeah!
Well, we can't exactly
roll over and let you win.
You can see the sparks flying!
Hey, hey, Sano.
Who are those two guys in the back?
Ah, they're two of what
they call their "Big Four."
On the right is Kitahanada, a second-year.
On the left is Kujo,
their vice captain and a third-year.
They call him both "Bodhisattva Kujo"
and "Asura Kujo."
Not the kind of guy you wanna tangle with.
He seems nice, though.
What was that?
This year, we're claiming victory.
You will taste the bitter
nectar of defeat!
Now, let us impose no more!
We're off!
Yeah!
Let's just say that was a demonstration.
Pay them no mind.
We've gotten off track,
but remember what what we win in
the festival will change our lives here.
That is all.
Oh, and as usual, we will also be holding
our regular Miss Osaka beauty pageant.
There's a beauty pageant?
You can nominate yourself or others,
so if you're even a little easy
on the eyes, step up.
The school festival sounds like a lot.
Whaddaya mean?
Don't think it sounds fun?
I mean, you could say it's a lot, yeah.
But it's not without its merits.
Right?
'Cause girls are gonna be coming!
Real, actual girls!
That's right! On day three,
they'll be here in droves!
Anyway, are you in, Ashiya?
What do you mean?
You gonna enter the beauty pageant?
By the way, Nakao won last year.
Why the hell would I do that?!
Why would I go out of my way to enter
a competition that could expose me?
Saw that coming.
Aw, Mizuki isn't going to enter?
I Don't Look Good
in Women's Clothing!
Well, good night.
Night!
See you tomorrow.
Mizuki in girls' clothes, huh?
Nakatsu.
That's crazy cute!
Pervert.
Your aura is turning pink.
Are you in love?
So, what kind of events
happen on the first day?
Stuff like a 500-meter relay,
an obstacle course, a scavenger hunt,
a chicken fight, and swimming, I think.
You'd better not enter the chicken fight.
Why?
Are you seriously asking that?
What even is a chicken fight?
Whatever. Just go to sleep already.
What's a chicken fight?
If you won't tell me, I'll...
tickle you!
You doofus, stop it.
You wish!
You little...
Sheesh! Stop fooling around.
Get to bed.
Y-Yeah, good night.
Yeah.
That caught me off guard.
Makes me think of what happened
at our summer job...
Back then, Sano held me in that grove.
I even had a dream that we kissed.
I mean, it was an accident,
but we have kissed before.
I still remember what his lips felt like.
The feel of his shoulders and back...
The warmth of his arms...
The heartbeat in his chest...
My body remembers it all.
My heart just flutters.
Everywhere he touched me feels so warm.
I guess I like him just that much.
Do I just want to be around her?
I...
Rock, paper, scissors!
Swimming
Dodgeball
2,000 m relay 500 m relay
Obstacle course Chicken fight
Awesome!
And you two are in
the chicken fight as well!
I told you to steer clear of this event.
Swimming
Dodgeball
2,000 m relay 500 m relay
Obstacle course Chicken fight
It'll be fine! Just fine!
I'm light, so I won't get caught!
That's not what I meant.
Yeah, Nakatsu!
Let's do this!
You bet!
Ashiya!
Nakao-kun?
You'll enter the pageant, right?
You'll be our runner-up for sure!
I'm not entering.
But why not?!
I don't look good in women's clothing.
And you think anyone here
would look better than us?
I, er... th-think they'd do fine.
I really can't enter the pageant!
What's this, Ashiya? You're not entering?
Nanba-senpai!
The pageant is very important for us.
Don't forget that cash prize. Cash prize!
Ashiya, please enter!
You could do it for sure!
Cash prize! Cash prize! Cash prize!
Everyone's lost their minds
about the cash prize.
Okay, it's settled.
N-No way!
Nakatsu, your aura is pink.
Watch yourself, man.
M-My bad.
Anyway, the pageant isn't
the only thing I'm here about.
On the final day, we've got the
time-honored 2,000-meter relay from hell,
which is worth enough points to make
or break the entire competition.
There's a relay on the final day too?
It's a five-man event, with each
runner taking 400 meters.
It's pretty tough.
A lot of responsibility.
To keep our participants'
identities secret,
I will be picking the runners myself.
This is not up for debate.
He's a demon!
Soft! You're soft! You're all soft!
These guys again?
God, you're annoying.
Scheme all you want!
It won't do you any good!
There's no way you guys can win.
Yeah!
This year for sure...
This year, victory's going to Dorm 1!
And you know what, Nanba Minami?!
Once we win, I'm going
to cut off all your hair!
Leave my hair out of this.
Your stupid, flashy mop
makes me wanna puke!
That's rich from the dorm
that bombs the pageant every year!
Shut your mouth, whelp!
Eek! Senpai!
Speaking of the pageant,
yes, it's true that we used
to struggle every year,
but no longer!
Kadoma!
Here!
H-He's cute!
No way!
This can't be happening!
You get it now, you dolts?!
Captain, I need to tell you something.
That kid over there? He's their...
So it's you!
Ashiya Mizuki in the flesh.
You've got a face like a girl.
Looking at you, I have my doubts
about the rumors of your leg strength.
Maybe you're only good
for the pageant after all.
Don't put me down.
I'm also entering the chicken fight.
The chicken fight?
Don't make me laugh.
A little shrimp like you is just
going to get hurt and run home
with your tail between your legs.
You can't know that before we compete!
And I am not gonna lose to someone
who judges based on appearances!
It just had to go there...
Fine then.
It's on in the chicken fight, you brat!
I'll take you down!
Infirmary
You? In the chicken fight?
Is that a good idea?
Come on, not you too!
Well, do your best.
Sorry I'm late!
Io-san!
Why, it feels like forever, Mizuki-kun!
Damn it.
Can you not use my office
for your little meet-up?
You say something, Hokuto?
N-Not a peep, my dear sister!
Look, I finished your vest.
Oh, thank you so much!
There's soft wire inside,
so you'll look completely
flat from outside.
Completely flat, huh?
Wow, you're entering the pageant?
I kinda got strong-armed into it.
Minami was in it too.
That takes me back.
Wait, N-Nanba-senpai entered?
Back when he was a first-year.
Look.
Oh, wow! He's so gorgeous.
Right?!
He was that year's Miss Osaka.
He looks just like you.
Like mother, like son!
Gorgeous? I'm gorgeous!
Really, and just like him, you get
more shameless every year.
I wasn't expecting that!
Who would've thought that
Nanba-senpai was Miss Osaka?
Speak of the devil!
Nanba-senpai...
I've never seen him like this before.
All right!
Sano and Nakatsu got put in basketball,
while I got put in volleyball,
but let's all do our best!
You're really fired up, huh, Mizuki?
Of course!
This is how we're gonna fight back!
That squirt? He's who
we're supposed to watch out for?
He does seem especially fast.
Don't let Ashiya Mizuki
from 2-C out of your sight
Ashiya Mizuki, huh?
Izumi!
It's in!
Ashiya, it's nearly time
for our volleyball match.
Already?
But this is the finals!
Come on, let's go.
But you know...
Nakatsu's feral, so that was his usual,
but Sano's pretty good, huh?
He's not even on the team,
and he's that skilled.
He had the third-years
on the other team scrambling.
Guess it's his jumping power!
That's right!
Ashiya, you perk right up
whenever Sano's involved.
Do I?
It's all over your face.
And the winner of the basketball
tournament is Dorm 2's class 2-C!
Awesome!
Nanba-senpai!
We won the basketball tournament!
This is bad.
Huh?
The winner of both the individual and
group swimming competitions is Dorm 1.
So what's the overall ranking now?
Overall Ranking Announcement
Right now, Dorm 2 is in last place.
And we were so happy just now...
Those bastards.
You're not allowed to compete
in sporting events you're on the team for,
so they had their guys quit
the swim team temporarily.
That's so dirty.
Let's call it what it is: strategy.
Strategy, I say!
Tennoji...
You could try using your head for once.
Right!
You got a lot of nerve coming
in here to talk trash
when you're using all kinds
of dirty tricks to win!
You're too soft!
All is fair in love and war!
I'll send you packing
in the chicken fight,
you big-mouth brat.
I can't wait to see you try!
What the...?
Don't get mixed up with Kujo.
There's talk that some punk
tried to mess with him.
He dislocated the dude's arm.
They say he didn't even blink.
Paging all volleyball players.
Please gather up.
Keep calm, keep calm, keep calm!
Okay!
Go on. They're calling for you guys.
Right. Now we've got to pay
them back in volleyball,
no matter the cost!
Let's go, maggots!
Yeah!
We lost...
We're out in the first round...
It would appear some of our dorm
members have behaved roughly.
Can you stand?
I am the RA of Dorm 3, Oscar M. Himejima.
You're Dorm 3's...
You poor thing.
A beautiful kid like you
stuck in that squalid place...
I know.
Transfer over into Dorm 3.
You will want for nothing. Well?
I'm fine, thanks...
Hey! Get yer filthy meathooks off of him!
How dare you, you uncivilized caveman?!
That's an insult to cavemen.
You tryin' to piss me off, Izumi?
Who're you even fooling?!
We all know your name is Masao!
Real name
Himejima Masao
Th-Then what's with "Oscar"?
Till we meet again, little kitten!
Adieu!
Get outta here already!
Man, he's really overdoing it.
He's nearsighted real bad.
You're sure in the know.
He's president of the theater club
and has apparently won some fancy awards.
Goes around saying his great
grandpa's German or some bull.
Like, dude, gimme a break.
Oh, I see.
He's a bit of an oddball.
Dorm 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 2\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 3
After the morning events,
our dorm is in last place.
I guess Dorm 1 really is going hard.
Guess so.
Enough with the long faces.
No use crying over spilled milk.
Whoa, Nanba-senpai, you look so cool!
What are you up to?
I'm going to be in the upcoming
cheer squad competition.
The RAs wear white uniforms.
How do you score the cheer squad event?
It's decided by Osaka faculty and staff.
The students would just
vote for their own dorms.
Oh, I see.
Dorm 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 2\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 3
Dorm 1 has a pretty big lead.
We're sorry.
Ashiya.
Y-Yeah?
You'd better beat Dorm 1
in the 500-meter relay.
What?
If we lose that, we're done for.
You can do it, right?
Yeah!
May the cherry trees here
blossom abundantly!
As we brave the mountain air upon us!
Show us your smoldering spirits!
This is our Osaka!
How cool!
Our RA really knows how to bring it.
I'm so glad I got to witness
this, Nanba-senpai!
Dorm 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 2\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 3
The results are in!
All right, we got the most votes!
Your aura is golden.
Nice!
We're a lot closer than before!
S-Sorry!
I'm still behaving like I'm in America—
Wh-Wh-What?!
Payback for last time.
Wh-What happened last time?!
Mizuki!
Let's get to the 500-meter relay!
What? Already?
I wasn't expecting that.
My heart is still pounding.
And now, on to the climactic event:
the 500-meter relay featuring
all three grades!
Mizuki!
The baton has just been passed
to their anchor runner, Ashiya.
He certainly is fast!
The Dorm 2 team has done it!
They finish first!
Second is Dorm 1.
And third, Dorm 3.
Good one, Ashiya!
You did good too, Nakatsu.
What, I'm an afterthought?
Hey, why did you bring that?
Oh...
The events are finished,
so we already cleaned up.
Take that back to the storeroom.
Right!
Let's see... Where's the storeroom again?
Nanba-senpai?
Senpai!
Where's the store—
What's going on here?
Is he seriously trying to pick up
some girl right now?
I wonder if he's got an older girlfriend.
She was crying.
Did he break up with her?
I'm doing that thing again where I
stick my nose into people's business!
I need to hurry up and take this back.
I wasn't expecting him to be that
good in the 500-meter relay.
Crush Ashiya Mizuki in the chicken fight
You can bet they'll put him in the
2,000-meter relay on the last day.
The key to our team's victory is none
other than yours truly, Oscar M. Himejima!
These beautiful cheers will become
hymns of praise for my beauty!
Praise me!
That's just Masao cheering for Masao!
Next Time
Nanba-Senpai?