It really lacks impact.
Should I bring out the
ultimate torturer combo?
This idea you just sent me,
the torturer duo, is great!
They're inspired by my mentors at work.
People like this actually exist?!
They do.
We should definitely run with this idea!
Will do!
Books
Torture Bullet
Cleaning, cleaning!
You really like to clean, don't you?
It's just so much fun to watch
the water in the bucket turn red!
I totally get it!
But you can leave it there for today.
Huh?
The cleaner is here.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Huh? You two haven't met yet?
This is the first time.
This is Rische, the cleaner,
who cleans the torture rooms
for us at regular intervals.
Oh, I see.
Whisper, whisper, whisper...
Sure thing.
You're being asked for your name.
GLOOM...
I-I-I'm Mike!
Not often you see that one
ask for someone's name.
Huh?
Maybe you're her type.
She's a woman?!
If she asked you out, would you say yes?
Oh, I'm good without any of that.
I have three older sisters, and...
I'm in the right here.
No, I am!
No, it's me!
It just makes me feel like
women are too much work.
Aw, what a waste.
What about you, Sero-san?
Didn't you break up with your girlfriend?
We broke up, but I got another one
and then broke up with her.
You're just rotating them at this point.
How rude.
They're the ones who come
to me and then leave.
And I always only date one at a time.
You really are popular, aren't you?
Sero, I'm finished. Please sign.
Sure!
That room was way too dirty.
I'm adding an extra charge.
Come on. Give us a discount.
Nope.
Penny-pincher.
What?!
I'm not a penny-pincher.
A beautiful young woman?!
Loves Beautiful Faces
She had a face that cute under the mask?!
Um, Mike-chan...
Y-Yes?
Are you, by any chance,
the Mike-chan of Torture Bullet?
What's Torture Bullet?
A novel. It's good.
Really?
The main characters are genius
torturers and their apprentices.
What? That's like Siu-san and me!
The author's name is
the same, so I thought...
It's me.
I'm the one writing those,
and Sero-san and the others
are the inspiration for it.
For real? Sweet!
I feel oddly embarrassed!
Sero-san, I did get permission
from you and everyone else.
Is it okay if I model
characters after you?
Yeah, go ahead!
Sure.
Oh, right. You did say
something like that.
I really like that novel!
Thank you.
I never imagined I'd
get to meet the author.
Or that you were...
such an adorable girl.
Huh?
Can we exchange contact info?
Would you like to go hang out sometime?
Rische, you have the wrong
idea about something.
Mike is a man.
What?
Um... just the contact info, then.
Please keep working hard at your writing.
Of course.
Just when I thought she was
being unusually forward...
Th-Thank you.
Birthday: 2/28 Age: 20
Height: 145 cm Weight: 38 kg
Blood Type: B
Siblings: 2 Older Brothers
Interests: Trying Different Bakeries
Skills: Calculations on an Abacus
Favorite Food: Croissant
Disliked Food: Fish Innards
Her Type: People with Compatible Interests
A Later Day
What?
You met up with Rische after that?
Yes, a few times.
And after she was so
disappointed that you're a man.
She's been telling me
all about being a cleaner.
I'll be seeing her again
to gather more material.
I see.
Still, I had no idea she'd
mistaken you for a woman.
It happens sometimes.
But if I were more manly,
people wouldn't dote on me
the way they do, so I don't mind.
Well, your cuteness is
your weapon, after all.
And my adorable self would really
like to eat a delicious steak today!
Very well.
Your big brother here
will treat you to one.
Yay!
This... definitely doesn't make sense.
This must be some kind of conspiracy.
They're just too cute!
So this is your usual spot, huh?
I come here sometimes.
I stopped going to cat cafés
after I started working at Spirytus.
Well, kitties are sensitive to smells.
After I tried the detergent
you recommended,
it wasn't a problem anymore.
It's so much better.
It's a little expensive, though.
Thank you for your patronage.
To Rische-chan
Is this okay?
Yes!
Torture Bullet
Thank you! I'll treasure it.
I'll buy an antibacterial case
and keep it in storage.
That's unique.
So you aren't going to
just focus on your novels?
My publisher has asked the same thing.
Sometimes my schedule gets pretty tough,
but I feel like I shouldn't quit.
Since I started torturing,
my writing has gone better,
so I think I need both things.
Together, they're like your calling.
Our regulars are torturers.
All my other jobs always
come in without warning.
I see.
And I've taken normal cleaning jobs, too.
Like after a conflict.
A conflict?!
It seems like there's a lot more
to cleaners than meets the eye.
The work itself is pretty boring, though.
Should I ask our president if
you can come along and watch?
Curious
Yes, please!
Inquisitive
Café
Come to think of it, when we first met,
you mistook me for a girl, didn't you?
Sorry.
It doesn't bother me!
It seemed like you were
disappointed. Do you hate men?
It's not that I hate them,
but it's easier to be more
open with your own gender.
I see.
Girls are cute, and they
smell nice. I love them.
Would you prefer if I was a girl, too?
No!
I think you're fine just as you are.
You're cute, and you smell nice.
But...
you can smell even nicer!
Wow! What a nice smell!
Would you like to try
our fabric softener?
You're such a shrewd saleswoman.
Mike!
How was your date with Rische?
I told you, we just hung out.
Oh.
I bought some fabric softener.
That sounds like she sees you as a mark.
You say that, but you're
using it, too, aren't you?
Well, their products are just so good!
That's right.
They're so good, I can't help buying them!
Victory.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Do you two work at Spirytus?
Huh?
Yes.
There's a man there called Doppel, right?
Could you take me to him?
Doppel is...
The one Sero-san's in charge of today.
Hurry up and take me there.
I've already cleared it with your boss.
May I ask who you are?
I'm Manika, a contract killer.
What?
A contract killer?
Oh, the contracts overlap.
What do you mean?
Sometimes, the same person has both
a torture order and
a kill order out on them.
Basically, a double booking.
Wow.
I'm sorry!
We're not quite done yet,
so if you'd like to wait—
Sero.
It's been a while.
Oh, it's you, Manika.
Sero-san's girlfriend?!
Ex.
Birthday: 8/30 Age: 25
Height: 164 cm Weight 46 kg
Blood Type: A
Siblings: Only Child
Lives In: An Apartment, Alone
Interests: Eating Out
Skills: Judo, Karate
Favorite Food: Avocado
Disliked Food: Garlic Chives
Her Type: The Person She Ends Up Liking
Weren't you in charge of
a totally different area?
It changed recently.
I see.
Anyway, just hurry up
and hand over that man.
I'm on break right now.
How did the two of you meet?
Oh.
Host and customer.
It was that job?!
We dated after he quit
being a host, though.
I'd already joined Spirytus,
and we ran into each other at a bar.
Really?
How long is your break?
I want to go home already.
Now, now.
They're both so casual about all this.
They must not have any lingering
feelings toward each other.
Heh...
He's the kind of target that gets more
freaked out when you leave him alone.
I'll take him down fast. Just wait.
Huh?
Manika-san, could it be that you
still have feelings for Sero-san?
What?!
No, no, no!
I mean, sure, he's got
good looks, and he's kind,
and he's resourceful, and he
remembered every anniversary,
and he chose the perfect presents!
But he's the kind of man who keeps using
things his exes gave him
like it's no big deal!
What's wrong with that?
Everything!
I'm still using the wallet
you gave me. Is that bad?
It's not.
Should I throw it away?
Please don't.
Got it.
Wow.
All right.
Round two.
This time, you're gonna be
completely honest, right?
Wouldn't it be better to just be honest?
No one asked you to meddle.
And the problem that led to our
breakup probably hasn't changed.
What do you mean?
It was...
I heard the contract killer for
Sero's target is his ex-girlfriend.
There's the number one cause!
Damn, you're loud.
Oh, I know you.
You're the only girl Sero ever dumped.
Would you like to talk about your workplace worries?
Don't take it all on alone. Come and give us a try.
Free consultations
Every time he opened his mouth,
all he'd talk about was work and Siu-san!
It's all because of you and his job.
You said the wrong thing
and got dumped. That's all.
I just went a tiny bit too far!
She said just one thing wrong?
That makes Sero-san seem pretty mean.
Well...
Oh, honestly!
Why do you even like a depressing job
that keeps you stuck in a
tiny room, bullying villains?!
I think we should break up.
I feel like that was the only
thing he could've done.
Contract killers are so uncivilized.
You brought it upon yourself.
This is the problem with torturers!
Let's build a fun,
cheerful workplace together!
Stop harassment!
Besides, I never forced him.
You must've just been low
on his list of priorities.
I know that!
Sero's list of priorities goes like this!
Siu-san
Work
Little Brother
Girlfriend
His little brother is higher.
Even so...
Even knowing he was like that,
I still wanted to be his number one!
Because I loved him
so much! Even now, I—
I'm done.
D-Did you hear that?
The gist of it.
Say, Sero, can't we start over?
Manika, you're...
You're beautiful,
and you have a great figure.
You have blood on you.
You have a great personality, too.
What? You have some on you, too!
And since we both have bloody jobs,
there was a lot we understood
about each other. It was fun.
The longest relationship
I've ever had was with you,
and I know you didn't
really mean what you said.
Sero...
But I can't do it!
Torture's more important
to me than a girlfriend!
Sero, you jerk!
Hey, Manika, it's you.
Sero! What a coincidence!
It's been a long time!
I take good care of my girlfriends,
but me and my work come first.
Same here.
That's why it never works out.
Oh! Maybe we'd suit each other, then!
Yeah, maybe.
Hey, were you serious
about what you said?
I was serious, but what about you?
Want to try dating?
I was serious, too.
Okay, why don't we try it, then?
What do you mean, "then"?
What else would it mean?
Sorry, I had a job come in,
so I'm gonna head out.
Okay.
Sorry, I won't be able to
take time off for a while.
Okay.
Sorry, Siu-san's asking
for me, so I'm gonna go.
Sorry, today—
Hey!
Please don't go today.
I have to. I'm sorry, Manika.
I'm sorry.
I know exactly why he dumped me.
But...
I sitll love him!
Sero-san!
Should you have turned
her down like that?
It's fine.
My work and this place are still
the most important to me.
That won't change.
Besides, there are lots of girls,
but you only get one calling.
Oh, my!
Manika-chan, you're on a rampage.
Something happen?
Shut up!
Noe-san! Can we do a cool pose?
Anything's fine.
Siu-san, you're being
way too lazy about this.
So are you.
That should do it.
What are the photos for?
Oh, I'm planning to use these
to introduce our employees.
Hang on a sec.
I didn't know we had a website!
It was just for the look of it at first.
But now that some promising
rookies have joined us,
He said we're promising!
there are more jobs we can take on.
Yeah!
This is the perfect opportunity
to appeal to those looking for jobs!
And I want all of you to help.
Of course!
Noe-san, let's do it!
Thank you.
What a pain.
So you won't do it?
Oh, I'll do it.
Then, first...
Please tell me again
why you applied here.
I liked that there wouldn't be much
need to meet people face-to-face.
Short hours, high pay, and curiosity!
That's easy to understand. I like it.
It's a type of work
I'd never done before.
Oh! That's a good one!
I lined up a bunch of them
and threw darts to pick one.
Give me a break.
I was approached by a suspicious
person in a back alley.
Suspicious
Person
Hela-san...
Mike and Hugh's reasons are good,
but is there a way to bring out
a little more personal flair?
What about mine?
It's the worst one.
Hey.
Most torturers start on a whim.
That's true.
Isn't there some more convincing reason?
Like, you've always loved
the idea of torture,
or you wanted to do it so
badly you couldn't stand it?
Who would like someone like that, though?
That's true.
Okay, then, why do you
keep doing this work?
Because I have a talent for it.
These two are no good.
Things like, "The human body is this
sturdy?" and "This part bends, too?"
Every day is filled with the
wonders of the human body!
It's exciting and happy, happy work!
He seems like he's having
fun, but he's scary.
Pulling the truth out of filthy beasts
and contributing to society...
It's a very worthwhile job!
That sounds like a good
answer, but he's scary!
Don't use that as-is.
I'll soften and water it down
as much as I can first.
A wise choice.
So you're taking photos inside
the torture rooms, too?
Well, I might be able to
use them for something.
I thought Noe-san was scarier,
but he's a nice guy, huh?
Yeah.
That should be enough.
Thanks, both of you.
You were a huge help!
Squee!
Siu-san?
You seem pretty fired up about this.
Not really.
It's just that this is about all I can do.
And we started this company
with just the three of us,
but there are lots more
people involved now.
It... makes me sort of happy.
Siu-san?
Siu-san?!
Oh. You done?
For now.
Then you can have this.
Why?
Why? Uh...
A bribe?
Write "Sero-sama is a genius"
on my introduction page.
Like I'd write that.
By the way, I don't like my coffee black.
You can't drink it? What a little baby.
I-I can drink it!
Noe?
You're still awake?
Yes.
Everyone was kind enough
to answer my questions,
so I wanted to write it all up today.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Thank you!
You looked like you were
having fun with everyone.
It made me feel better.
Having a place where you
belong is nice, right?
I've had a place to belong all this time.
The place where I belong is with you.
Like it?
Uh-huh.
Come with me. Let's try being a family.
You're so silly.
You can have as many places
to belong as you want.
And Spirytus isn't a place
that I just handed to you.
You built it yourself.
Hela-san...
Now, keep on making lots
of cozy places for yourself.
I will.
The Next Day
Hey, Noe! Get over here for a sec.
It's less cozy with that in here,
so can I toss it out?
What did you just say?!
You may not.
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Elanor Sakamato
John Chandanais
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Becky Cottrill