Adapted from the story of the same title
by author Ku Xuan
from Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen
Group The Daily Life of the Immortal King
The Daily Life of the Immortal King 5
Episode 12: Siblings Alliance
Hahaha.
Being betrayed, abandoned,
and hunted down by those closest to you,
how does that feel?
You didn't alter everyone's memories.
I'm not alone.
My most trusted friends always trust me.
Hahaha! Now that you're here,
I'll refine you siblings together.
You siblings truly are monsters.
This was the Spiritual Realm
of Cultivation Ancestor.
You can still move after being here!
Go.
Crush him!
First, eat that infant.
Then, deal with those dead-fish eyes,
and we'll have a better chance of winning.
What?
Your sister was just born,
she already has such
astonishing Spiritual Energy.
I'm getting more and more
eager to devour her.
Hahaha.
I summon the Demon Sword.
Let's see how you defend against this.
Thanks for reviving me, Lord Bai Zhe.
Today I'll eliminate both of you.
Hahaha!
Just a mere blade of grass,
what can it possibly do?
It can slice through the sun,
moon, and stars.
Dao Ancestor Avatar stands before you,
let's see what you can do against me.
Seal of the Dao.
Dao
It symbolizes mastery
over 3,000 Heavenly Dao.
Ha? Who would've thought
that at such a tender age,
you're already riddled with
ailments and applied a patch.
I'll show you the difference
in our strength.
Dao
What?!
Who said I only have 3,000 Heavenly Dao?
Wang Nuan, let's do it together.
Yeah!
♪Inscribing a page of illusion♪
♪We mourn the crown and the outlaw♪
♪Then gild the throw anew♪
♪Even the dust of life♪
♪is but a stroke of yin and yang♪
♪Your Excellency♪
♪have you seen bleached bones
and a transient dream of splendor♪
♪I have learned♪
♪to forgive the madness♪
♪Anyway, the world has always been like this♪
You've forged your own Dao?
Worry about yourself.
Oh no, I can't break free.
What divine power is this?
♪Carrying a river of moonlight♪
♪Measuring the world♪
♪Never to return♪
♪Who hasn't returned?♪
♪Your Excellency, do you know
who stands before you?♪
I always thought 3,000 Heavenly Dao
was the ultimate limit.
I never expected you to have so many
Seals of Dao.
Come back to the First Prison with me.
If I were to restore everything
and atone in the First Prison
for a thousand years,
will you save me when we meet again?
Think carefully before you do it.
Your little sister is inside me.
If you kill me, she will be gone, too.
Ah?
Don't worry. I'll make sure you're safe,
even if it costs my life.
Hand over the child.
You damnable evil cultivators,
won't even spare a child.
The child on your back
is crucial for my Night Skull's Big Plan.
You must be well aware of
the difference in our powers.
To protect him,
all of this child's relatives have died.
You're his master,
but you're gravely wounded.
Leave now, and I'll spare your corpse.
I won't let you succeed.
Oh no.
Damn it.
I never expected him
to have a Spatial Magic Treasure.
He teleported the child away.
I leave this matter to you,
you must bring him before me.
No worries, I've dispatched
the Soul-Chasing Hound.
It'll succeed.
If you wanna be powerful,
devour this jade.
Devour this jade, Devour it!
From that day on.
Hahaha.
I knew that all this
talk of heavenly justice
and rules and morals was nonsense.
Hahaha.
The only law in this world
is survival of the fittest.
I must constantly devour others
to ensure that I'm not devoured myself.
Only by becoming the top cultivator
can I change the world's laws.
You are the final piece of my plan.
Once I refine you, I can... Ouch!
What kind of twisted logic is this?
You... can talk?!
I just wanted to be an
ordinary, adorable baby.
But your morals are so warped,
you're forcing me to scold you, huh?
You're just a three-month-old infant,
what do you know?
What survival of the fittest?
What natural selection?
If I beat you up now,
would you just let me devour you?
You know my past,
so why don't you understand me?
I don't understand!
If you're sick, go to a mental hospital!
Don't lose your marbles here!
If you want revenge,
report it to the authorities!
Every sin has its punishment.
How could you drag
so many innocent people into this?
It's because you grew up without
proper discipline from your parents.
You've never learned
society's harsh lessons.
If Heavenly Dao can't punish you,
I'll do it myself.
Think carefully before you do it.
Your little sister is inside me.
If you kill me, she will be gone, too.
If you want her to be
safe, you'd better...
How is this possible?
Inside me, she...
It's Wang Nuan.
That's what my sister would do.
Do you want to become powerful?
Do you want it?
Just form a contract with me
and I'll take you
to the pinnacle of the mortal world.
No!
Greetings, Sage Ling.
Thank you for saving us, Sage Ling.
Restoring the world, and bringing back
people's memories, can you do it?
Of course.
Sage Ling, where are you going?
She's waiting for me.
Ah, Senior Wang.
Sun Rong, are you hurt?
No, don't worry.
I've taken care of everything.
- Why did it become like this?
- What exactly happened here?
What happened to Heavenly Paradise?
Was this place ransacked?
Senior Wang Ling,
it looks like you've
saved the world again.
Thank you, Sun Rong.
When the whole world was against me,
you stood by my side.
Senior Wang, could you give me a reward?
A reward?
Songhai First Prison
Is the First Prison a restroom?
You think you'd come and go
as you please.
Wang Ling.
You and I will settle this someday.
My dear friends and family,
today we gather together
to celebrate our little Wang Nuan
on her first birthday.
From the moment she was born,
Nuan has filled our lives
with endless joy and touching moments.
Her brother, as her guardian,
has always protected her with care,
showing his responsibility
as an elder brother.
Today, we'll hold her Zhuazhou ceremony.
We firmly believe that,
with her courage and wisdom,
Best-Selling Product
Nuan will create her own wonderful life,
whatever path she chooses.
Wanneng Crispy Noodles
Nuan, you're the most
precious gift in our lives.
Welcome to our family.
Finally, thank you all again for coming.
Let's raise our glasses
and celebrate Nuan's first birthday.
May she grow up healthily,
may everyone be happy.
Cheers.
May your wealth overflow.
Little Wang Nuan, come here.
May you soon break through
to the Foundation Establishment Phase.
Don't listen to him, come to me.
Become a female sword
cultivator in the future.
Wang Nuan, over here.
I prepared smoked chicken
and Mongolian milk skin for you,
may you always have food
on the table and clothes on your back.
Why don't you come to me?
I can grant you eternal youth.
I knew it, Nuan loves crispy noodles too.
I'll be the master of my own future.