It's okay now.
I'm so happy you're still alive.
Like, honestly...
What a relief.
You have received 234 experience points.
Shut up, don't say a damn word!
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
You're my one
you have earned an additional
and only precious friend that I trust!
234 experience points.
Young Plague Dragon has gone
As long as I have you,
from level 33 to level 37.
I don't care if I can become a human
or not anymore!
You have received the skill
"Human Transformation."
For real?
Say, Lady Meltia...
Why'd you take a C-rank request
even though you're with me?
C-rank is pretty difficult, right?
Shouldn't we have waited
for our other members to come?
Actually, it's easier
if you're the only one with me.
I can just flee if the going gets tough.
Uh, I'm not too confident
I can escape, though.
Are you assuming I'm fast
because I'm part dog or what?
Hold on!
You don't mean you're okay
with me dying, right?!
I was joking.
Even though this is a C-rank request,
the objective is not to kill monsters,
but to search the forest.
So I didn't think it'd be
particularly dangerous.
Oh, yeah.
We're searching for a person, right?
Somebody who's supposed
to be dead or something.
Sounds fishy...
Tsuyoku nare itami yo yuuki ni nare
Nani ga umaretan darou
Te o nobashi fureta sekai wa
Kanashikute moroi kagayaki
Dakara koso no more painess
Kono basho de mirai no kodou
Kanjitara mou tomerarenai
Hikari oikakete
Gliding Claw
Dare ka no koto mamoritakunatta
Sou... dakara makenai makerarenai yo
Gliding Claw
Wakatta no wa chiisana jibun ga kawareru koto da to
Tsuyoku nare itami yo yuuki ni nare
Is this it?
Yes.
They said we should just go
straight inside.
It isn't often we see
an elf in a human village.
To be precise, I'm only half elf.
My name is Marielle.
Thanks, Myria.
Please leave for a little while.
Okay. Please, excuse me.
I don't want her to hear
the details about this mission.
So, this dead-yet-alive
person we're looking for is?
His name's Doz.
He was in a group with that girl,
and they fought against a Rock Dragon.
We'll head out to investigate now.
That girl is staring at us.
Myria feels responsible for Doz's death.
I suspect she's been
going into the forest to look for him.
It's extremely dangerous
for her to go into the forest alone.
That's why I want you
to uncover the truth behind the rumor.
So basically, we need to search the forest
and find proof that Mr. Doz is dead?
Finding his corpse would be best,
but in the worst case, we can settle this
by just searching for several days
and reporting that we found
no suspicious persons.
Your injuries should heal faster now.
Rest up, okay?
Looks like she's asleep.
All right.
I just want to check my stats
after leveling up...
Human Transformation
It's there! It's really there! Yeah!
I should get away from the cave.
The black lizard might attack
if I suddenly became a human.
I-it's not like I want to do stuff
like go to the village,
or interact with people,
or see Myria again...
Nope! Totally not on my mind!
Okay, it kinda is, but...
I can't believe...
I got Human Transformation the moment
I thought I'd be okay without it.
But supposing that I do become human,
what should I do?
I don't want to part ways
with the black lizard,
but living in a proper village
would be nice...
If I switch every three days, maybe I
can live in both the cave and the village?
Well, in any case,
just the possibility that I could
gain the trust of humans is awesome.
Oh my god, I'm super excited now!
I hope I'm a really handsome guy.
Ah, what if I turn into a human girl?
I'd lose it if I were a hot babe!
I'd stare at myself
every time I look in the river!
I could think about this forever.
I just have to go for it!
Human Transformation!
My body?!
Is this...
me?
Ew!
Shock
I'm even more grotesque
than a Young Plague Dragon, dammit!
Is Human Transformation
supposed to be this jank?!
The Divine Voice cannot provide
explanations of that nature
at level three.
How many times are you gonna give me hope
then snatch it away from me, stupid voice!
I want my excitement back, you killjoy!
Like, how do other Young Plague Dragons
use this piece o' crap skill
to do anything evil?!
Human Form Limits
Attack: Halved
Defense: Halved
Both Attack and Defense are down by half,
and my MP is getting used up
really quickly!
This is gross.
I'm done.
We managed to beat it...
I'm glad you were here to help.
It's gotten pretty dark...
It has.
And we haven't seen any sign of Doz.
I don't think he's this far
inside the forest, though...
The monsters have gotten stronger, too.
We should head back now.
One is clearly a dragon.
The other looks kind of like a human.
Some kind of shrine
made by dragon worshippers?
I don't think this village
has any religions like that.
I can tell these figures
have been imbued with a powerful magic.
This scent...
That's meat, no doubt about it.
Let's take a look inside the cave.
It's bright.
Those are Light Shrooms on the walls.
Furs?
Something in this pot smells good...
There's tons of red fruits in it.
I think these are spices.
Red fruits used as spices?
Could they be Red Gold?!
You mean Piperis?
Maybe.
I've never really
seen them before, either.
I'm gonna take some of this home with me!
You can't do that!
This cave is likely a hideout for thieves.
We could get caught up
in some shady business.
Huh?
Stay far away from that!
What is that?
A monster nicknamed the Venom Princess.
One bite from it can kill.
Luckily, it seems to have fled.
In any case,
we should get out of this cave ASAP.
Shh! Everything's fine!
I saw the two of them go in the cave.
A human female knight,
and one with ears and a tail...
could she be a dog-type demi-human?
They've gotta be impressed to see my pad!
So, if I showed up right now...
Monster
they'd just assume I was a monster
wandering into the cave.
Fine then!
I have no choice!
I'm using Human Transformation again!
This world has demi-humans, after all.
There's a chance they could
think of me as a puppy-human!
It's not impossible!
Hey, how are ya?
Don't be afraid, Yuno!
O-okay!
Lucent Luna!
That's a Plague Dragon!
My MP is already out! Let's run!
R-right!
Wait! I'm...
I'm just...
Sob.
I Became Human and Got My Butt Kicked
It's not following us, right?
Yeah.
Seems we're safe.
I can't believe there are
Plague Dragons living in this forest.
What a nasty surprise.
They did tell us about
Rock Dragons, though.
What do we do?
Should we go back to the village?
No, we hardly have anything to report
if we go back now.
Besides, we're going to need more manpower
if we want to investigate further.
Then are we gonna call the usual crew?
Yes.
Let's leave the forest
and get in touch with them.
That was some good rest.
Looks like I'm fully recovered.
Yesterday was the worst, even though
I finally got Human Transformation.
Dang, I still feel down about it.
Oh, I know!
Say, I need to ask you for something.
There are some stupid monkeys that're
always stealing the jerky I make,
so I want to poison the meat
to teach them a lesson.
I'd like the poison
to be as strong as possible,
without any color or smell
that gives it away.
Well? Can you make it for me?
Is this poison?
There's hardly any color or smell.
You're so awesome!
Just you wait, you stupid monkeys!
They're here.
Yes, it's working!
Stupid vermin,
stealing other people's jerky!
I'm gonna knock you all out!
None of you are a match for me!
So they're going for a team attack, huh?
Bring it.
We have better teamwork, anyways!
That's how we do it!
What's that sound?
What's it mean?
It was a skill that called for back up?!
Is this the alpha of their pack? Crap!
They knew they couldn't win
and called in a higher ranking monster!
What are its stats?
Attack:
Defense:
On par with mine, huh? Except...
Giant Orangurang
Status: Normal
Quick
Power
Supporter
Clan Boss
Oh no!
It has a skill
that strengthens its followers!
I have to end this fast!
I took too long!
Gah, they're so damn fast now!
B-Black Lizard?!
At this rate, things are just
going to keep getting worse.
What do we do?
Tell me more about this thing, please.
Giant Orangurang, D+ rank monster.
The evolved form of an Orangurang
that has fought and defeated
the former alpha to become chief.
Evolving through battle
is considered sacred to the Orangurangs.
Furthermore, they know a lot
of support magic to assist their clan.
An Orangurang that evolved through battle?
That information didn't help me much...
Oh wait...
I think I saw telepathic communication
among its list of skills earlier!
Telepathy
Yes!
Maybe there's room
to negotiate with this fella!
Listen to me!
Or else!
Interesting.
You must know about my abilities,
I take it?
Whoa! It's speaking telepathically!
This one may die from the poison,
but the black lizard
can give it an antidote.
If she does that, you have to let us go!
That is out of the question.
You've proven yourselves
too big of a threat for us to ignore.
It's better to dispose of you now
while we have the chance,
despite the sacrifices it may take.
If the black lizard and I
come at you with all we've got,
I have confidence
that none of us will walk away alive.
Weed out the weak and let them die away.
That is the way of our clan.
Just as I killed my forefather
and ascended the throne.
Is there seriously no room
for negotiation?!
There must be something I can do.
We can't go on like this.
Well, then...
Let's fight!
I'm challenging you to a duel!
In our world,
duels only occur in disputes between clans
or when an alpha is supplanted.
This is unprecedented, but it may work.
The rules could still apply even when
fighting another species.
But only if you and the lizard
are your own clan.
We are.
Very well. I accept your challenge.
The duel is a sacred ritual.
None may interfere
until there is a winner.
All right, then.
What are you doing?!
Don't get the wrong idea.
This is just to ensure the black lizard
respects the rules of our duel.
She will be released if you beat me.
I found a way to make this one-on-one.
But he's got buffs and stuff.
How do I fight that?
What is wrong, small dragon?
Running around does not make a fight.
Your actions are an insult to us
and disrespectful to our ritual.
I don't know what will happen
to the black lizard if I keep running.
I've gotta do something!
Take this!
Rolling Tail Attack!
How'd you like that?!
Confusion (Minimal)
That took off more
than I thought it would!
Crud! I've seen this before!
Quick (Major)
All his MP is going into Agility!
He's fast!
I can't possibly
get away from him like this.
What do I do?
Okay, then. I have no other option!
A head-on fist fight!
This is a duel between two chiefs!
Come at me, head on!
Or are you scared?!
You dare call me scared?!
He took the bait!
Get wrecked!
I'm reaching my limit.
This is my...
Dragon Counter!
Dragon Punch has gone
from level two to level three.
I won!
He countered me back?!
You have received 162 experience points.
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
you have earned an additional
162 experience points.
Young Plague Dragon
has gone from level 37 to level 39.
You have gained
the title Clan Boss, level one.
Can you tell me? Shinjita kotoba
Never ending kawareru bokura
Always remember yakusoku nakutashita page
Owaranai monogatari o
Don't let nobody bring you down
Tokihanate break of dawn
Kirei na mama no omoide nara
Oitakita through the rain
Tesaguri demo mae ni susumu emotion
Tsune ni mune ni daite
Atomodori wa nashi
Kokoro ni oshita rakuin
Shoki shoudou no mama ni
Attouteki na made ni
Hisometa ketsui hyoumei wa
Kakumei no makuake sa
Hajimeyou ka 3, 2, 1 GO!!
Can you tell me? Shinjita kotoba
Never ending kawareru bokura
Always remember yakusoku nakushita page
Owaranai monogatari o
Shukumei wa ima da mikansei
Shimesu sono kanousei
We fly together koko de wa nai dokoka e
Yoru ga akeru made
Hane hiroge
Itsuka sora ni kieru made
I Went on a Date and Got Ditched
Get stronger.