Hand-to-hand combat training?
Yeah!
It occurred to me in our last battle
that my kinetic vision and core strength
can't keep up with my Onipien buffs.
If I could conquer that, I probably
wouldn't take so many hits.
So...
Kasubata.
Please give me the benefit of your
strength by sparring with me!
Assholes.
I hate every last one of you.
Hey, Kasubata?
Would you mind sparring...
Give it a sec.
Kukuru's doing his daily routine.
His routine?
Now that you mention it,
he is always doing something.
I'm so sick of this shit.
Tea Butter
You moron. Or maybe I should call you a
terrorist, because what you do is a form
of terrorism against...
He calls it his fight against
the encroaching hordes of online evil.
Pretty high-and-mighty, right?
Sorry. That's kinda cringe.
Why?! I'm making the world better!
What you do with your smartphone
affects your cyberkinesis.
So I guess Kasubata's used
to laying the smack down on people.
Assholes.
I still don't know much about him at all.
All right, routine complete.
Enishiro, drink your tea.
It's good. It calms you down.
Say, Kasubata, were you in a gang?
I mean, you've got ink!
I saw it in the hot spring.
That's prejudice based on appearance!
Don't assume I'm a criminal
because of my tattoo.
You called it, Enishiro!
This was Kukuru in middle school.
Stop that!
We've been friends since we were kids.
We're locked in what some
might call a bromance!
Why did you phrase it like that?
I knew it!
Figures. You totally haven't mastered
the whole honor student thing yet.
Let me tell you.
Ren was in the gang, too.
It's not like that.
I was just following the group.
I'd love to know more
about the people here.
Kasubata and everyone else.
I'm touched!
You're not like a flamebaiter
at all, Enishiro-kun.
Ask me anything!
So, why're you here again?
Oh, I forgot!
Hand-to-hand training, eh?
I think there's someone
better suited for that.
Let's see... Where is she?
She's usually the one
who jumps out at me and all.
Oh, there you are, Haijima!
Haijima's a hand-to-hand
combat specialist.
This little doll? Seriously?
Hey, Haijima. Can we talk?
Hey, say something.
C'mon, what's with the cold shoulder?
Haijima cloned herself!
Incredible!
What foolishness is this, Aori-chan?!
Haijima!
That's the real you?
Denmi-chan is Miden Academy's official
mascot and best-selling merch!
I've simply possessed one of her dolls!
Possessed?
My cyberkinesis lets me
remotely control dolls.
My true body is in my dorm room.
Convenience Store
Hand-to-hand combat training?
Perfect!
I'm jumping at the chance
to fight the Aoringo!
So heavy!
Thanks, Emo!
Why did I have to haul out
this heavy thing?
Now, are you ready?!
You're done with me now?!
R-Right!
Emo, you'll be our referee.
Seriously, why me?!
Round one. Fight!
This is a joke, right?
I'm not sure how I'm supposed to
punch an adorable mascot—
Better take her seriously.
Haijima's a champion in the esports world!
My favorite genre is fighting games!
I wanna throw down with strong people!
My goal is to become
the top real-life fighting gamer!
Haijima, I'm sorry
for underestimating you.
Time to get serious!
Then I'll go all out, too!
Cyber out!
Hardcore Gamer-Powered Doll
Hardcore Gamer-Powered Doll!
I can change my host when
the eyes of my doll meet another's.
A little one like this
can't hit very hard, after all.
Behold the masterpiece
of our school's artisans...
Denmi-chan: Battle Version!
Denmi-chan: Battle Version
Hiyori Haijima's bursting onto the scene!
Round two. Fight!
Th-That's a lot less cute.
But it looks easier to hit!
How does she react so fast?!
She's blocking before I even move—
For a pro gamer, a single frame
determines life or death.
Every moment matters.
Reading your opponent's
breathing, their rhythm...
These are the super reflexes of a gamer!
Super reflexes?!
C'mon! What's wrong, Aori-chan?!
Seriously, the disparity between that
face and those attacks is too much.
Breathing and rhythm?
Breathing and rhythm...
Looking good!
Breathing and rhythm!
He's dodging her attacks!
Hell yeah!
These are super reflexes?!
Don't get cocky because
you blocked one attack.
I'll show you one more
thing you're lacking!
Something I'm lacking?
Indeed, and that would be...
A special move!
A special move?
So powerful!
And... you're also totally awesome!
I knew you'd get it, Aori-chan!
You're amazing, Haijima.
No! Can I call you my master?
It's been a long time since someone
blocked my attack in this form.
You're gonna get even stronger
Weird energy here.
Nurse's
Office
You kids get banged up too often.
Training is fine,
but go easy on each other.
My bad!
And 'cause I'm always
patching you guys up,
I keep falling behind on the
principal's anti-aging. She's super pissed.
What about my appointment?!
Our bad.
Super reflexes and a special move...
I feel like things are right
on the verge of clicking!
Master Haijima is incredible.
I hope I get to meet
the person behind the doll!
Really, I can just use
the shower in the room.
It's fine. You gotta
get out sometime, right?
I, u-uh... S-Sorry...
What? Nah, that was on me.
Oh, Enishiro.
Urusugawa?
Some guys just don't respect
women's personal space.
You okay, Hiyori?
Your glasses are crooked.
Kiyomin... th-thank you.
Hiyori?
Hiyori Haijima?!
M-Master?!
Bumping into a girl
as you turn the corner?!
What is this, a dating sim?
I knew it was you!
What's with the one-eighty?!
Hiyori's a completely different
person when she's gaming.
She's usually a total shut-in
with social anxiety.
Living that shut-in life!
With AC, energy drinks, and online
shopping, my room is a paradise!
I... I hope...
we can... fight again... sometime.
I think I'm learning
a bit more about the crew.
Today
Azaki-sensei sends this message
Let's have a strategy meeting
about exorcising K!
-Azaki
The Next Day
I wish you'd at least
send your own messages.
No, see, but batching the picture...
Attaching the picture.
You can't—
Where are you going?
Gonna talk to my kids about the big plan.
Surely you don't intend to let
the demon flame boy participate.
Well, that won't be up to me.
But I do believe the principal
acknowledged Enishiro-kun herself.
Well, either way,
as long as my students are around,
class 1-B will never be chosen.
I agree.
Bye!
I won't accept it!
1-B
Azaki-sensei!
What's this about a plan
to exorcise Sad Boy K?!
Has it been officially decided?
Based on the recent incident,
the principal seems to believe
that K has grown more dangerous.
The Society has undertaken two
previous missions to exorcise K.
Both of them failed.
Failed how?
All appeared to be going well,
but then K made an unexpected move
and many of the
participating students died.
We need to get him this time.
With careful planning
and personnel selection,
we'll bring the full might of the Society
of Spirit Mediums and Miden Academy
to bear in order to exorcise K.
Have you determined his location?
Well, you see, they're using
one of those... dealies, you know?
We don't need to hear
from the tech illiterate.
The intelligence division is analyzing his
past movements via the Pig Camera server.
We'll carry out the mission
the minute we find him.
It will most likely be
at the end of the year.
Two months from now.
Let's get it done!
I'll get strong by then,
and this time...
Oh, you guys aren't part of the plan!
Wuh?!
Rules say that first-years
Ghost Account Ranking Chart
Low-level
aren't allowed to participate in exorcisms
of high-level accounts or greater.
Mid-level
High-level
Extreme-level
You can't do me like that!
We're not supposed to let first-years
fight mid-levels by themselves either!
You can't keep me away
even if you expel me!
There are exceptions, though.
Like if a student has a kind of
cyberkinesis needed for the plan
or they've sufficiently proven themselves.
Proven themselves?
And how do I do that?!
The A-B Battle is probably the main way.
A-B?
At Miden Academy,
each year has a class A and a class B.
A
The A-B Battle is a competition
we hold once per term.
B
Your rating in it determines how
you're perceived as an exorcist.
It's a competition?
Heck yeah!
Then let's get training!
I know we're practicing coordination,
but I can't even tell where the
Yumomi-kuns are with all these obstacles!
Don't move!
Cyber out!
Nirvana Wall
Nirvana Wall!
A barrier!
So this is Emoto's cyberkinesis?
Awesome! Thanks a bunch, Emoto!
You saved—
Hey, Enishiro!
What's with the face?
You're thinking defense powers
are lame, aren't you?!
I knew it! I'm a total coward!
I'm not a fighter!
I wasn't thinking that!
Why'd the barrier disappear?!
My Nirvana Wall cuts out
when I can't focus on my music!
Then focus!
You two! Make for the
big oak tree up ahead!
Hasumi?!
Split up there!
Got it!
Kukuru, run toward the
school for fifteen seconds!
Urusugawa, lie in wait behind that tree!
Holy crap! How'd we end up
in such a good position?
World Through a Shutter
Cyber Out: World Through a Shutter!
Smarts determine life or death
on the battlefield!
Hasu-Hasu is the brain of class 1-B!
I can just make windows from
shots I've taken with my phone.
They're basically only security cameras.
My ability's nothign
compared to everyone else's.
Yeah, right.
Enishiro!
All right!
And my contribution...
Asshole!
In this cute little form,
I can cheer everyone up!
Tee-hee!
Tha-thump
Master Haijima!
Don't get excited!
Good teamwork.
I always love to see young people improve.
Well, Master? How was that punch I threw?
You've got a long way to go!
More like this, then?
More like this!
Enishiro-kun!
I thought I was your master!
S-Sensei, you're my teacher.
But I wanna you to call me master!
It's really taking shape, right?
They've certainly improved
a lot since the last A-B Battle.
Emoto and Hasumi are great, too!
Having you with us definitely
opens up our options.
But your timing was kinda slow
on that last attack.
No way! I think you were too fast!
Aori-chan, you spend too much time
winding up when it's time to strike.
For real?!
You burn your spirit power too fast, too.
I guess instead of having
my flame out all the time,
I should just call it out when I need it.
Cyberkinesis burns the most spirit
power when you call it into being.
Leaving it running is more economical
than constantly turning it on and off.
Oh, I getcha!
Wait, what am I, an appliance?!
A group of such amazing people,
taught by such amazing teachers...
Class 1-B is great. And I'm a part of it!
I'm gonna do some solo training.
Don't wear yourself too thin!
Akari, I'm going to keep fighting.
Whoa there!
Wh-Who are you?
I'm Dei Surugi,
a student at Miden.
And you're Soji Enishiro, right?
You're a real celebrity here!
Th-Thanks.
I was training so hard I passed out.
Really gotta push it, right? I feel you.
We come from the same place.
Did K kill someone in your family, too?
Did this belong to your sister?
Yeah. Thanks for catching it.
I kinda kept it after she passed.
I gave her that barrette as a birthday
present. It's Skull Cat, her favorite.
She was always wearing it.
It's what reminds me of her the most.
Got you.
It means that much to you...
Dei Surugi, huh?
I hope he and I get to work
together on the K mission.
Here, take it back.
Thanks.
Hot!
That was so damn funny,
it brought me to tears.
I've also got flamebait cyberkinesis.
Like I said, we come from the same place!
Here ya go.
Don't wanna lose it, right?
Wait, are you pissed?!
So, whatcha gonna do? I wanna see it.
Gonna snap? Gonna cry? What'll it be?!
Why...
Why would you do that?!
He snapped and cried!
Love it!
Man, this is even better than I expected!
Rage, confusion, grief, pity...
So many emotions! I'm eating good today!
I don't what the hell
you're talking about,
but it's clear you're picking a fight!
H-H-Hang on, man. Back off.
When you look at me like that...
it makes me wanna bully you more!
Lay off, jerkface!
Oh, the doll girl from 1-B.
M-Master...
You okay, Aori-chan?
What a disaster.
This guy's the master troll Dei Surugi.
Basically a giant shithead
with a bullying fetish.
He's also...
part of class 1-A,
the awful group of neighbors
we're going to be up against.
So this is the other class
that Azaki-sensei mentioned?
Dei, what are you doing?
Don't sneak out of our training.
Ya caught me!
Just back out now, Aori-chan.
They're an even nastier bunch than we are!
We'll be going now.
Sure thing! See ya later!
Cyber out.
Onipien!
Just give me one shot at carrot-top there!
We can talk after that!
Love that look on your face!
Let's do it!
What just happened to me?
Hey, Wagari.
Stop picking on our flamebaiter.
Kasabata-kun! It's been a while.
You're as quick to violence as ever.
And you call yourself class rep!