Golden Kamuy
Thinking back, those were
his last words to me.
I'm praying for Asirpa's happiness.
I don't want her to be someone who stays
in a safe place while others fight,
but to be someone who chooses the path
of thorns to find her own happiness.
Like Sofia.
That's who Aca is.
That's right. If he just
wanted to protect his family,
he could've chosen to live in
hiding instead of fighting.
And then everyone would forget the
words of the Ainu and the kamuy.
Everything that helps in life
is believed to be a kamuy,
and the stories of the
kamuy that are passed from
parent to child teach us
how to live in this land!
If we forget the kamuy,
the Ainu will disappear!
And now I'll tell you the horrible
fate that Wilk and his friends met,
battling to protect the kamuy!
Episode Fifty-Five:
The Cause of Everything
Just as Wilk
and his friends were going to find the
old man who knew where the gold was,
we'd found out where information
about him had come from.
A man named Siromakur.
Ariko Rikimatsu's father.
He was the first to find
the old man named Kimuspu.
A beautiful carving.
This pattern has been
passed down in my family.
I'm making it for my son in the army.
So that he won't forget the Ainu.
Ariko-san, we in the 7th
Division are like a family.
When the battle begins, we risk
our lives for one another.
Of course, that goes for
Rikimatsu-kun as well.
If you truly trust
Rikimatsu-kun like family...
We captured the old man over a month ago.
We've probably found the gold by now.
Why didn't you go to
find it with the others?
Because I couldn't agree
with how they do things.
When Kimuspu refused to
tell us where the gold was,
the more short-tempered
ones began to threaten him.
They even said that if he didn't
tell us where the gold was,
they'd find his family and harm them.
I couldn't allow that!
It was smart to part ways
with those who would try to
divide the Japanese and Ainu.
Now that we know of
this plan for rebellion,
the 7th Division must take action.
Tell us everything, Ariko-san.
For the sake of those young Ainu
who live as Japanese, as well.
I understand how they feel.
I worked with them, thinking there was
a way to use the gold without violence.
But those six, especially,
are all difficult men with little
relationship to one another.
Only their extremist beliefs about
the Japanese bring them together.
And one very clever man is all
that keeps them working together.
So it's true that the Ainu
near the Saru River eat dirt, huh?
We call it cietoy, "the dirt that we
eat". We've eaten it for generations!
The Japanese will call you cows and dogs!
That's right.
I've got less respect for you for
giving a shit what the Japanese think.
What the hell did you say?
What, you want to fight?
Cietoi is called diatomaceous earth.
It's a fossil made from a type of algae.
It's eaten around the world by
tribes like those native to America.
In Karafuto, there's a dish called
chikaripe that uses diatomaceous earth.
It was the best food we had.
It mellows out the seal fat.
You really do know everything.
You really are amazing.
This is pretty good. I'll take seconds.
Aw, you...
Discrimination is born of ignorance.
If nothing else, the Ainu
must understand each other,
and come together as one...
Where does this Ainu live?
He lives in Bihoro or Nemuro.
He's from Karafuto, I know that much.
Can you tell me his name?
What he looks like?
Father...
Everyone calls him "Wilk".
He has blue eyes and a scar on his face.
So he's come back into my life once more?
I fired a single poison arrow at Wilk!
Did Wilk tell you of
his past as a guerrilla?
He came to Hokkaido seeking the Ainu gold,
so that he could give it to
revolutionaries in Russia.
Ask him yourself.
I waited outside for a while, and saw
Ariko Siromakur leave in a hurry.
We lost him.
It's too dark here in the mountains.
That Ainu moves too damn fast.
Gunfire!
At dawn, I found Ariko-san near death.
Did Wilk do this to you?
No, he did nothing.
We all killed each other...
Those who defended Wilk and those
who did not killed each other.
The balance that was only
barely kept by trust in Wilk
was torn apart by the
poison arrow I fired.
And now that Wilk knew someone was
after him who knew of his past...
Lt. Tsurumi!
He ripped the skin off his own face
and put it over another's skull
to fake his own death.
Any other survivors?
Hey, don't die yet!
Damn it.
There are supposed to
be seven Ainu, right?
So who tore apart the bodies?
Oh dear.
All the heads have been flayed of their
skin, and their eyes were removed!
Why?
Look!
I assume the skulls and
skins were swapped.
And one of them is Kimuspu.
There were eight Ainu present.
He used the old man, Kimuspu,
whose existence was barely known,
to hide his own death.
He ripped out the eyes because his
own eyes were easily recognizable.
He could've just burned them until
there was nothing but bones.
He wanted us to think that
he was definitely dead.
Usami, bring more soldiers.
Kikuta, secure the scene.
I'll go after Wilk.
Is something wrong?
What should we tell Private Ariko about
our involvement in his father's death?
There's no need to tell him.
They killed each other without our help.
But our plan was that they would.
That's Ariko Ipopte!
What resolve it must've taken
to rip off his own face!
Given what happened, there was
no doubt Wilk would be suspected.
And how, then, would you be
treated in Ainu society?
And Kiroranke might give
up if he knew that Wilk,
the clue to the gold, was dead.
Even knowing all that,
a normal person could think about it
for three days and nights
and still not decide to
rip off his own face.
But he decided and took
action in no time at all!
His one mistake was
that I was his pursuer.
Hasegawa-san...
Near Lake Shikotsu
there was a prison where prisoners
were forced to work illegally.
Who is your leader?
Inudou Shirosuke.
Tell Warden Inudou that 20 kilometers to
the south he'll find seven murdered Ainu.
And the man who knows where
their gold is hidden is here.
We had never gotten along
with the prison authorities.
At Warden Inudou's orders,
Wilk was secretly moved to a prison.
And that's how Wilk became Nopperabo,
the man in Abashiri prison.
What was Kiroranke Nispa doing then?
When I was following Wilk and
trying to track down the old man,
there was an uproar about seven
murdered Ainu near Tomakomai.
Wilk... Wilk...
Would I be able to understand
Wilk if I had a family?
After coming back from the Russo-Japanese
war, I heard a rumor...
One of the seven corpses was Kimuspu.
There weren't seven Ainu.
Kimuspu was there as well.
It hadn't been some other
person who'd killed the Ainu.
And Hijikata Toshizou
came in search of Asirpa.
The rumors of Nopperabo
in Abashiri Prison.
The code in the tattooed skins.
Could Nopperabo be Wilk?
I had a family I loved, but I failed
to reach the same answer Wilk did.
Wouldn't using the gold for the
Russian far east help the Ainu, too?
Isolating ourselves in
Hokkaido wouldn't help us win
against Imperial Russia
or the Meiji government!
He really had changed.
Wilk was a wolf who'd gotten
weak among the pack.
So I killed him with the way of
the wolf he'd admired so much.
Golden Kamuy
Where's Old Man Hijikata and the others?
Searching for Asirpa.
It'll be hard to do this
with just two people.
He Doesn't Count
Damn it!
Even as we speak, Asirpa-san...
Do you know where she is?
Looks like Lt. Tsurumi has
her locked up in a church.
I'll go see.
If I can grab her, I will.
You sure? They don't trust you.
Neither do we, to be honest.
Asirpa is still so young, but she cares
about the Ainu much more than I did.
And it shamed me.
So I want to help you.
Okay, I'm betting on Ipopte.
Get ready to run as fast as you can!
So what do you think the
cause of everything is?
If Wilk had shared his past, the seven
Ainu wouldn't have killed each other.
And if he hadn't come to Japan
in search of the gold...
Kiroranke...
And Fina and Olga, too...
I think Fina knew that I wasn't
just an ordinary Japanese man.
She stayed with me because my love
was the one thing she believed in.
When she was dying, I wanted
her to know my real name.
It was no confession of betrayal.
I believe my wife was
smart enough to realize that.
I couldn't get rid of their bones...
I'm a failure as a soldier.
If that makes me weaker
for loving my family...
Then in a way, I understand Wilk, but...
Thank you for telling me, Sofia.
As a reward, I'll release you
from your years of guilt.
This is the bullet recovered
from my daughter, Olga's, skull.
Yes.
It wasn't a bullet from your Berdan.
Or Yulbars' machine gun.
It was a bullet from a pistol.
The secret police's Smith & Wesson
"Russian" guns were .44 caliber.
A little bigger than this.
Wilk's weapon was a Schmidt
M1822. A 7.5mm round.
Which means the one who shot
my wife and daughter...
...was Wilk.
It was your father that killed
Olga and Fina, Asirpa.
Asirpa...
My beloved daughter, Asirpa...
My daughter...
Hasegawa-san...
So that's it...
My Aca was the one who made
Lt. Tsurumi into such a sad person...
Was it all hatred?
To destroy Asirpa...
Wilk's hope, our future...
If that's your real goal, I'll kill you.
If I wanted revenge, I had
any number of chances,
in Karafuto or at Abashiri Prison.
My one goal is the prosperity of Japan.
I need money to protect it from
the Russian threat to the north,
and other nations as well.
It's just a tiny, tiny memorial on the
roadside of the path we must follow.
My comrades in Manchuria.
Fina and Olga in Vladivostok.
A prayer that the land their bodies
rest on becomes Japanese soil...
But I will never stray from my path
for the sake of my personal past.
During the Russo-Japanese war, many
Ainu soldiers fought bravely, and died.
Is it right for only the wishes
of a few extremist Ainu
who chose to separate themselves
from the Japanese to be respected,
while the souls of those who chose to
live in Japanese society
and risk their lives
to raise their standing are ignored?
As a soldier, I cannot
allow Japan to be divided.
Asirpa was entrusted with
the gold by her father.
She can choose a future for
both Ainu and Japanese.
You're the only one who can
atone for your father's sins.
Private Ariko Rikimatsu!
What are you doing here?
Lieutenant Tsurumi is inside?
I was told to let no one in.
Knock it off.
Who told you about this place?
Warrant Officer Kikuta.
Oh, that's right!
Sugimoto the Immortal was over
there, trying to find Asirpa!
Huh?
Sugimoto!
The concerns of Kiroranke
and Wilk are ones
that we, the people of Yamato, share.
In this world, only the strong survive.
And the weak are devoured.
The Far Eastern Federation
that Kiroranke, Sofia,
and her revolutionaries are planning
will likely be able to make a federal
government on the continent.
But if it falls to Imperial Russia,
Hokkaido will be taken by Russia.
So what of Wilk and Hijikata
Toshizou's Ezo Republic?
If they want to be a powerful nation,
they'll have to bring in
immigrants from outside.
And it's very likely many of those
migrants will be enemies of Japan.
I'm not speaking of discrimination,
simply probabilities.
Hokkaido should be ruled by those
who would have it join with Japan.
Someone whose ancestors
have lived in that country,
who treasures their homeland
and loves its people.
The Japanese must come
together to survive.
The Far East Federation and Ezo
Republic are simply not possible!
Asirpa, have you ever seen
one of these gold coins?
They belonged to the Ainu
who killed each other.
I assume they dreamed of
an independent country,
and tried to make a currency that
would help to bind the Ainu together.
But look at this.
Look at the different shades of gold!
The gold dust was taken
from different areas
and contains different purities of gold,
so it didn't mix properly.
Ironically,
doesn't it feel like it represents their
attempt and failure to come together?
As I see it, Wilk alone wasn't
the cause of everything, Asirpa.
The Ainu have treasures
made of brass and iron,
but not a single one made of gold, yes?
Gold was something the Ainu simply did
not need to live. It was useless to them.
If anything,
the search for gold dust polluted
their rivers and made them starve.
You said that the kamuy
dwell in all things, yes?
Clothes. Knives. Tobacco holders.
Dishes. Homes. All contain a kamuy.
And there are kamuy such as disasters
and smallpox that threaten humanity too,
are there not?
If there is a kamuy of gold,
then isn't it an evil god that
brings disaster to the Ainu?
One that brings terrible
death to all who touch it.
One more ugly and violent
than any other.
A kamuy that's dazzlingly bright,
and shines with golden light.
You could call it a...
golden kamuy.
Next Time
Ipopte
Next Time: Ipopte!