I apologize for the wait.
You even had a change of clothes for me.
Thank you so much.
Have you made up your mind?
Yes.
Pride, who was it
that saved me from the pub?
Val!
Come over here, right now!
What?! Get off my back!
You don't need me for anything!
Whoa, Mistress!
You shoulda told me
when the pretty boy woke up!
Damn it!
Cuz this is what happens!
Oh, that's right.
I gave him permission to ignore decorum,
but only while he was
keeping an eye on Leon.
At any other time, he's bound to show
deference by the fealty contract.
It was you?
Thank you very much
for everything you've done.
I don't know what would have
become of me without your help.
I will make sure
to repay you for this kindness.
No, I didn't choose to do it.
I was ordered to by my mistress!
Hey, Mistress!
Gimme a break already!
You have permission
to ignore decorum with Prince Leon.
I only saved you
'cause my mistress ordered me to.
Couldn't give a crap what happens to you!
That doesn't matter.
You saved me, and that fact is undeniable.
I truly am grateful to you.
And thank you to you two, as well.
I'll make sure to repay you in kind.
Now that's a genuine smile, right?
Let's go to the castle.
Tatta ichido kiri darake no kyou o
Mudatsukai shiten na yo
Tadashisa nante mon wa sa
Dareka ni totte tsugou no ii risouron
Atama no oku de kikoeru koe ni
Madowasareten na yo
Futa akerya karappo nanda kitto
Kokoro no ugoku mama ni ikite
Kodoku mo oikosenai kurai no speed de
Dareka ni totte no risou o michibiki dasu made
Ima, nanimo kamo o seotte
Kawaranai koto sae utagatte
Mukuwarenai nara mukuwareru made
Yamenakerya ii
Mada, dekiru koto ga arun nara
Mirai o torikaese yo
Daremo shiranai kotae ni tadoritsukeru made
Ima, nando demo taguriyosete miseru
The Cruel Queen Makes a Declaration
I do apologize for the sudden visit,
Your Majesty, King Gregorio.
Please excuse my intrusion.
I would like to explain to you
the events leading up to now,
but before that,
I have one request to make.
Will you please summon Prince Erwin
and Prince Homer to join us right now?
I would really like to see them.
Well, as it happens...
I'm sure my sons would love to meet
with Leon's fiancée.
Oh my.
Don't get the wrong idea, Your Majesty.
As it currently stands,
I am not here as his fiancée,
but as a representative of the queen.
I received official permission
from my mother to make this visit.
I will ask you once more.
Please bring Prince Erwin
and Prince Homer here.
Elder Brother!
You're home safe!
It is an honor to meet the both of you,
Prince Erwin and Prince Homer.
Thank you for taking excellent care
of my darling fiancé.
By the way, Your Majesty...
Before we get down to business,
I know Leon has something to say
about his situation.
Father.
Last night, I woke up sitting at a pub
in town and unable to move,
but Pride saved me
before anyone noticed.
It was all part of a plot
by Erwin and Homer to frame me.
They came to my room
and made me drink spiked wine,
then abandoned me at the pub.
Wait a minute, Leon!
I think there's been a misunderstanding!
Homer is right!
We only insisted
on sharing some wine last night
because we were sad to part ways with you.
But we'd never spike it!
That's just a wild accusation!
Except it's not.
Pride's subordinates
rescued me from the pub.
They determined that I had been drugged.
Well, that proves nothing!
It's all just rubbish
cooked up by Princess Pride!
The Kingdom of Freesia
is trying to pull the wool over your eyes!
He's right!
Freesia has been buttering you up,
Elder Brother.
Now they're painting us
in a bad light with this nonsense
to give them an excuse
to declare war on our nation!
I guarantee it!
I mean,
it hardly seems like a coincidence
they somehow found you
just in the nick of time, right?
It's painfully obvious.
The Kingdom of Freesia
has fabricated this entire thing,
either by hiring someone
to do the kidnapping,
or even just convincing you
to play along, Elder Brother.
Erwin, Homer...
I thought I made myself clear!
I warned you to clean up your act
before it's too late!
They have done an intensely foolish thing.
I deeply apologize for their insolence.
Under my authority as the king of Anemone,
Erwin Adonis Coronaria...
Homer Adonis Coronaria...
I hereby strip you both of your
royal titles and all rights therein!
Arrest them!
Yes, sir!
Let me go!
You ruffians!
Who besides me or Homer
is fit to inherit the throne, Father?!
Your Majesty.
I had a premonition.
I know you have
something to discuss with me.
Or rather,
something you originally
wished to discuss with my mother, yes?
It's regarding...
the cancellation of the engagement
between Prince Leon Adonis Coronaria
and myself.
Isn't that right?
In order to officially give Prince Leon
the right to the throne back.
How did you know?!
Crown Princess Pride, at this time-
Wait a moment.
Please,
listen to what I have to say first.
As representative of the queen,
I formally received permission
from my mother.
I am here to request the
immediate dissolution
of the engagement between
Prince Leon Adonis Coronaria and myself.
For that is what
the Kingdom of Freesia wishes.
Ridiculous!
Our brother is the perfect prince!
There is no reason for Freesia
to want the engagement to be dissolved!
He's right!
But there is a reason.
It's because the original need
for our engagement no longer exists.
The engagement was first proposed
as a way to solidify the alliance
between our two kingdoms.
And furthermore, to put that alliance
on display for our neighboring countries.
But I had a premonition.
I saw the future of the Anemone Kingdom,
which fell to the verge of ruin
after Prince Leon left.
Prince Leon, you are someone
that this country needs.
If you wish to become a ruler who loves
and cherishes their citizens,
much like I do,
then we shall be sworn allies.
There is no need for an engagement.
Sworn allies...
Precisely.
As long as our relationship is solid,
there should be no need
to prove our alliance.
The only thing we wish from the
Anemone Kingdom
is to retain the equal partnership
that we've had until now!
And solidify it further!
A strong alliance that doesn't falter
in the face of a cancelled engagement.
There is nothing more ideal!
And as the Crown Princess,
I will make sure it happens...
with my sworn ally, Prince Leon.
It will happen.
Without fail.
You'll regret this, Leon!
You're a joke!
A soulless puppet like you
can never become the king!
You're a dumb patsy who never realized
what Homer and I were up to!
You don't have what it takes
to rule a kingdom!
Everything will fall apart in no time
with you in charge!
Then you'll look back
and realize the truth!
That I was the one worthy of being king!
I'm obviously superior
to a pathetic bastard like you
who can't live without being loved
by the masses!
Shut your mouth!
Now you listen here.
Prince Leon has all the qualities needed
to become a great king.
He is not a puppet
or anything of the sort.
He loves his people more than himself and
strives to live up to their expectations.
He's a vital asset who has
dedicated himself to being a worthy king.
You think everything will fall apart
with him in charge?
In my premonition,
that's exactly what happened after
Prince Leon left and YOU became king.
Under your reign, the people became
so poor they had to leave the country,
which tanks the trade market.
Things got so bad for everyone,
including the royal family,
that they could hardly believe
the Anemone Kingdom was ever prosperous.
Elder Sister...
And worst of all,
the instant things start looking bad,
you come to Freesia
begging for Prince Leon's help!
That's how things play out for them
in the game.
Despite being the source
of Leon's downfall,
they shamelessly
come to him for help over and over.
They beg him to come back.
And then...
They have the gall to ask him:
"Do you not care
what happens to our people?!"
This infuriates Leon
who sends them packing.
And then he breaks down
in Tiara's arms afterwards.
It's one of the most
heartbreaking scenes in the game.
Ever since his brothers were young,
they harbored a sense of inferiority
towards Crown Prince Leon.
That's why they spread rumors about him,
which resulted in Leon being forced
to marry into the Freesian royal family.
However,
the king later learned the truth...
and upon deciding that Leon should be
the heir to the throne after all,
he warned them:
You best clean up your act
before it's too late!
But that doesn't stop them.
Determined to force Leon
out of the running for the throne,
they make him drink,
and drop him off at a pub.
That alone makes them utter scumbags,
but it gets worse...
You witch.
Just how much
did your premonition show you?!
I know all sorts of things.
For example, the fact His Majesty already
learned about your wrongdoings,
and told you he would make Leon
heir to the throne a few days ago.
Remember this.
From here on,
no matter what punishment you face...
if you ever pose a threat to this kingdom
or my sworn ally Prince Leon again,
I will NOT stand for it.
If you dare to cross that line,
then you will be making
a personal enemy of Pride Royal Ivy.
And I will punish you both
with my own two hands.
As if some lucky bitch
born into a Queendom is worth anything!
Ignorant hooligans like you
who don't even try to understand
the role and duties of royalty
are even more worthless.
Leon was racked by so much grief
at the start of the game...
because all of the Anemonians who were in
the pub with him got sentenced to death.
Made even worse by the fact
Pride ordered Leon to kill them himself.
To top it off,
it was his brothers who offered
the innocent citizens to Pride
as "criminals" in the first place.
Soon after Leon moves to Freesia,
the king falls ill and dies,
causing his brothers
to inherit the throne.
They proceed to make
an absolute mess of everything
and then have the gall
to ask Leon to fix it.
They pressure Tiara to help them convince
him to return to the Anemone Kingdom,
and even kidnap Tiara to use as a hostage
and threaten Leon into coming back home.
We all carry the duty of royalty,
so I can't find it in myself
to cut them any slack right now.
Tell me something.
What sort of vision did you have
for this kingdom after taking the throne?
Because if the citizens
weren't the first thing on your mind,
then you're failures.
You have no right to reject Leon
and his incredibly pure heart.
I'm sorry for stepping out of line.
Elder Sister, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Pride...
Thank you.
Prince Leon, please be proud.
Please love. Please wish for things.
Your pure heart and this country
that you love so much...
It's all so very beautiful.
He's gone through so much suffering
these past few days because of me.
Despite being tormented
by the love of his country,
he kept it all bottled inside
to maintain appearances.
He played the role of sweet prince
and suppressed all his true feelings
to avoid any problems.
All while smiling
and whispering words of love to me.
But in reality, he was full of more pain
and tears than anyone.
Thank goodness.
I'm so glad I could give him
the Anemone Kingdom back.
And return him to his rightful place
in the Anemone Kingdom.
Crown Prince Leon Adonis Coronaria.
Do you swear,
in times of sickness and health,
in times of prosperity and poverty,
to love and protect
the people of your country,
and make the nation better for everyone,
by ensuring they can maintain
their livelihoods?
I do!
Your Majesty King Gregorio,
I have one more thing to ask of you.
Allow me to introduce my younger brother
and the knights who helped
to make this right.
Please honor them
with a handshake and a greeting.
Of course.
I will do the same!
Everything should be okay now.
In the game, the king had to make Leon
take responsibility
for the commotion at the pub
and exiled him from the country.
But as soon as Leon was sent to Freesia,
the king fell ill and passed away.
However, Arthur's special ability is the
power to heal anything in creation.
Based on the look he just gave,
I'm sure the king's sickness
has already been healed.
Princess Pride...
You can keep calling me Pride
like you have up to now, Prince Leon.
We are sworn allies, after all.
Then, please call me Leon.
I'd be happier that way.
All right, Leon.
I look forward to seeing you again.
You do?
Yes, I do.
Okay.
Your Highness.
Go ahead.
Pride...
I am forever in your debt.
If you or Freesia ever need anything,
the Anemone Kingdom will...
No, I will come running to your aid,
no matter what.
Let us keep in touch.
I will come see you as often as needed.
And I will be waiting for you here
in my beloved country, always.
Farewell, my darling fiancée.
You are my first love.
P-Princess Pride?!
Elder Sister!
First love?!
Pride? Me?!
Oh jeez!
That's the incredible seductiveness
of the "flirt" archetype
from the first ORL game for you!
Tararebabanashi de yume mitai
Mirai yochi ga dekitara
Hyaku ten juu hyakunijuu ten no mainichi de kuraseru no kana
Tatoeba ano toki iezu ni
Koukai shita gomen ne mo
Ietetara soba ni ita kana
Moshi umare kawaretemo
Mata kono sekai o erabu kana
Doushite? tte
Sonna yabo na koto kikanaide yo
Takai pride ni kokoro odorasereteirun da
Mattaku shou ga nai na mou
Kotoba ga nakutatte wakaru yo
Hitori de kakaekomu nante gohatto
Tsuyosou ni miete dare demo igai to
Yoru wa sentimental ni
Naru no ga kimarirashii
Tararebabanashi de yume mitai
Mirai yochi ga dekitara
Hyaku ten juu hyakunijuu ten no mainichi de kuraseru no kana
Tatoeba ano toki iezu ni
Koukai shita gomen ne mo
Ietetara soba ni ita kana
Tararebabanashi de yume mitai
Mirai yochi ga dekitara
Hyaku ten juu hyakunijuu ten no mainichi de kuraseru no kana
Tatoeba ano toki iezu ni
Koukai shita gomen ne mo
Ietetara soba ni ita kana
The Most Heretical Last Boss Queen:
From Villainess to Savior.
Episode 5:
The Cruel Queen Takes Notice, and is Noticed
"The Cruel Queen Takes Notice,
and is Noticed".