HEAVENWARD
Heavenward!
Yuuki...
You just keep getting stronger, don't you?
Now, let's put an end to this!
Miss Mira... I'm on my way to save you!
My heart sunk and I no longer feel hope for the future
It felt like time froze and now it's all over
Brooding and silent
The umbrella of my heart began to open
Still, I kept my chin up and went on
I won't ask you to comfort me
I want to grow strong and focus on what's ahead
But weakness crushes me
Meeting you is what filled my world with light
I didn't have an ounce of hope, and yet I could laugh
Ordinary conversations always brought me a smile
I won't say thanks 'cause you'll blush and laugh
But I'm thinking it
Can I move forward from here?
O light, come to me
Slave: Heaven
Episode 11
Your trump card, huh?
Fun!
Now it's our turn!
On it!
Slave Support Fist!
Predictable.
Chains? Big deal!
Above us!
That's what happens
when you get caught in them?
They're no ordinary chains then!
Coco... Naon...
I've got you!
You're already done!
Stay outta this!
Yuuki! Cover me!
Big Sis!
Mighty Blade Cross!
Stopped it, huh?
Still...
A god's wrath will always be felt.
Seriously?
It's one attack after the next.
This is gettin' old!
I'll keep drawing them in!
In the name of the Azumas!
We'll hold the line!
Ame-no-Mitori!
Heavenward!
HEAVENWARD
Heavenward...
(TENSHIN)
HEAVENLY FLOWER
(TENKA)
I'll be sure to live up to his feelings.
Peaks of clouds above
How many sink to lay bare
The moonlit mountain?
Free my mind of its limits...
My movements will be enhanced
for a limited time.
The technique I developed
to deal with the Eight Thunder Gods.
I'll show you a powerful technique
of my own!
Bear witness!
MILLIONFOLD
DIVINE
PUNISHMENTS
To my breathtaking majesty!
She's only cloning her arms!
Tremble in terror before my
Millionfold Divine Punishments!
Picture it...
See it in your mind!
They broke through a god's multi-attack?!
But I was going for the kill!
A superficial hit.
I'll push harder with the next one!
All right!
To be on the safe side, I'll send
my clones to deliver the final blow!
Go!
What's wrong?
Get out there with them!
Mira?!
Your clones are slow...
You haven't absorbed Mira completely.
Knock it off!
Let's do it, Yuuki!
Yes, ma'am!
Damn you, Mira!
When I gently opened my eyes
You'll be fully assimilated before long!
I am beautiful!
I was shrouded in darkness
I am a god!
One... then another... I bore the sorrow
I pledge my body...
Through falling tears
to Miss Kyouka!
And I vowed to hold onto hope
Yuuki vanished?
No...
Yuuki's inside that sword!
I always had this dream
One so very far out of reach
It has to come true, that what I wished
That was the moment you and I connected
Accept your punishment from on high!
"Always be positive"
"Always be true"
If I'm with you, everything will be okay
I will turn this world into a garden of light
Sword of Subjugation!
SWORD OF
SUBJUGATION
Wha-
I swear I'll do it, I'll lead us to the future
This...
...launches me from inside her sword...
...using one of my lethal strikes.
It combines my Heavenward power...
...with my martial arts.
Ultimate dual technique!
They're all alive!
If you resist or try to pull
a disappearing act...
you die.
Is this her default form?
Look out!
If you insist on assimilating me...
then it's time to bow down.
Heavenward...
You made the most of it.
Thank you, Miss Kyouka!
I forgot!
What about Big Sis and her friends?
Let me handle this.
Don't move! If you do, I'll shoot!
She retreated underground...
Thank you, Miss Tenka!
Looks like ya conquered a god!
Heal up and relay news
of the enemy's defeat.
I'm going to secure the perimeter
just in case.
I'll get on the report.
Leave the healing to me!
I got plenty of energy left!
That's right!
With Miss Tovera here,
we'll be back on our feet soon enough!
Oh crap... I can finally breathe, but...
I feel like... I'm gonna...
Hi.
Kuusetsu!
Don't panic. None of this is real.
It's your inner world.
A mind palace of sorts.
My... inner world?
I lost my corporeal form, so I manifested
where traces of my energy remained.
Energy?
You drank highly concentrated
divine nectar, remember?
Oh, that...
The thing about gods is,
they don't just vanish into thin air.
That said, my corporeal form is gone.
It's impossible for me to affect
the ouside world, much less fight.
You and I...
are left with no choice but to get along.
You're about to wake up...
Well, from now on, we can chat whenever.
You should feel lucky having
a beautiful god living inside you.
L-lucky?
Where am I?
The 7th Squadron dorm in Mato, Mr. Yuuki!
What? Was that whole thing a dream?!
H-huh? But...
Calm down right now!
Senpai's orders!
O-okay.
You lost consciousness after the battle
in Yokohama, Mr. Yuuki.
You've been asleep for about two days.
And they... brought me here?
Your wounds have been healed.
It seems you're perfectly healthy!
The commander is at HQ with
Commander Kamiunten and the others
relaying what happened in Yokohama.
In that case...
I should also get to work.
For today...
you should rest!
Nei will handle the cooking.
You should have a bath, too!
Thanks.
I'll take Nei up on her offer
and freshen up first!
I had a feeling you'd be awake.
My body started moving on its own.
I forgot!
She hasn't given me my reward yet!
How are you feeling?
Fit as a fiddle!
Feelin' right as rain, myself!
And they say you're the one who saved me!
Thanks, kid!
Everyone worked together.
He's right.
A victory earned
by all of the Demon Defense Force.
Especially you, Mira.
Fighting back even after she consumed you?
Stubborn as ever.
The thought of lettin' her absorb
all my power got me worked up.
Perfect timing since we're all here!
Lend me a hand with the debriefing.
I'm sorry, but the debriefing has to wait.
What?! How come?!
His reward is starting. Give us a minute.
I intend to reward him, too.
What for?!
It's like you said, Kyou-chin.
This victory belongs
to the Demon Defense Force.
So those who can reward him should.
Squeeze
Squee
Is that the issue here?!
eeeze
He did go out of his way
to rescue me himself...
I-I'll help with the reward.
Quit pressuring yourself.
Wha-
From the looks of it,
we're taking a bath together.
A-a bath?!
We don't even share a journal!
Tremble
There's no way!
And what the hell, Tenka?!
Your body isn't moving on its own!
TURMOIL
Why aren't you freaking out more?!
I can't get undressed!
It's too embarrassing!
And I was the one who suggested it!
B-being met with a sight like this...
I'm so nervous, I'm paralyzed!
Are you feeling dizzy?
I think he's shy.
Doing something like this
in a hot spring...
Pervert.
You did great out there.
U-um...
Th-there's something you should know!
What is it?
A god inside of Yuuki...
Sounds harmless enough.
It's difficult to tell
whether it was just a dream.
Right.
I can't talk to her right now, either.
I'll be sure to keep a close eye on you.
We'll see how it plays out.
From now on, report anything unusual.
Y-yes, ma'am!
N-nope... Still can't do it!
The Next Day
In anticipation of the
Eight Thunder Gods' next attack,
Kyouka and Mira held a post-mortem
on the battle with Kuusetsu.
They focused on Mira's loss to Kuusetsu,
carefully reflecting
on what factors caused it.
Yup. In the end,
I shouldn't have come at her head-on.
But it's because you were worn out
from saving the city-goers.
As a commander, I wish I could've
taken down a god, too.
Everything turned out fine, I guess.
But I can't settle for less.
As talented as Miss Mira is,
she's extremely hard on herself.
Kyouka.
Lemme borrow the kid.
Love beam!
Wanna know and wanna do, wanna touch
These feelings pouring out of me just won't stop
Sweet, so sweet, let me in with your body darling
I'll domesticate you, time for a reward
With the heat from skin on skin overlapping
It's fully charged
Now ready to launch!
Shoot from my hand now, love love beam
Aim for your heart now, love love beam
Bridging the gap between us
And firing from point blank
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
You won't escape my love love beam
To the ends of the Earth, love love beam
Yeah, love is what changes the world
Dye it all heart-colored, even the darkness
This is the story of a dream
that Yuuki had!
High school?! What am I doing here?!
Hello?
Quit zoning out
first thing in the morning.
Uh, s-sorry!
Yo, underclassman!
Hey! Lessons are starting soon!
Get to the classroom!
Everyone's a student now?!
This is your world.
I can make things like this happen.
A god meddling in my head?!
Combing through your memories...
You didn't have a mate in school, did you?
I'll be your mate.
We'll pick up where we left off!
Wh-what's going on?
My body's moving on its own again!
Play it cool!
There's a ton of questions
you need to ask!
I have to turn this around before-
Ah, he escaped!
Yuuki cuts class.
Gods Assemble
Episode 12
Next time, Episode 12: "Gods Assemble"!
Here's today's bonus!
Welcome to Slave High School!
Oh, you don't have a mate?
Well, in that case...
I'll be your mate.