m 0 0 l 0 102 32 102 b 3 75 3 32 32 0
OSHI NO KO
Top of the Idols
Do you ever go out with boys, Ruby-chan?
With boys? Oh, just the other day,
my brother and I went out
to get curry buns at the store.
Uh, I don't think he qualifies as a "boy."
No?
Does that mean Onii-chan is a girl?
Like hell he is!
How about you? Don't you ever
want to go on dates and stuff?
Oh, never!
I don't even have anyone to go with!
Why do they keep asking us
about boys and dates and all that stuff?
Those are the topics that attract
the most interest, probably.
Top of the Idols
Guest Idols
Dressing Room
Here's B-Komachi to have
their makeup retouched.
Thanks in advance!
Oh, hey there.
Kana-san, MEMcho-san,
please sit down here.
Ruby-san, could you wait
over there for a bit?
Hey, Iwasaki-chan.
Can you cover this up with concealer?
Oh? Is that a hickey?
My boyfriend actually
has this thing for biting.
He keeps trying to mark me before gigs.
Oh, wow. That's risky.
I know, right?
You've been living with your
boyfriend for what, four years?
Are you getting married once you retire?
Nah, that's probably not happening
until I'm thirty or so.
By the way, does Anmi-chan
still go drinking in Kabukicho?
You bet. She's totally
a dude on the inside.
Seriously?
When is she gonna grow out of that?
My first thought after diving
into this business was,
"Wow, a surprising number of
these girls have boyfriends."
The idea that idols can't date really only
exists in the minds of the consumers.
Enter Passcode
If you do, cover it up.
Don't get caught. That's how many insiders
define professionalism in this biz.
When idols go eat with the opposite sex,
they always pick private rooms
and choose restaurants
far away from concert venues.
*Here we have a girl whose lack of popularity
with the boys drove her crazy
YouTubers don't talk about their partners,
and they're careful to keep their
relationships low-key in public.
Many male voice actors keep
their marital status under wraps.
Merry Christmas!
We got together to have Christmas cake!
#MerryXmas
And some female VAs
meet up to take Christmas pics in advance
to make it look like they're single.
Half the human race is the opposite sex.
Living life avoiding the other half
may seem possible, but it's really not.
So what risks do you or don't you take
to live your own life?
That dilemma is a huge part
of an entertainer's job.
Or at least, it used to be.
That idea of professionalism has
started to change a bit in recent years.
Hot topic!
Actor E Remarries & Purchases Luxury Home
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hNew Life In a Highly Desirable Residence
His partner, a classmate from high school
Popular Idol H and Actor K Affair Discovered!
Women's Heaven
The cause is a shift
in the nature of gossip reporting.
2.5D Actor Caught Two-Timing
Actress Momoka Kotori With Coactor
Fans Livid
Heroine In Affair
Steamy Love
While the rise of social media has led
to a huge increase in gossip stories,
Lover Found
Attitude Changes Overnight
Model's Apartment
it's also watered down
the significance of each individual one.
Exclusive: "It was Hell"
Decides on Comeback
Scandals no longer do
lethal damage to entertainers.
Now, even the ones who get outed
can make a full comeback in time.
You didn't break any laws or anything,
so the fans will understand!!
Welcome back!!
Ignore the haters!
I'll root for you no matter what!!
This trend has probably given a fair few
idols some much-needed peace of mind.
After all...
most "steamy romance" gossip about idols
is leaked by members
of their inner circle.
Showbiz is hardly just glitz and glamour.
It's such a cruel and harsh place that
sometimes you just want to run away.
Tokyo
Super Hot
Weekly Social Media Hit Chart
PM Sakaichi Meets With President Stump
Niigata Records Largest Snowfall in History
Brohei Kotani Prepares for New Season
Popular Idol Holds Retirement
Press Conference
JP Burger Chain Lands in USA
Another Bear Spotted in Tokyo
Spring Fashion Lineup Revealed
Popular VTuber Holds First Budokan Concert
Reiwa's Noodle War
Food Researcher Launches Channel
Nina-san suddenly announced
her retirement last night.
Wow.
She's quitting?
Her group had really been
picking up in popularity, too.
We asked her fans for their thoughts.
What a shame.
Doesn't matter if you're popular or not.
Some girls just aren't cut out for this.
Sticking with a job can be pure torture
if it feels like a bad fit for your life.
Hey, hey! What's with the doom and gloom?
What's the matter? Wanna talk?
Why don't we go out and get smashed?
Wait, you're only 18! Can't drink yet!
Drink...
Sorry.
It's nothing. Don't worry about me.
I'd just like to be
left alone for a while.
Aqu-tan! Aqu-tan! Aqu-tan!
Whoa, why so frantic?
MEMcho, I bet your scalp smells good as hell.
I'll pay 100,000 yen for your dandruff. Deal?
Did you get a creepy message
in your Marshmallow Q&As?
MEMcho, I bet your scalp smells good as hell.
I'll pay 100,000 yen for your dandruff. Deal?
Swing and a miss!
That happens all the time!
Why would I pitch a fit over it now?!
We need to do something!
Kana-chan might leave B-Komachi!
What makes you think so?
You know how she always runs her mouth
but never lets her actual feelings show?
She's always talking smack to cover up
what she's thinking on the inside.
But lately, she's been making it
obvious that she's in a funk.
It seems like a pretty clear yellow flag.
If this keeps up,
things might really turn sour.
Look after her somehow.
I'm doing everything I can, okay?
But...
I bet nothing I say
will get through to her.
And you know how Ruby is now.
The only one who can
really fix Kana-chan is...
Don't come to me for help with Arima.
Like I told you before,
I'm not going to half-ass this.
I won't be irresponsible.
I have no right to.
I get what you're saying.
You don't want to lead her on...
You don't wanna hurt her any more, right?
But hey, listen... Kana-chan...
Kana-chan's probably only being
an idol for you, Aqu-tan.
She believed in and took this path
because you asked her to.
She became an idol
because that's what you wanted.
You're the one who
dragged her into this world.
It doesn't have to be a lot.
Just give her something, anything.
Excuse me.
You're Kana Arima-san, yes?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Questions Regarding Kana Arima-san
Dear Saitou-sama of Strawberry Productions,
My apologies for contacting you out of the blue.
I'm Itano, part of the editorial team for Houdensha's
True Showbiz Weekly. We plan to publish a story
on your talent, Kana Arima-san, in our next issue.
We're sure you would like to review the content
and/or contest certain points.
So it might be best for both parties
if we could conduct an official interview.
2 Attachments
File 1
File 2
Oh, no.
This is going to be a real mess.
Excuse me.
You're Kana Arima-san, yes?
I'm a reporter with True Showbiz Weekly.
I'd like to ask you a few questions
about your relationship
with Director Masanori Shima.
Huh?
A tabloid reporter? Why?
Is this about that night?
The two of you went into
his apartment the other night, yes?
His staff had all left by that time.
What do I do?
He's a married man, and yet
you spent all night together.
What do I say?
What were you two doing?
Arima-san.
This is you, is it not?
What can I say?
You two seem quite close.
Why are you silent?
Could you—
Huh? Wait, Arima-san?
Does running away mean you admit it?
Why won't you explain yourself?
Arima-san!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Are you free rn?!
I'm having dinner
in Roppongi
Director Shima's
gonna join me
Wanna come??
There you are, Shima!
If he takes a liking to you,
you could land an acting gig.
Go for it.
He's not a playboy or anything.
Is this going to be in the news?
I didn't do anything!
But I did follow him into a private room.
I was alone with a man all night...
I definitely look guilty!
This is gonna hurt the other B-Komachi
members and the agency staff, too.
What do I do?
So I looked up
"how to keep white ants as pets"...
Huh? You can't get in touch with her?
No. And we have no idea where she's gone.
Did Ruby get anything?
A message? A call?
Sorry, Ruby-san's shoot is running
behind schedule right now.
I'll ask her once she's done.
Okay, please do.
Nope, Kana-chan's not answering.
She wasn't in the studio, either.
She's never once skipped lessons before.
I...
I'm gonna go look for her!
Hold it.
Do you have any leads?
Just running around isn't going to help.
I know that...
But I can't just sit around and wait!
It could be that Arima-san's
already heard the news.
I swear...
We need to hear the details from her
to figure out how to counter this, too.
But she may not come back today.
She will.
You don't get it.
I know you're an exception,
but kids around her age
normally aren't that tough.
Publishers, fans, and us agencies...
We prey on young, fragile kids
You're an idol.
Please act more responsibly.
you're so unserious
and put too much pressure
and responsibility on their shoulders.
please think about
how your fans might feel
This business thrives on breaking
the hearts and lives of you kids.
I'm heading out, too.
I have to bring MEM back, at least.
An idol, falling for a guy?
Talk about unprofessional.
Hurting your peers doesn't bother you?
That was so cute, right?
Yeah!
Way to ruin your image.
You're just so... filthy.
I trusted you.
Gimme back all the money I spent on you.
I've seen what happens to disgraced idols
too many times to count.
You let me down.
I know exactly what fans say to them.
If you cared about your fans at all,
you never would've done this.
I tore up your trading cards.
I'm done being an otaku.
Disgusting. I can't.
Scamming little whore.
Just quit already. Get out of my sight.
Some guy's probably
consoling her right now.
If you're gonna be a pro idol,
be a pro all the way.
I trusted her, and she betrayed me.
Nobody would care if she'd
done this after she retired.
"I spent the money you spent on
me on dates with a guy, lol!"
She didn't even stop to think
this would hurt her group.
I only stanned her 'cuz I
thought she'd never do this.
The girl lost to horny.
Don't be an idol
if you want a love life.
Lack of character,
plain and simple.
You do this after acting
all high and mighty?
Can't even stick to
her own word, huh?
In the end, you only saw being an idol
as a way to stay in the industry.
read
Where'd you go?
Come back already
Sheesh, that MEM...
Miyako
Got it
Kana Arima
Sent a sticker
There aren't many people in my life I can
empty my head and shoot the breeze with.
But I don't have to care
about all that with you.
Care a little, damn you!
But hey...
Being chosen for that role
doesn't feel so bad, I guess!
If I quit, will they let me off the hook?
I guess I never was meant to be an idol.
I have a foul mouth
and a nasty personality,
and I'm always whining about
not getting the gigs I really want.
I'm nothing like the ideal
idol in everyone's minds.
I'm not genuine enough to believe
I'm "doing it for the fans."
I'm the furthest thing
from sweet and innocent.
I tried to hang in there somehow,
and look where it got me.
I don't know what I'm
supposed to do anymore.
Somebody tell me.
Nobody wants the real Kana Arima.
I'm not cut out for this.
I'm not meant for this!
Help me...
Help me, Aqua.
What the hell did I just say?
I turn to a guy for help
only when I need it?
How gross can I be?
Am I trying to make myself feel better
by playing the damsel in distress?
Am I begging and pleading
for forgiveness and approval?
Shame on me.
Oh, man. They're gonna say I'm a slut
who's sleeping her way up.
Talk all the shit you want, you losers!
I've been dealing with that crap
since I was a preschooler!
I don't even like the fans!
What do I care what they say about me?
Somebody else can play
the sweet and innocent role.
No matter what, no matter how...
I'm gonna be myself!
And I'm gonna survive in showbiz
as just little ol' me!
See?
It'll take way more than this
to break Kana Arima.
I'm heading out to look for her too
Let me know if you find anything
Thanks, Aqu-tan.
I'll hit up places she's likely to go
Where'd you go?
Come back already
Arima will be fine.
Look around here
She has B-Komachi and the rest.
Me?
She doesn't need me.
Hikaru Kamiki
Started an agency at 25
Was in Lalalai for six years,
from the age of 10 to 16
No details on later activity
Might have an accomplice?
Aqua Hoshino
Been in showbiz since childhood
Thinks the target of his revenge is dead
Must not be allowed to come in contact
Hikaru Kamiki.
He started his own agency when he was 25.
Getting information on someone is easy
once you know who you're investigating.
I couldn't figure out what he did from
16, when he quit Lalalai, until 25...
Media EYES, Inc.
But that's the place.
Maybe I should have become
a private eye, not an actress.
Episode 30
Idols and Relationships
Translation
Sriram Gurunathan
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check
Gabriella Alabanza
Translation Check
Michelle Tymon