This is all we were able to recover.
We found the remnants
in the guild fireplace,
although most of it had burned away.
What's this?
A contract receipt of some kind?
Mahaeyzel Zelkoff.
If only we could get
that man into custody.
That seems unlikely now.
He has either left this town
far behind or...
Permission denied.
I'm not authorized to release him.
Yes, I realize your hands are tied.
However, circumstances have changed.
I have a special order for his release.
Is this genuine?
Of course it is. That's the seal
of Galtuile right there.
The local military supervisor
was very understanding.
Of course, you're more than free
to confirm it with them.
But locking up a hero hardly seems
like punishment, don't you think?
He'll be sleeping his days away,
safe and secure as can be.
Right?
Wait here a minute. I'll go confirm this.
By all means, please do.
Sentenced to Be a Hero
I desire an outing, my knight.
Do you not feel the same way?
You like that zeff butter way too much.
I can suffer no more
of this confinement.
I wish to go outside.
It's not like we have a choice.
If you desire an outing, my goddess,
I recommend the Dujin Art Museum.
It houses a collection of masterpieces
from the middle classical era,
while the building itself is a showcase
of modern Nashida techniques.
It has much to recommend it.
Of course, as a strategic port,
Ioff City is home to many great works...
What's so fun about some dumb museum?
If you wanna go out,
hit the ocean.
The view's great when you fly out to sea.
Aerial hunting in the forest
is a great choice, too.
Those all assume you can fly.
Try to think of stuff
a non-dragon would like.
Huh? You got a problem with dragons?
I-I would accept anything.
I simply wish to go into town.
Not happening.
Did you forget there's a target on your back?
They're never letting us out again.
Disappointing.
Actually...
I can give you permission.
You can?!
As long as you don't go farther
than the Temple.
The barracks are close,
and we can arrange a full security detail.
Kivia, on occasion, you are
the bearer of excellent news.
Is there a reason for this?
Yeah, this isn't your usual MO.
No reason. I simply wish
to improve Goddess Teoritta's mood.
As you should. Xylo, you should seek
to curry favor with me as well.
You're not supposed to ask for it.
Xylo.
Let High Priest Marlen
know about your outing.
I'll put together a unit of
trustworthy soldiers for you.
You're not coming?
I...
I'm busy.
Got it. I'll look after Teoritta.
Goddess!
Great Goddess of Swords, Teoritta!
Will you sign my tunic?
Sign my book, too, please.
All will be done!
I, the great goddess Teoritta,
shall bestow my blessings upon you all.
Yay!
Do mine!
And mine, Goddess Teoritta!
There's an old superstition that a goddess's
signature wards off misfortune.
Goddess Teoritta, one for my sister!
And for my mom!
I guess people still believe it.
Get what you need, then clear out.
Blessed goddess.
Here. For you.
You're no bigger than my grandchild,
yet you go fighting the Demon Blight.
Indeed so. I am a truly mighty goddess.
Do you see, my knight?
This is the treatment all goddesses seek.
You must take great pride in it.
Oh, I will also share my sweets with you.
Thanks, I'm sure.
Still, I should probably check for poison.
Sorry, ma'am.
I'll have to confiscate these.
Isn't that the Soaring Lightning,
the Demon Lord hunter?
He's the Thunder Falcon, Xylo Forbartz!
Think he'll sign something for me?
They know about me, too?
You've gained considerable popularity.
High Priest Marlen.
Word has gotten out about your deeds
at Mureed Fortress and Sodrick's Shell.
Right, but I'm a penal hero.
It's the high priest!
I'm sure these children
don't yet know what that means.
E-Excuse us!
I've reevaluated you, too.
C'mon, let's go!
R-Right!
My niece has told me
a great deal about you.
Patausche tends to value honor
over her own life.
A desire to be remembered
for great deeds, I suppose.
It's a troubling thing, don't you agree?
Couldn't say.
There are more people like that
than you'd think.
Especially in the Demon Blight fight.
Though I'm sure it's not easy
when it's your own niece.
I care for Patausche
as if she were my own daughter.
If anyone were to betray her
or bring her sorrow,
they would answer to me.
Listen to me, Xylo Forbartz.
I understand you have a fiancée—
What's that?
That bell means...
Xylo. What does it mean?
It's an attack.
Ioff City once more finds itself...
under siege.
Ah, fancy meeting you here.
What are you doing in here?
Oh, I realized I made a mistake
in a recent report.
I figured I should try
to put it right at once.
Crucial military and Temple documents
are stored here as well.
Only officers are allowed in here.
Oh, is that so?
I had no idea. Do forgive me.
We're preparing for combat.
Get out of here.
Yes, of course.
I'll get the hero unit together.
I hope we can keep this between us.
I wish you'd consider the fact
I have to free you every time.
Oh, Xylo?
Hello there, Comrade Xylo.
Glad to see you're doing well.
Seems you had quite a time
while I was away.
My heart broke for you
in my prison cell.
And you're as smug as ever.
Would this be the goddess
everyone's talking about?
It's my pleasure, Goddess Teoritta.
I am Rhyno.
I serve as artillery
for Penal Hero Unit 9004.
Comrade Xylo and I are partners,
you might say.
I would not say that.
Hey, Venetim.
Maybe we pulled him out too early.
Just looking at this bastard
is pissing me off.
You're the one who wanted him released.
Seriously, a volunteer hero
getting himself stuck in a cell...
What the hell were you thinking?
I merely wished to be of service to the
vulnerable folk trampled by the faeries.
I had no choice but to do what I did.
You had no choice
but to shell civilian houses?
That makes no damn sense.
Now, now.
For now, let's work together
to get through this latest trouble.
Well, then.
Ioff Cheg is the port district.
It seems the faeries
first came from this area.
The horde then moved
to occupy this location:
the Coral Tower, Tui Jia.
That tower's crucial
to our coastal defense.
There's a Demon Lord in the horde,
and there's concern
Tua Jia will be faeried.
It's a trap.
They've got artillery, too, don't they?
With the current wind direction and speed,
you could hit anywhere
in Ioff Cheg from there.
So they're holding
this whole region hostage?
What are Galtuile's orders?
W-Well, regarding that...
The Thirteenth Order of the Holy Knights
and the Ioff City Guard
will be stationed in the inland district,
while the hero unit alone
will defend the port district.
We're to hold out until reinforcements
arrive to begin the counterattack.
Wait for reinforcements? So they're
abandoning everyone in the port district?
I-I'm sure the Noble Alliance wish to
prioritize defense of the inland district.
That's where the government facilities
and noble properties are concentrated.
Damn it. Only concerned
about themselves.
Listen. There's no point in getting hurt
or killed for a mission like this.
W-We should probably avoid
any particularly aggressive plans.
Have you no shame, Venetim?
No matter the trials we may face,
we are the people's sole line of defense.
This is a battle worth
laying down our lives for.
Hey, lay off the suicidal talk for a—
What a magnificent goddess.
Your willingness to die is truly radiant.
I'm in complete agreement.
Comrade Xylo, the time
has come for us to fight.
Let us join hands and fight together
for the people's hope and futures.
Shut up. It's just our job either way.
Xylo, I believe you can do this.
I have faith in you.
Yeah. I won't let those assholes
have their way.
They'll pay for underestimating me.
We'll construct our stronghold here.
It will be a site the people can evacuate to.
Construct a sacred seal fence
in accordance with my blueprints.
Sir!
Next, we'll set up fires.
Gather sacred seal-infused
cookware and food.
Sir!
Hey, what are those guild people doing here?
Apparently, His Majesty
said he'd give them work.
Guaranteed them salaries and titles, too.
Titles?
First, let's go gather the wood!
As much as your arms can carry!
Sir!
Hurry it up! Look lively!
Well, better than them
becoming highwaymen, I guess.
Very hot, but very good.
Here, Tatsuya.
Have some.
You idiot. Not with your hands.
That is what happens when you rush.
You're spilling yours, too.
A hot meal invigorates
a soldier's spirit.
Prioritizing securing meals...
Comrade Norgalle is a brilliant leader.
Wonderful, isn't it?
Th-That is quite an outfit.
A Neven Artillery Seal Compound.
Don't ask me why he's got
that old-fashioned armor on.
I thought we'd have the whole unit
back together at last.
Won't Comrade Tsav
and Comrade Jayce be joining us?
Tsav's getting treated for his arm.
But in the circumstances, they'll likely do
the bare minimum and send him to us.
Ow, ow, ow!
And Comrade Jayce?
He didn't receive the order to deploy?
Venetim's negotiating that now.
They think sending a dragon
for urban warfare is too dangerous,
but he'll make it happen.
His Majesty probably
won't leave the base.
We need Dotta out scouting.
So it'll just be the four of us
heading to Tua Jia.
Which, I have to say...
is clearly not enough.
Could I make a suggestion?
Sure, why not?
I can shell the wall down.
Flood the inland district with faeries,
and the other soldiers
will be forced to fight.
It'll solve our manpower issue.
Pain and suffering
should be shared equally.
It's a beautiful thing.
It's how humans form bonds.
Uh, my knight, this man is...
Yeah, I know.
Request denied.
You'll put civilians in danger, idiot.
Do you have a better idea, Comrade Xylo?
Rhyno, it's not bonds
that motivate most people.
It's profit.
Shell the ships moored in the harbor.
You can hit them from here, right?
Yes, I see. You really
are brilliant, Comrade Xylo.
Then we're taking that down.
We'll take back Tui Jia
and kill the Demon Lord.
Captain Kivia. We'd like
your instructions for the mission.
Right. I'm on my way.
It's a foolish order,
no matter how you slice it.
I'm afraid we have no choice.
Keeping the support
of the nobles is vital.
There are a lot of Temple buildings
in that district as well.
Ah, so sorry to barge in.
What do you want? The hero unit
should be in the field already.
Yes, indeed. As their commander, I'd love
to be there, rallying them to the cause...
But I fear faeries have attacked
the sacred seal vessels in the harbor.
What?
The loss of the Temple's resources
is simply unacceptable.
I seek permission to make use
of our dragon.
Ridiculous. Why would the faeries
attack sacred seal vessels first?
New orders!
A large sacred seal vessel
is currently on fire!
The Temple is requesting our aid.
Thank you. Dismissed.
Ma'am!
I see. You were telling the truth.
So it's all true.
I also found it hard to believe
when I first heard the news.
A terrible shame, isn't it?
Very well.
I authorize your unit to use a dragon.
Captain?
The Temple's request
is all the reason we need.
We'll also send some of our soldiers.
Your generosity is most appreciated.
Oh, and...
Give my regards to High Priest Marlen.
What's that supposed to mean?
Huh? Oh, I was merely—
What was that about my uncle?
What are you insinuating?
I-I swear, I wasn't—
My uncle, High Priest Marlen,
is a great man!
He's devoted his life to the Temple!
His support for me and the Holy Knights
has never wavered!
And yet, you dare...
Y-You have it all wrong.
It's just, well...
I have a suggestion about security
in the underground waterway.
Run!
No, not that way!
Get to the shelter!
Xylo! They're coming right for us! Bogies!
From the right, too! You're surrounded!
Right! Dotta, keep an eye on the situation.
Incoming!
Well, well...
Bogies are the bane of artillery.
Comrade Xylo, if you please?
Got it.
Let's get in there too, Teoritta.
Right.
I shall grant you my blessing!
Get gone!
Truly, nothing beats
a comrade hero by your side.
How lucky I am.
Keep running. We'll charge
all the way to Tui Jia—
Wait!
There's a warehouse up ahead. Um...
It's got a Verkle Corp mark,
and the braziers are lit.
I think people are holed up inside.
And the faeries are swarming it.
They improvised a shelter?
Of all the damn times...
What should we do, Comrade Xylo?
Xylo. This would be an honorable battle.
I wish...
Yeah, I know.
Rhyno, I'll be working you to death.
Get ready.
But of course.
For the sake of strangers whose names
I'll never know, I serve gladly.
Isn't this fun?
The breaking flash seal was a direct hit.
We make a great team, don't we?
You especially, Goddess Teoritta.
Your power is incredible.
Y-Yes.
Though I feel strangely ambivalent
about your praise.
There's no need to be
so uncomfortable around me.
You and I are really very similar.
You're not similar at all.
Anyway, the Holy Knights
should be on the move now.
Isn't that right, Venetim?
What? O-Oh, yes!
I managed to get permission
for Jayce to participate.
And I got the underground
waterway locked down.
The waterway?
Was it invaded?
Actually, it was
a spur-of-the-moment suggestion.
You did that off the cuff? Seriously?
Well, seems like a good idea to me.
Defense of the urban area
should be taken seriously.
Frenci and the night-gaunts
are defending the urban area.
Spriggan's still out there, too.
Uh, Xylo!
Ahead and to the right! On the roofs!
That's really not good!
What's not good?
Oh, lightning staffs?
So they can use sacred seals?
Are you kidding me?
Did the coexisters arrange this?
Rhyno!
Yes, I see.
Good. No damage.
Though it did drain some luminescence.
Damn it. I'd like to duck
into an alley, but—
No time for delays.
Wait, don't—
Th-The houses...
Well, saving lives takes priority, after all.
That's not the problem here.
Now, onward.
To the people awaiting our salvation.
Go!
Kill them all!
Don't let them into the inland district!
Fire!
Good. These are the last of them.
So they locked down the waterway?
We'd planned to send
the faeries in that way.
Impressive planning.
You have my praise.
What? Someone's there.
A faerie?
A-A human?
Who are you? What are you doing there?
I would advise you not to resist.
A painful death is a pitiable thing.
Uncle!
Patausche. Thank you for coming.
I hear faeries have been sighted
in the inland district?
Yes. I received word from the guards.
They seem to have come in
through the waterway.
The military and the Temple
are working together?
Did you coordinate this, Uncle?
This is no time for us
to be butting heads.
What is a high priest for
if he can't bring people together?
This peril will strengthen the bonds
between military and Temple more than ever.
Those bonds are what will
bring humanity our victory.
Uncle.
I am moved by your words, Uncle.
I'm counting on you, Patausche.
Let's overcome this trial together.
Right.
May Saint Mahaeyzel protect us.
Now, let's go on the attack.