Partway through the 21st century,
the mafiosi who ruled the
underworld became "Dark Lords."
And the bounty hunters who
would slay these Dark Lords?
They are known as...
the heroic Braves!
Broke again.
Dammit, if only they hadn't
found me at that last hotel...
If I can't find a gig before
the end of the month,
I won't be able to afford this room.
Should I try and sell
off the extra E3 I have?
No!
Illegal
Or I could take a hit job
from a random Dark Lord...
Absolutely not!
Illegal
Yashiro-san
You coming today?
Well, no sense sulking around here.
Guess I'll head to Ed's
and see what's available.
Scum of the Brave
A Brave's Errands
Master!
Jogamine Aki
Brave in Training
Why are you here?
Oh, that's so mean.
Not you, her!
HER
I told you not to come back again!
I invited her.
You wanna die?!
Ishino the Musician
Hobby: Recording Death Cries
Don't worry, Master!
Your assorted harsh words
from the other day—
Go home. Leave!
Flunk out already!
We have accepted them all as trials!
I, Jogamine, am prepared
to come call upon you
until you accept me as your apprentice!
Ignore her.
I actually have a job for Jogamine-san,
related to her encounter with
the Count of Amber Thorns.
You're actually looking into that?
And I accepted, in order
to pay my monthly tuition!
Considering she can read people's minds...
She might be able to find something
about that weird regeneration power.
Interested?
Hell no, leave me out of it.
Hey, Yashiro-san, you've been
off your game lately.
Are you losing your edge
with Malta-san being gone?
That's rich, coming from a
joke of a swordsman like you.
Excuse me, who is Malta-san? A woman?
You wanna hit up the dojo
so I can kick your ass?
Unfortunately, I have a job
that needs attending to.
Could you please answer me, Master?!
Shut up! Go home!
I will not!
Hey, Ed!
Throw this noisy kid out!
You're noisier.
And if you're not gonna
order, go home.
Fine then.
Now, wait a second, Yashiro-san.
Can you serve as Jogamine-san's
bodyguard during her investigation?
Why in the hell would I?
For 115,000 yen.
The exact amount you owe
me after losing at cards.
Since I need to do some
shopping for this job,
I really need you
to pay it back right now...
Then again, if you help me out with this,
I suppose I could call us even...
Sorry. Don't have the cash on me.
Then how about some of
your cards as collateral?
Four copies of "Assault of the
Mountain Infantry" should cover it.
This blows.
Master?
What do you think of my disguise?!
Sara picked it out for me!
Oh, the delinquent princess?
It's less that she's a delinquent...
Oh, never mind.
But seriously, what do you
think of the disguise?
I guess it works?
Not that I care.
Thank you!
Your disguise is great too!
You give off the exact impression
of a hoodlum with no prospects!
Are you trying to start something?
Well, whatever.
Let's get in there and
take care of this, quick.
Right! Leave it to me!
I hate working.
Today at 9PM at a club in Shinjuku,
Matsugi—the peeping tom—will
provide you with some E3.
When that happens, Jogamine-san
will ask a certain question.
What question?
That is something
for you to look forward to.
Hey, you okay with using E3
for an errand like this?
Yes!
If it's to further our mission
of public order,
we are allowed to utilize
it at our discretion.
I see.
And that leads to more junkies.
It's fine, it's fine!
Everybody's doing it.
Master, those people...
Yeah, they're using, too.
The feeling of excitement that comes
from using E3 can become addictive.
It costs an arm and a leg,
but there are still people
who use it recreationally.
Hey, c'mon, don't stick your neck
into unnecessary trouble.
They might even be in
the same business as us.
Granted, I mostly just wanna
get home unaccosted...
Wait, she can hear me, right?
What's your problem?
You drunk off of ginger ale?
No. My ether perception...
I'm able to sense other people's thoughts
as they surface in their minds.
But in a crowd like this...
It's hard to tune into a specific channel.
Not to worry!
I'll be fine after a bit of rest!
Me, worry?
You oughta read my mind.
I think you deserve it.
You really do...
You're a sadist. How perverted.
Huh?
It's Yashiro!
I heard I was meeting with a girl.
So, who is she? Your girlfriend?
Absolutely not.
No, although I don't mind
the misunderstanding!
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Jogamine!
I'm Master's first—
This is Ishino's gofer.
She's real stupid,
so I have to babysit her.
That's cute.
Want some candy?
Candy?
Come on, we're in a rush.
I'd rather we settle this
smooth and quick.
Sure, sure.
Here you go. Nine doses.
Indeed, it is!
Oh, also...
I'm not sure why,
but Ishino-san asked me
to ask you a question.
Yeah?
Sure.
Do you happen to have any E4 for sale?
E4? What's that?
Some kind of codeword?
I dunno. Don't ask me.
In that case, it's quite all right!
Well, I'm off.
Sure.
Oh... Jogamine was your name, right?
Yes!
You really should stop
working for that four-eyes.
Did you read his mind just now?
Yes, perfectly.
The second I posed the
question, his animosity—
no, more like suspicion?
His suspicion of us became very strong.
It's hard to explain, but I think...
Nah, don't bother.
I'm just here as an escort.
You can give Ishino all the details.
Right!
I guess that's this job taken care of.
I see...
Then, I'll be on my way!
I'm a bit curious about that group we
saw before, so if you'll excuse me!
Hey!
Miss—
Pardon me!
Toss
You know her?
Nope.
Pleased to meet you!
I am a second year at the
academy, Jogamine Aki!
I sensed incredible evil,
which led me to this place!
You, the red-headed young man!
You two have taken two women against
their will and confined them here,
with the intent of administering
illegal drugs to them,
before taking advantage of
them in a lascivious fashion!
Because of my ability to
read minds, I know all this!
Release the two of them right now!
If you don't,
then in the name of the academy,
I will serve you justice!
No, no. Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
You've gotta be drunk.
We were doing no such thing.
You know you're not supposed
to mix drinks and E3, right?
I see!
Still, it's inconceivable that
I'd be drunk! After all...
It's illegal for minors to drink!
Get over here.
Listen, you...
Oh, I'm sorry!
It was a somewhat urgent matter,
so I decided that I should
take action immediately!
Braves are professional killers, not cops.
I'm not getting involved in this kind
of mess when it's not even for a job.
Is this really the kind of situation
you should stick your nose into?
Master!
They want help.
I was right after all.
Should've known a gig from
Ishino the Musician...
couldn't end without some trouble.
Scum of the Brave
Hey, Sahara.
Who're these psychos?
Did you pull something?
We're just some Braves passing through.
Braves?
I don't think I've ever seen
a for-real Brave before.
What, am I not for-real enough for you?
What's your name, mister?
Malta. Malta the Mole.
You're lying.
This stuff about you being
a Brave is real,
but that's not your name.
I can tell with stuff like that.
He's telling the truth!
Apparently he can read people's impulses?
Or emotional signals, perhaps.
He's able to perceive that
information as colors.
You could've mentioned that sooner!
What's your real name?
Yashiro. Yashiro the Reaper.
For real?
Looks like it.
So, this guy is who the
Coffin Count's after...
What about you? This your place?
Nope.
But I'm friends with the owner.
Yeah?
And is that friend of yours a Dark Lord?
No.
But he's acquaintances with a
Dark Lord who deals illegal drugs...
Or, rather, a woman who is the
minion of said Dark Lord.
The... Verdigris Quarter?
That's what she goes by.
Okay. Stop. Don't read anything else.
Yes, sir!
You boys have two options.
You can try and kill us right now.
Or you can hand those two over.
I don't get it.
Why are you working
with an academy student?
Do I need to explain myself?
I was really hoping we
could do this peacefully.
That's right!
Master would rather go home
without any more work!
But he's willing to strike you down
if it means saving the others!
Yeah... personally speaking, I think...
It'd be boring to just let them go,
so since we're both pros here,
how about a one-on-one duel?
Ether perception use is allowed.
You can lose via surrender.
And neither side reveals their power.
How about it?
Okay. I'm sure you'd rather keep
your rep intact, after all.
My rep?
I'm a little offended you make
it sound so... professional.
All I really care about
is having a good time.
Master—
Not a word.
He's not lying, right?
He... isn't. But...
That's all I need to know.
He probably understands the
nature of my ether perception.
Considering that he decided to change our
confrontation into something like this...
Well, let's be...gin...
Control of an invisible weapon.
That's his power.
From his stance, it's probably a katana.
There's a chance its
length can change, too.
Dodging isn't gonna get me much.
But at this range, if I step
in with full strength...
Wanna keep going?
Nah. I surrender.
Cool, cool!
You're strong, Yashiro the Reaper.
Wanna come work for our boss?
Let's go.
Right!
Their parents are on the
way to pick them up.
Isn't that great?!
Not at all.
Those pains in the ass
know who I am now.
What a nuisance.
Yes! And I appreciate your
assistance in spite of that!
Why a Brave?
Excuse me?
You could've picked another
way to help people.
Like being a cop...
Or a firefighter.
Fair enough. I think in
my case, it boils down...
to the fact that my father was Brave.
He died before I enrolled at the academy,
but he used to speak to me of
the ideals he held as a Brave.
And so, my dream is to follow in his
footsteps and become a great Brave!
Your old man...
Must've been a decent guy.
That's right!
Only the lowest kind
of scum become Braves.
The good ones all die.
Don't walk so close to me!
But why not?!
'Cause you're obnoxious.
Are you embarrassed?
But you escorted her back
to the dorm, didn't you?
You're so diligent, Yashiro-san.
As a freelancer, you should really
try and enjoy your work more.
Hearing that from you freaks me out, man.
And don't call her to the
bar anymore, seriously.
Are you worried about her?
It's not like that.
She's just in the way.
Still, I don't think
she's going to give up.
Did she happen to tell you?
About who her father is...
Don't.
I don't care.
My chicken's getting cold.
I'm hanging up.
Call Ended
Yashiro
What a shame.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Next Time
Blue skies!
Adorable shibas!
And the encroaching threat
of a wild panda!
Uh, Master, am I even in this one?
Sure aren't.
Next time, Episode 5: "A Brave Teacher".
A Brave Teacher