Beyond Journey's End
Episode 30: The Hero of the South
Will you polish the statue of the hero?
What's the reward?
A spell to scratch the
itchy parts on your back.
29 years after the death of Himmel the Hero,
in Fabel Village, located in the northern lands
We're doing this kind of job again?
There are statues of Mr. Himmel
everywhere, it seems.
Well, odd jobs like these are fun, too.
Let's get polishing.
It's a bronze statue, so we can use magic.
You won't have anything to do, Stark.
Huh?
Wait, who's this guy?!
Is this your first time seeing him?
That's the Hero of the South.
Himmel was the one who defeated the
Demon King, but he wasn't the only hero.
All kinds of heroes made the attempt.
Among them, the Hero of the South
was said to be humanity's strongest.
That seems a bit extreme.
I wouldn't say that.
He was worthy of that title.
At the time, the greatest
threat to humanity
was the Seven Sages of Destruction
who controlled the major regions
around the northern lands.
We actually only defeated two of them.
Of the remaining five,
two either fled or went missing.
Like Aura the Guillotine.
The Hero of the South
defeated the remaining three.
His rapid advance was incredible.
In just a year, he annihilated the
Demon King's front-line troops
and reached the northernmost
end of the Northern Plateau—
the heart of the Demon King's
supply route back then.
That was where he was defeated
by Schlacht the Omniscient—
the Demon King's confidant who could see
1,000 years into the future with magic—
and the combined forces
of all Seven Sages.
All Seven Sages...
That's insane.
The Hero of the South still managed
to defeat three of them,
and he and Schlacht the
Omniscient slew each other.
That battle liberated many people
in this region from the Seven Sages.
The people here are devoted
to the Hero of the South.
Since his body was never found,
legends claim he's still fighting
Schlacht the Omniscient to this day.
Though, given that the demons he
fought had a taste for human flesh,
I think he was actually just eaten.
Shall we get this cleaned up?
I refuse.
I can't defeat the Demon King.
So you refused after all.
As I thought, I don't know the
right words to convince you.
You speak like you already
knew this would happen.
That's because I did.
But I suppose I can tell you why.
Even if you learn my secret,
you'll never tell anyone.
So I shall tell you, and only you...
the reason I am humanity's
strongest hero.
I can see the future.
Huh. That's impressive.
You don't seem to believe me.
It's not that. I just don't care.
Then perhaps this
will pique your interest.
You know of the Seven Sages
of Destruction, do you not?
One year from now in the Northern Plateau,
I will be defeated and slain
by Schlacht the Omniscient
and the Seven Sages.
I will die without achieving my goal.
Don't feel sorry for me.
Even if you accompanied me,
my fate would not change.
But soon,
a young hero will visit you.
I hate to admit it, but he is the one
who will save the world, not me.
You will travel with that young man's
party and defeat the Demon King.
I really can't see that happening.
You'll understand once you meet him.
He'll change your life.
Well, I should go.
May I ask you for one thing?
What is it?
When you meet that young man,
tell him this.
I swear...
I will clear a path for you.
I, humanity's strongest hero:
the Hero of the South.
Even if my accomplishments should
be buried in the shadows of history.
Wait!
You won't get away!
Some future sight you had.
The people here remember you.
History hasn't forgotten.
29 years after the death of Himmel the Hero,
in Graf Dach's domain, located in the northern lands
It's been a while since we
were last in a big city.
We're leaving as soon as
we're done resupplying.
Seriously?
We're not gonna take our time?
Hey, they've got magic shops.
Don't you know, Stark? Time is finite.
Yeah, I know.
That's everything.
Hey, why don't we at least
get something nice to eat?
You know we don't have the money
to spare for that, Stark.
Yeah, but...
Let's hurry.
She's been acting strange
this whole time.
Normally she thinks nothing of staying
in a big city for a few months.
We're too late.
You must be Ms. Frieren.
My lord would like to
invite you to dinner.
We're in a hurry.
Ms. Frieren was a member of the party
of heroes that saved this land.
My lord wishes to thank you all.
This is good.
Thank you for the invitation, Graf Dach.
She looks really unhappy.
Ms. Frieren, thank you for
helping my great-grandfather.
What do you want?
Straight to the point. I appreciate that.
My family's treasured heirloom
sword was stolen by a demon.
It was stolen again?
"Again"?
It was stolen from his
great-grandfather, too.
How does that keep happening?
Very well.
I'd like a grimoire as a reward.
I'll be counting on you, then.
Honestly, a lot of nobles in
the northern lands are pushy,
but this family in particular
makes unreasonable demands.
If you don't get my sword back,
I'll throw you into the dungeon.
What?
Talk about tyrannical.
At least they know which way
the demon fled this time.
That's better than before.
It was a real ordeal looking for it
with no leads at all last time.
Ultimately, we found the sword
at the top of the Schwer Mountains.
That's ridiculous.
But why would the demons
keep stealing this sword?
The Dach family's heirloom sword
originally belonged to a famous demon.
It must possess some appeal
only demons understand.
Anyway, I'm surprised
you accepted this job.
I thought you'd turn it down.
I didn't have a choice.
Himmel brought back that
heirloom sword once already.
If I'd refused, his efforts
would've been for nothing.
Besides, Himmel wouldn't
abandon someone in need.
This village...
It's in ruins.
There's no one here.
No, there's one here.
Are you from this village?
No. I'm a traveling priest.
Who are you?
We're adventurers passing through.
This village was destroyed
by the sword demon.
I was mourning the villagers.
The sword demon...
Probably the demon we're after.
Countless villages have been
destroyed by the sword demon.
There have been no survivors.
How awful.
Adventurers,
will you offer a prayer?
Ms. Frieren?
I knew it.
There are no bodies buried here.
But why?
Because that priest is the sword demon.
There are no corpses left, are there?
I killed them so I could eat them.
I had to in order to survive.
Even though you can eat things
other than humans?
Why is that a reason not to eat humans?
Speaking to it is a waste of time.
Let's take it down.
It's quick.
Mr. Stark.
This is what front-liners are for.
So cold.
This was an awful job.
But we got to defeat a demon.
Sometimes difficult jobs like these
ultimately help lots of people.
That's why I never abandon
someone in need.
You just like taking on difficult jobs.
The challenge is what makes it exciting.
No kidding, huh?
Good job, you two.
Why did you get violent
all of a sudden, anyway?
Because you were about to pray.
It was all I could do in the moment.
People close their eyes to pray.
That demon must have been taking
advantage of that to kill travelers.
Thank you for returning my treasured
heirloom sword, Ms. Frieren.
Now this city is safe again.
I want to go shopping.
Could you drop us off at the marketplace?
Certainly.
The graf seemed quite happy.
I just hope it doesn't get stolen again.
If the demons find it so appealing,
they'll probably keep trying.
I'm sure they will.
That was only the second time
it was stolen,
but they've been attacked
a number of times.
So the demons will keep coming
as long as they have that sword?
It may be a treasured heirloom,
but shouldn't they get rid
of something so dangerous?
It's not that simple.
I guess not.
Nobles can be stubborn about
letting go of treasures like those.
There's that, but letting it fall into
the hands of a demon would be worse.
Demons can't resist showing off
the power they've acquired.
Is that the nature of demons?
A demon went on a rampage
the last time it was stolen, too.
It destroyed a town and three villages.
Seriously?
Not only that, but they say
the demon sweet-talked
one of the graf's servants into helping.
But ever since then,
Graf Dach's family has prioritized
protecting the heirloom sword.
Perhaps now it's not just
his family's mission,
Will I grow up to be strong, too?
but that of the whole city.
Sure you will.
Did the demon have help stealing
the sword this time, too?
I'm not sure.
But as long as humans know desire,
demons will take advantage of that.
Humans also fail to
resist their impulses.
If that happens, I hope you'll
help again, Ms. Frieren.
That depends on the reward.
You'd do it for a grimoire, wouldn't you?
Maybe.
I got a good one this time, too.
That's great, Ms. Frieren.
What kind of spell is it?
A spell to turn a red apple
into a green apple.
Talk about useless.
Translation
Sho Stifler
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Edgar Cruz
Quality Check
Alicia Ashby
Translation Check
Elizabeth Ellis
This brings back memories.
I think I'd like to visit.
You just called me a grandma.
You're so inconsiderate, Mr. Stark.
You sure love hot springs
for someone so young.
It was a truly ridiculous adventure.
You said it'd be quick!
I'm telling you, there's something here.
Episode 31
Somewhere She'd Like
Somewhere she'd like.