Episode 5
This guy doesn't seem
to understand Chinese.
Hey, can you understand me?
I'll remove the tape from your mouth.
If you scream...
Now, answer me.
Who are you guys?
How did you find this place?
What are you doing here?
It flew away!
Tell me! What the hell just happened?
Who on earth are you people?
What's this? Is it blood?
How disgusting, this red stuff...
So the monkey evolved
and its secretions changed color?
That's ridiculous.
What other creatures in this strange
mountain could secrete this?
Maybe poisonous snakes or something?
Are you crazy, Chanon?
It might be poisonous!
It tastes like Godmother!
What's that?
A Chinese sauce!
Sauce? Has the monkey's diet evolved too?
It's poison! Definitely poison!
This environment...
isn't suitable for Aimolu.
I-I've already told you!
Don't hurt me!
I see...
These people are basically
experienced explorers.
There are a few strange guys
among them, probably insiders.
They don't know anything
about their employer.
What...
They'll follow orders from their leader,
Liu Mingyuan, throughout the mission.
What just happened?
A short, fat, bald guy...
Listen! It's Jinbao's voice!
I wonder if the spirit within
Jinbao has unleashed its power.
In this environment,
even a spirit needs time
to prepare its body, right?
I can't hesitate anymore,
even if it means revealing
myself to ordinary people!
This thing is protecting him?
It hasn't attacked us either...
What should we do?
This guy is irrelevant,
but leaving this thing
alone would be problematic.
You guys go ahead.
I'll figure this thing out.
Be careful.
I will.
This thing activates passively.
Average speed...
As for its strength...
It can regenerate.
The scattered branches that it shot out
didn't regenerate along with it.
It might be judging re-usability
based on the extent of the damage.
Approaching it normally...
triggers no reaction.
But if attacked...
it will retaliate.
The black thing inside is its core.
Attacks with a large amount
of qi will be more effective.
Also, this thing isn't very intelligent.
At my level,
getting past it to take the guy out
shouldn't be difficult.
Tell me, what the hell is this thing?
No matter what it is,
you couldn't have made it!
This thing must have been made
by Outcasts from the other side.
It activates whenever
someone gets attacked.
It looks a lot like Ma Xianhong's doing.
Either the whole team was
rigged with one of these,
or everyone on the team has one.
Anyway, whatever it is,
it can leave now!
Foreigners
They're here right now,
Target
and the location of the collection
is roughly where the target is.
All those seemingly complex, winding
branches connect back to this main area.
Qiu, Foreigner, Zhang
If that guy's telling the truth,
then these hired people don't
know anything about this place.
So, they won't be stupid enough to
split up and crawl into narrow branches.
When the time comes,
I'll be in this main area...
Zhang...
This is Granny and Xia's business,
and I'm practically Xia's disciple.
So, let me make the plans this time.
Judging by the time, Xia should
be back from recon soon.
Zhang Chulan, you're right.
The main area is crucial,
so I'll guard it.
Watch out!
What's that?
What's that blurry shadow over there?
Can you see that white humanoid monster?
What the hell is this? Open fire!
So fast!
And their movements are
precise and accurate,
aimed at knocking out the opponent.
The fallen still released Aimolu.
They're all still alive!
These things are man-made!
God of the Jungle,
do you feel the people's fear...
Awaken!
So, everyone has one inside their body.
Baron, you were spot on!
We need to finish this quickly,
before those black things
turn into monsters!
These monkeys are becoming
more and more outrageous.
Telekinesis!
Thanks.
Metal bullets won't destroy them.
Your little tricks don't
seem to be working.
The ability users here aren't ideal.
If you guys stepped in...
Better not.
Ability users from different systems
shouldn't work together until
they fully understand each other.
To put it simply,
I don't trust you yet, Miss Mambo.
There's nothing surprising here.
I'm familiar with all of this.
As for this thing,
it's clearly being manipulated.
You knew we'd encounter ability users,
so you brought us along, right?
Liu?
Vista, you cover the rear.
Chanon, Honda, let's go check it out.
What the hell? Look!
Honda is spouting flames!
Those guys are literally freaks!
Who the hell are you?
And why haven't I seen you all this time?
Well... me neither...
Damn it! Who is she?
Stop her!
Not a monkey or some monster! She's human!
Get away!
Stop! Or I'll shoot!
What's happening?
That gaze feels familiar...
What a tough opponent!
Come back!
Why?
I'm the one you're supposed to fight!
My aim is to sneak up on you
and knock out as many as possible.
So I won't fight you, you badass.
He regenerated? No way!
His speed and strength
are inferior to mine.
But this strange fire disperses
and gathers again...
Judging by this foreigner's
appearance and his weird body...
Void Finger!
Manipulating his body to this extent...
Not bad, this Indian.
He sealed my Kundalini Fire
with that black thing...
Never seen this before.
Hey! Don't shoot!
You'll hurt Chanon.
Vista.
Yeah.
Brave warrior,
I grant you omniscient eyes!
Ozera!
My children,
go!
I can keep up!
Did you get him?
No...
Western alchemists
and Eastern qi cultivators
are the two largest and most organized
factions of ability users.
Not only do these qi
cultivators have abilities,
but they are also physically enhanced.
Don't let them get close.
Even with your protective runes,
you could be taken out in an instant.
He escaped!
They're hiding in the passages! Rally!
Rally! Don't get separated!
You guys check over there!
Don't get close.
Nothing over here!
Over there!
Bao'er, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Okay, that's good.
Wang Zhenqiu, your plan's not bad...
Zhang, Baobao, have you
ever dealt with gunmen?
No.
Yes.
Zhang, let me give you some advice.
Even if your Golden Light Incantation
can withstand high-caliber bullets,
don't let your guard down.
A moment of carelessness could destroy
years of cultivation with one iron bullet.
Here's the plan. I'll guard the main
path leading to the collection.
Qiu
Zhang
Zhang, you'll watch the return route.
That's the least stressful position.
Target - Qiu - Foreigner - Zhang
You don't need to do anything.
Just keep an eye on the overall situation,
especially that bald guy
named Liu Mingyuan.
Qiu, you're so considerate,
setting up this trap,
putting me at the rear.
The others handle the harassment
and scare those guys into retreating.
Even if we advance,
I'll still be the last one
to get to the collection.
What a schemer! Well played!
Everyone but Zhang, move towards
the opening to the main area on my side.
They're already panicking,
especially the outsiders.
They'll probably choose to retreat...
Qiu!
I've got a problem over here...
What should we do?
W-We should retreat...
I've had enough!
Die, monster!
Don't be scared!
This environment and its enemies
are beyond your understanding.
This is the guardian that I
have prepared for you guys:
the God of the Jungle.
In my homeland, it's called "Aimolu".
It's true, this thing was
protecting me just now.
Each of you has one.
Aimolu will attack anything
hostile to you.
Unfortunately, you guys
aren't the chosen ones,
otherwise you could control it perfectly.
The chosen ones?
Miss Basha, the chosen
ones that you speak of...
It's them, right?
Elijah, Vista,
Honda, Nash, and Chanon.
Hey! What are you doing?
Ben! Have you gone mad?
Tell me, why?
Compared to these weird friends,
we're just getting in the way!
So why did you bring us along?
Tell me!
Translation & Timing: Henry Lin
Editing: Alicia Ashby
QC: William Haggard
FQC: Sriram Gurunathan