Episode 6
"Judge's Grandfather"
Oh, how unusual.
You're up early.
I'm sorry. Did I wake you?
I always get up around this time.
You should sleep in.
You had quite the scuffle yesterday.
It's fine.
What is it?
Nothing.
Hey, look.
Huh?
Is he a noble?
He's not the local lord, right?
Nah, look who's next to him.
That's the Blade.
Then that's him?
Who should I tell if I have
information to share?
Don't ask me.
Good morning!
Good morning.
How can I help you?
I'd like to update a map.
Certainly. For which labyrinth?
The Crystal Ruins.
The Crystal Ruins?!
That old labyrinth's been
thoroughly explored.
The map hasn't been updated in years.
I found something.
You... found something?
Wait a minute.
Lying's a pretty risky play.
Are you that desperate
to show off to Layla?
Is that your name?
Yes.
That's a cute name.
Thank you!
Stop trying to seduce her!
A twink like you has new information
on the Crystal Ruins of all places?
That's impossible!
So?
S-So? So, uh...
Sh-Show us the proof!
Is proof required to update a map?
No, that's not necessary.
Any lies would be exposed anyway, and no
one would risk the loss of credibility.
So go right ahead!
Well, I don't believe you!
That's fine. As long as
the guild believes me.
Oh, but... since I do have proof,
I might as well show you.
What?!
A-A strategy guide?
Does this satisfy you?
Th-There can't be anything new in that.
There was a hidden room and
even a treasure chest.
Naturally, we took it.
But it's still worth entering.
There's a very rare monster inside.
W-Wait!
Please don't share more than that.
Don't worry. That's all I'll say.
By the way, this is my first
time sharing information.
This is it.
That's a very accurate map.
Should I tell you about
any traps as well?
You'll receive a greater
reward if you do.
In that case...
One moment, please.
I'll get set up right away.
Come closer to the counter, please.
I see. A silencer.
The ones you have here also
block out outside voices.
Depends on the silencer.
Go ahead.
This looks like an ordinary wall at first
glance, but this section can be destroyed.
I see. A destructible labyrinth wall
would've been overlooked.
Gil kicked the wall down.
He kicked it down?!
It was about this thick.
That's a proper wall!
Oh, but it's made of crystal.
That would be really hard!
It's like kicking down a brick wall.
That's not something people can do.
Beyond that, there was an altar.
Opening the treasure chest there
triggered a teleportation spell,
and then...
I see. That sends you to this room.
Actually, we fell.
You fell?!
A magic circle transported us into a
crystal pit about two meters across.
Was it a bit less than two minutes?
That sounds right.
It felt long, but it really wasn't.
W-Were you all right?
Do we look like we weren't?
Well, no.
Also, there was a subterranean
dragon at the bottom.
It attacked with its breath
weapon as we fell.
Also...
Wait!
You fell several kilometers,
a subterranean dragon
was waiting at the bottom,
and you took a direct hit
from its breath weapon?
That's absolutely brutal!
You knocked this over.
I can't believe I did that.
Since we've already come this
far, I have one other thing...
What kind of scale is that?
A subterranean dragon? It's huge.
Do you believe me now?
Uh, yes.
Here you go.
What?
I thought I'd give this to you.
After all, it seems some
people don't believe us.
You're giving...?
You could probably sell
this for a lot of money.
That's all right.
We harvested plenty more.
I-In that case, could I see your guild
card to certify your information?
Certainly.
Rank F?!
Is everything all right?
Um, I feel like you're ready
to apply for a promotion.
But it's been less than two months
since I became an adventurer.
B-But...
Besides, I know someone who'd be
unhappy if I raised my rank here.
What?
It's nothing.
He's coddling him again.
This is your reward.
Thank you.
Stop by anytime to offer more
information or take on jobs.
Would it be better if I raised my rank?
What?
It can't look good for
your leader to be rank F.
Doesn't bother me.
I don't care what people say about me,
but I wouldn't want others to doubt
your achievements because of me.
Idiot. It wouldn't bother me if they did.
It doesn't matter if your rank is S or
F or if you're a king or a criminal.
I'd be here either way.
You should probably avoid criminals.
This is it.
That's a big shop.
This is nice, but I believe Judge's
shop carries higher quality products.
They serve different customers.
True.
Excuse me.
Are you here to meet Mr. Judge?
Yes.
I've been told to take you to him.
This way, please.
Mr. Judge, your guests have arrived.
Mr. Lizel and Mr. Gil, I am so sorry!
I planned to wait for
you downstairs, but...
You can relax.
You're our client. You can throw
your weight around.
I'd never do that.
Did we arrive early?
N-Not at all. My grandfather has
been giving me gifts, and...
Judge! Take this, too.
You've already given me enough.
Oh?
Gil, huh?
Judge told me about you,
but you really haven't changed.
Shut up.
You've been putting that to good use.
You better not be slacking
on maintaining it.
Of course not.
Good. And you must be...
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Lizel.
I'm terribly sorry for dragging
your grandson into our trouble
and ruining your family's time together
on the first day of our visit.
I was thinking about giving
you a piece of my mind,
but you apologized before I could.
Um, Mr. Lizel, would you
like to have lunch with us?
Are you sure?
My grandfather said he'd
like to speak with you.
I'm honored. Please allow us to join you.
The name's Insigh.
I hear you've been helping my grandson.
I receive far more help from him.
I always stop by his shop
anytime I need anything.
You're an adventurer, right?
You don't look like one.
Grandfather!
Aren't you a mighty adventurer?
Then eat like one.
Grandfather!
I've been working on my appetite.
By the way, was it two
years ago that you met?
Yeah.
And he recommended that sword to you.
I wouldn't say he recommended it...
You can't even tell what
weapon's right for you?!
Are there any swords that would suit me?
What? You've never properly swung a
sword in your life. Don't be absurd.
Show me what you're using now.
This is it.
You want a sword when you can use this?
I didn't want to waste the opportunity.
Honestly, you're screwed up in the head.
The head?
Oh, you're curious?
His gun uses mana control.
Few mages can manage such
precise control over mana.
Then Mr. Lizel must be amazing.
Yeah, amazing for even considering it.
He uses mana control to
aim and position the gun,
control the recoil,
and even pull the trigger.
Let me give you an example.
Try singing a song in
your head. You got it?
Yes.
Now add another song.
Keep playing both at the same time.
It's like that.
Mr. Insigh, I can't do that either.
It's just a comparison.
I'm saying your head's just that crazy.
I'll prepare for our departure.
Make yourselves at home.
You're not having dessert with your
grandpa on your last day here?
We had lunch together because
you said the same thing.
By the way, I have a request.
Huh?
Could you give this to someone?
These are the tunnels beneath Marcade.
Where'd you get this?
It was a coincidence.
A coincidence?
It happened to be stuck in
a book I won at an auction.
So, who am I giving this to?
Count Shadow. You know him, don't you?
What makes you say that?
It was written in this book.
You sure love books.
The Marcadia Company was involved in
Marcade's development, wasn't it?
And you think I still work with
them because my grandfather did?
I'm certain you do.
Judge is a good and very dutiful boy.
The man who raised him
undoubtedly is as well.
Well, you got me.
Since you know his name,
have you met him?
Yes. He treated me to dinner.
You mean you extorted him.
You did that to Shadow?
Speaking with a worthy opponent must've
been a nice breather for him.
Here.
I'm not eating this.
What a waste.
I'll make sure this map
gets to him. Don't worry.
I appreciate that.
Should I mention your name, too?
If you'd like.
I'm certain he'll make
a sour face, though.
Well, that's no good.
I'll be sure to tell him.
Mr. Insigh.
Huh?
I'd like to ask you for something else.
You trying to charm me?
They're pretty big.
Judging by the shape, are they
a subterranean dragon's?
I'm impressed.
They're a beautiful jade color.
So, what about these?
I'd like to sell them to you.
If possible, could you run a large-scale
advertisement and put them up for sale?
What?
I acquired them in the Crystal
Ruins just yesterday.
From a subterranean dragon of this size?
Well, you had Gil with you.
I'm not surprised.
So that labyrinth's boss was a dragon?
It was the boss of a hidden room.
Oh? There was still one left
in that old labyrinth?
I reported it to the guild this morning.
I see you understand the
concept of influence well.
By putting a few scales on the market,
you'll show adventurers that the
subterranean dragon is real.
Some people don't trust the
word of a mere rank F.
Who cares if anyone chooses not to
believe you and gets themselves killed?
That labyrinth is a famous
tourist spot, isn't it?
I've never heard of anywhere else where
you can see the inside of a labyrinth.
If people went missing there,
you'd lose a valuable attraction.
How nice of you to worry about that.
Okay. Let's get these appraised.
Judge, come here!
I'm almost done getting
ready, Grandfather!
Just for a moment, please.
Okay!
What? You acquired these?
It was mostly Gil.
Were you hurt?
Why the change in tone?
Here, for the scales.
Thank you.
You make bank like it's nothing.
I'm lucky to be an adventurer.
Shut up.
I finished packing everything.
The old man made you take
a bunch of gifts, didn't he?
Of course I did.
Such as items incompatible with spatial
magic that you mentioned on the way here?
I have some of those.
I managed to acquire them for cheap.
Please show me them later.
Cheap?
From the high-quality shop
you mentioned before.
Their business practices
are a bit questionable.
Yeah. They might be pushing it with
how they acquire some of their items.
But because of that,
I paid hardly any markup.
You're a good businessman.
And surprisingly assertive.
He gets the job done.
Thank you for accommodating
my sudden requests.
It's for the good of Marcade.
It wasn't insolent in the slightest.
Lizel.
Look after my grandson.
I don't have to. He's a fine merchant.
If anything, I depend on him.
Yeah, I know.
See you next time, Grandfather.
You sure you don't wanna
stay another day?
Another time.
May I take first watch again?
Sure.
I'm glad I bought so many new books.
You'd better actually keep watch.
I'll do my best.
So you'd better get some
proper sleep, too.
I know.
Well, good night.
Yeah.
Were you actually asleep?
Yes.
And Judge?
He's asleep.
I hope he's sleeping soundly.
I don't want to scare him.
You're being overprotective.
They're using cheap bows.
Bandits?
I've only seen monsters
use bows in labyrinths.
Then they must be human.
Oh? Did I miss one?
No, he dodged it.
So one of them is skilled.
Well, he's gone now.
It does seem that way.
How does it feel to be used as pawns?
Big talk coming from a twink.
Will you withdraw?
We're not letting an
easy mark like you go.
Then there's no deal to be made.
You'll regret catching the
eye of the Forky Gang!
Your boss's name isn't Forky, is it?
Eyes on the enemy.
My apologies.
Is that everyone?
We'd better move camp.
I'll do it.
But it's not your watch yet.
I'm telling you to go
coddle him all you want.
Judge.
I apologize for scaring you.
It's not that.
I'm glad you're safe.
You stayed hidden, didn't you? Good boy.
Can you sleep?
I...
It's all right. You can
keep holding my hand.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
Good night.
Is he asleep?
I'm sorry. Could you handle the rest?
It's fine. You should sleep, too.
You really coddle them too much.
Next Time
"The Night of the Promotion"
Next time: "The Night of the Promotion."
Illustration by: