Good. That should do it for today.
Indeed. Now, Lord Van,
let us begin your studies.
Huh? We're starting now?
That's unreasonable after finishing work.
I do not know of anyone
who has died from studying.
That would prove it is not unreasonable.
He's a fiend.
Lord Van.
Welcome back. You've already
returned from hunting?
Well, actually...
Please forgive us.
For what?
The truth is we discovered
the entrance to the dungeon.
Oh? The dungeon?
Wait, the dungeon?
The thing we were trying to avoid finding?
Lord Van.
If a dungeon has been discovered,
you must report it promptly.
Send a messenger to the royal capital.
I really don't have a choice, do I?
Correct.
With the discovery of a dungeon,
adventurers will flood the village,
and my father will learn
about the development work.
It's our fault.
Forgive us.
Well, now that you've found it,
our hands are tied.
On that note, I'd like to ask you
to go report this to the royal capital...
Kusala.
By myself?
As the party's scout,
you discovered the dungeon, didn't you?
H-How did you know?
I agree Kusala's well-suited to the task,
but we should go with him.
I want the two of you to explore
the area around the dungeon.
As for your reward...
How does one large gold sound?
Later, Kusala. Take care on
your solo trip to the royal capital.
Safe travels!
Huh? You're being way too mean.
Well, I do feel bad for you,
so I'll give you a mythril short sword.
We've used up all the mythril ore,
so it's kind of precious.
Is that a good enough reward?
Yes!
Hey, wait! Kusala, switch with me!
No fair! I'll go instead!
Hey, wait!
I'm the one he asked to do it.
Where are you going?
Take me with you!
Sucks for you two, huh, boss?
Okay, I'm heading out now!
Safe travels!
EASYGOING TERRITORY DEFENSE
BY THE OPTIMISTIC LORD
EPISODE 8: A POSTAPOCALYPTIC BAND'S
ROWDY DUNGEON EXPLORATION
Must be thanks to my good behavior.
Gazing at Lord Van's special-made
short sword the whole way
makes the journey to the royal capital
go by in a flash.
Normally, these foes would
prove slightly tough for me,
but they hardly feel like
a challenge to me now.
You should quit while you're ahead
for your own good!
You're not coordinated at all.
This is crazy.
I could get hooked on this.
Um...
Thank you very much for saving me.
My name is Flamiria.
You strike me as a man of great renown.
May I perhaps know your name?
Ah, I'm just a humble adventurer
named Kusala. I'm not famous or anything.
No.
I can tell you're distinguished
from the way you carry yourself.
Huh?
No, I really am just...
I understand.
I'm walking from here
to the royal capital,
so allow me to repay you at a later date.
O-Oh, I'm on my way
to the royal capital, too.
Hop on my horse.
Oh, no, I couldn't trouble you further.
Hup.
See? Even the horse is happier carrying
a young lady like yourself instead of me.
Flamiria, where were you heading to
in the royal capital?
Well, my father was a baron, but he died
in battle and his lands were conquered.
So I came to look for work
as a maid in a noble's house.
Oh, so you're free like me?
Huh?
I currently live in a remote village,
but if you'd like,
why don't you come with me?
I'm sure there'll be work
for you to do there, Flamiria.
Besides, I can protect you.
You won't regret it.
Okay. Thank you so much for everything.
Now that a dungeon's been discovered,
I think I'll build a separate outpost for
all the adventurers that'll flood here.
An outpost?
A small outpost for the adventurers.
I see.
In that case, it'd be best to name
a governor for this new outpost.
Since you will remain in this village,
you'll need someone
to oversee the outpost.
Then, could I ask you
to serve as governor?
Yes, that will be fine.
You should also establish a new chivalric
order to keep the peace in the outpost.
True.
Okay, Dee's group will be
the Seatoh Chivalric Order in Seatoh,
and we'll establish the Esparda
Chivalric Order in the new outpost.
Is this payback?
Huh? Payback for what?
I'm only eight, so I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Pull that rope over there.
Yes, sir.
Lord Van, where should
we put the materials?
Oh, thanks. Just set them down over there.
Thanks to everyone's help,
it's going well.
At this rate, we might have
the outpost done in a month.
Leave it to us!
We'll acquire the necessary
materials this very day!
Yeah!
Huh?
I could make this group
my chivalric order, right?
Dee?
Yes? What is it?
Could you headhunt some of these guys
for the Seatoh Chivalric Order?
Oh, interesting idea.
I'm afraid we were already recruited
for the Esparda Chivalric Order.
We've all signed contracts
saying we'll join.
Huh?
Esparda wasted no time.
I can't believe he secured men
before the Seatoh Chivalric Order could.
Lord Van.
What is it, Khamsin?
Kusala has returned, but, um...
Lord Van, I filed that report
with the royal capital.
Welcome back.
Um, who's this?
Stuff happened and long story short, she
had nowhere to go, so I brought her here.
You're still accepting residents, right?
Of course. People are more than welcome.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm the lord of this village, Van.
I'm Flamiria.
Kusala rescued me when I was attacked
by a band of orcs near the royal capital.
Huh?
Nah, I didn't do much. It was all thanks
to that shortsword you gave me, Lord Van.
So you say.
But to me, you were more wonderful
than the heroes of legend.
So that's what's going on.
I-It's the apocalypse.
The apocalypse is here.
It's no cause for concern.
Huh?
They're adventurers here for the dungeon.
When I told the guild, a bunch of idiots
hoping to strike it rich set out for here.
I-Is that so?
Hey now. Yer out playin' in
an awfully lawless place, ain't ya?
Listen up, brats. The village may be
close, but it's dangerous out here.
Yer a pretty young filly. A gal like you
is gonna get attacked by perverts.
So run on home now.
They really are like villains
in a postapocalyptic world.
Wait.
Are they concerned about us?
Sounds like it.
They may lack tact,
but they seem like nice people.
Th-Their faces are a little scary, though.
Did we frighten ya?
Our bad.
Still, what're ya doin'
all the way out here?
Ya'd be in trouble if a monster attacked.
Thanks.
But I'll be fine if something shows up
since it's not far to the village.
Village? Where?
Over there.
Ya call that a village?
With those huge ramparts?
How'd they make all that?
I'll show you.
Buh?
Wh-What the...
Well, this is just temporary fencing,
so it should do for today.
What was that freewheelin'
magic just now?!
Lord Van! I've brought you
additional logs.
Thank you.
L-Lord Van?
Th-This brat is the Van Nei Fertio
on everyone's lips in the royal capital?
"Brat"?
Whichever one of you
just said that, step forward.
As House Fertio's—no, as Seatoh Chivalric
Order's commander, I'll punish you!
And who the hell're you?
Any time the mohawk guys saw Dee since,
they trembled in fear and greeted him.
Afternoon, boss!
Workin' hard, I see!
Hello!
I won't allow you guys to do anything bad!
Yessir!
In contrast to their behavior around Dee,
they seemed amused that
I was the lord and still just a kid.
Why're ya in this remote place, Lord Van?
I was driven out of my home.
Huh? That's a cryin' shame.
It's a tough world for nobles, too.
Ya know a lotta words, Lord Van.
Well, I am the lord, after all.
What? When did we get so many rivals?
Oh, Ortho. Did you all just
get back from the dungeon?
Uh, yeah. We got back a few moments ago.
Oh, hey, Kusala. So you're back, huh?
Hey, who's that woman?
This is Lady Flamiria. I met her
on the way to the royal capital.
Nice to meet you.
Well, we'll go stay in the inn.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Please excuse us.
A-Are we dreaming?
There's no way.
Maybe I should go ahead and build
a home for Kusala and Flamiria?
What? A new home for those two?
Yeah.
Damn it all!
So? How was the dungeon?
Seems there's hardly any monsters
in the area around it.
However, the entrance
is in a deep crevice,
so it's in a pretty dangerous spot.
A deep crevice?
Hm, sounds challenging.
Is it far from the village?
About two to three hours by carriage.
That's far!
The natural environment
around most dungeons is harsh.
So while people could build small bases,
no one could build anything full-scale.
Until now, that is.
What's this? She looks like
she wants to say something.
But you could do it,
couldn't you, Lord Van?
And there it is, Pluriel.
But the forest's really dangerous.
I also have a curfew,
so I can't stay out too long.
We'll protect you.
We've been to the dungeon
a few times now, so it isn't dangerous.
But she's not backing down.
I want to enjoy my fun city building here.
You'll have to take me to the dungeon.
I'll need desserts and things for a nap.
We'll also bring my attendants,
Till and Khamsin, as well as Lady Arte.
Dee and Esparda have city building
to work on, so they'll stay here.
We'll also need lots
of people to escort us.
How's that for an unreasonable request?
Who knows what I'd be capable of
if I wasn't eight? Yup, terrifying.
Understood. We'll make the preparations.
We can go tomorrow.
Huh?
Ortho, Van's joining us for some base
building tomorrow, so let's go prepare.
Oh, okay. I'll go round up some guards.
Huh?
I can't believe they're actually
taking me there.
Are you okay, Khamsin?
I-I feel sick.
You're the one who suggested this.
G-Going to the dungeon.
Hey, lookee!
It's a giant troll!
I'mma kill it!
I'll help!
Let's get it!
Their shouting is so annoying.
Wow.
What a lovely view.
Yes. The air is so crisp
and refreshing, too.
Lady Arte, look!
It's a flying monster!
See?
Wow, amazing.
The women seem to be enjoying
their outing, at least.
Lord Van. We'll be there
once we cross here.
Stop! Hold it!
Stop right here!
Huh? But we're almost there.
Hey, what are you doing?!
This is one hell of a deep crevice.
What is it?
Is something wrong?
You're kidding me, right?
Adventurers apparently don't get
the whole concept of "safety first."
Let's rethink places like this
where one mistake could mean death.
Predict danger. Manage risk.
Got it?
Is there a place like that?
Okay, everyone on your knees.
Sit and think about your mistake.
Yessir!
Here, look at this.
And you, Kusala,
hopping about over there...
Wanna try, too, Lord Van? It's fun.
What would happen
if I kicked this log right now?
I'd die!
Kusala may be light on his feet,
but the logs could roll or break
and he'd plummet to his death.
Do you understand?
Yessir!
Then, what do you think
we should do with these logs?
Tree-d very carefully.
'Cause they're trees.
I won't build your base.
We're sorry!
The correct answer is...
We build a sturdy bridge.
You only cross once you're sure it's safe.
Wow!
Now, as for this base...
That's the entrance to the dungeon
over there? There's not much space.
My first question is:
What kind of facilities should I build?
What would you all like?
A gambling den!
A tavern!
An amusement park!
Rejected.
Well, anyway, I began building their base.
First, I created a gate
for the dungeon entrance
to stop the dungeon
monsters getting out.
Next, I built a facility for
the adventurers to stay in.
I figured if it was well-made,
the adventurers would make
more headway in the dungeon.
The base is finished.
You can go inside the building now.
The first floor has a rest area
and a storehouse.
So spacious!
Wow! We could hold races in here!
The second has a cafeteria.
This is huge, too.
Let's have an eatin' competition.
The third has the sleeping area.
Beds!
So fluffy.
Let's have a pillow fight!
Whoa. What a great view.
I feel like I've conquered the world.
I also made a terrace overlooking nature
to give you all somewhere to relax.
Impressive work, Lord Van.
Now everyone can rest up
between forays into the dungeon.
Plus, I built water tanks
and rain catchers on the roof.
You can use them for the flushing toilets,
but keep in mind that you can't drink it.
Everyone got that?
Yessir.
No, clearly not.
I'll leave the management
of this base in your hands.
Please watch over everyone.
Roger that.
They're like spotted eels.
Oh, you guys! It's getting dark,
so we need to head back!
Aw.
My curfew is sunset. We're leaving.
Esparda will be mad at me.
Even the lord's afraid of somethin'.
Well, he is a child.
Maybe I should destroy
this base I just made?
L-Lord Van.
What is it, Arte?
That's mythril ore, isn't it?
Yup, no doubt about it. That's mythril.
Good job finding it.
You're incredible, Arte.
No, I didn't do much.
E-Esparda is smiling...
Lord Van.
We need to talk.
Please, right this way.
S-Somebody help!
Till!
I-I'll come with you.
That's not what I mean!
Khamsin!
I can't.
Why can't you?!
Arte!
Huh? M-Me?
No, bad choice.
Ortho!
This is all because
I helped out you adventurers!
Uh, Sir Esparda, well...
We're kinda responsible this time.
That's it, Ortho.
That's right. It's not my fault.
Silence.
Yes, sir.
Now, let's get going.
I-I'm sorry!
TRANSLATION: JOHN PICKETT
TIMING: ANDY ELLIS
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: RILEY DALTON
TRANSLATION CHECK: REI MIYASAKA
NEXT EPISODE: THE TIMID GIRL'S
BEAUTIFUL MARIONETTE DANCE