Sero-san! Sero-san!
Our torture target collapsed!
You must've gotten too enthusiastic.
Did you kill him?
We hadn't done anything at all yet!
He just suddenly passed out.
He must have some kind of
preexisting condition.
The types we get in here
aren't usually in good health.
Well, I 'll get it taken care of.
Hey, Noe! Call Iz-san for me.
You went too far again, didn't you?
It wasn't me, moron.
If you call someone a moron,
it means you—
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
What?
Is he dead?
If he was dead,
we wouldn't have called you.
We'd have called Fon-san.
Birthday: 11/11 Age: 42
184 cm Weight: 73 kg
Blood Type: O
Interests: The Zoo
Skills: Sudoku
Favorite Food: Grilled Fish
Disliked Food: Blue Cheese
His Priority: His Patients
I ran an inquiry and found out
he had a preexisting condition
and medication for it.
I knew it.
I'll treat him. The rest
of you, step outside.
Sure thing.
All right.
Now, then...
So there's a doctor
who'll come to see them.
In unexpected situations like this,
or times when we go too far, yeah.
If they die, we can't torture them.
I'm done.
Okay!
Thank you.
He should be able to
talk in about an hour,
so conduct your torture after that.
Just an hour? That's pretty harsh.
Is there a need to be
considerate of these guys?
Nope.
Right?
Are you leaving already?
No.
Gonna visit Hela and the rest.
Thanks for your help!
Please...
Please save him.
You need immediate treatment, too!
I'm fine.
It's my fault.
Find a way to help him. Please!
He says he wants to talk.
My wounds... are pretty bad, huh?
I'm... sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
It's my fault you're...
Siu...
I'm the one... who got
you into this... right?
I just... did what
I wanted to... that's all.
I'll be... just fine.
Hela-san...
I'm sorry.
It's my fault someone so important
to you is in that condition.
I'm sorry.
How have you been lately?
The same as always.
It hurts every once in a while.
Then I'll give you the usual medicine.
Thank you.
Where's Siu?
He got away.
Dear, dear. What a problem child.
Running from Iz-san again?
I'm not running.
That scar...
You always hide it, huh?
And you haven't shown Mike or Hugh.
Some people would worry
about me if they saw it.
Hiding it is easier.
Leu and Nero kept putting bandages on it.
My, how adorable.
And there are people who
would be hurt by this scar.
In that case...
it won't hurt me, so please show me.
How twisted are you?
I'd say it looks pretty cool.
After all, without that,
you and the others
wouldn't be who you are now.
I'm sure there are things only the
people who were there understand,
but I can see that those scars have left
you two with more than just regrets.
This place is the proof of that, right?
I cut my finger!
Wow. That's a pretty big cut.
It hurts!
There. All done.
Thank you.
And also...
My target frothed at the
mouth and collapsed.
You should've said that first!
Seriously? Again?
Sorry to call you so frequently.
Safety First
Let's stay safe today!
I'm such a klutz.
Show me!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
You're a grown-up,
aren't you? Deal with it!
This bear's mean!
I'm not just some bear. I'm Amumu-sama!
Hiya! I see treatment is underway.
Sero-san, who is this?
Oh, she's a nurse who works with Iz-san.
Her name is Merim.
This is Merim-chan. Nice to meet you.
Birthday: 9/26 Age: 25
Height: 158 cm Weight: 42 kg
Blood Type: B
Interests: Handicrafts
Skills: Memory Games
Favorite Food: Cheesecake
Disliked Food: Japanese Taro
Her Priority: Amumu and Izua
Make sure you don't get it
wet for a while, okay?
Okay. Thank you.
It's been a while since the
last time you came, Merim.
We came because you guys are a mess.
Sorry about that.
Oh, right. Iz-san said to go help
him when you're done here.
You numbskull!
You should've said that sooner!
She's a strange one.
She's got skills, though.
Huh? She left it behind!
It's fine. Don't worry.
She only uses Amumu with us.
Izua.
Get the usual ready.
Of course.
This is your first time
meeting Mike-kun, right?
Did you get along all right?
Much conversation was had...
with Amumu.
I see.
Why not speak with him normally?
I don't want to. I'm terrible at talking.
But through Amumu, I can hold
a conversation properly.
Properly, huh?
Don't cry, kid! Look at the
magnificence that is me!
And children find him to be
tremendously reassuring.
What's that? It's so cute!
That's true enough.
And it's a big help...
but speaking to others
besides me would—
It's fine.
You're special, Izua.
Doctor!
Will my legs never get better?
Don't worry. They'll get better.
You'll be able to go wherever
you want with this guy again.
Amumu! But he was all torn up!
Well, your doctor happens
to be a very amazing doctor.
He can even fix dolls.
Amumu's face didn't look like this before.
Doctor, you're awful at this.
What? You think so?
When I grow up, I'll come
and help you, Doctor.
Well, that would be a big help.
In that case, you'll have
to work hard to get better.
I will!
We're done over here, too.
Thank you.
It's rough when they're
all so unhealthy, huh?
I'll see you.
Thanks for all your hard work!
Hey, kid!
Don't interfere with Merim-chan and
Izua's lovey-dovey time too much, okay?
Later!
Huh?
What?
Iz-san doesn't see her
that way at all, though.
Really?
Izua!
I've finished... cleaning up...
He's sleeping in an odd place again.
I'm going home.
Right.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Hi there! I'm devoted
part-time torturer Mike!
The truth is, there's another side to me.
I'm also a novelist who uses torturers
as subjects for the novels I write.
Actually
Writes
With a
Keyboard
*Artistic Rendition
Torture Bullet
The source work has sold even better
since it got a manga adaptation!
We're having to do
yet another huge reprint!
And that novel of mine seems
to be a hit at the moment.
It just doesn't feel real.
Well, make it feel real, please!
I've always written
psychological suspense novels,
but when I made torture the theme
and shone a spotlight on the characters,
it was much better received
than I expected.
Your readership has started to stabilize,
so should we do a longer work?
That sounds good!
I'll go ask for some more stories
and think up some ideas.
Stories?
Oh, from the people at your part-time
job that you used as inspiration?
Yes. The legendary torturers
who are my mentors.
I asked you this before...
but do these torturers really exist?
Like I said...
they do exist!
Then would you like me to tell
you about my mentors again?
Y-Yes.
Torture Bullet
One of my mentors is Se—um, A-san.
'Sup?
A-san is Spirytus's ace.
Would it be all right if
I observed your next job?
Sure. No problem.
Why does a human have twenty nails?
I think I finally know the answer.
It's for people like you...
who just don't know when to give up!
Mike, are you heading home?
Yes! I'm all done!
Let's grab dinner together.
Really? Thanks for treating me!
I really want to try doing that.
That, huh? It's hard
to get it just right.
How about we give it
a try together next time?
Yay!
He's like a big brother who's really
good at looking after people.
Torture Bullet
My second mentor is Si—er, B-san.
Hey.
He's like the on-site boss.
He's solved all kinds of big cases,
and he's famous in the torture industry.
He can be a little scary...
What was that mistake?
How many years have you been doing this?
I'm sorry!
but he's really nice to us rookies.
You did well on that job yesterday.
Thank you!
I worry that you give your daughters
that same kind of education.
Are you stupid? Of course I don't.
He's Papa to two adorable daughters!
Torture Bullet
And that's what the two
I used as inspiration are like.
Right. Are you certain
you didn't make them up?
I told you, they really exist!
Mike.
I hear your novels have been
doing really well lately.
Thanks to you.
Oh, I'm going to be writing
a slightly heavier story this time,
so I'd love to hear some more
stories from both of you...
No problem.
Heavier, huh?
Currently being told about major
cases that everyone would recognize.
Something like that?
I think those cases are
a little too well-known.
If you want to do research,
you should look through
the documents Noe has.
I'll go try that!
Oh!
Um, it's a little late to ask,
but do you hate the
characters I modeled after you?
I mean, I am exaggerating
them a lot when I write them.
Oh, you mean like,
"the Legendary Torturer"?
Legendary
Torturer
And his apprentice being
"the Genius Torturer."
Genius
Torturer
I don't really think anything of it.
It's pretty much the truth anyway.
Right?
Pretty much.
Pretty
much.
That's so them.
If that's the kind of case you want...
The files around here should do.
This is such a huge help!
Your novel seems to be quite a hot topic.
I'm grateful that so many
people are reading it.
The torture industry has
a very negative image,
but maybe your readers will gain
a better understanding of it.
Hela-san was happy about it, too.
Keep working hard for us, okay?
I will!
But you're not comfortable
torturing people, right?
Were you all right reading my novel?
I was fine on that front.
I reduced my imagination to the
bare minimum and treated it as data.
I do the same for
the reports.
I see.
Yoo-hoo! Las-kun!
Hey!
Mike-san! Hugh!
Did you come to listen
to the professor again?
Yeah.
He said he wanted to ask about some
torture methods touched on in the novel.
Torture Bullet is pretty popular, huh?
Can't you put me somewhere
in your novels, too?
Sure!
What? Really?
Do you want to be a character
who can or can't keep a secret?
Oh. I'll be a character
who gets tortured, huh?
One who can keep a secret, then.
Okay.
That was helpful in so many ways.
Mike-san, why did you
decide to write novels?
Maybe... because it seemed interesting?
There are things that
aren't possible in real life,
or that are possible,
but you can't do them,
and things that you don't
want to do at all, right?
Fiction doesn't have
those kinds of limitations.
Diving into stuff that's different
from everyday life is fun.
And that's why you dove into something
that's different from the norm?
That's what this part-time
torturing job is, right?
Oh, that's true.
You started torturing because you
were looking for material, right?
And now you feel totally at home in it.
It's a funny thing, isn't it?
It really is.
The world that I thought was so different
from the norm has become my daily life.
If not for my writing,
I'd never have jumped in.
And if writing was all I did,
I'd never have found it.
I'm so glad I tried both.
The plot you sent me
was absolutely wonderful!
Just when you think it'll be all
about the main characters,
in comes a new character!
Someone who gains something precious
through finding work as a torturer.
It's a classic sort of theme,
but it's lovely!
Thank you!
It felt like you were even more
passionate about this than usual.
Is this new character modeled
after someone, too?
That's a secret.
Cleaning, cleaning! La, la, la, la, la!
What's wrong?
I've discovered a mysterious box!
I want it!
Okay.
Th-This is...
Oh! These bring back memories!
These are the games we
used to play to kill time!
So the two of you play games like these?
We played them quite a bit.
To figure out stuff like who
would torture the annoying target.
We'd use these to decide.
Right.
Now...
here we have one page of instructions.
The target is an ideological offender.
An ideological offender?
That's a very intriguing
torture target, but...
Since that type has such a
strong sense of purpose,
it tends to be hard to get them to talk.
Not only do they take a long time,
they'll criticize the system,
spew their convictions,
and say a bunch of stuff
no one asked about...
They're a pain!
What game will we play?
Why don't we play in teams?
I don't wanna do it alone!
Yes, that's true.
How about Reversi?
No way. You're too good at that one.
All right!
Sero & Mike
Join the Fight!
Siu & Hugh
First, we'll play shogi-kuzushi!
I'm confident in my sense of balance!
I feel like I've got this.
Good, good.
Go, Mike-chan!
Looking good!
TICKLE...
And we win.
Grin...
Hugh totally pulled the Old Maid.
Who falls for a simple bluff like that?
Sero isn't going to pull
the Old Maid from Hugh,
so that means we lose.
That pisses me off.
My acting was pretty good, right?
I thought he'd be able to
read Sero-san's hand,
but I guess Siu-san can be tricked, too.
We didn't play Old Maid very much.
Why not?
It's no fun with only two people.
Young people
don't often
find a place
in the world
of torturers
Then the four of us should
play it lots from now on!
Yeah!
Let's play daifugo, too!
Yeah, we should.
That was so much fun!
Yeah.
It's nice every once in a while.
Yeah, it is.
But we played so much,
I can't remember the wins and losses.
Yeah...
Well, why don't we take
the ideological offender?
What?
It's tough, but worthwhile, you know?
Roger that.
And we won anyway. Right?
Let's do this again sometime!
Next time, we play as individuals.
I'll win.
I'll do my best, too!
Well, time to get to it. Let's go, Mike.
Okay.
A Later Day
Board games?
Of course those don't
count as a work expense.
Oh, all right.
We'll let you play, too.
Okay?
That's not the problem here!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Elanor Sakamato
John Chandanais
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Becky Cottrill