The Sword of Domination's taken over Gai!
Shion!
Did I... make it?
Sorry I couldn't finish you off.
Humans really get me fired up.
You had me worried there, you dopes.
Jun, are—
Do you have a moment to spare?
Be careful when you use
the Sword of Domination.
We can't deal with you going berserk
and turning on us again.
Give it a rest, would you?
I told you I get it already.
What?!
N-Nothing to see here.
Keep your voice down!
You asked Mirei out? When?
When we were practicing supreme arts.
You mean that time she
got falling-down drunk?
So, what'd she say?
Wh-Where's the enemy?
Did those chickens run for it?!
She shot you down, huh?
Sh-Shut up! I'm gonna keep trying!
Wherever you are, bring it on!
Huh? What's this?
They match the colors of our armor.
Late, I see.
I nearly died of boredom.
Dad!
I shall subject you to a trial.
You are each to enter a door alone.
Like hell! Stop wasting
our time and get out here!
Perform your supreme art
and I will face you.
What was that?
We do need to master our supreme arts to
invoke the Armor of the Supreme Emperor.
But you expect us to just play along?
You will once you've seen this.
Mirei!
Guys?
Huh? Wait, what's going on?!
Get this crap off me!
What do I have to be tied up for?!
I tie people up,
not the other way around!
At least she's well enough off
to rant about her fetishes.
Put a sock in it!
I can handle myself!
You guys focus on your own—
Mirei!
Be quick about it, or who knows
what may befall this woman?
What should we do?
We've only got one choice.
We wipe the floor with my dad
and take Mirei home.
EPISODE X
SACRIFICE
Nasti!
The demons took Mirei!
Huh?
What the...?
Where am I?
No way. How?
What's going on?
This is our orphanage.
Yama!
Musashi!
What are you doing here?
Don't ask me! I came from over
that way and wound up here.
Are the other guys around too, then?
Pick 'em up.
The only ones in this world...
are you and us.
I know those voices.
You're from the Ten Warriors!
Granny!
I'm sorry to say that was an illusion.
I heard this world's
based on your memories.
Aren't you...
Kamanosuke, in the flesh!
Let's have us some fun.
How does it feel,
revisiting your demon self?
Dad's Sorcery, huh?
Your supreme art requires
the spirit of Righteousness.
That entails compassion
for your parents and comrades.
I bet that means squat to you.
After all, you've never felt...
a parent's love!
Yamato Hojo!
Explain to me the spirit of Justice!
Shove it! How should I know?!
Moron!
What is Justice if not humans
as they ought to be?!
Musashi Hojo!
Explain to me the spirit of Faith!
"Faith" as in trust?
Or like the religious kind?
Moron!
What is Faith if not
humans free of deceit?!
The Wisdom for which you are being tested
hinges on your ability
to discern right from wrong.
How do you intend
to overcome this battle?
The best way to beat you demons
is to outmaneuver you
and master my supreme art!
Hey, hey, Ishy! You know what
the spirit of Grace is all about?
Respecting others, right?
Oh, I knew you were smart!
But if you know that and still
can't pull off your supreme art,
that proves you can't put it into practice!
I'll ask you again!
For what reason do you fight?
Shut up!
We're obviously fighting for what's right!
And what do you think is right?!
We're going to defeat you demons
and bring back peace!
Even if it kills us,
we know it's the right thing to do!
Self-sacrifice, hmm?
If you consider that good,
then you truly fail to comprehend
the spirit of Wisdom.
What has that infantile justification
made of your world?
It's about time you realized
that there wouldn't be so many victims
if you guys weren't a total disaster!
You call yourselves samurai without
bothering to learn the samurai spirit,
instead devoting yourselves
to paper-thin notions of "what's right,"
and this is the result!
If you wanna play hero,
go do it somewhere else!
How can you save anyone when you don't
know the first thing about what's right?
Look at you failing to save
one lousy woman right now!
You can't protect anyone as you are.
What's wrong with you?
What do you think Nezu and Kakei died for?
They were sacrificed because of you!
Your body stole their powers
to become the ultimate Puppet!
So what is this?
How are they supposed
to rest in peace now?!
Is that...
Mirei?
Isn't this that song...?
The one she was singing then?
Not a bad song choice.
But if she wanted to cheer
you on, she's too late.
Wanna bet?
Sure, I don't know jack about
Righteousness or doing the right thing.
And of course my dad never
loved me that I can remember,
so I don't even know how
to spell "compassion."
But you know, even for me,
these guys are different.
Our idea of what's right may be infantile,
but are the bonds we formed
because of it right or wrong?
As far as I'm concerned,
they couldn't be more right!
WISDOM
As long as they're hanging in there,
maybe we can pull through, too.
There's nothing phony
about my trust in them!
That's how it oughta be!
JUSTICE
FAITH
I bet they're all wailing like babies
while they get back
on their feet about now.
Excellent.
I couldn't ask for a better bunch of guys!
GRACE
They changed me.
So I... can't just drop dead here!
RIGHTEOUSNESS
So you've mastered
the Sword of Domination.
Have Kakei's and Mochizuki's
powers taken root already?
Supreme Art: Mind Clear!
Supreme Art: Vigor and Vitality!
Supreme Art: Unparalleled!
Supreme Art: Light Beam Flash!
Supreme Art: Void of the Five Skandhas!
What would they do without me?
I can't believe you actually
pulled off a supreme art.
Got you all fired up, did I?
This fire's just getting started!
Enough!
You have fulfilled your purpose. Withdraw.
Understood.
What, you're just gonna do
whatever my dad tells you?
Shut your mouth.
Where am I now?
Huh? What's this place?
I used supreme art, then
blacked out all of a sudden and...
You used the Sword of Domination?
Yeah.
I guess I absorbed the strength
of the dead Ten Warriors,
so I can control it now.
Then we've got everything we need
for the Armor of the Supreme Emperor.
All thanks to Mirei.
Her song gave me the push I needed.
Even if she did miss a bunch of notes.
Worse, she got way too full
of herself partway through.
I hear you! Like the way
she drew out the chorus!
You just know she looked
awful singing that.
Those jerks...
Who asked them?!
H-Huh?
Weird. I feel kind of heavy.
I guess I need more exercise.
Man, what was she thinking?
Drop it already!
There they are!
And they're still trashing me?!
Hey!
Line up to take your lumps!
Whoa! A monster!
Huh?! Where?!
And it talks.
Come on, where's the monster?!
Hey, doesn't that sound like...
Mirei?
Listen, what are you guys talking about?
Can't you tell by looking at me?
Wait... Is it just me,
or did you guys get smaller?
Huh?
What is this?
You've gotta be kidding...
H-Huh?
It's getting harder to...
talk...
Sorry. I didn't mean to.
My body just...
What's going on? Something's weird.
My mind's fading...
No!
I don't want this!
Sorry, guys.
I think I'm done for...
Sorry.
I'm really... sorry...
Oath of Righteousness, emissary of Fire!
RIGHTEOUSNESS
Armor of Heat!
The true trial begins now.
Mirei!
What now?
We've gotta take her down.
Like hell we do!
That's Mirei you're talking about!
I know that!
Then help me come up
with a way to save—
I'm saying it's too late for that!
There is no saving her.
Mirei!
Wake up, Mirei—
Musashi!
She's stopping herself from hurting us.
But I thought her mind was gone.
She's still trying to protect us anyway.
That sounds just like her.
"You can have my life anytime."
That's what Mirei told me.
Mirei!
W-Would, um...
Would you consider going out with me if—
I'm sorry.
That was quick!
Sorry.
I'm tickled you feel that way,
but I want a different kind
of relationship with you guys.
More like comrades or fellow warriors.
I mean, a love interest just waits
to get rescued when there's trouble.
But I don't want to be like that.
I'd rather go out fighting
than weigh everyone down.
Know what I mean?
More or less.
Then I have to decline a hug or a kiss,
but you can have my life anytime.
It's not fair, Mirei.
This is just too much.
We can't save her, no matter what we try?
Right.
In that case, we end this ourselves!
See you.
Supreme Art: Void of the Five Skandhas!
Supreme Art: Vigor and Vitality!
Supreme Art: Unparalleled!
Supreme Art: Light Beam Flash!
Supreme Art: Mind Clear!
Translation\h\h\h\h\h\hWilliam Varteresian
Timing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Editing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRiley Dalton
Quality Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSMR
Translation Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMichelle Tymon
EPISODE XI
RETURN
Armor races through your heart.