Episode 8
A place where you can truly
stand tall and upright!
You bastard, what are you doing?
Why did you come back here?
Because I figured out the
meaning of sincerity!
Huh?
This would be
"standing tall and upright!"
Actually, neither riddle is
hard to solve on its own.
The difficulty is how
to put them together.
The character "sincerity"
must be above "who is human."
It's extremely hard to process the
power gained from crossing the valley.
After crossing it, the extraordinary
power profoundly changes one's mindset,
making it hard to focus
on the sincerity clue.
This is a common flaw for
most people who do things.
Theoretically, we should aim for 100%,
but we get distracted by external factors,
such as unfavorable circumstances
or insufficient capability,
ultimately settling for an outcome of 80%.
Even so, we might even be
happy with a score of 60%.
But the master here doesn't
see it that way.
At least when it comes to
what it means to be human,
he only accepts 100%.
Never mind. It's my fault.
Bao'er, I forgot about your
intermittent moments of clarity.
The answer to sincerity
is remarkably simple.
Sincerity is trustworthiness.
Sincerity is the Way of Heaven.
The Way of Heaven does not
negotiate with people.
The Way of Heaven leaves
no room for compromise.
Sincerity is one of the Way
of Heaven's characteristics.
Outcasts who understand what it means
to stand between heaven and earth
shouldn't be confused
by that valley outside.
We must pursue it 100%!
Find the place where one truly stands
tall between heaven and earth!
I get it! Standing tall between heaven
and earth refers to my Baihui acupoint!
Xia, why must we necessarily
focus on the "heaven" part?
In order to reach the sky, you
must be standing on the ground.
Granny, you've never tried
this spot before, have you?
Oh... so that's how it is.
Yeah, this is it:
standing tall between heaven and earth.
The acupoint reaching towards heaven
is the Baihui point on top of the head.
So "standing on the ground"
would naturally be this one.
It follows the Kidney Meridian of
Foot-Shaoyin, facing downwards.
It's also known as the bottomless
cave, the Yongquan acupoint!
So a place like this actually exists.
No doubt about it,
this is the answer to "standing
tall between heaven and earth."
Granny, we found it...
What? It's just another empty room.
Look over there, you guys.
The Nine-Bend Winding Cave...
This is the Sect Leader's!
I recognize the Sect Leader's handwriting!
Hey! Come check this out!
Something was carved on this wall here.
It was erased later.
There's more here too!
There's some here too... They're words!
If you look closely, a lot of this
cave's surface has been polished.
Over here!
There are complete words here!
"This method is true and wonderful,
because I am unique and
different from others.
I know that the reversal
arises from Li and Kan,
But who recognizes that floating and
sinking determine host and guest?
The golden cauldron wishes to
retain the cinnabar within.
Within the jade pool, first deposit
the silver into the water."
The Divine Jade Capital?
Huh? Wasn't this by...
Zhang Boduan...
also known as Master Ziyang!
Zhang Boduan?
Who's Master Ziyang?
Jinfeng! You innate types, honestly!
Zhang Boduan, known as Master
Wuzhen or Master Ziyang,
is the founder of
the Southern School of Alchemy.
It's no surprise that an innate
prodigy like you wouldn't know him.
But for those who
cultivated later in life,
not knowing him is like a carpenter
not knowing Lu Ban, right, Zhang?
Zhang Boduo? Of course I know him!
It's Zhang!
This guy doesn't have a clue.
If the master of this place is
the legendary Master Ziyang,
then it's not unthinkable for one
person to have created all of this...
I see. So that's the answer the Sect
Leader always wanted me to find on my own.
The master of this place is
such an extraordinary outcast.
Yes and no.
Zhang Boduo is indeed the answer,
but there's more behind the answer
that the Sect Leader wanted to convey.
Huh?
Why do you think Wu Gensheng modified
the patterns on the valley walls outside?
Why?
We can never understand why
he does what he does...
Xia, how much space do you think it would
take to engrave the entire Wuzhen Chapter?
Hmm...
This wall should be enough.
But look, this entire stone cave
is covered in erased engravings.
Combined with that Nine-Bend Winding Cave,
Wu Gensheng is clearly
refuting Master Ziyang.
As expected of the Sect Leader!
He doesn't even show respect to
the legendary founder of alchemy!
What exactly is the Sect Leader
refuting about Master Ziyang?
This very Nine-Bend Winding Cave
also originates from a story.
A master and his three disciples
passed through a place called Yuhua
on their cultivation journey.
The city lord of Yuhua showed
them great reverence and respect,
so the three disciples passed their divine
abilities to the city lord's three sons.
This alerted a den of lion
spirits living nearby.
The ancestor of these lion spirits resided
within the Nine-Bend Winding Cave,
known as the Nine-Spirit Primordial Sage.
Nine-Spirit Primordial Sage?
So you're saying this
is where spirits live?
No, the key lies in the name
"Nine-Spirit Primordial Sage."
"Nine-Spirit" refers to the Nine Heavens,
and can also be
interpreted as the Nine Suns.
This Primordial Sage is also interesting.
While many have been honored as sages,
only one has been
revered as the Great Sage.
And the one whom this Great
Sage so vehemently revered…
was the Primordial Sage.
Only the Primordial Sage is worthy of
being called the "master of masters."
The story also reveals that
the Heavenly King Guangmu
tells the Monkey King the
root of the calamity.
It is because you wanted to
become a master to others
that you stirred up this den of lions.
This convoluted tale serves as
a warning to future cultivators:
do not recklessly become a master!
This place was probably intended
to screen for such individuals.
They must have enough luck or be fated to
understand this place and its riddles.
Furthermore, this person must
have enough sincerity.
Only those who ultimately
qualify can reach this place
and receive the message
engraved into the stone cave.
Hey, so are you saying that after the
Sect Leader solved the riddles here,
he thought Ziyang's method of conveying
information was too careless,
so he erased the engravings in the cave?
Yes. Do you guys think
this valley is miraculous?
Miraculous... Just going through it
once allows you to open your meridians.
This is as incredible as Spirit
Manipulation or Divine Craftsmanship.
But Wu Gensheng only
modified what was outside.
He completely erased what
was inside the cave.
Bye, Xia!
Thanks to you, I've seen
some interesting things.
If anything like this
happens again, call me!
I will, I will!
Hmph, what a weirdo.
All right, you guys really
helped out a lot this time.
I thank you on behalf of Jinfeng.
Let's part ways here.
Granny!
I'll definitely visit you again.
You won't give up looking for
whoever took the collection.
I won't give up looking for
clues about Qi Genesis.
That collection might not have
any clues about Qi Genesis.
No. Even if it doesn't,
I'll still deal with whoever took it.
Why are you helping me?
You're from the Express Delivery Company,
and I'm from the Quan Xing Sect.
We're both family members
of the 36 Thieves!
F-Family?
What family?
Jinfeng is no family of the Sect Leader!
Whether they brought suffering or joy,
without the 36 Thieves, none of
what we've experienced would exist.
We should inherit their legacy
and unravel their mysteries.
If what they left is harmful,
then we should eradicate it.
That's all. I'll contact Xia
through Qiu later to find you.
Hold on.
Here's my number.
Keep calling if you can't get through.
I'm not used to carrying a phone...
I just don't trust
that bastard Zhang Chulan!
Don't listen to his bullshit!
Jinfeng! How are you the
Sect Leader's family?
Then... what about me?
Do... Do I count as a
member of your family too?
Cut the crap!
You're coming back
to the cave with me later.
Huh? We just got out and we're going back?
Do you have any connections...
for obtaining explosives?
Explosives?
Uh... I know a few guys
who could get some.
I want to go back because I finally
understood the Sect Leader's intentions.
Bao'er, how's your injury?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You're fine? How did you get hurt?
I got shot.
Like you said, just a scratch.
Doesn't affect my movement.
There's another thing.
If you really get into a fight with
Wang Zhenqiu again, keep an eye out.
After I give you this signal,
find a chance to get hurt.
Just a scratch, nothing
that affects your movement.
This bastard has definitely
got me on his radar.
He'll be a major pain in the neck
inside the Company from now on.
It's better to keep a close eye on him,
but why am I feeling conflicted
about this outcome?
Maybe deep down, I didn't want
Wang Zhenqiu to make that choice?
What's up? Did you have
that much fun this time?
Why do you look like you want more?
Want more?
No, how should I put it?
These two are both top-tier,
totally different from
anyone I've met before.
Bao'er is amazing!
But she's too naïve.
Zhang Chulan is the interesting one.
I think I saw several sides to him,
each with a completely different vibe,
but they all seemed real.
There are just too many
contradictions in this person.
By the way, that curly-haired
guy Feng Baobao dragged in,
why did you just let him go?
Oh, him...
Hello? Can you hear me?
Hello? Hello?
I'm losing control! What's happening?
As he didn't stop cultivation,
the result would've been the same
whether I let him go or not.
You're so boring.
See, people are just so
complex and contradictory.
Don't fob me off with that.
Zhang Chulan is the most interesting one.
He's incredibly goal-oriented.
There must be a clear guiding principle
behind all those contradictions in him.
I'd love to dissect that guy.
If that guy was really just a jerk,
I'd be much more relaxed.
What kind of backbone is wrapped
up inside this guy's rotten flesh?
Did you use the Golden Light
Incantation or Thunder Magic?
I used both.
Is it that bad?
You won't die, but it's hard to treat.
I can't compare to you.
You got shot and were fine by morning.
Not by morning...
I was fine straightaway.
By the way,
what happened after I rushed in?
No idea.
No idea?
That woman rushed over and hugged me,
then extended a hand.
A hand?
Yeah, a blue hand.
My head hurt so much...
The last time I remember it
hurting that much was years ago.
By the time the pain
subsided and I could focus,
she was already dead.
Brother San!
Zhang Chulan!
Hey.
How's Baobao? Where are you two?
We'll be back soon.
I need you and Brother Si to
help with something first.
Yeah, I'll tell you about Lyu Chi and
the Lyu clan's actions when we get back.
Sure. Hurry over. We also
have some stuff to tell you.
Huh? I'm being targeted again?
Who is it?
Lu Linglong? Lu Lin?
Bao'er, there's some stuff
I need your advice on.
Hello? Chulan, how are you?
Have you thought about
what I asked you to do
when you were last at the Company?
Want to talk? Sure.
Hmm, I see...
Wang Zhenqiu has already reported
the details of this incident.
We've already told people
to find Liu Mingyuan.
As for those foreigners,
they were probably hired.
Zhang, you can speak freely here.
Tell me what's on your mind.
What can I say about this...
What do San and Si think?
I haven't told them yet.
Not yet?
You suspect them too?
From your perspective,
it's understandable.
So does that mean you trust me?
I'm talking nonsense.
It's not that you trust me,
you just have no other choice.
With Feng Baobao's situation,
if I were the enemy, you'd
be completely helpless.
You're wise.
Fine, we can proceed with this,
but I don't have much hope.
But if you want to get involved,
you must discuss it with San and Si.
I watched those two grow up.
I know exactly who they are
and what they're capable of.
Zhang Chulan, do you feel
you need to have everything
firmly in your grasp before
you can feel at ease?
No, not really.
You shouldn't have to shoulder
Baobao's burden alone.
You can't handle it.
You must weigh the risks and rewards of
choosing a trustworthy person yourself.
I know that.
But this isn't my fault!
Think about someone like Erzhuang!
Ultimately, it's because there are too
many weirdos in the world of Outcasts...
Fine, let's go with your plan as it is.
So, what about that favor
I asked you last time?
Oh, about that.
Tell me where he is.
I'll head out immediately.
But I have two conditions.
One: I need an assistant.
If I succeed, he'll be the one.
Two: with a subordinate, I'd be a leader.
How about a raise?
One is fine,
but for two,
go discuss it with San and Si!
Don't be like that, Chairman Zhao!
Those two are cheapskates!
Come on! Master, read my fortune!
Fortune-telling
That's...
What's his deal? He didn't
say anything for ages!
That's why he's cute!
Then that's not fortune-telling!
You look like you're about to eat him!
Master...
I've been having bad luck lately.
Could you read my fortune?
Bao'er!
Get him! Don't let him escape!
Let me go, Zhang Chulan!
Get this Bao girl to let me go!
Wow, still so arrogant?
Zhang Lingyu, you disgraced
disciple of the Tenshifu!
It's only been a while since we
parted ways at Longhu Mountain,
and you've caused so much trouble
that you got kicked out of the sect.
Zhang Lingyu,
our master went down the mountain
and single-handedly wiped out all
those members of the Quan Xing Sect.
And you also went down the mountain,
but you allied with the Bone-Scraping
Blade and the Seed of Calamity,
and fought those who were assisting our
master in eliminating the Quan Xing Sect.
Did you come to lecture me, Zhang Chulan?
Lecture you?
To be honest, I've never truly
known a woman in my life,
let alone loved one.
So there's no way I can
understand your feelings,
nor do I have the right to lecture you.
But I admire your willingness to
sacrifice yourself for others.
Didn't you say yesterday that he's
just an idiot with no future?
Miss Bao is right.
I have no future.
What are your plans?
Why don't you come with me
and work at the Company?
I don't need your pity.
Hey!
Remember how you used to brag to me?
Pity you? I'd be happy to see you fail!
You're not pitiful, you're useful.
It's just that no one will hire you now.
Longhu Mountain has
already kicked you out.
Even if you hadn't cause that scene,
as a disciple of the Tenshifu,
those so-called righteous
guys won't take you either.
But don't forget, you have the
Heaven Communicating Talisman!
Eventually, someone will
come looking for you.
Fortune-telling...
Couldn't you have written more?
Made it sound more mysterious?
You can't even pull off being a conman
after leaving Longhu Mountain.
You don't look well.
What's wrong?
I got beaten up,
for cleaning up your mess!
Not that I blame you.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm not being nice to you.
Master Zhang, I'm begging you to help me.
You're... begging me?
The Quan Xing Sect,
Longhu Mountain, the World Association,
Wang clan, Lyu clan, Lu clan...
ever since I stepped into this
world, everyone's been watching me.
I can't hold on alone much longer.
Master, I'm so tired.
I just want a friend I
can trust to support me.
I know you've never liked me
and we're completely different people.
All right, Master, just think it over.
Give me an answer whether
or not you're coming.
Bao'er, let's go.
Sure.
By the way, if you join me at the Company,
I'll still go back and visit
Master when I have time.
Bringing a colleague along
doesn't seem inappropriate.
Translation & Timing: Henry Lin
Editing: Alicia Ashby
QC: William Haggard
FQC: Sriram Gurunathan