The mansion...
What?
You're all still here?
Bernd?
Where have you been?
I was inside the mansion.
I figured if it was all gonna burn anyway,
I'd grab some of it as severance pay.
But don't worry.
I'll split it with the rest of you.
Well, I'll be on my way.
Miss Elise, I'll be in touch!
Mistress.
What do you intend to do now?
Huh?
I'm afraid you got to see
the absolute worst of all of us last night.
I'm sure it left
a very unpleasant impression.
However, we still do view you as family.
Yes'm, indeedy.
You're like a baby sister to us.
So why don't we all stay together?
No.
You've all supported me
through everything up until now.
But I think this is a good time
for me to leave the nest.
But...
I promise to come see you.
But I want to be able to stand
proudly on my own two feet.
We will meet again.
Lord Arne.
Is it true I was never human to begin with?
I never expected the mistress
to have already been bled.
It appears she was already not human.
That must mean...
From the very beginning...
L-L-Lord Arne?
You aren't carrying my blood after all.
H-Huh?
Take a look in the mirror.
Oh! I have a reflection!
How did it take you this long to realize?
Also, whenever I drink your blood,
it revitalizes me.
Blood from animals and
other species doesn't do that.
In other words, you are definitely human.
Both then and now.
Then, why...
I don't understand it either.
But does it really matter that much?
Huh?
Whether you're human or something else,
you're still Lynn Reinweiß, correct?
As surely as you are Lord Arne.
You're right.
Well, I believe I have fulfilled
my contract with you, human.
Yes, Mister Vampire.
"With my beloved family."
Oh, Father.
What you did was very wrong, Father.
But I know you still loved
your family very much.
And that's something I'll never forget.
Everything I'd known
changed for me that day,
but that doesn't mean
my story ended there.
Please allow me to stay here for a while.
I became Lord Arne's assistant,
met many new people,
and investigated lots of new cases.
Let's get going, Lynn Reinweiß.
Coming.
We still had many more days
full of mystery waiting for us.
THE CASEBOOK OF ARNE
PART 6: TIME WILL TELL
Man, I'm bored.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch!
Quit fooling around, Nachzehrer.
I'm not fooling around!
Hurry up and get this furball off me!
Ouch! Ouch! Quit pawing at me!
You'd never guess it, but this round
and fluffy stuffed animal is Nachzehrer.
Get off! Ah! Ouch!
We call him Nach now.
His heart was returned
to Lord Arne's body,
but his personality was placed
in this stuffed animal.
Oh dear. Look at your stuffing.
Here, let me fix it.
It's always been like this!
Come on. Open up for me.
We trust each other, right?
Don't do that!
Hey! No! Let me go! Don't poke me!
Here I go. You won't see it, but it's a-coming.
A one, a two, a three!
Incidentally, Amy here is an old friend
of his. They were very close.
Hey! I said don't poke me!
Afternoon, kiddo.
Thanks so much for finding
my stray cat, kiddo.
Ah, Sheepie.
This is Sheepie, the mail carrier who
brings jobs to the Arne Detective Agency,
and is just handy in general.
I've actually brought you
a new job, kiddo.
A new job?
Heave-ho!
Let's go!
What is this infernal racket?
Heave-ho!
Let's go!
Heave...
...ho!
Let's...
...go!
Are you the vampire detective?
I need to find out...
why my lover, Hanna,
would try to kill me!
THE MERMAID'S ATTEMPTED MURDER CASE
I hope you find it to your liking.
Why are you giving her seaweed?
B-Because I'm not sure
if mermaids can drink tea or not.
You said your name was Yurate?
What do you mean your lover
tried to kill you?
I was fast asleep one night
when Hanna suddenly assaulted me.
I fought back without thinking
and accidentally killed her.
You killed her?
Mm-hmm.
So who was this Hanna?
A human girl.
She was so kind and charming,
and also a bit of a crybaby.
But anyway, I happened
to save her life one time.
Oh no!
Are you alive?
Huh?
The first time I saw her, I could tell...
we were destined to meet
in the ocean that day.
After that, we became inseparable.
We had both been all alone before.
You were alone?
I'd gotten separated from my pod.
I don't really know what Hanna's deal was,
but she said she could never go home again.
Ouch.
Every day with her was so much fun.
We were only together
for a short while, though.
Isn't it lovely?
Like a real summer romance!
So why did Hanna attack her?
No deductive reasoning necessary.
The woman was probably after
the mermaid's flesh and blood.
Flesh and blood?
Yes, her flesh and her blood.
When humans eat mermaid flesh,
they become immortal.
Because of that,
many humans hunt mermaids.
But not her. Hanna was different!
I mean, she swore eternal love to me.
Eternal? Even though
human life is so short?
Maybe she was just promising to love her
and stay with her until the day she died!
Oh, then perhaps she decided
to kill her out of love?
Kill her...
and make Yurate hers forevermore?
I don't understand what you mean!
It's probably something like that.
Maybe she wanted to stuff and mount
the dead mermaid to keep her forever.
Your reasoning is too sloppy!
If she'd meant to kill her from the start,
she'd already had plenty of chances.
True. And even if it was
just for a short time,
there was probably no need
to start living together.
I'll take the job.
It'll kill some time, at the very least.
That night, I was sleeping
in the shack like always.
Hanna?
Huh?
Yura...
Wh-What? Why?!
Please understand, Yura.
No! Stop!
Hanna! Please!
Stop!
Hanna?
Hanna! Hanna!
Was she going to use the syringe to drain
her blood and the knife to carve her up?
Was there anything unusual about
the woman before she attacked you?
Now that you mention it, she'd seemed
to be researching something recently.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
A nautical chart?
Say, Yura. Are you sure
you're the only mermaid left?
Huh?
Don't you have friends?
Don't you know where
to find other mermaids?
No, I don't.
Are you sure?
After that, Hanna stopped talking to me.
She must have been
searching for mermaids.
Perhaps she was planning to build
a harem of mermaids. Dirty girl.
More like eat 'em all alive.
No... So Hanna really did mean to do it?
Are you feeling okay?
I'm so sorry.
But I'm glad I at least
threw up in the tank.
Uh, y-you are?
I-I'll help you clean it later.
Thank you. You're very kind.
I really shouldn't be doing this.
I keep saying I want to
understand her reasons, but...
Why shouldn't you?
I had been alone for a long time.
I'd gotten separated from my pod
a very long time before.
And I was so lonely.
But then, Hanna made me a promise.
What's wrong, Yura?
I don't know. I just feel so happy.
I never knew my heart
could feel this full.
I can't help but laugh.
And I know that's because I'm with you.
Hanna?
Let's get married, Yura.
Huh?
I, Hanna, hereby swear to love you
for all eternity, Yurate.
All eternity?
Yes, all eternity. As in forever.
Forever?
"Forever" it is.
I lied. I don't want to know why.
Yurate?
The truth is, I probably just want
to hear someone tell me
that Hanna wasn't actually
trying to kill me.
But why did this happen?
I want to know, but I'm also scared.
Maybe it's best if I never find out.
No, that isn't right.
You cared about her that much,
but you'd rather not know what happened?
I don't believe that at all.
I know it's scary, but knowing what
happened should bring you peace,
and help you find a way to move on.
I want to believe Hanna
was sincere in her promise.
Even if she swore eternal love,
compared to an immortal mermaid,
a human life would pass by
in the blink of an eye.
I'm sure it must be terrible to die first,
leaving your loved one behind.
Mermaids aren't immortal.
Huh?
They certainly live much longer
than humans, but they're mortal.
What? But I was sure...
Bring her in here, Lynn Reinweiß.
My original hypothesis still stands.
The woman assaulted the mermaid
because she wanted to become immortal.
But you said there was no point in living
together if she just wanted to kill her.
There was a point.
That was the woman's ultimate goal.
Goal?
The woman wanted to continue
living with the mermaid,
so she tried to eat her.
Huh?
But that would defeat the purpose.
Yup, sure would. Unless...
What if that woman believed
mermaids were immortal, too?
She's 200 years old,
but just look at her.
It wouldn't be unusual for a human
to assume she's immortal.
Don't you agree?
Yes.
And the syringe the woman
used during the crime
likely wasn't meant
for draining her blood.
Only someone like you, Lynn Reinweiß,
would jump to a conclusion like that.
There are many other possibilities.
Taking a blood sample, poisoning her,
giving her an anesthetic...
Maybe she wanted to make the procedure
as painless as possible for the mermaid.
She was gonna eat her, after all.
Why would she bother doing that?
I need to ask one thing first.
How much time did you
spend with the woman?
I don't know. I wasn't counting.
Maybe half of a hundred years?
Or a little more?
A hundred? But you said
you were only together a short while.
That isn't very long.
Different species
experience time differently.
In the mermaid's eyes, the woman likely
looked the same as when they met.
However, time had surely taken its toll.
Nearing the end of her life,
the woman was probably afraid of dying
and leaving the mermaid behind.
If she died, the mermaid
would be alone again.
So she decided to use the mermaid's flesh
to become immortal
and continue living together,
thereby fulfilling her promise
of eternal love.
B-But...
"It must be terrible to die first,
leaving your loved one behind."
Those were your words.
Hanna.
What a relief.
Thank you.
Love can take many forms.
Isn't that what makes it wonderful?
Sometimes, I have trouble
understanding the way people think.
Also, those two will never—
Uh-huh?
You're so cute when you're sad, Lynn.
What does that have to do
with what I was just saying?
One sip of mermaid blood.
How silly.
Am I...
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
TIMING: HENRY LIN
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: ELISABETH CRIST
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS