Khorosho!
Asirpa!
Who the hell is she?
Call our comrades!
They should be close!
The main force in Otaru, too!
She was speaking Russian.
Those two weren't Japanese either.
Their weapons were Swiss.
I saw that woman in the Otaru hospital.
They followed us all the
way from Ako Prison?!
They probably followed Asirpa, I'm sure...
But they seem to have it out for us.
Shall we kill her before she wakes up?
No, we take her prisoner
to learn what she knows.
If she's with Kiroranke, there should
be more of her friends nearby.
Our encampment at Tsukisappu is a
long ways away, and it's dangerous.
We're changing plans.
First, we hide Asirpa
somewhere safe nearby.
Hurry!
Golden Kamuy
Episode Fifty-Four:
Pinky Bone
Sugimoto, get on!
Good work, Shiraishi!
Go! Floor it! Floor it!
What are you doing, Shiraishi?!
The cat's going faster than us!
Get to the back!
I'll drive!
Do you know how?
How do I speed this up?!
Argh!
I think it's the lever
and the left pedal...
Sorry, Botaro...
Hey, Shiraishi.
You seen that guy with
the two pistols before?
Nope, never seen him.
Did Botaro say anything before he died?
"Don't forget me.
Tell your kids about me."
He talked all that crap about
wanting to be a king...
But I think in the end,
he just wanted to get back the
family and homeland he lost.
So you never heard anything
about the Ainu from him?
No, he told me everything.
Koito, Tsukishima, Kikuta, go find
our men who were separated from us.
Don't come back until you've
eliminated the pursuers.
These guerrillas fought
the Russian empire.
Don't underestimate them.
Sofia...
Lieutenant Tsurumi, we found this
in the woman's things.
Four men on foot have arrived
at the rendezvous point.
The three on horseback
should've arrived long ago...
We'll split up and look for them.
Wait here, Lieutenant Koito.
They may show up.
Are you okay, Hijikata-san?
We'll get back Asirpa!
Find the 7th Division!
We're going after Sofia.
What the hell are you doing here?
Are you trying to spy on Lt. Tsurumi?!
What about you, Lieutenant Koito?
You say to believe in you, and
your belief in Lieutenant Tsurumi!
But you don't believe him, do you?
No, I believe in him!
Don't just decide that.
So why did you say...
There was a tattooed prisoner
underground, but he escaped.
Until now, you've spoken
with a fast Satsuma accent.
You stopped believing in him at some
point, without even realizing it, right?
Nikaido!
I want you to stand watch outside.
Hide someplace far away
so you won't be spotted.
Yes, sir!
Even if the others come
back, keep them away.
Strengthen our defense outside.
He just checked that there
was no one outside.
Is there something he doesn't want heard?
That was definitely
Lieutenant Koito, right?
Yeah, he went into that church.
I'm sure Asirpa-chan is inside.
Want to break in and save her?
No, we'll bring Hijikata and the others.
We're at too much of a
disadvantage with just one gun.
But we need to hurry.
He can't trust any information
he learns through torture.
Lieutenant Tsurumi's going to take his
time to put pressure on her.
We don't know that.
He was acting a little
crazy in Karafuto.
Yeah, that's right.
You want to bust in there
right now even more than I do.
Okay, let's hurry and
bring reinforcements!
Asirpa!
I'll take this off,
but you mustn't scream.
I don't want to have to get violent.
There we go. A brave Ainu girl,
hachimaki wrapped around her head.
We didn't get to talk enough
at Karafuto, Asirpa.
And... Sofia Goldenhand.
The "Golden Hand." Quite the title.
The people see you as the shining
golden hand, the noble thief.
But you're also the cursed golden hand,
who's sacrificed many people
for the sake of the revolution.
I had a feeling I'd run into you again!
Who are you?
I should expect you wouldn't recognize me.
We've both changed.
Has it been... 17 years?
Can you remember me at all?
Zoya-san.
Have you forgotten my family, too?
Unfortunately, I burned
all the photos that day.
Only these finger bones are
left to prove they ever lived.
My daughter, Olga.
And my wife, Fina.
Hasegawa-san?!
Thank you, for remembering us.
That's Aca and Kiroranke Nispa.
A photo taken in Russia?
Lieutenant Tsurumi had
a wife and daughter?
We found in Kiroranke's belongings letters
proving he was in communication
with Sofia in Ako Prison.
What I know, and what you
learned from Kiroranke...
Why don't we put it all together
and share it with Asirpa?
Who killed the Ainu?
Why did Wilk have to die?
Let us be the ones... to remove her pain.
Golden Kamuy
Vladivostok
Do you know what the
word Vladivostok means?
Rule the Far East.
The only warm water port
in the Russian far east.
A military port that can
be used all year round.
An important point of conquest for Japan.
I've told high command
that occupying Vladivostok is
critical in the event of war.
You Japanese?
You know a man named Hasegawa?
He went missing six years ago.
Sorry.
Can you speak slower?
The bodies of his wife and daughter...
Hasegawa... Photography?
That's the name the old man was saying.
A Japanese man running a photography
studio in a place like this?
Thousands of Japanese live in this city.
One of them must've been odd enough to
open a shop far away from Japantown.
Hasegawa...
Wasn't that your mother's maiden name?
When I went with you to visit
her grave in Niigata.
You have a good memory, Tsukishima.
It's a common name in Niigata.
So that "Hasegawa" was
Lieutenant Tsurumi, huh?
Around 50 years ago...
A group of Ainu extremists gathered
gold dust as part of a certain plan.
Their plan was to buy warships, weapons,
and ammunition from a Russian
captain, then start a rebellion.
It's a truism that in any country,
soldiers far from home
will go out of control.
But just before the
trade could take place,
a Russian warship collided with a
passenger ship in Vladivostok port.
Everyone involved in the trade
died at the bottom of the sea.
With no use for it, the Ainu
gold remained where it was.
Asirpa's father, Wilk,
came to Hokkaido to find the gold.
You could say that's when it all began.
The man in the Russian photography studio
who taught my father and
the others Japanese.
He was Lieutenant Tsurumi?
That day, the secret police
were after me alone.
If my wife hadn't picked
up that warrant...
She wouldn't have come back.
And what's more, if you
hadn't chosen that studio...
My wife and daughter might
not have died in Vladivostok.
He said he wanted to expand
Japan's territory in the far east
so that the place where his comrades
slept could be Japanese soil!
Don't tell me the truth is...
He only wants it for personal
reasons, to make Vladivostok,
where his wife and child
rest, into part of Japan!
What was my wife and daughter's
role in this world?
I want you to tell these bones.
Yulbars' letters told you what
happened in Hokkaido, right?
What did you and your friends
gain from Fina and Olga's death?
Would you please tell me?
Yulbars' letter...
"Wilk changed."
"Because Asirpa was born."
Sofia...
Perhaps I should only
tell you this in person.
But it's too soon for Asirpa to know
this, so I'm putting it into a letter.
After coming to Hokkaido, the plan
was that I would part ways with Wilk.
We would live among the
Ainu and seek out the gold.
Wilk married to blend
in better with the Ainu.
And he had a daughter.
"When Wilk holds Asirpa..."
"He has a kind face like
I've never seen before."
Years later, I heard a certain rumor.
An old man who was believed to have
died from smallpox was found alive.
He was living all alone in the mountains.
The old man's name was Kimuspu, yes?
We found that same information
about the same time.
One of the Ainu who tried
to buy weapons from Russia.
A man who knew the location of the gold.
Noboribetsu
His discovery changed everything.
When you met that man
you weren't able to hear
where the gold was, right?
Siromakur
He refused to say.
Mesira
Let's persuade him to talk.
Do any but the seven of us
Sukuta
know about Kimuspu?
I spoke to several people about him,
but didn't say where he was.
Irenka
Ratci
He was deep in the mountains,
and no one knew he was alive.
He won't be found easily.
Oskeporo
If we go to find him,
will it be easy for us?
I know where he sets his arrow traps.
If we wait there, we'll find him.
Excellent! We'll hurry and find him.
Before someone else does.
Wilk?
Why aren't you letting me come with you?
Go on without me.
Explain what the hell you're thinking!
We should change the plan.
The entire Russian far east is too
big to protect from Imperial Russia.
I've decided it's better to just
gain independence for Hokkaido,
which is surrounded by the ocean.
After all we've done?
You're betraying us?
My people, who live in Karafuto
and the Russian far east?
We'll let anyone migrate
here who wants to.
All the different peoples
can live in Hokkaido,
worshiping their gods and
following their culture.
What are you saying, Wilk?
The village you were born in disappeared
because they abandoned their homeland!
I know why the Karafuto Ainu
failed in their migration.
We just have to not make
the same mistake again.
What about the Uilta people?
Hokkaido is too warm to keep reindeer!
How are they supposed to
protect their culture?
Migration here will be voluntary.
I think you've just stopped caring
about the minorities in Russia,
and want to protect your daughter's
future as a Hokkaido Ainu!
I'm just choosing the realistic option.
Hokkaido had nothing to
do with us at the start!
But now you have a family you love,
and this is your new homeland!
A battle for the survival
of their tribe...
Or love for his daughter?
Maybe only one of those two was the
real reason, but neither was a lie.
Sofia is still waiting for us in Russia!
Kiroranke Nispa was the same.
The reason for his anger wasn't just
the fate of the Russian minorities.
It was his love of Sofia.
Sofia!
Aca understood that well.
That's why he tried to keep
Kiroranke Nispa away, I think.
Wilk left without finishing me off.
The old him would've killed me before
I could be a threat to his plans.
The Wilk I knew before he changed...
He really had changed.
He wasn't the Wilk I'd loved!
Next Time
The Cause of Everything
Next Time: The Cause of Everything!