WANTED
FLUM THE MURDERER!!
Get back here, girl!
It's the slave girl!
Now Dein's flunkies are here.
They might've gone over to our place, too.
Milkit!
Master...
Do you miss Flum?
P-Please don't make
fun of me, Miss Eterna.
I mean, when you see what's outside,
I can understand being worried.
Master...
PARTINGS
MEETINGS
MEETINGS AND PARTINGS
I don't want them following me home.
I'll shake them off here.
Freeze!
Die, slave girl!
Got her!
Wh... What was that?
You're the ones who started it!
Don't blame me for this!
She leapt away?
She's no ordinary slave!
After her, you fools!
They're everywhere.
Milkit...
Eterna, please keep Milkit safe.
WANTED
FLUM THE MURDERER!!
"Flum the Murderer"?
Those punks went and
made all this crap, too?
Found her! Flum the Murderer!
She fell over there!
Damn, they're everywhere I go.
What do I do?
I can't even go home
when they're heading me off like this.
I'm getting tired.
End of the line, slave girl.
Dein!
I didn't think you'd show up personally.
Heh. I just felt like
taking part in the fox hunt.
You must be beat by now, right?
Give up and bow down to me, Flum Apricot.
I'm gonna have to refuse.
Will you die here and join
your mummy friend, then?
What did you do to Milkit?
It wouldn't have been any fun
just to kill her, y'know?
Right, boys?
How despicable.
Phil.
Oops! My hand slipped!
This is a rare poison.
Rumors say it can even kill a dragon.
And this here's a blind girl
we picked up on the streets.
Be a good girl and drink this, missy.
C'mon, bottoms up.
Down the hatch.
Stop it! What does she
have to do with this?
All right, then.
If you drink this
and drop dead in her place,
I'll let her go.
Screw this!
Whoa, there!
You are going to drink it, right?
You're too much of a goody two-shoes
to let her suffer. So get drinking!
She went for it!
Bitley, Dolph... I avenged you.
Dein.
Oh, good timing.
I just got revenge for Bitley and Dolph.
S-Slave girl?!
No way! She should be dead!
You said you'd let her go
if I drank the poison.
Didn't you?
I said I'd let her go
if you dropped dead in her place!
R-Right, you monster!
Who takes that lethal poison and lives?!
How could you drag
an innocent girl into this mess?
Scum like you deserve to die!
Seriously?
Fall back!
What are you saying?
Let's just take her out ourselves!
Dein!
What's the matter?
What's happening here?
Dein Phineas...
There you are.
Flum the Murderer identified.
Kill her!
There's ten... no, even more.
Give up and die, or fight and die in pain.
It wasn't the first time Flum
had been faced with that choice,
and her answer remained the same.
Have some shame,
you who have defied Milady
and disgraced the kingdom.
Who's there?
If there's corruption in the army,
I, Ottilie Fohkelpi, will stamp it out!
L-Lieutenant General Ottilie?
She's the second-highest-ranking
officer in the royal army.
Genocide Arts...
Anguis!
Dein, she's trouble!
Yeah, we're running!
You're not getting away!
Hurry, Dein!
Dein!
Phil! We'll meet up you-know-where!
Right!
I let him get away. How careless of me.
Lady Ottilie.
You're late.
Round up these fools.
They are to be court-martialed.
Yes, ma'am!
You can rest easy.
The kingdom would never harm—
Ottilie! It's been ages!
Flum?!
Why are you here, Flum Apricot,
and whatever is that on your face?!
It's a long story.
Are you okay?
That voice... You must be
the lady who saved me earlier.
Where do you live? I'll walk you home.
Where I live? Um...
I don't know. I have amnesia.
Huh?
Well, that's hardly ideal.
Master.
Milkit! I'm so glad you're safe!
I knew you'd keep her safe, Eterna.
No problems there.
I washed those scrubs away...
with my Aqua Stream.
Thank you, really.
No problem.
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh...
What? You too?!
Why is the Timeless Witch,
Eterna Rinebow, here?!
Why, you ask?
I left the party.
It was getting to be a real drag.
Curse you,
Jean Inteige!
Flum's parents left her in my hands!
Ottilie came to pick me up
when I was named a hero.
She escorted me on the several-day trip
from my home village to the capital.
I don't know what to say.
Oh, don't worry about me.
I'm doing okay.
Is that so?
I'm relieved to see you're doing well.
So, who is that girl
you brought here, Flum?
Oh, her?
She was a hostage taken by Dein.
She says she has amnesia.
Something must've happened to her.
Is it okay if she stays
with us for a while?
I'm basically a freeloader.
You don't need my permission.
Of course.
I would be very grateful.
It was corruption in the royal army
that led to this in the first place.
I'm truly sorry for causing you
so much trouble.
Don't be. This is all Dein's fault.
He blackmailed the West District guards
using evidence of their misdeeds.
I suppose he's not a Phineas for nothing.
A Phineas?
Oh, you didn't know?
He's the oldest son of House Phineas,
a ruined noble family.
What? Dein's a former noble?!
Yes.
He has the knowledge, smarts, and cunning
to set him apart from the common thugs.
That's how he built his influence
in the West District.
As the conflict between the Church
and the royal army grows more intense,
we heard that the West District guard
was under his influence.
Milady decided that the matter
must be dealt with at once.
"Milady"?
Uh-oh.
I mean none other than my dear Henriette,
General of the Royal Army! Squee!
Why, I can already bring to mind her
lovely legs! The back of her knees!
Her slender fingers! The webbing
between her index and middle!
Her nape! The back of her ears!
Her no*****s! Her lips!
Ah, don't gaze at me
with those beautiful eyes!
Uh... she kinda let herself go.
Is she always like this?
Oh, yeah.
She got like this a bunch of times
on our way to the capital, too.
Sounds like quite the ordeal.
I wouldn't say that.
Milady's busy enough as it is.
Why'd that stupid Dein
have to trouble her even more?
This is why I never get the chance
to have a leisurely chat with her!
She died.
WANTED
FLUM THE MURDERER!!
I got super worried when I saw this,
so I came to check on ya.
Thanks, Sara.
Who's this girl?
Oh, this is Sara, a nun
at the Central District church.
And this is Ottilie,
Lieutenant General of the Royal Army.
Nice to meetcha.
The pleasure's all mine.
The royal army... and the Church?
A beast?
Yes.
We ran into it by the mountains
in a village called Anichidey.
Yep! It also had an abandoned
Church research facility!
The Church has a bunch of research teams.
It must've been one of them.
That reminds me.
Remember how we got attacked
by a lady with a spiral face there?
A spiral face?
That lady was wearing the same clothes
as the kids in the Church's orphanage.
What?
Does that mean they're
experimenting on orphans?
An all-too-plausible possibility.
That's unacceptable.
Oh, I nearly forgot!
Weren't you wielding a cursed sword?
Oh, yes. That's what Reversal does.
Reversal?
Yeah. It seems I can reverse
the effects of curses.
I had no idea that rare affinity
could be used that way.
I only found out recently myself.
If we'd realized it on our journey,
you wouldn't have been sold into slavery.
I wish I'd done more.
Don't blame yourself. Even I didn't know.
Huh?
So you were chosen for the party
because the Church knew how effective
Reversal could be? Was that it?
Otherwise, it'd make no sense for her
to be chosen with all zeroes for stats.
But if the Church just wanted her power,
they could've simply abducted her.
Why was I chosen
to go fight the Demon Lord?
What is my worth?
Master.
Thanks, Milkit.
Either way,
there's no doubt the Church
is involved in all this.
I always thought the Church's
clandestine research
was for the purpose of
invading the Demon Realm again.
But considering Flum's power,
perhaps they have a different objective.
Either way, I'm happy to know
there are others out there
who suspect the Church of wrongdoing.
Could we continue to meet like this
and share information?
Of course.
I'll help out, too.
The more, the merrier.
We have an accord, then.
Come to the royal castle barracks
if you ever need help.
I will.
It's so good having Ottilie on our team.
I don't want you to take
any more risks, Master.
You must have put your life in danger
to fight Dein today, too.
Oh, it was nothing to worry about.
Really?
Uh, er...
I can't lie to you, Milkit.
So you were in danger.
I'm glad you're all right, though.
I knew you were waiting for me.
So I had to come home no matter what.
I'm happy to hear it.
And I'm happy to hear you say that.
She must've been really exhausted.
Yeah, that's the same outfit
as the Church's orphanage.
Should we really be taking
those off without asking?
Something's bothering me.
Magical tattoos?
Did she... run away
from a research facility?
I'll look after her.
I swear I'll make 'em pay!
Is that Phil? Or maybe...
Kahnis!
There you are, Dein.
You came looking for me?
Oh, don't bother getting up.
You... You sold me out to the army?!
You're not worth much
if a brat like that can defeat you.
I'll take over
the West District from here.
Good work all this time, "Mister Dein."
Screw you, you big lug!
Outta my way!
After him! Don't let him escape!
No matter what... I...
Just you wait, Flum Apricot!
What's that?
The hell is that?
Phil?
Is that you, Phil?
Dein called out to his lackey—
the same one who'd fallen to
Ottilie's sword in a bid to protect him.
It was Phil.
Hey, Phil! It's me!
It's Dein!
Wh-What happened? Answer me, Phil!
Or at least, it had been Phil.
But by that point, it was Phil no longer.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
BUDDING AND WITHERING