How many dynamite punches will it
take for you to fall, I wonder?!
Captain!
I already said... this is nothing to me.
If that's the best you've got...
Then you can keep it coming,
and it won't matter!
Captain!
This is...
A Sky Egg-exclusive All Might hoodie?!
Catastrophe
Great upheaval in society or the natural world.
Major change.
Can also refer to a tragic outcome in stories.
Often accompanied by destruction.
Balloon Soul
We're shaking again.
Is it really just an earthquake?
Control, this is Ingenium.
What's happening to the Sky Egg?
Pick up the phone, boss!
Should I go check things out?
Hello?
What now?
The power's out.
My phone!
It won't turn on anymore!
Mine either.
An EM pulse to shut down
all the electronics...
And make sure no one crashes
the Captain's last stand.
Here's the layout of the Sky Egg.
In the event of an earthquake
or other disasters,
the elevators shut down and the
emergency stairwells open up.
But the power rooms for each powered
down while they were still locked.
In other words, we're trapped.
And it was done on purpose
by a third party.
So if this isn't an accident
or a natural disaster...
It's an attack, with malicious intent.
Whoa, you mean a terrorist attack?!
Steady yourself, Death Arms.
Heroes are meant to be a reassuring
presence in emergencies—
you can't let yourself unravel.
Miss Tsukauchi, what's the
status of Captain Celebrity?
Unknown.
I see.
Then we'll assume the worst case
scenario, that he's incapacitated,
and respond with just the
heroes on the scene here.
We need to confirm the status
inside and out of the building,
ensure the safety of the audience,
establish a line to the outside, and
prepare to intercept any enemies...
Based on our individual Quirks, we'll
split up and handle these tasks.
Fifty thousand lives are in our care, and
we will not let a single one be lost.
We'll combine our strengths
to weave a safety net.
Are we agreed?
Teamwork ain't my thing, but fine!
Everybody, listen to me!
All this shitty shaking and
blackouts? An earthquake!
Or at least that's what we're
led to believe, for now!
You folks bear with us while we
make sure everything's safe!
Please, sit still!
If anyone is feeling sick,
please let us know!
There's an access port for the upper area
of the dome that can be manually opened.
It won't get us down
to the ground, but...
It'll suffice.
Authorized Personnel Only
No Trespassing
A group will head to the access port—
So we can let a group with
flight Quirks escape,
and establish contact with the outside.
If we can't re-establish power,
let's arrange for transpo—
More shaking...
Having CC around would be a real
relief at a time like this.
Boss...
Oh, sorry! I almost dozed off there.
What with how those punches of yours have
been so soothing, like a nice breeze.
That said, I'm wondering how much
more you've got left in the tank.
Blowing up your hands like
that, over and over...
It's not like you can
regenerate forever, right?
Why don't we both stop
wasting time like this?
I was in the middle of work, y'know.
And dealing with you isn't
part of this job...
I'm just throwing in a bit of fan service!
You!
I'm the man who's going
to defend this tower
with the stuff that
shoots out of my hands!
The Crawler, Sky Egg version!
Boy, what are you doing?!
Get out of here, now!
I can't! He's been
clobbering you, Captain!
No! I'm fine! Just look at me!
Act tough some other time!
It's just annoying right now!
Look, if I can nail his exploding fists
with my projectiles, and detonate them...
That'll save you from
any more direct hits!
Rapid fire special...
The Crawler's SGBBBB!
Shooty-Go...
Blam-Blam-Blam-Blam!
Hey, boy. You've just made something
really important clear to me.
Yeah? What's that?!
We're just buying time
here. Caught in a quagmire.
Without a lot of movement
toward a resolution.
Considering that thing can regenerate...
I don't mind getting a little dirty!
And if those blasts keep going
off, I know what'll happen!
The heroes will show up!
You're counting on someone else
to save us, at a time like this?
Doing my best while counting
on others to do the same!
That's always been my style!
Not the smartest way
of going about things,
but...
Right now, we don't have
a lot of other options!
I'm counting on you, my boy!
Right!
When that thing starts
flying towards Captain...
I use my SGB to stop him!
I need to stay on the move
and match his movements
so I'll always be in
position to defend Cap
with another SGB!
But if I don't pay attention to
maintaining the traction for my feet—
I'll fall!
Hey! Be a little more careful, my boy!
Th-Thanks!
If you fall, I'll have
no one defending me.
And if I go down, nothing will be
holding the Sky Egg's dome up!
All because of your carelessness!
I get it! Maybe ease off
with the pressure, please?!
You've got this, my boy!
I was always popular.
When I would fly around, people
would happily wave at me.
Adults, children, and especially girls.
But then...
Hey there, sweetheart! What's wrong?
If I see someone with a sour look on their
face, I can't help but ask about it.
It's nothing. This is
just how my face looks.
All right, but I happen to know a magic
spell for turning that frown upside down.
See?
I've been told this is more
exciting than a rollercoaster!
If you get scared, just hold on
tight and let out a scream—
What?!
Hang on, you're gonna fall!
I'll put you down, just wait! One second!
Sorry. I guess you didn't like it?
Being forced onto a rollercoaster?! No!
Not to mention your smug
smile being annoying!
No one's ever said that about me before.
I bet! Why bother getting
mad at a balloon?
A balloon?
Cheery, flashy, and empty on the inside.
And you're talking about me?
That's awful!
"Hey! Good afternoon! I'm a balloon!"
Look, I wanted to apologize
about the other day.
I just wanted to make you happy.
You still mad?
Not really.
Well, that's good.
I thought you might hate
me or something...
Considering how you glared
at me when we first met.
That's not what that was.
I just thought about how it must
be fun to fly around like that.
Really?! Then—
No more roller coaster
rides for me, thanks.
Only idiots and children
enjoy that kind of thing.
Okay, how about a balloon ride then?
Balloon ride?
Why are we so close to the ground?
It feels ridiculous in
a whole different way!
By your request, the balloon
tour will now ascend!
I never wanted anyone to hate me.
Especially when it came to girls.
And I have to admit,
the idea of taming a such a surly
young lady may have appealed to me.
But...
I was the one who ended up being tamed.
I went on a full-out
offensive afterward.
Desperate for you to look my way.
Wanting to see your smile.
Chris...
You might be a stupid idiot
who always seems fishy,
but when I think about how most of
the world is irredeemable trash...
You start to seem pretty nice...
in comparison.
Should I take that as a "yes," then?
Hey! Chris! Knock it off! Do
you want to make me mad?!
Honey, if it gets to be too much,
just hold me tight and scream!
Dummy.
I was so happy.
The thought of being able to
spend our lives together...
And getting to see your smile every
day for the rest of my life.
That was what I thought at the time.
Honey...
But ultimately, you were
mad at me all the time.
And I gradually started
having trouble with work...
People I thought were my good friends
used my name to swindle
people out of money.
I would think I was taking down a bad guy,
and then end up being sued,
making me seem like the villain.
I wonder where it all went wrong?
Honey, what should I
have done differently?
Everything was so complicated,
both at home and out in the world,
and even now, I'm not
sure what the answer is.
Hey, Captain? What are you smiling about?
Pardon me, just doing a bit of thinking.
We're facing off with a powerful,
exploding villain.
I have 50,000 lives
resting on my shoulders.
A very easy to understand dilemma.
Even an idiot like me
can't screw this one up!
I'm not sure I'd trade danger
for complexity, myself.
Wait! He's putting his hands together—
Crap! Captain!
A dud?
What have we got, Eraser?!
I managed to keep him from going
off, but it's a temporary measure.
It's not like the threat's actually gone.
And if he flies to the other side of the
tower, my Erasure won't be able to reach.
You won't escape, villain!
That's...
Best Jeanist! What's he standing on?!
This is the aerial escape team.
We've made contact
and reported the scenario.
We're now moving to deal
with the villains!
It seems the thread of
hope has found its mark.
Luna Fall!
This is Snipe! The flying villain
that was above the dome is down!
Ingenium.
Got something for you from Airjet.
These are the communicators
we use on Team Idaten.
Let's establish an
operational center here,
where we can support
and receive updates
from the assorted heroes
who are in action.
All right, people, get those
engines going at full throttle!
Ninpo:
Thousand Sheet Pierce!
Jeanist!
It's here.
It's time.
High-capacity carbon fiber cables.
Is this gonna work? They're really heavy.
It won't be a problem.
They can weigh tens of tons...
But if they are in the form of fibers,
they bow to my will as Fiber Master!
See, I was right! The heroes
managed to save the day!
I see. Well, if we're in the clear now...
I need to ask you for something, Koichi.
What's up? Why so dramatic?
Let my wife and baby know...
That Daddy was a great hero.
Sure! I don't mind.
Are you two all right?
Oh, we're fine! Hey, it's Edge Shot!
But you really ought to tell them
that yourself when you get home.
Pushing my limits... taking
it as far as I can...
I've never done anything
like that before.
But it's not a bad feeling.
Say, honey...
I feel like I may have finally
earned some praise from you.
What do you think? Was I cool?
Would you be proud to
call me your partner?
Boy?! What are you doing?!
Captain! Stop spacing out and fly!
And save me while you're at it!
I don't have the strength anymore!
That's why I'm falling!
What have you done?!
I kinda just got carried away!
God, heroes, anyone, please help!
I don't care about me, but save Koichi!
Don't let this brave boy die!
That's...
Captain and Crawler!
In this battle...
They've contributed from the shadows!
Which more than earns them our help!
Oh, no. Hell no.
This isn't happening.
You folks managed to hang on by the skin
of your teeth, I'll give you that,
but you were outgunned from the get-go.
That wasn't obvious because
I was trying to run an experiment.
Turns out, I can kick off the
climax whenever it suits me.
A detonation to get out
of the restraints!
Not good! I can't see them
inside of that smoke!
Not to mention, frankly,
a bunch of nobodies pulling out all
the stops to make a big save...
really pisses me off for some reason!
So, you can all die!
Causing the exploding villain's
body to limitlessly reproduce...
for one big boom! Game over, man!
Things have never been more desperate!
So, who else would show up
other than the number one hero,
and my idol, All Might?!
Next time: This Is a Hero!
And in the shadows, my master
begins a solo battle.