Episode 8
"The Midday Attack"
You stick out like a sore thumb, Gil.
Shut up. You're the one
who dragged me here.
We contributed to the production.
Don't you want to see it?
How much longer until it starts?
Not long, probably.
What's that supposed to mean, damn it?!
She's as boisterous as ever.
She sounds a bit desperate for
someone inspiring their troupe.
Excuse me, adventurers.
Is there anyone in the audience
who can play the violin?
We'll submit a job request
and pay you, of course.
Please.
Did something happen?
Our musician was injur—
You tripped and sprained your
hand? What are you, a child?
Get some rest!
You heard her.
I get the picture.
Can you play?
No way.
I knew this wouldn't work.
I don't have time to learn songs,
so could I play ones I know instead?
What?
I can't compare to a professional,
but if you're all right with that...
Thank you!
Boss, boss!
I found someone!
Really? I bet it's that
really classy guy.
Now then.
If it comes to it, let's
synchronize our timing.
What?
Excuse me.
I knew it was you. I appreciate it.
Ma'am?
I'm playing a handsome young boy.
These instantly heal external injuries.
It's low-level, but it should be
completely healed by tomorrow.
Everyone, on your knees!
However, it's not a labyrinth good,
so it will probably hurt a lot.
That's fine. Do it.
I don't expect you to memorize it.
I'll just explain the timing.
With five minutes, I believe I
can memorize the general plot.
Then do it. Please.
How many songs can you play? How well?
Well enough that a nobleman with
a good ear wouldn't complain.
That's more than good enough.
I can play just over ten minutes of
complete songs without sheet music.
I know four songs that would
suit the script I saw yesterday,
plus ten more partial songs.
Are you sure you're an
adventurer, damn it?
I am indeed a genuine adventurer.
For the adagio at the start...
Keep it light, with a steady tempo.
It's like a waltz.
Also, for this fight scene, I won't
be able to match the choreography.
I know, but could you just stop playing
here when their swords clash?
As long as I know the timing.
All right. You're perfect, damn it!
I apologize for any inconvenience,
but I look forward to working with you.
Excuse me.
It's almost time.
I am Verda, Prince of Incadia.
Let me tell you about the strange
events that affected my family.
I shall take your head
as a lesson to others!
You're soft for a scoundrel!
If you want to make an example out of me,
you have to hang me while I'm alive!
I shall be your opponent.
Not bad.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Your timing's off. Four.
Two.
One.
Zero.
Impressive as always.
Explain yourself, damn it!
You suddenly made the stage dark!
My apologies. But I did say
I'd inconvenience you.
I didn't think you were referring
to a specific event, damn it!
I'm sorry, but he'll recover by tomorrow.
Whatever. I appreciate your help today.
Thanks.
You shouldn't have volunteered
if you knew they'd attack you.
We helped with the production.
Don't you want to see them succeed?
You should've told me beforehand.
I didn't have time to explain.
So, was it worth it?
Yes, but I wish I could've
practiced more.
You're generally sincere, aren't you?
That was the same type of arrow again.
Did they think I couldn't
defend myself while playing,
or were they warning me that
they can get me at anytime?
You need to do something about this.
I'm kind of excited to see
what they'll do next.
So this is just a game to him?
That's not a very nice expression.
This is how I always look.
Several Days Later
I have a feeling they'll try
to shoot me again today.
You're treating this awfully lightly when
they're trying to shoot your brains out.
It makes no difference
if they can't hit me.
They keep popping out of nowhere.
They must have access to endless fodder.
The kid asking to join our
party is a bandit, isn't he?
Yes.
Couldn't we solve this by catching
him and making him talk?
Instead of making him talk, perhaps...
Gil suggested a practical
solution for the first time.
Perhaps he's getting tired of this.
If you still want to play,
then do what you want.
I'll do the same.
Really?
Yeah.
I suppose you're right, though.
I think he'll properly sell himself
today. Perhaps it's about time.
For this to end?
That depends on him.
But I can't let them run out of patience
and attack the people around me.
Well, you certainly look like
you're straight as an arrow.
They'll do it if they
want to provoke you.
What do you mean, look like?
If they hurt Judge or the others,
I'll be properly angry.
Oh, yeah? I'd like to see that.
Also, he isn't just a gang member.
What?
He's their boss.
There's a show going on in the plaza.
Oh?
I've always been helplessly
drawn to excitement.
I taught myself how to fight.
I'd nearly die taking on monsters
single-handed and laugh it off.
Eventually I learned about adventurers.
It seemed like a good way to profit
off my interests, so I became one.
One day, while searching for a powerful
monster, I was attacked by bandits.
I turned the tables on them instead.
I even killed their boss.
The insane survivors suggested
I become a bandit.
I went along with the idea.
That was the start of my life as both
an adventurer and bandit leader.
That's crazy.
Hey, boss. Let's name our gang.
Since we've gained members, we should
have a real bandit gang name.
What?
Wouldn't that be awesome?
In that case...
I heard the Forky Gang showed up again.
They're really making a splash.
How many times is that?
They've mistaken our name
for something really lame.
Hey, did you hear the news?
The Blade joined a party.
Yeah, with that nobleman, right?
They say he's a real adventurer,
despite how he looks.
A nobleman-like adventurer who
brought the Blade to heel?
Maybe I'll try poking him if
there's money to be made.
Let's see you struggle like
you never have before.
Wow!
Can I join your party?
Your strengths and motive
are conflicting. Try again.
I'm beneath his notice, huh?
He's so annoying. What should I do next?
I'm excited for tomorrow's show.
The Blade is crazy.
This is practically an invitation.
Don't shoot to kill.
We might as well wait
for an exciting scene.
What?
I don't get it. Was that magic?
You shouldn't be able
to block while playing.
Shall we go?
I wonder if he'll say yes today.
Let me join your party.
The usual, please.
Eleven, solo C.
My strengths are my dual-wielding
skills and night vision.
My weaknesses are my flashy
red hair and overconfidence.
I was moved by your
performance yesterday.
Taking jobs with someone like
you is bound to be fun.
Those are appealing qualities
for an adventurer to have.
Will he reject me because
he doesn't trust me
or accept me so he can keep an eye on me?
Either way, the man standing before
me will have to look at me.
You were overconfident.
Why don't we have a chat?
Does this mean you'll let me join you?
You've dropped a few hints until now.
Huh?
But today, you've given
me something decisive.
What?
How does it feel to properly face me?
You figured it out? Seriously?
Don't try to trick me into
talking. That's lame.
That won't be necessary.
How'd you know?
Actually, it was so obvious,
I thought it was deliberate.
You really were overconfident.
What?
Your reason for wanting to join.
I was moved by your
performance yesterday.
Taking jobs with someone like you...
Aw, man.
The only people who knew I
was playing were the troupe,
the audience members around me, and...
The shooter?
Isn't it possible that I happened
to watch the show and saw you?
Your beautiful red hair.
What?
You're eye-catching enough
for it to be a weakness.
I wouldn't miss you from the stage.
And that's how you knew?
But who welcomes in someone
they know is a bandit?
Even with a bodyguard,
that's some overconfidence.
He's not my bodyguard.
He's my party member.
Also, I noticed long before that.
What? Since when?
The moment we met.
You mean you found me suspicious, right?
No, I was quite certain.
Why?
I may not have known if
you'd sent someone else.
What?
Your split tongue. Forked tongue.
The boss of the Forky Gang himself
came to see me, didn't he?
You figured that out, too? Wow!
You don't trust anyone, do you?
I seriously doubt there's a
second snake beastman around.
I've never seen one
around here besides me.
So, what now? Will you turn me in?
If I say I will, will you run away?
No, although I doubt I could
under these circumstances.
To be honest, I don't
particularly care about that.
What?
That you're a lying,
ill-mannered bandit leader.
None of that particularly matters.
But you're about to attack
those around me, aren't you?
I'd prefer you didn't do that.
I'm still beneath his notice, huh?
I shouldn't let it get to me.
I can find someone similar
to play with, and then...
Thank you.
And you, Stud.
You're so annoying!
My wrist's broken. Let go of me.
That hurts!
You think I'd let go of someone who's
still fighting with a broken wrist?
You're quite the bandit leader if
Gil allowed you to get this close.
I wonder who's faster, him or Stud.
I've lost my edge, but I'm
still not easily beaten.
It's amazing.
When you move so quickly,
I can hardly tell what's happening.
You'd better learn to do it.
Aw, man.
So, who do you choose?
I'll give you what you want.
You think I can't do it?
You're young. You can turn a
bit of fear into pleasure.
You've probably never
felt true fear before.
Where have your spirited responses gone?
Fear is self-control.
Because you lack that, you don't
understand why
you should act accordingly,
despite knowing right from wrong.
Do you see now?
I-Is this...
If you cross the line,
I will be very angry.
...fear?
You understand where the
line is, don't you?
Shall I have him arrested?
No.
Did I scare you to tears?
It's all right. I'm not angry yet.
Come on. Don't forget to breathe.
You're a sucker for tears.
Even when you made him cry.
Huh?
I knew it. I'm short
three labyrinth goods.
The store isn't ransacked,
so I wasn't robbed.
Which means...
Picking a fight with the
merchant's guild is too scary.
Next Time
"Judge's Problem"
Next time: "Judge's Problem."
Illustration by: Utako Yukihiro