Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
Smooth as ever, I escort you
And this voice, seducing you
Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
I am your ace darlin'
Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
Please Please
Whisper just to me, call my name
You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
Hey, girl
Look this way!
I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
So take my hand and let's roll
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
It's a spell that makes your heart race
We can't go back
You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
Sweetie honey
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
There we go...
Washing everything away
Great work, Tamon-kun.
Tamon's B-Side
Why couldn't I realize it back then?
Thank you for the amazing
performance the other day.
Of course we're disappointed
that he couldn't take the center spot,
The sky in a morning without you—
so carelessly clear
but...
The RAIN won't stop
Under the sky, I start running
It's a new start - My days with you
I tuck them into my heart
and now I take a new step forward
Thank you for being there
RAIN—rain is falling
Wow...
Hey, didn't Tamon-kun
seem different than usual?
I didn't know he could look like that.
Oh, man...
Thank you very much.
In the end, Tamon-kun gained
a ridiculous amount of fans.
Meanwhile,
Ouri-kun has established himself
as the eternal bridesmaid.
He struggled so much with that
heartbreak ballad in the beginning,
but he got it down perfectly by the end.
Tamon-kun is a god who evolves.
Pochi, wanna go on a walk?
There, there.
Isn't red a great color, Pochi?
Isn't Tamon-kun a god, Pochi?
What's the matter?
Hey!
Hey, where are you going, Pochi?!
We ended up at Tamon-kun's place...
Stay right here, Pochi!
Ta-mon-kun!
This only took 15 seconds
Don't do anything rash!
Kinoshita-san?!
What were you thinking?!
How could you put your precious body
in danger like that?!
Please don't stop me!
There's no reason for me to live anymore!
It's a waste for someone like me
to be breathing everyone's air!
The world is better off without me!
If I disappear,
there won't be any more suffering!
In my next life, I want to be a creature
that makes people happy just by existing!
Like a hamster!
Please, calm down! It's quite
difficult being a hamster, too!
For example...
They have to spin their wheel...
Or struggle
to peel sunflower seeds!
Oh, no! Is this world doomed?!
It's hopeless!
Gloom!
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Have you calmed down a little now?
Yes... I'm sorry.
Why would you do something like that?
Did you realize just how beautiful
your face is and lose your mind?
Do I seem that merrily off my rocker?
Or you became afraid
of your beautiful voice...
I wasn't able to be the center.
Even though I received so much support,
I messed up the fifth round badly...
But I wanted to sing
that song as the center.
Please don't be so depressed!
Your performance at N Station was amazing!
I'm sure a lot happened
until you got to that point.
But your performance on that stage
is burned into all of our brains.
So...
You'll still be smack dab in the center
of the hearts of us fans, Tamon-kun!
Not to mention, you've gained
an insane amount of fans since then,
and the old-school fans
are all happy that you've leveled up.
And you, Kinoshita-san?
Huh?
Of course, that goes for me, too.
You were cheering for Ouri-kun, too.
I'm sorry. Say that again?
You two seemed really friendly...
and before I knew it,
you were going to his house...
So, um... I thought
you might be Ouri-kun's fan...
If you have something to say,
just spit it out, please.
Spit everything out right now
until you're satisfied,
and then smile again
as Hottiehara-san tomorrow.
Huh?
Please don't go to Ouri-kun.
Um, I'm sorry. I'm gonna say
something really weird right now.
I'm sorry?
I don't really get it...
But whenever I remember you
being near Ouri-kun,
I just lose my will to live
for some reason...
Will... to live?
This is affecting my work, so I've been
trying to figure out what to do...
G-Gloomyhara-san?
This is the first time
I've ever felt like this...
Um...
I'll keep doing my best!
I'll even lick some boots and eat garbage.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What are you even say—
I'll do anything if it makes you happy.
Gloomyhara-san's... being weird!
I can tell a lot's going through your mind
after the results the other day...
But you shouldn't say
those things, Tamon-kun!
He's probably just tired.
It's getting dark, so you
should return to your apartment.
Pochi's waiting for me downstairs,
so I need to head out, too.
No matter how much of a failure I am,
please just be my fan, Kinoshita-san.
Otherwise, I'll...
die.
Huh?
Wait, what?
Am I being threatened right now?
You don't have to ask.
I'll only ever be your fan.
Wait, is he holding me...
Am I just imagining it?
P-Please don't say you'll die so easily.
You mean it?
I'm not imagining it at all!
Yes!
I-I'm so sorry. I just got
really anxious all of a sudden.
I didn't know what I'd do
if you changed oshis on me.
I'm sorry.
The usual Gloomyhara-san.
And the usual Hottiehara-kun.
Then earlier... was that...
Tamon-kun's B-Side or something else?
Oh, there's some tea left.
What was that?
Please wake up, Kinoshita-san!
No! No!
Kinoshita-san! Wake up!
Man, that startled me.
Please wake up!
Gloomyhara-san's acting differently
than he usually does.
I'm so sorry! It's all my fault!
What should I do?
I guess being removed from
the center position really got to him.
That poor thing...
But I'll continue supporting you.
Kinoshita-san!
No! No!
Please, wake up!
Please get a hold of yourself!
Please! Please, wake up!
EYES ON YOU! We are F/ACE!
Everyone! Thanks for supporting
F/ACE of F/ACE!
To everyone who's heading to work
and everyone staying at home,
thanks for watching!
Yeah, thanks!
Well, let's get started.
Keito-kun got chosen as the center
for your new song, "RAIN."
How do you feel right now?
Yes, well, I had a tea stalk standing
in my tea just now, so I feel great.
No, no, no. I mean how do you feel
about being the center?
Oh, I see. Sorry about that.
Jeez, get a grip already!
I became the leader
because I'm the oldest,
but starting today,
I'm also going to be the center.
Of course, I'm a bit nervous,
but I'll do my best and also
get advice from Tamon, too.
Leave it to me!
Tamon-kun, you've been switched
out of the center position, but...
Honestly, I'm a bit disappointed,
but any position is just as important.
Also, Keito's a bit of an airhead usually,
but he's super awesome
when he's singing, so I'm not worried.
Thanks. I'll do my best not to get
leg cramps from being too nervous.
And to all my girlfriends
that I love out there...
I'll show you a new side of Tamon Fukuhara
that you've never seen before.
You better look forward to it!
I wuv you.
And that's all from the members of F/ACE!
Thank you very much!
See you later!
F/ACE's New Song "RAIN"
New Visual Just Revealed
But wow, since the spacey
Keito-kun's now the center,
I'm sure we'll be seeing
a new side of F/ACE.
We're looking forward to
the release of their new song "RAIN"!
We'll be going now!
Thank you very much!
F/ACE is super popular,
but they know their manners.
Their leader Keito-kun
seems like a great guy, too!
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Keito
Home | Favorites
Tama @tamachan_keito791...
He's so cute
#Keito-kun
Keito 4 Life @life_k_face341
I'm relieved that he seems the
same even after becoming the center
#KeitoTachibana #Keito-kun
Hoshityami @starhoshi1122
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah not enough Keito,
not enough Keito Hnnnnnnnnnnngggggghhhhh
#F/ACE #Keito-kun
He's super popular.
All according to plan.
Keito Tachibana @keito_face_official
I'm F/ACE's silly center-slash-easygoing one.
I'm Keito Tachibana and it's a pleasure
#KeitoTachibana #F/ACE
It's so nice that they're all fools
that're easy to manipulate.
Seriously, the difference
in your personas is so intense.
It creeps me out.
You're one to talk.
Shut up. And don't mock our fans, trash.
Goodness, you've got a bad mouth.
I guess the other three
are headed elsewhere.
Incidentally, Ouri.
There's something I want to ask you.
You saying "Incidentally" pisses me off
for some reason, so nope.
I'll rip off your bangs.
I saw Tamon with a mysterious girl.
Do you know anything?
Wh-Who the hell cares about her?!
Why would I know?!
So you do know.
Is she the reason that Tamon's condition
has been so volatile lately?
There's no reason to hide it,
so I'll just tell you.
I'm gonna make that chick
fall for me someday.
The rest of this info doesn't matter.
She's an obsessive Tamon fangirl
and also his housekeeper.
A... fangirl?
Grand Maison Musashino
This is the first time in a while that
I'll be working at Gloomyhara-san's place.
Hopefully, he's gotten over his shock
at losing the competition for center.
Hello.
Thank goodness.
It's his usual, barely audible voice.
It's the usual Gloomyhara-san.
Or not!
Splash Splash Splash
I must repair the World Heritage artifact!
Wipe Wipe Wipe Wipe
Voooooooor Vrrrrrrrrrrrrooor
I guess weak flour explodes...
I guess the name was nothing
but a lie and a trap.
Weak Flour
Um...
Yes?
Is that a new outfit?!
Ah! I'm sorry for trying to stay clean
despite being garbage!
Getting to be that close to you
and protect you...
The apron couldn't be more blessed!
But why are you wearing an apron?
I was trying to make a cake.
Weak Flour
A cake? Where did that come from?
The competition for center
didn't go like I wanted,
but you've been helping me out so much...
Huh?
So I wanted to thank you somehow.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
You're baking me a cake?!
I couldn't possibly accept it!
Spend that time on your physical and
mental health and for your future instead!
You're right.
Gloom, gloom. Gloom.
Huh?
No one would ever want to
eat something I've made.
I should just sip on some muddy water
instead of baking a cake, huh?
If it's a cake that you've made,
Tamon-kun,
gatoo chocolat
tAmoN fuKuhAra
it would be Gâteau au chocolat
even if it was made of clay!
Gloom, gloom, gloom.
Weak Flour
Fresh Milk
100% Raw Milk
Rich Butter
I've definitely made cakes for my oshi,
but to think the day would come
where the roles were reversed...
Life is full of surprises.
Are you sure you don't need any help?
Yes.
When I die, I want to make sure
I die without troubling anyone.
Please don't risk your life making a cake!
Okay, I've learned the steps.
Yes. First, you need to sift
the weak flour through a sifter.
Ah...
He's terrible at this.
No wonder a dust explosion
occurred earlier.
Next, he needs to melt
the butter in hot water.
And he put it directly into the hot water!
It's hot!
I won't help,
but can I watch you from here?
I love watching cakes being made.
R-Really?
Yes!
This takes me back to when I made
a birthday cake for Tamon-kun.
June 12
Tamon Fukuhara's Birthday Celebration
It turned out pretty well
if I do say so myself.
An Otaku's
Biggest Event
Unconditional Love
for Tamon Fukuhara!!
A Birthday Party Without the Actual Birthday Boy
Baking cakes is fun, isn't it?
On my birthday, my fans make me cakes.
It's not like I can actually eat those,
but they make me happy.
Cakes really are special.
And then all of his followers cried!
All of your fans around the world
would sob if they heard you say that.
We're all making them
filled with our love after all.
Love...
Okay, I'll put all of my feelings
into making this, too.
I hope that Kinoshita-san will be
able to deliciously enjoy this cake.
He's too friggin' cute!
I hope that Kinoshita-san will
continue coming over forever.
You're giving me that privilege?!
I hope that Kinoshita-san never hates me.
That won't happen—
And never betrays me.
Huh...?
Or cheats on me.
May she never show any interest in
the rest of humanity for all her life.
I'm going to make this delicious.
Gloom, gloom, gloom, gloom...
I thought he was better now,
but he's still acting weird.
No matter how much of a failure I am,
please just be my fan, Kinoshita-san.
Does anyone say all that
to their housekeeper?
I mean, I told him that
I'd only ever be his fan, but...
I-It's done!
Kill... me...
Kinoshita-san
Kill... me... Kill... me...
Wow! A homemade cake that my oshi made!
I'm going to freeze it
and make it my gravestone!
No...
Please, eat it.
I even bought some delicious
Poca Cola to go with it.
I'm sorry.
But I'm currently working, so...
I'll humbly accept the thought, though.
Oh, no. I made Tamon-kun sad.
But I just can't...
I'll go clean the bathroom!
Huh?
Eat it.
Even just a bite.
Come on. Please?
Open up.
Accept it... All of my love.
Tamon-kun, no...
We mustn't...
It has no taste.
W-Well,
it's not unusual to have some tea
and snacks after finishing work,
so a little won't hurt...
Okay, I'm done cleaning,
so I'll have some.
This is the first time in my life
that someone gifted me a whole cake
on a completely random day.
It's delicious.
Gloomy, gloom... Gloomy, gloom...
I had been treating Tamon-kun like
a cute little needy puppy...
But then he got all weird to the point
that I'm getting worried that
he might not even be from this planet.
Have some cola, too.
Th-Thank you very much.
He... totally flipped his switch
on purpose earlier, didn't he?
Let's eat.
He did that knowing full well
that would stop me, didn't he?
Looking back on it now,
this isn't the first time it happened.
Lately, it's almost been normal
to be so close to him,
but Gloomyhara-san is a super idol who
puts people everywhere under his spell.
And he's playing a character
he created to do just that.
Meaning, finessing one fangirl
would be nothing to him.
Kinoshita-san
And he definitely finessed me...
This is dangerous.
I should get going.
What? Already?
This fanservice is so extreme...
He's basically devaluing
himself as an idol.
I can't let this escalate any further.
I'll take the rest home with me.
Could I borrow an ice pack?
Oh... sure.
I need to keep my distance.
Being overprotective isn't always love.
I need him to be able to
survive on his own.
Kinoshita-san, you've got some
frosting on your face.
Huh?
Right here.
It's fine! Please stay back!
You needn't dirty your hands
over something like this!
You don't need to hold back.
Huh?
We're closer than that, aren't we, Utage?
He...
He did it again!
This fanservice is too extreme!
I'm sorry. I just reacted.
But I figured you'd be
okay with it, Kinoshita-san.
Kinoshita
Huh?
He's sulky, gloomy, and always
sensitive to others' moods.
That's exactly what
makes him a sharpshooter...
Kinoshita-san
Because...
You think I'm hot.
Tamon-kun's... always been like that.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michelle Tymon
\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
\h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
Translation Check:
Alicia Ashby
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
Uh huh...
Na na na...
I wonder what the world
would look like without you
When I look back,
you've always been by my side
Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
A speedboat sails across the endless skies
An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
Like a wilted flower coming back to life
A light that shines
Through the impossibly dark night
(Light of your soul)
I wanted to grasp it
(I love you so)
So I strived for it
Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom