Adapted from the story of the
same title by author Ku Xuan
from Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen
Group The Daily Life of the Immortal King
Nuan, come here.
Daddy got you something.
Ta-da!
Hehe.
I finally got my writer's fee.
I spent a lot
asking the Spirit Sword 4S Shop
to make it for you.
Do you like it?
It's useless, dad.
Ordinary Spirit Swords can't handle
Wang Nuan's Spiritual Energy.
What are you doing...
I'm putting it back together
and asking the 4S shop to accept
unconditional returns within 7 days.
Alas.
I've seen other kids have Spirit Swords
by their side day and night since birth,
and nurturing sword spirits.
We can't let Nuan
fall behind at the starting line.
Dad. Mom. Leave the Spirit Sword to me.
The Daily Life of the Immortal King 5
Episode 9: Making
a Sword Spirit for Little Sister
Go inside.
Prisoner is taken to the cell.
Headquarters got it.
Hmph.
You all remember this.
When I break free,
every last one of you will die.
What bad timing.
First Prison just tightened security.
What took you so long?
I gave you chances,
but you just couldn't get it done.
Bai Zhe, you...
You're Sword Immortal Fan Rui's disciple,
so you'd know where the Demon Sword is.
Do you really think I'd tell you?
How about we make a deal?
No need.
Lead the way.
Yes, Lord Bai Zhe.
Nurturing a Sword Spirit
is a long-term process.
Master Ling, if your sister
wants a Sword Spirit,
she's gotta practice
swordplay day and night,
and form a bond with the Spirit Sword.
And wait until your sister
comes of age, the Sword Spirit
will be summoned from
the Sword Spirit Mystic Realm.
Sword Spirit Mystic Realm?
Exactly.
Why not go to the Sword Spirit
Mystic Realm to find one now?
Sword Spirit Mystic Realm's
entrance is right here.
But it only opens automatically
every 2,000 years.
The next opening is
still 1,000 years away.
No need to go to all that trouble.
What?
So, they can be one?
Whoa! This is so wild!
Who said this peachwood sword was weak?
This peachwood sword is freaking awesome!
My respects, Sword Master.
I'm going in.
Alright.
This... This is the legendary...
Sword Spirit Mystic Realm.
Well, this is my first time
seeing someone going inside so directly.
Back then,
you pushed your Master off
the Cliff of Enlightenment.
So, this's also where
the Demon Sword's spirit was sealed.
Step back.
Hmph.
Let me see how long you can last.
My lord, it's time.
Just a Demon Sword, it's mine now.
So this is the inner
world of the Sword Mound.
Why did Sword Spirit Mystic
Realm become like this?
Ah?
What's wrong?
Last time I entered, there
were many small Sword Spirits.
Why did they all disappear now?
Sword Master, I'll take care of this.
Such a strong, intense vibe.
Ah!
Why is there such a vicious
Sword Spirit here?
Eh!
Aren't you... Aren't you shocked at all?
I've gotten used to it.
So these little guys
were all hiding from it,
so they didn't come out.
Nuan.
It's going to rain soon.
Let's go inside.
These are Sword Spirit infants?
Yeah.
Sword Spirits can take human form,
bestial form, or even plant form.
After having the Spiritual
Aura from nature,
the Sword Spirit infants
evolve into different forms.
It seems Master Ling killed
that fierce creature,
so they finally dared to show up.
That vicious Sword Spirit beast
devoured plenty of these little guys
over the years, so it got so fat.
So itchy.
Don't do that.
I need to pick one for my little sister.
How do you want to choose?
Don't be afraid.
I found it.
Hahahahaha.
Hear my summons.
Show yourself, Spirit of the Demon Sword.
Huh?
Where did it go?
What?
What...
What's happening?
Would you like to be my little
sister's Sword Spirit?
So cute!
Can this little guy really protect Nuan?
What's your name?
What's going on?
Someone is summoning it.
It's not quite what I imagined,
but it's the Sword Spirit
of the Demon Sword.
Destroy this place.
What?
Why did it run away?
I will be back.
It got teleported away
before the ceremony even ended,
because Nuan summoned it.
My little sister is way crazier
than I ever was as a kid.