Why, though?
What does he want with the village?
I don't get it!
Th-this is awful!
The thing Mr. Doz had...
It might be a Rock Dragon egg.
And if he brings it into the village...
I get it now!
That Doz guy is baiting
the Little Rock Dragon!
We have to give it back
as soon as possible!
Where'd Doz go?
Is he leading it
to the village on purpose?
Is this part of some revenge plan?
And why is he riding
on the back of those monsters?
Ah, my thoughts are all over the place!
Damn it!
I can't shake them off
with Myria on my back.
Illusia!
Leave me behind and keep going!
I'll hold the monsters at bay!
Please stop Mr. Doz in the meantime!
Are you crazy?!
There's no way you can beat those wolves!
I beg you!
Please save the village...
Illusia!
You bastard!
Get wrecked!
Myria...
Everything's okay now.
Illusia, please...
Hurry to the village...
Okay, I'll protect the village!
But...
I'm going to protect you, too!
C'mon, slow poke!
Wait up!
Hey, kids, the sun's going down.
Get home quick.
Yes, sir!
What's that sound?
I thought I heard some kind of roar...
No, I must be imagining things.
It's getting dark fast.
I have to find Myria
as quickly as possible.
I have to hurry to the village!
Oh pain, become stronger and turn into courage
What was I born as?
The world I reached out and touched
Shines sadly and delicately
That is exactly why, no more pains
The pulse of the future in this place
Once felt, cannot be stopped
Chase after the light
Gliding Claw
Now wanting to protect someone
Right... There's no losing and no giving up
Gliding Claw
I understood that little me has changed
Oh pain, become stronger and turn into courage
Myria, are you okay?
Illusia,
you're bringing me to the village.
Thank you.
Her injuries don't seem that bad,
thank goodness.
She should be fine
if she uses her recovery magic.
Rest.
Huh? That's for me?
Your back must hurt from all the strain.
I can't cast any more after this, though.
Myria! You are truly so kind.
Let's hurry.
What's going on?
Don't tell me Marielle's warding stones
aren't working!
D-don't you dare try to go any further!
Just like I thought...
Please wait, Mr. Gregory.
This dragon is named Illusia.
He's come to save the village!
Myria?!
It's true, please believe me!
A dragon with Myria on its back...
Huh?
His face looks familiar...
Is this... the dragon from before?!
That dude who stabbed me in the leg!
Yes.
I know it looks like a Plague Dragon now,
but it's the same dragon.
A Plague Dragon?!
But he's very kind.
And he's friendly to humans!
Wait, so he was trying to help you
that one time?
Yes.
Hard to believe there are
Plague Dragons who help humans.
Although I had no way of knowing,
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Gregory!
You're such a good, reasonable guy!
What is it?
Are you replying to me?
Illusia can understand what we're saying.
Get outta here!
A Rock Dragon?!
Mr. Gregory, have you seen Mr. Doz?
He sicced this thing on me
then ran off by himself!
Mr. Doz is planning to get that
Rock Dragon to attack the village!
He's using its egg as bait!
What'd you say?!
We have to stop it.
Let's go, Illusia!
I'll join you!
Things could get chaotic if the villagers
freak out at the sight of this dragon.
That would help a lot.
Can I hop on?
What was that sound?
Came from the forest...
Ah! It's Mister Doz!
Oh, Doz!
What'd I tell ya!
There he is, livin' and breathin'!
I-it's a dragon!
That's Gregory and Myria!
Why are they with a dragon?!
Did any of you see Doz?!
He went towards the watchtower!
I-it's a Rock Dragon!
No way! What the hell?!
This is bad.
It's getting real close!
We have to stop Mr. Doz quickly!
No, just let the dragon and I handle him.
Myria, you grab everyone
and evacuate west of the village!
Huh? But...
You're injured, aren't you?
That's just going to make you a liability
if you come with us.
He's right about that.
I don't want Myria
to face any more danger.
I'll be with this guy the whole way,
so don't worry about him.
As for you,
please take care of the villagers.
Okay, I'll do that.
You two be careful.
Same to you.
Let's go!
Man, it's crazy to think that little
hatchling became this big Plague Dragon.
I mean, I've heard stories of monsters
growing bigger and stronger, but still.
Once this situation is taken care of,
I'll introduce you
to everyone in the village.
Let's be friends, all right?
Are you kidding me right now?!
Am I on my way to herodom?
Will everybody cheer
for the dragon of justice, Illusia?
And welcome me with open arms?!
You rule, Gregory! Best guy ever!
Put down your sword!
What's goin' on with Mister Doz?
It's a dragon!
Gregory, what's with the dragon?!
He's our ally.
What in the world?!
Let us handle Doz!
Everyone get out of here, now!
What's going on?
A Rock Dragon is headed this way!
There's no time! Hurry!
Okay! Move quickly, everyone!
Run!
This way!
Mom!
Gregory!
You really think you can slay me
with a sword like that?!
You're done for!
I can't do it.
Even if it's justified,
killing a human will make me
a real monster!
Take a nap!
I'm a dragon of justice.
I avoid killing whenever possible!
He is a friend to humans, without a doubt.
Gotta get the egg immediately!
Are you really human?
View stats!
Status: ****
This abnormal status
is the same as the Mahawolfs'!
Mister Doz!
M-mister Doz, it's me! Jean!
There's nothing I can do now.
But...
The Little Rock Dragon will make it here
if I just stand around...
What the heck do I do?!
I Went to the Village and Found Carnage
If I make any hasty moves,
he'll kill that kid for sure.
What?!
First that abnormal status and now this.
What is going on?!
Oh no, it's already made it here!
Is he going to smash it?!
Not on my watch!
Damn it!
Okay! Now where's the egg?!
What was that?
Miss Marielle?!
Oh, Myria!
Thank goodness you're safe!
What in the world is happening?!
Mr. Doz lured
the Rock Dragon into the village.
S-say what?!
Doz?!
This is hell!
Did I screw up when I didn't kill Doz?
Is this what it leads to?
Seriously?!
The kid is okay.
What a relief!
Hey, you okay?
Gregory!
You're telling me
to take the kid and leave, huh?
But what are you gonna do?
You're gonna fight that monstrosity?
Okay, but you'd better not die!
I can't back down.
There are still people out there
I must protect.
So I'm going to fight for their sake.
Because that's...
my way of the dragon!
View stats!
Little Rock Dragon
Status: Enraged (Major)
Attack:
Defense:
Magic:
It's far stronger than it was before.
I have no idea if I can win or not.
But at the very least...
I can buy time for everyone
to get out of here safely!
Let's go!
Too slow!
Take this!
Dragon Punch!
Ouch! It's really hard!
In that case...
Baby Breath!
That didn't work, either.
Well then...
Meteorite!
Nothing's working!
Damn.
Its attack and defense stats...
they're way higher
than anything I've encountered so far!
I took too much damage just now.
Worse yet, I can't think of a move
that'll actually work on him.
Am I done for?
Back up's here, dragon friend!
We'll protect our village, no matter what!
We'll beat that Rock Dragon together!
Gregory!
Go to hell!
I ain't done yet!
Come on!
Listen up!
Me and the Plague Dragon
are gonna get its attention!
Aurus, Lucas!
Aim for the opposite eye
when you get the chance!
Okay!
Leave it to us!
Hell yeah! Bet that attack hurt!
View stats!
It barely did anything?!
No way!
This is bad! It's using Tremor!
Lucas!
Watch out!
Gregory!
Damn it, we're done for at this rate...
There's gotta be something I can do!
Run away.
r u n
R U N
Divine Voice
Lv 4
The Divine Voice skill has gone
from level three to level four.
You can now access the
simplified simulator rendered by Laplace.
Laplace
Simplified
Simulator
What's the big idea?
Whaddaya mean
the Divine Voice leveled up?!
But I imagine...
you will not run
no matter how much I warn you.
You were an exception to the rule,
in so many ways.
It's unfortunate
this is where we must part.
So you leveled up
just to tell me this crap?!
I never got tired of watching you.
Rest peacefully now.
I'm so sick of your condescending babble!
Just who the hell are you?!
The Divine Voice cannot provide
explanations of that nature at level four.
Screw that noise!
I'm gonna prove you wrong!
I still have my last resort...
Evolution.
But it'll change how I look,
which means Myria and the black lizard
may not recognize me anymore.
There are four different evolutions
I can choose from now.
Which one should I choose? Think!
Jormungand.
I might stand a chance at winning
if I pick that,
but its deadly poison
is seriously bad news!
Rolling Dragon!
It specializes in the Roll skill, right?
Is that actually powerful?!
Dark Drago-human!
But are demi-humans good in battle?
I have no idea what to expect!
Little Arc Dragon!
Can white magic be used to attack?
Is it enough to beat that bastard?!
Which one?
What should I choose?!
Which one is most likely to win?!
What was that just now?
It's like all my MP got taken from me...
You have received the title
"Laplace Authority Interference."
Little Arc Dragon
If you evolve into Little Arc Dragon,
your odds of winning are 4%.
There is a less than 1% chance
of you saving all your injured allies.
The hell does that mean?
Are you telling me I can't win
even if I evolve?!
Jormungand
If you evolve into Jormungand, your odds
of ending the battle in a draw are 98%.
There is a 94% chance
the village is totally destroyed.
What's the point
if I can't protect the village?!
Rolling Dragon
If you evolve into Rolling Dragon,
you have less than a 1% chance of victory.
Your odds of a successful escape
are over 99%.
So you're still telling me
to run away, then?!
I don't get it.
Why are you giving me
all these predictions?!
You stupid voice!
Can you tell me? The words I believed
Our changes can be never ending
Always remember the page that's lost its promise
Of our eternal story
Don't let nobody bring you down
Release the break of dawn
If the memory is still beautiful
Left there, through the rain
Even emotions from feeling the way forward
Always keep them in mind
There's no going back
Branded onto the heart
On first impulse
Until it overwhelms
A quiet expression of determination
Is the beginning of the revolution, now
Let's start 3, 2, 1 GO!!
Can you tell me? The words I believed
Our changes can be never ending
Always remember the page that's lost its promise
Of our eternal story
Destiny yet to be fulfilled
And the possibility it presents
We fly together to somewhere that isn't here
Until morning comes
Spread your wings
Until you someday disappear into the sky
I Evolved Into an Evil Dragon
"I Evolved Into an Evil Dragon"!