m 0 0 l 0 102 32 102 b 3 75 3 32 32 0
OSHI NO KO
Both of Ai-san's twins are
currently active in show business.
They've overcome tragedy—
What have you done?!
It was necessary.
For Arima, and for us.
For us?
How? You basically dug up Mom's grave!
You hurt her reputation!
She spent her whole idol career
keeping up that lie,
and you outed her just like that.
How are you okay with this?
I'm not. How would I be?
But remember what you said?
You said you'd help Arima if there was
a way to, even if it brought you pain.
What would Mom think
if she saw this from heaven?
Her own son sold her out.
Knowing Ai, she'd just laugh and go,
"Yikes, the cat's out of the bag."
Ai is dead.
Her secrets ought to be used
to help the living.
Oh...
So that's how you think.
You're not wrong. This gets Senpai out of
that mess and ups our name recognition.
Everybody wins.
But you've changed.
In the past, you always put Ai first
and did everything you could
and more for her.
You cared about Mom more than anyone,
and because of that,
I felt a kind of familial bond with you.
But you don't care about her
anymore, do you?
You're wrong.
Liar.
Liar. Liar.
Liars, liars, and more liars!
Everybody's a damn liar!
I don't consider you family anymore, Aqua.
Goodbye, "Onii-chan."
I thought we were family too, you know.
You run an agency, so make sure
you take advantage of this.
It really is necessary.
Now, even after I'm gone,
you'll be able to get by in this world.
After it became public that
Aqua and Ruby were Ai's children,
one week passed,
and then two...
Diet Member Opens Recruitment for New Female Staff
Hot Rookie Actor Takes On Hollywood
But even as more time passed,
no story about me ever broke.
Aqua Hoshino, Son of Former B-Komachi Idol Ai
It was obvious why.
Aqua had protected me.
Maybe he was trying
to protect B-Komachi as a whole,
or maybe he had some other
motive in mind. I didn't know.
Special
Former B-Komachi Member, Ai Hoshino-san
The Bright and Shadowed Sides of an Idol
Why would a popular idol do this?
The Victim
Ai Hoshino-san
That story was all anyone talked about.
Look at him digging deep into his own mother
Idols are just illusions after all
He deserves praise for coming forward
Ai's a traitor
I'm starting to think I'm their father
All kinds of people jumped in with
their takes, fueling the discourse.
gg outrage farming
Kudos to her for keeping her kids
under wraps while she was alive
Selling out your own mother to put food
on the table? It better taste divine
The idol business is so prehistoric
Love you!
I'll support you forever!
Ultimately, the fact that the twins were
working to honor their mother's legacy
Hope I can help somehow
I'm praying you can smile more in your coming days
Hang in there! I couldn't stop crying
cemented the news as
a heartfelt, tearjerking story.
I'm praying you can smile more
in your coming days
I fell in love all over again
No regrets loving B-Komachi
I'm starting to like Aqua
I can't stop crying
that hoshino hnng
I respect that
A ray of hope in showbiz
My love won't stop
Sibling bonds!!
All my support
We stan a queen
No reason not to stan them
B-Komachi forever
I'll always be cheering for you
I'll keep stanning you!
A beautiful world...
Their resolve made me cry (T_T)
Fan for life!!
It's gonna be hard,
but hang in there!
A ray of hope in showbiz
Supporting you both!
What a beautiful family
Ruby-chan's smile gives me hope
I'll keep stanning you!
Their resolve made me cry (T_T)
Ignore the haters
I wuv Ai, Ruby-chan, and Aqua
No reason not to stan them
lovelovelovelovelovelove
My love won't stop
We got your back
We stan the Hoshino family
As my mother was dying, she said she
thought I might grow up to be an idol too.
My dream is to make her unrealized dream
of performing at the Tokyo Dome come true.
You're Aqua-san, right?
Um, I-I'm cheering for you!
Things may be rough,
but please hang in there!
After capturing the public's fascination,
they both became a hot commodity in TV.
They were squarely on the path
to becoming big-name stars.
And with barter deals and whatnot,
more jobs started trickling down to me.
Now we're all busy every single day.
I read the news story.
Come to think of it, Ai was in the cast
with us when we first met.
Back then, you were a lot more bright
and cheerful than you are now.
You never recovered from it, huh?
I recovered just fine.
You're not fooling anybody.
You're probably a lot more
fragile than you think.
Don't talk like you get it.
I get it, okay?
I get how much it hurts when your
loved ones leave you, if only a little.
My mom's alive, but she stopped caring
about me as my time in showbiz went on.
Not that it even holds a candle
to your situation, of course.
I see.
Why'd you do it?
To bury that story about me?
If so, you gave up too much in the deal.
It totally wasn't worth it.
Or were you after something else?
That's not for you to worry about.
What the hell?
You, Ruby, and MEM can keep
working as B-Komachi like always.
What more do we need?
Right.
All said and done, I am very grateful.
You're a way bigger
pushover than you think,
so you'd better be way more
careful from now.
I know, I know.
But I'm gonna quit being an idol
sometime in the near future.
Why?
It's my way of settling things.
This incident made it crystal clear to me.
I'm fundamentally not idol material,
and I want to act more than anything else.
I'm not saying I'm gonna quit right away,
and I plan to give it my all for
Ruby and MEM until the very end.
So...
If you're gonna make me
your fave, do it now.
When it comes to your star idols,
you should stan while you can.
Wise words.
How dare you show your face to me
after pulling a stunt like that?!
We need to talk.
Excuse me?
Talk?!
You dug up your mother's grave
and pissed on her reputation!
You're a scumbag who'll stoop
to anything to make it big!
Why the hell would
I give you the time of day?!
Because...
I know the name of the guy
who masterminded Ai's death.
You what? Ai's killer?
Who is it? Spit it out!
I can't.
If I tell you, you'll try
to go kill him right now.
Damn right I will!
Do you really wanna let that bastard
go scot-free after all he did?!
Like hell I do.
Killing him would be letting him off easy.
What's your game?
What are you trying to do
by telling me this?
I've been thinking about it
ever since I was a kid.
What's the best way to get revenge
on the man who killed Ai?
How can I make him suffer the most?
I took all my hatred
and put it down in words,
creating a rough draft that was
like a child's temper tantrum—
a completely selfish and reckless plan.
However...
Ever since I learned
how Ai felt about it all,
I've gained all the cards I needed
to build the perfect hand.
This plan could've never come
to pass without a miracle,
but now everything's fallen
into place to make it possible.
So I've got no choice but to run with it.
The curtain's already risen
on the final act.
The moment Ai's story went public,
there was no going back for me.
I want your help.
Help me drive that man into a corner.
Gotanda Studio
GOTANDA
Ai
Hey, Ai Hoshino.
Your kids are living strong.
Pitch
The 15-Year Lie
(Tentative Title)
It might be time to make good
on that promise.
Pitch
The 15-Year Lie
(Tentative Title)
Oh, wow!
He fell asleep?
Get this log off me and take him home.
No way. I wanna watch this some more.
Why?
Because Aqua never takes
to people like this.
Maybe he thinks
you're his dad or something.
Please stop. That cuts deep for
a guy who's still single at thirty.
The Beginning
You wrote this story yourself, right?
The script was a great read
all on its own!
How do you write stuff like this?
Huh?
In the end, it all comes down
to whether it's got real emotion.
For this movie,
that'd be the lead's inferiority complex
and her desire to be beautiful.
You can't half-ass that stuff
in favor of the plot.
You have to film what's real.
That's really the only thing
that matters in filmmaking.
Though of course, it takes technique
to make that more appealing.
Wow.
That's kinda amazing.
You're a real professional.
Duh.
Oh, I know!
My agency's been talking about
filming a B-Komachi documentary.
You should make it, Director!
Huh? Why me?
'Cause I feel like you'd
make a real good one.
You'll do it, right?
Don't be silly. I've got enough
on my plate already.
Oh, come on! Please?
Like I said...
You'll do it, right?
Wrong.
Pretty please?
For the last time, I'm not doing it!
After that,
I filmed the original B-Komachi's
documentary bit by bit.
B-Komachi
We'd finalized the screening schedule.
B-Komachi Moved to Tears As First Tokyo Dome Concert Is Announced
Shooting the Tokyo Dome concert
was all that was left.
But that was when...
B-Komachi's Ai-san Attacked by Fan
Dead
Idol Group B-Komachi's
Ai-san
the murder happened.
Ai was killed,
and everything got scrapped.
I heard that as Ai was dying,
she asked the boy wonder
to apologize to "the director" for her.
I'm the one who should apologize.
I may have been one of the few adults
who could've reached out to help her.
Sheesh. I haven't filmed a documentary
since I was in school.
Listen up.
If I'm doing this, I'm not
making something shoddy.
If you're gonna put up a front
or show a version of you that's
made up of lies like you always do,
I won't hesitate to cancel
filming on the spot.
I guess you did say
you wanted to film what's real.
But are you sure?
If you film me when
I'm not being a total liar,
you probably won't be able
to use any of the footage.
If you're okay with that,
then I won't lie.
Please film the real me.
The 15-Year Lie
Script
A movie based on a real-life incident?
The script's pretty much finished.
An idol shoots to stardom
and is killed by a fan on the day
of her Tokyo Dome concert.
Why did it happen, and what was
going on behind the scenes?
Ai-kun, huh?
Right.
It's a movie based on a true story:
the murder of an idol fourteen years ago.
We'll bring it to life
using today's actors.
Pretty intriguing story you've got here,
but it'll be hard to pull off.
The subject matter is far too delicate,
and too much of it's based on speculation.
Do you have anything to back this up?
If you're not careful, this could get you
sued by a bunch of places.
Pitch
The 15-Year Lie
Script
Taishi Gotanda
Aqua Hoshino
No major film distributors
or investors will take this on.
You won't get the funding required.
I'm sorry to say this project—
We can back it all up.
It's based on an account from Ai herself.
What's more, the script
was written by the director
Script
Taishi Gotanda
Aqua Hoshino
and Ai's actual son, me.
I get it. So that's what you're going for.
While I do get the feeling that you're
taking Gotanda-kun and me for a ride...
Lie
From how you describe it,
this could get interesting.
Very interesting.
Very well. I'll take this movie on.
I'm the only one who could produce it.
Pitch
The 15-Year Lie
Script
Taishi Gotanda
Aqua Hoshino
The cast I have in mind for starters is...
Ruby Hoshino,
MEMcho,
Kana Arima,
Melt Narushima,
Frill Shiranui,
Akane Kurokawa,
Taiki Himekawa,
and Aqua Hoshino.
Let's go with that for now.
Who do we want for Ai, the lead role?
It's gotta be a huge box-office draw.
Well, I do have someone in mind.
Yura Katayose-san.
Would you be willing to let us
book her schedule for next spring?
Well, we have gotten other offers,
but you've always been
good to us, Kaburagi-san.
I guarantee she'll have a leading role.
Very well.
Excited to work with you next spring.
Members Only
Maru-chan Bar
It all just rubs me
the wrong way, I swear!
Get me another Maru-chan special!
Sure.
Man, what would your fans
think if they saw this?
Actor
Yura Katayose
The biggest and hottest
actress right now,
getting wasted like this?
I mean, work just gets me so stressed.
TV Guidance
\hSpecial
Feature
Yura
Katayose
If I don't blow off steam
somewhere, I'll explode!
If you're looking for a home, come to HOMESHOP
Now Taking Tenant Applications
Take today, for example.
My manager brought me this movie role.
But they just booked my schedule.
Everything else is up in the air.
Oh, but isn't that pretty
common with TV series?
Sure, but this is a movie.
Neither my manager nor the producer
are treating me with the care I deserve.
It feels like all they care about
is my brand value and fame.
You know that's not true.
You're pretty, and it's amazing
how much your acting's come along.
Thank you! You really are
the best drinking buddy, Miki-san!
C'mon, drink up!
Wow, damn.
Everything that producer offers me
is an adaptation targeting a younger demo.
I'm twenty-five now. I can't pull off
a school uniform anymore.
They should be giving those parts
to actual high schoolers.
Like, isn't Frill Shiranui
still in high school?
And recently, there's... You know...
Ruby Hoshino!
She's all the rage right now.
Oh, her? I've got my eye on her, too.
Knew it!
She must be getting
a ton of offers right now.
There's always a demand for pretty faces.
I bet the showrunners
would rather use younger actors, too.
They just come to me because nobody
that age is a big enough box-office draw.
But, well, I refuse to just
be their crowd puller.
That's a wonderful mindset.
You see...
I want to become a better actor
and a bigger name,
and free myself from
all these business obligations.
I'll act in great movie after great movie,
and play the lead in a masterpiece that'll
be talked about a century from now!
Do you think I could do it?
Your talent is the real deal.
It has that kind of staying power.
Thanks.
Do you have the day off tomorrow?
Yup.
Every time I finish a big job, I make a
point of taking a month off to unwind.
I'm going mountaineering next week.
I've gotten hooked on it lately.
See? I have an app to keep track
of the mountains I've hiked.
That's lovely. I like the mountains, too.
Be careful, though.
In the mountains,
they might never find you
if something goes wrong.
Be sure to watch your step.
Are you still alive?
I warned you...
to watch your step.
You... murderer...
Her light's gone out.
I've gone and extinguished another one,
Ai!
Episode 32
Plan
Translation
Sriram Gurunathan
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check
Gabriella Alabanza
Translation Check
Michelle Tymon