I couldn't tell him
that I'm his girlfriend.
I need to go home.
I wanted to see Kizuki.
Ouch.
I shouldn't have worn my new shoes.
Whoa!
I rushed out and bought some chocolates.
Acting like a girlfriend
all of a sudden...
I feel so stupid.
I'm going nowhere, all alone...
Found you.
Kizuki!
What are you doing?
Coming out here all on your own?
Oh...
This is the first time I've seen him
make such a scary expression.
What do I do?
I made him upset.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to see you, Kizuki.
I was going to leave
as soon as I gave you this.
Sorry for being such an inconvenience...
Don't do things like this!
I heard from Coach
that a girl came to visit.
I immediately thought it was you,
so I rushed over.
I was so worried you'd get lost.
You wouldn't even answer your phone.
Don't worry me like that!
You're loved by the person you love.
You're in the best possible reality.
I...
If something happened to you, Mizuho...
I don't know what I'd do...
Kizuki.
Hmm?
I want to kiss you.
I understand now.
To be a "girlfriend" is to be
the person most precious to someone.
Kizuki. You smell like the pool.
And that's a huge miracle.
I Fell in Love After School.
Vampire Boys
Dormitory
Haruka
Nishino-senpai.
You look so gloomy today.
You won't be popular looking like that!
Sakura...
Do you need something?
You see—
Nope! Never mind!
I don't want to hear it!
I don't ever want to bring snacks
to Mitsuharu-sensei and apologize!
Aw, come on!
I'm going to a dinner party with people
from my job hunting days tomorrow.
I messed up and failed
to invite enough people.
So please come with me, Nishino-senpai!
I'm not going.
It's not like you're doing
anything besides work!
You also haven't had a boyfriend
for a while, right?
No, I haven't...
See?
I came to see you, Mizuho.
I can make it end.
Huh? Are you angry?
That's enough.
Hurry and finish your work!
What?
But you're the only one
I can count on, Senpai!
I finished ordering the bouquets
for the graduation ceremony.
Thanks!
Congrats on Graduating, Seniors!
From the 1st and 2nd Years of Ao High Swim Club
Don't Forget About Us!
Is this from the seniors' retirement meet?
I'm glad Saito-senpai
came back to the swim club.
But...
Last year, club activities
couldn't resume for a long time.
All the inter-highs were canceled, too...
In that case,
would it really be appropriate
to tell the seniors "Congratulations"?
"Congratulations"...
It doesn't feel quite right.
You were in shock when you found out
the competitions were canceled, too.
But most of the official matches for this
season have been confirmed to continue.
Even though the seniors weren't
able to participate,
I'll be able to.
Just because I'm a year younger...
We will firmly inherit
the traditions, hard work,
Graduation Ceremony
and spirit that our
predecessors have built
and continue to take steps
towards the future.
We sincerely wish all the
graduating seniors the best of luck
as they embark on their journeys.
March 10th, 2021.
Shin Kashiwagi, Student Representative.
The graduating class
will now exit the building.
Please give them a round of applause.
Would it really be appropriate
to tell the seniors "Congratulations"?
Senpai! Please give me your tie!
I'm going to miss you!
Say "cheese."
Cheese!
Good job.
Thanks.
Do your best, even without me.
Please come back to visit anytime.
Saito-senpai!
Kizuki! Everyone!
This is from all of us at the swim club.
Wow! Thanks.
Why do you all look so down?
Starting tomorrow, I won't be
wearing this uniform anymore.
I won't be coming back to Ao High.
Can you believe it?
It's like this ceremony's the day
I disappear from Ao High.
Saito-senpai...
Okay!
Let's head to the pool!
What? But they're doing repair
work starting tomorrow—
I know.
All right, everyone!
We're going to the pool!
Hey! Kizuki's childhood friends!
You're coming, too!
What?
Us, too?
Come on down, guys!
Look at all the messages on the pool!
Ryuta and Shunsuke
Guys That Will Be the Talk of Next Year
So Sad
My HS Days are Over
You're free to write whatever you want!
They'll all be gone after next week's
repairs and new pool coating.
For real, Teach?
Yup! We even have
the principal's approval!
Seniors, feel free to write
your heart out as a memento!
Got it!
What's that, Airu-kun?
"Love"...?
It's a secret!
Koigahama Highlands Forever!!
Hoshikawa
Hey, Mizuho.
Don't go drawing
a weird face on my message.
Koigahama Highlands Forever!!
Hoshikawa
Manga Writer
Debut!!
I drew a caricature of you, Syugo!
Isn't it cute?
The real one is much cuter, obviously.
Take a good look.
What?
Nice!
I'm taking a picture!
Yeah.
What are you doing there, Shin?
You should write
a heartfelt message, too.
C'mon!
I don't really have one...
Let me see the blue marker, Airu.
Here ya go.
What should I write next?
Go Beyond the Average Record!
I'm My Own Rival
I Want to Surpass Saito-senpai's Record by Summer
Why aren't you writing anything?
Holding yourself back? Because
I can't be in any competitions?
Oh...
It's frustrating.
What do they mean
"an unknown infectious disease"?
Why are we the only ones
who have to feel this way?
Give me back my chance at the inter-highs.
Give me back
my final summer of high school.
Senpai...
Well, those heated words would be
what the past me would say.
The one that couldn't compete
in last year's meet.
But I'm different now.
When I look back
at my high school days...
Win First Place!
I thought that I'd remember winning
competitions and setting new personal records.
I Want to Surpass Saito-senpai's Record by Summer
But instead, what I'm remembering is
the time I spent with all of you.
When I was worried
about improving my time
and you guys came to encourage me.
Or when we talked on and on about
the most random things after practice.
Or that time Kizuki joined the team
and almost beat my time
for the freestyle stroke.
You made me anxious.
These memories
just suddenly came back to me.
None of them ever disappeared.
These precious memories
are overflowing within me.
Ao High Swim Club was My Adolescence!
I Have No Regrets!
Ryosuke Saito
I'll continue swimming in college.
I realized how much I love swimming
after having that taken away from me.
And Kizuki.
You better go to
the inter-high championship!
And if you make it to the finals...
I can brag about how we used to
compete in high school.
Then I'd know the hardships from my
final year of high school were worth it.
Of course!
Nishino-san!
Oh? Uh, yes!
The very first page
in my book of adolescence
starts with the day you
scolded me at the bus stop.
So thanks for that.
Way to go, Saito!
Show us what the seniors' got!
You're as fired up as ever, Saito!
Saito-senpai!
I don't really like that!
Please forget about that!
Whoa!
That's cold!
What was that for?
Jeez!
Seniors! Congratulations on graduating!
Cut it out!
Good job!
Stop that!
Congrats!
Hold on!
Congrats, Senpai!
Congrats on graduating!
Hey!
Get him!
No, wait! Stop that!
Were we tested by the heavens?
So cold!
There's more!
Shin!
Hey!
When the scene before us
suddenly disappears...
Is it possible
to stand up again with hope?
Will we realize
what's most important to us?
Hey! Shin!
Would we be able to enjoy the present
that will never come again to the fullest?
Get 'em! Get 'em!
Hey!
That's cold!
I Won't Give Up!
Senpai...
Nishino-senpai!
Come on...
Could you please stop daydreaming
and act like you're having fun?
Are you sulking because one
of the guys is running late?
You ladies must be well
experienced in romance
since you're editors
for shojo manga, am I right?
What?
That's not true!
Take Nishino-senpai here.
She hasn't had a boyfriend in three years!
So this is what she meant by "dinner
with people from my job hunting days."
Oh, but Nishino-senpai is amazing at work!
The stories she's been assigned to
have been debuting one after the other!
She's also been working on hit series
from some authors as well!
Wow! That's so cool!
You don't need to say all of that.
You two are so close!
It's not because of me.
It's because of the authors themselves.
As for me, my boss
keeps nagging at me and—
And just like this, my days pass on by.
The days I shared with Kizuki
will never come back.
Look at this face.
Wow, so cute!
I feel a little tipsy.
I'm going out for some air.
Are you okay, Senpai?
Yup.
This is fine.
Here it is!
Senpai! It's this one!
Sorry for being late!
While I was at it, I brought someone
who was planning to eat all by himself!
Why?
Mizuho?
Why do I have to see Kizuki again?
Cheers!
So you're part of a food manufacturer's overseas
business development
department, Hazawa-san?
Is that why you go abroad
on business trips often?
That's amazing!
I bet your girlfriend has it rough
with you having to go
on so many business trips!
Hey, Sakura!
You don't need to say stuff like that!
Sorry about that, Senpai.
She can't control herself
around handsome guys.
Oh no! He's hot from any angle!
Sakura, go cool your face!
Don't you mean my head?
Let's go there sometime.
Really? Yes, please!
And who is celebrating
their birthday today?
Oh, over there, please!
Huh? Is this?
Nishino-senpai!
It was your birthday the other day, right?
It's late, but let's celebrate!
Happy Belated Birthday!
Happy Birthday!
Okay!
Make a wish and blow
out the candle, Senpai!
My wish right now...
My wish is...
What should I wish for
when I blow out the candles?
Does only the birthday girl
get to make a wish?
Of course.
At the time,
I didn't realize that in 2020...
I wish to become your boyfriend.
Let's go.
What?
Hazawa-senpai? What's with you?!
Wh-What's happening?!
Nishino-san's my type.
She looks like my first love.
Whoa! Senpai are you serious?
So cool!
I'm taking notes!
Everything's okay now.
Kizuki.
I'm right here.
I'll try my best again.
So, watch me.
I'll never regret it.
When I'm an adult, no matter
what the future holds...
I've decided.
I'm going to be your first...
And your last boyfriend.
It hurts.
It hurts, Kizuki.
Let go!
Keep your hands off of her!
Syugo?
Syugo?!
Where were you these past three years?!
Do you know the pain
you put Mizuho through?!
Apologize to her!
Syugo, wait!
That's dangerous!
# 18 I've Liked You This Whole Time