How do you feel about nurse uniforms?
You mean you want to see Lynn in one?
Me?
Huh?
Nice to see ya, kiddo.
I have some great deals
to share with you today, kiddo.
There.
I have all these premium items
at super low prices,
but this offer is today only, kiddo.
You even brought weapons.
They look like antiques, though.
It's a pile of junk.
I can tell you don't have
an eye for quality, kiddo.
Where's Arne, anyway, kiddo? Arne? Arne?
He can't hear you.
Kiddo?
Zwei isn't here right now.
Kiddo!
He said he was going out,
but that was about three days ago.
Right?
Where could Lord Arne have run off to?
PART 11: BIRDS OF A FEATHER FLOCK TOGETHER
All of our recent cases
have something in common.
And that is?
Paintings.
Paintings?
During the Medusa
and leannán sídhe case,
there was one in Medusa's house.
During the invisible man case,
there was one in the family manor.
During the golem case,
the witch's restaurant had one.
We saw some in the cat-sìth
and mermaid cases, too.
In other words, I suspect
that behind the scenes,
all of these cases are connected
by a single painter.
That one's by a talented painter
with a very promising future ahead.
Yet not even the art museum director knew
the painter's whereabouts or identity.
You never fail to impress, Lord Arne!
You went off alone
to solve another mystery!
My respect for you grows and grows!
Let's pay this painter a visit.
Okay!
This must be it.
Lynn Reinweiß. Toss Nachzehrer
over the gate so he can nose around.
Huh?
We can't do that!
She's right. It was an absolute nightmare
washing the filth off from that air duct.
Don't you remember
what Amy always says?
"Giving a real dog a bath
is easier than this."
Would you quit worrying about how I look
and spare a thought for my feelings?!
Listen to me!
LOUIS HARTMANN'S FINAL CASE
Is that Louis?
THE CASEBOOK OF ARNE
Louis?
Who's that?
I'm so glad I got to see you guys again.
Impossible.
Louis Hartmann
unmistakably lost his life.
So why is he here?
What does this mean?
I don't understand it either,
but I woke up and was alive again.
You came back to life?
I didn't know what was going on,
so I went to the police,
but as soon as they saw me,
they started yelling, "Zombie!"
and kicked up a huge fuss.
That's why I left Blumenstadt.
But are you really Louis?
Yeah, I'm Louis Hartmann,
the one and only.
Oh, since I've got you all here, why not
come in and look at my paintings?
I'm a painter now.
I'm kind of new to it, though.
Sure. Let's take a look.
They're in here.
Feel free to look around.
What?
Don't look at them, Lynn Reinweiß.
These paintings are designed to instill
bloodlust and greed within the viewer.
Bloodlust and greed?
Lynn?
Isn't this...
You painted the painting
my father owned?
Sorry, but I don't really keep track
of who gets my paintings.
You're not Louis.
You're not Louis, are you?
Lynn?
The Hartmann Detective Agency
is after that killer!
I'm going to catch him!
I must avenge my father's murder!
Louis wanted to be a detective.
Not a painter, nor anything else.
Is your painting what caused
my father to act the way he did?
I really don't know what you mean.
Your painting...
It made my father...
It made my kind, dear father...
I'll never forgive you for what you did
to my father and my home.
How long are you going
to keep imitating Louis?
Reveal your true identity!
True identity?
Right now!
Shame. I'd hoped to stay
like this a while longer.
I am known as Vlad.
Vlad? Vlad the Third?
Vlad Țepeș?
Vlad the Impaler?
Oh? What a well-informed girl.
You've heard of him, Lynn?
He's one of the nine vampire kings,
also known as Count Dracula.
I haven't been called by that name in ages.
Wait a sec. Dracula? The vampire king?
Yeah, I remember now!
Man, it's been a super long time!
I have no recollection
of you whatsoever.
Yeah. My heart is inside this guy right now.
But it's me. Nachzehrer!
Nachzehrer?
You must remember who I am!
I'm one of the vampire kings, too!
Yes, as you have now realized,
it was all a vampire's fault.
A vampire's fault?
I came here to confront
whoever had caused this mess,
but I never expected
to find a vampire king.
It is indeed a surprise.
I did not realize you were
Neuntöte until just now.
What a coincidence that the individual
who sensed the power in my paintings
and tracked me down was,
in fact, my counterpart.
A vampire's fault?
That's a good girl. See that?
There is a vampire standing
right before your eyes.
A wretched vampire.
You should kill him.
Kill him.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill you, Arne Neuntöte!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
What's with her?
It's the paintings. They're too powerful.
I'll kill you. I'll kill you.
Settle down, Lynn Reinweiß.
What was I just doing?
How annoying.
Do not interrupt, my counterpart.
If I'm your "counterpart,"
why are you trying to make her kill me?
There's no way a young girl
could kill you, is there?
Vampires aren't the ones who get killed.
They do the killing.
Lynn!
Lord Arne!
Now, why would Neuntöte
be protecting a human?
Especially when he's my counterpart?
Who are you calling a "counterpart"?
Your delusions are getting the best of you.
Oh? It seems you still have
enough spirit to malign me.
But that will change very soon.
Lord Arne!
I see. It seems it was true that
his heart was inside Neuntöte.
Lord Arne!
Stop, Lynn.
Please let go of me!
If we try something now, we're done for.
Let's retreat.
Lord Arne!
I fail to see why my counterpart would
risk his body to protect that human.
Lord Arne! I will come back to save you!
Save him, huh?
The trivial ramblings of a human girl.
You shouldn't underestimate
Lynn Reinweiß.
Oh, I can hear you, my young counterpart.
Very impressive.
And yet, by now, you shouldn't
be able to move an inch.
I guess we'll see.
I can see you also hate to lose.
Perhaps I have inherited
Neuntöte's tenacity.
How very interesting.
Young human girl. If you wish
to rescue Neuntöte, come to my castle.
Castle?
I look forward to your visit.
Zisye! Amy! I need your help.
I want to save Lord Arne!
Okay. I'll let Leah know, too.
The werewolf community's in chaos right now,
thanks to Count Dracula's paintings.
Then, please tell Little Red that
Amy and I are heading to the castle.
Castle?
Dracula's castle, of course.
Dracula's castle?
There are two castles
referred to as Dracula's castle.
The first one is Bran Castle,
but Vlad only stayed there for a short time.
So I expect the other castle,
Poenari Castle, is where he is right now.
A floor map of the castle?
You're always so prepared, Lynn.
Dracula's castle is a key part
of vampire history, after all.
Poenari Castle, huh?
Got it. I'll tell Leah.
Please do.
Lynn.
Just between us,
I must be honest and tell you
that I am unfortunately not confident
I will be able to protect you from Vlad.
Why, Amy?
As you can see, I am a delicate
and darling young lady.
When it comes to fighting,
I'm much weaker than Zwei or Little Red.
And Nachzehrer is nothing
but a stuffed animal now.
When I think of the danger
I might be putting you in, I can't...
I can't...
Amy.
I don't think that will be a problem.
Huh?
Because we will be facing off
at Dracula's castle!
I see what you mean.
Can't sleep?
I'm too worried about Lord Arne.
I understand, but you need sleep.
You are still human, Lynn.
All right.
Sweet dreams.
Little Red Phantom Thief
has marvelously arrived.
And my appearance today
is even more marvelous than usual.
It seems Lady Lynn
and the others aren't here yet.
What's wrong, Leah?
I believe I smell blood.
It's coming from the castle.
I suppose I should go investigate
the castle marvelously.
Isn't that...
Leah!
There is nothing marvelous
about a sneak attack.
It appears I will have to show you
what a truly marvelous fight looks like.
Leah!
Oh? They have arrived,
still unaware they'll be killed
the moment we meet.
You will regret making
an enemy of Lynn Reinweiß.
This looks like a good place for it.
Let's get started.
Please.
Looks like your plan is a success.
Vlad the Third is said to have
taken more than 80,000 lives,
and the bodies are all buried here.
This castle is the best.
Heave-ho. Heave-ho.
But why are we making them do this?
Well, why not?
Walking gets tedious sometimes.
If I knew it was going to be this easy,
I would've brought tea and snacks.
Here they come.
Enemies at 12 o'clock.
We must breach their defenses.
Yeah!
Forward.
Heave-ho!
Yes, good. That's the spirit.
There's no reason to fear their weapons.
After all, you're already dead.
It appears the enemies
aren't normal soldiers, either.
What do you mean?
They were probably once humans
whose blood was drained by Vlad.
Lynn.
Zisye?
Leah is in trouble.
I'll show you where she is, so follow me.
Little Red is in trouble?
Go and help her, Lynn.
Let me take care of things here.
Hey, you three.
Huh?
I order you to accompany Lynn.
Listen. You must protect her at all costs.
Understood!
Hurry, Lynn.
All right.
Take me that way, and hurry!
Yeah!
When we get home, you can thank me
by putting on that nurse uniform, okay?
I'll wear anything you want!
Just be careful, okay?!
These zombies are so strong!
We strong!
Turn there.
Here?
Yeah, that's the room.
Okay!
Oh! Little Red!
I was unable to see who attacked her,
so it must have been a vampire.
A really strong one at that.
Vlad.
Yeah, probably. Be careful, Lynn.
Vlad's paintings again.
Try not to look at them.
I'll try, but we need to get out
of this room quickly.
Let's give them everything we've got.
Here we go.
Evilly!
Bloody!
Fantastic!
Neuntöte!
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
TIMING: HENRY LIN
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: ELISABETH CRIST
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS