And there we go!
You're shining extra bright
today, guardian deity!
Are you all right?
You don't need to come
here every day, you know.
By the way, where's Yoki?
You didn't notice when he left earlier?
No, not at all.
He told us he was going to the castle.
The castle?
This is His Majesty Dartz Olta Clariness.
It goes without saying that
I have summoned you here
with regard to what happened
in the village of Dagaz.
I guess all kings in this
world are pompous asses,
whether they're human or demon.
Nah, that was way too stuffy!
Okay if I just talk normally?
It is not, Your Majesty.
Aw, don't be such a stiff, Sylvia!
A king must present himself with dignity.
Wait, does he always act like this?
C'mon, what's the problem?
Oh, sorry about that.
Let's get to the point.
You guys ran off the hero
Miller and a bunch of bandits,
saving the village of Dagaz.
You'll be granted an honorarium
for your meritorious deed.
In other words, you get a reward.
I do not desire anything in return.
I merely did what needed to be done.
I see. Well, that's why
you're Our Lady Cecilia.
Well, then, Yoki, what about you?
My only desire, Your Majesty,
is one that you cannot grant me.
My wish is one that I
must fulfill for myself!
A wish I can't grant?
What is it? Money?!
No.
A harem?
No!
The royal throne?!
None of these things!
What is it, then?! What is it you want?!
It is naught but the love of Cecilia!
The love of Cecilia!
Huh?!
Well, you're right! I definitely
can't give you that!
Did I just say that?!
I'm so sorry!
That was not the place for you
to declare your love for someone!
Have you no common sense at all?!
I'm sorry, seriously!
That one really was all on you.
I'm sorry!
Honestly...
You need to think about what you've done.
Starting today, you are prohibited
from seeing Cecilia for one month.
What?!
That's so cruel...
Um... I think he already feels bad enough.
Is that really necessary?
What's this? Would you miss
him for the whole month?
Well, um... the thing is...
Half a month, then.
Happiness.
Cecilia!
Captain, look.
Huh? Shiek?
I wondered why he wasn't back
yet. So that's where he was.
He's been sad for a long time.
It must be because of Miller.
He really feels bad that he couldn't
protect Teal and the gargoyle.
All done.
My guardian deity!
Now, don't cling so closely.
I'm back, Teal and Gar.
"Gar"?
Yeah, 'cause he's a gargoyle.
We need a name for him, don't we?
Oh, what a lovely name!
But he'll always be the
guardian deity to me.
You're just ignoring the name I gave him?!
You should be going back now.
Teal, come home.
Yes, you're right.
I'll come again, guardian deity.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Well, all of my strength
comes from you, after all!
Man, I blew it.
Has something happened?
I got carried away, and now I'm
banned from seeing Cecilia.
I see.
Then you'll just have to do whatever
you can to make up for it.
You do have plenty of time, after all.
And that's why you came to see me, huh?
I don't have any other choice!
Kramen, you gotta give me
as much work as you can!
I want to become a man worthy of Cecilia!
Okay, okay.
What's wrong with me?
Oh, my.
Who is that other cup for?
I-It's yours, Mother.
Oh?
It's been just about half a month.
Whatever do you mean?
I wonder what Yoki is up to right now.
My husband told me that he seems to
be putting in quite a lot of work.
I see...
I'm back!
What's this, boy? Were you
working all night again?
Well, I get to see Cecilia again soon.
Of course I'm fired up.
I see.
Well, I have something I
need to tell you, as well.
You do?
What the heck are you—
The wound was more serious than I thought.
You're falling apart.
If we don't do something...
I suppose I have but a few days left.
Why didn't you say anything sooner?!
Saying something would not
have made any difference.
But...
So I would like you to take
care of that little girl.
Teal?
She has not fully overcome her illness.
She could still collapse at any time.
But Shiek said her condition was stable...
As one who has been watching her
since she was young, I can tell.
Something has been off recently.
If I fall apart now,
she will be all alone.
Okay. Just leave Teal to me.
Really? Thank you.
Now I can move on with no regrets.
I'm still going to save
you, though! I swear it!
There is no time. You
know it isn't possible.
But this room would feel
so lonely without you.
I need you to stick
around as a work of art.
The gargoyle's body is cracking?
You can fix that by feeding him magicite.
What? It's that simple?
Everyone knows that.
What, seriously? That'll be a cakewalk!
Thanks, Duke!
Uh...
There's more to the explanation, though...
Wait, where can I get magicite, anyway?
Yoki!
Cecilia?
Yoki, there's trouble!
It's Teal!
Shiek, how's she doing?
It's bad.
What?
Her fever won't go down.
Magic can't get rid of the disease itself.
What can we do?
She's been burning through
her strength too quickly.
The medicine we have will
only buy her some time.
Is there anything I can do?
I'm short on herbs. I
need some twilight grass.
Twilight grass?
It's a flowering plant that only
grows in magic-rich places.
It doesn't grow in Minerva.
How can we...
Okay, leave it to me. I'll look for some.
In that case, I'll help you.
Thanks. I'd really appreciate the help.
There's still Gar, too.
Gar?
Has... something happened
to the guardian deity?
Teal!
Don't. You need to stay in bed.
Captain.
I'll keep an eye on Teal.
You can count on me.
Okay.
Where can we buy magicite?
The merchants' guild should
sell valuable materials.
Let's try there, then.
U-Um, this was all my idea!
Mother! Yoki was just...
Don't worry. I know you're
concerned for Teal.
Y-Yes.
Don't you need to hurry? Off you go, now.
Thank you!
You're all out of magicite?!
No twilight grass, either?!
I'm very sorry. Both are in short supply.
You're kidding me...
Hey. Good to go?
Kramen, sir! The quest form is all done.
Oh, Yoki. Perfect timing.
Nope.
I didn't even ask you yet.
You want me to
take a quest, don't you?
I don't have time for that.
You need magicite and
twilight grass, right?
Huh?
This quest is for the removal of a
monster hiding out in a magicite mine.
And that's not all. Magic power
accumulates in that mine,
so twilight grass grows there naturally.
Really?!
You'll help me out, right?
I can't believe it took two
days to get to the mine.
Only two days. You said
you were in a hurry,
so I arranged an express carriage for you.
Thank you for your help as well, Sophia.
When one of our maids is in danger,
the head maid can't very
well stand idly by.
We finally made it.
We shall head for the mine tomorrow,
once all preparations are made.
Tomorrow? We can't just go now?
The monsters are more active at night.
The one we're after will
be even more of a threat.
Is this thing really that nasty?
It's a rock eater that chowed down
on magicite until it mutated.
So not only is it even more savage now,
but it's also highly resistant
to attack magic.
Sorta like Miller's magic sword, I guess.
And the client wants someone
to bring back this jolly little
mutant rock eater's hide unharmed.
So we can't just brute-force it this time.
I have a plan.
Even if attack magic doesn't work,
it's still possible to
restrain it with magic.
Shall we get moving, then?
In your maid uniform?!
Will you be all right in that?
This is proper, order-made battle attire.
Huh...
My husband says he likes the
way I look in a maid uniform.
Is that the rock eater?
Damn, it's eating magicite like
it's just a crunchy snack.
Dear!
On it!
Don't underestimate us!
That didn't do a thing!
Hey, don't damage the hide.
Yeah, I know!
We need to get him to hold still first!
Earth Lock!
I'll help! Saint Chains!
How is it so strong?!
Well, what now, Kramen?
I'll cover Sophia with shikigami
so she can go in through its
mouth and kill it from inside.
Isn't that too dangerous?!
Close-range combat is my specialty.
My woman's the best there is.
Okay, I see! How about this, then?
Well done, Yoki!
All right, that big mouth's open now!
Leave this to me.
Quit flailing!
It split itself up?!
What?!
Kramen!
Just hold out for one more minute, milady!
All right!
Keep still!
Take this!
Damn! Magic doesn't work
on those guys, either?
Well, then...
how about some of this?!
Hey! At least try to protect yourself!
Keeping my shikigami up takes priority!
And go easy on the smitten husband thing!
Not... yet!
Cecilia!
You're not hurt, are you, Sophia?
No. I'm just fine.
They're such lovebirds.
They sure are.
All right, now get off of me.
We still need to find the twilight grass.
Oh, right!
Yoki! This is it!
So this is twilight grass, huh?
We need to hurry back to Minerva.
It's too dangerous to drive at night.
We'll leave in the morning.
Aw, we'll be fine!
Yoki, I understand how you feel,
but please bear with it this time.
Maid uniform...
Quietly...
Cecilia—
Shh.
There's twilight grass in here.
Sophia is sound asleep.
You should be able to fly to Minerva now.
Okay. I'm impressed you knew, though.
I was sure you'd try to go anyway.
Really?
Take care of those two.
I will. Leave it to me.
Well, I'm off.
Hey, wake up, Gar!
It can't be... Was I too late?
Come on, you little-girl-loving statue!
I'm not gonna let you lead that innocent
little girl on and then just die!
What has... happened to Teal?
She's gonna be fine.
Shiek's taking care of her.
I see. That's good.
So you need to hurry up and
eat this magicite, too.
I'm gravely wounded. A
little magicite cannot—
You never know until you try!
Or, what? Do you wanna make poor Teal sad?
She's fighting her illness
because she believes in you!
What's that? A claw?
Teal...
Well, all of my strength
comes from you, after all!
Right... I...
My body burns!
This must be what they call a miracle!
Awesome!
I'm going now!
Whoa, wait, Gar!
Teal!
Guardian... deity?
You're all right.
Damn. And I need to get
back to Cecilia by morning.
I'm so glad, though.
Yes. It's all thanks to you.
Me?
Both last time and now,
you protected me and Teal.
Thank you.
Good job, Shiek.
Guardian deity, your arm!
Worry not. That bad dream is over now.
Okay!
What's up with Yoki?
He seems particularly exhausted.
Yoki did work very hard.
Mrmph... Cecilia...
This is his reward.