There you are.
Wolfwood, thanks for your
help back there.
That's enough already. How many
times are you going to thank me?
Besides...
You mean thanks again
for my help as always.
You're right.
What would I do without you?
How's Emilio?
Still unconscious, but not in any
mortal danger, I'm told.
I see.
The guy tried to kill you,
yet you're relieved to hear he's okay.
I'm glad to see you haven't changed
in the past two and a half years.
I'm also glad to see you.
I'm being sarcastic.
I know.
So, Wolfwood...
What is it?
You were looking for me, right?
Oh, that's right.
Got something to give you.
You dropped this.
You've held on to it
all this time? Thank you.
Enough with the thanks. Listen.
Next time, use that gun
to kill without hesitation.
I mean that monster.
You do realize, don't you?
You caused that disaster
by being too soft.
If Nai is alive, I'll stop him
for sure this time.
But I won't kill anyone.
That's what I mean by "soft."
Someone has to bring the fangs.
Otherwise, someone else pays in tears.
Excuse us!
Pardon the interruption.
Yeah, no. We're in the
middle of something.
Stay out of it, girls.
Oh, don't worry! It's fine.
Don't mind us.
Who are you to— Hey!
Okay, first question.
Ta-da!
F-First?
Tell us exactly what you've been up to
for the past two and a half years.
Hey!
Um...
Okay, another question, then.
Ta-da-da!
What's your favorite food?
Huh?
What kinda question's that?
The first any reporter would ask.
Girls, enough is—
Now give us your reaction
to this dramatic reunion!
Ta-da-da-da!
Well, um, I personally never
doubted for a second that—
Why're you making me talk like that?!
All right! Vash, Undertaker!
Smile for the camera! Say cheese!
Whatever. Do what you want.
Well then, let us return
to the first question.
So far, deviation from the simulations
is within two percent, give or take.
I suppose everything
is coming along great.
To graft Knives with plants
in order to resurrect him...
When everything works out as planned,
he may well kill us all out of rage
for sacrificing plants like this.
If I get to see the world Lord Knives
creates with my own eyes,
I wouldn't ask for anything more.
Doctor, begin.
Okay.
Sorry about this.
Initiating grafting.
I wonder what Lord Knives dreams of.
Who knows?
He's a being from a higher
dimension, right?
There's no way we could understand.
Today is the twins' first birthday!
Today is Tesla's first birthday!
It's already been a year, huh?
It really went by in a flash.
Are you watching that again?
That makes you a "doting parent," right?
Indeed. Didn't you know?
I love you, the cutest in the universe,
which makes me the most
doting parent in the universe!
Should we have another
birthday party next year, too?
Of course! We will for sure.
Help me!
The seventh grafting was a success.
What are you waiting for?
To bring Lord Knives back,
we need lots more plants!
You don't have to remind me.
Let's go, Midvalley.
Can I take a guess about what's
going through your mind right now?
Give it a shot.
"Perhaps I should kill him now,
while I have the opportunity."
Well? How'd I do?
You must have felt it yourself
after Lost JuLai.
His powers are much
too strong, far too great.
Yup, yup!
Perhaps next time,
the catastrophe will be even greater.
In other words, you oppose Lord Knives
creating a world for his brethren?
I don't know.
In that case, why don't you give it a try?
Right now, Lord Knives is powerless.
This could be your last chance.
You can't resist Lord Knives,
even when he's in this state!
Midvalley.
Hurry up.
P-Please! Let us go!
Kids! I'm having kids soon!
Don't worry. I'll make sure you
see your children in the afterlife.
Please! I've worked so hard! Come on!
We weren't going to put our lives
on the line to protect the plants anyway!
I mean, help is on the way, right?
That colony fleet?
So please—
Humans are incredible, don't you think?
When they put all their muscles to use,
even ones they don't usually,
anything is possible!
Naturally, they still have
the ability to feel pain.
Even as your hands
are crushed out of shape,
you can't stop yourself!
Murder maniac.
Of course, the hell I want you
to experience is even more exquisite.
Isn't that exciting, Vash the Stampede?
Now, come. Let us retrieve the plant.
We're all birds of a feather, after all.
Yet another plant theft
has taken place.
Over forty people are confirmed dead
or missing. It is an utter disaster.
Vash the Stampede, considered
the prime person of interest,
has not yet been located.
Authorities are on high alert.
I repeat:
Another plant theft has taken place.
Over forty people are confirmed dead
or missing. It is an utter disaster.
Vash the Stampede, considered
the prime person of interest,
What's this "person of interest" nonsense?
has not yet been located.
Vash is right here.
He can't be the one who did it!
Authorities are on high alert.
Brad, please bring me the plates.
Got it.
All done!
Wait! Let me do it!
They're growing steadily, for now.
Flora, huh? Mm, that's kind of soothing!
I can't say I like the smell.
It's like... gooey or raw or something.
Isn't that what's nice about it?
Really?
Oh, look! There's water
coming out of the tip!
Flora can store up water inside.
And that's not all. Some are even edible.
Wow, that's impressive!
I only just learned myself, honestly.
Vash! Sorry to keep you waiting!
No way! Is that omelet rice?
It looks delicious!
This one's special! Here, Vash—
Thanks for the grub, little lady.
Wait, that's—
Mm, pretty good.
Jessica?
It's nothing.
Let's eat!
Let's eat.
Delicious!
I haven't had omelet rice in years.
Look at all this egg! How extravagant.
Thank you so much, Brad!
Jessica's the one who made it.
Thank you, Jessica!
You're welcome!
This really is tasty, Jessica.
Bet you had no idea, huh?
Yeah, you've really grown up.
There's lots more you don't know, too!
Yeah, there's so much I don't know.
Talk about obvious.
The world is full of shit you don't know.
Trying to learn it all is impossible.
True.
The Undertaker is right.
But the desire to learn
is what's important.
Yeah.
Appreciate it.
You're welcome.
I'll teach you even more about me!
Sure, in time.
So, I guess having lots of plants
means you get
to eat nice food like
omelet rice all the time.
Hardly.
This was special, just to welcome you.
That right? Sorry, that was rude of me.
Please.
I haven't apologized to you yet.
We knew Vash was alive after Lost JuLai.
But when you asked me,
I lied and said I didn't.
I'm sorry.
Luida, it's all right. You just—
You wanted to leave Vash in peace.
In a parental kind of way, right?
I completely understand.
You got nothing to worry about.
After that delicious omelet rice,
we're totally square.
But man, that omelet rice...
I'd love for them to try it someday.
"Them"?
You mean the kids at the orphanage
where you said you used to live?
When help arrives with the colony fleet,
I wonder if they'll get a chance.
About that, Vash...
Are you sure Emilio was
being manipulated by Knives?
I think so.
Assuming the colony fleet
arrives in six months,
I doubt Knives will just sit by and watch.
Agreed.
There must be plants
aboard the colony fleet as well.
It only makes sense he'd
try to take advantage of that.
What a predicament.
Thank you for the food!
Yes, thank you.
Thanks, Jessica.
Sure!
Oh, I know! We'll clean up.
Won't we, Undertaker?
Huh?
Well, I guess I owe 'em for a nice meal.
I'm a great dishwasher, you know.
That was delicious!
Glad you liked it!
Do you use a secret ingredient?
One thing is for certain.
We must stop Knives, no matter what.
Yeah...
You're right.
Like you said, even if it's difficult,
we have to strive to walk the right path.
Yes.
In other words, we should work
on what we can do right now.
So come with me, Vash.
I'll do what I can for you.
How many more do we need
to get Lord Knives back completely?
Well, according to my calculations,
for a full recovery, we'd...
Hey.
There are lots of plants on Ship 3, right?
Yes.
Then why don't we take all of them?
It'll save us a lot of time.
Hm, interesting.
Wait, wait!
Home... Ship 3 has defenses.
There's a chance they'd defeat us instead!
It is what it is.
But... No, I can't support
going after Home.
Midvalley.
Vash the Stampede is on Ship 3 right now.
A tip from the self-centered puppeteer.
Before we launch our attack,
you go in and capture him.
Capture? Not kill?
The rules of the game have changed.
In order to awaken Knives, we need Vash.
Ah.
Besides, just killing him
wouldn't be any fun.
I want to make sure
Vash the Stampede is dealt
the ultimate suffering by human hands.
He will learn the true nature of humans,
despite desperately trying to save them!
You must bring Vash the Stampede
to Lord Knives.
We will be taking
all the plants on Ship 3.
Understood?
You can run if you want.
Run?
Where in this world is there to run?
Sorry to cause you so much trouble, Brad.
How many times are you going
to break my masterpiece?
Spare parts on this ship are limited.
There's no telling how
many more times I can do this.
I-I'll be gentler with it from now on!
I sure hope so.
I already fixed up your gun.
Also, I got you a new coat
and a pair of sunglasses.
Brad!
We can't have you wearing
those rags anymore.
I helped sew up the coat, too!
Thank you, Jessica.
I'll be careful with it.
I sure hope so!
Now all that's left is to stitch this on!
Huh? H-Hey, wait...
Where should it go?
It's gotta be smack on the front, right?
J-J-Jessica!
Don't move.
S-Sorry!
Oh, I know, Jessica! Before that,
I need your help with something!
Huh?
You really want it cut?
Yup, real short.
You look cool with long hair, though.
How about a mohawk for a change of pace?
Yeah, I don't need that much of a change.
Wouldn't it be funny to get a ducktail?
Funny?!
Don't move.
S-Sorry.
Why not just shave it all off?
That sounds good!
It does?!
Well, maybe not shaved, but...
You just want it like it was before?
Nah. I've already decided what
kind of style to go for.
Done!
Well? What do you think?
It's great, Jessica.
It looks great on you.
Awesome!
Shaved would've been better.
But why this hairstyle?
Well, it's...
to show my determination, I guess.
All right, time to finish up the coat!
Are you really going to put that on?
Of course!
My head!
That's... Hornfreak!
Hornfreak?
Midvalley the Hornfreak.
One of Knives's goons.
Wait! Not yet!
But, Brad—
Are you going to fight with just one arm?
I'm telling you to stay put!
But...
I'm almost done!
Undertaker?
Wolfwood!
I'll go.
You owe me one, Needle-noggin.
The time to awaken is nigh.