Hurry! Hurry!
Sir!
Hurry, before someone beats us to it!
Right!
There's a big payment promised
for this one! Get ready to—
There they are!
Kill them!
I'm seeing a lot of potential chaos here.
This is hard to believe.
I never thought they'd be so aggressive.
Brother.
It might be best to retreat
through the underground passage.
No, it would be faster to slip out
through the city in the chaos.
You've mustered all the forces
we have, right?
I've put out the call.
Shiji Bau says she hired the Iron Whale.
The Iron Whale?
They may not make it in time, though.
Throw all currently available
adventurers at the aggressors.
Xylo Forbartz.
As it is, we have no choice but to kill
the one pacted to the goddess.
Iri. Stay close to me.
I will, Brother. I'll give my life
to protect you if I must.
Good.
Family willing to die for family.
That's how the world should be.
Sentenced to Be a Hero
That bastard, Xylo. He planned
for it to go this far, didn't he?
We can only hope so.
If he did, he's more reckless
than I ever imagined.
It's time! Kill them all!
Pathetic.
Well? Who's next?
An adequate performance.
Aw, come on. I can't do business
like this. Gimme a break.
There we are.
Take that!
My shop.
Hey! Show a little restraint!
I'm sealing off paths for reinforcements!
A child?
What do I do?
How many are there? Damnation.
They're nothing to fear. Just watch out
for their lower angles of attack.
I know that. But...
Too slow.
The seal of violet lightning, Gwemel, huh?
See how to fight them now, Holy Knight?
Xylo, what is the plan moving forward?
I hope you have something better than fruit
packed into that skull of yours.
We make the commotion bigger.
Lideo Sodrick won't be
able to ignore that.
Your skull's contents
are worse than fruit, I see.
I've never heard such a sloppy plan—
That's enough!
Would you be the ones
raising havoc in our city?
Time to get what's coming to you.
What a joke. They're letting ruffians
handle security around here?
Looks like it.
It seems you haven't had the pleasure.
We're the top party at the
Ioff City Adventurers Guild.
Arriving in a shower of blood,
it's the Giant-Hunter Brigade!
Never heard of you.
All right, men! Show no mercy!
Lightning staves?
Fire!
You idiots! Watch where you're aiming!
What are these things?
What an absolute farce.
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Anyone who hits them gets a big reward!
Given the lack of firepower and accuracy,
it seems they've brought
festival fireworks.
You handle them!
Wait! Don't leave me with these fools!
Take this!
Threaten Xylo or me and
you declare war on the Mastibolt family.
You will regret these acts.
If you care about the city, call off
this nonsense and do your jobs right.
Hey, they make a good pair after all.
A troll?
Sodrick was keeping a faerie, too?
It is certainly worse than an unruly pet.
How the tables have turned.
Now, let's finish the job.
Yeah!
Let's go!
If that's how you want it...
Aw, crap.
Ahem.
It appears you require
my blessing after all.
My knight, you are getting
your just deserts for leaving me behind.
However!
In my beneficence, I shall now save you.
Now, all of you, let us begin.
Come now. Come now.
I'll have to apologize
to Siena and Zofflec later.
Who are those people?
Let me give you a word of advice.
Every single one of you had better run
or surrender this instant.
If you don't, you're dead meat.
Brother, this way.
I won't rise to their provocation.
We need to keep
our heads down and get out.
I am Norgalle Senridge the First, king of
the United Kingdom of Zef-Zeyal Meht Kioh.
My loyal subj—
Shut up!
Who the hell are you?
Die!
Get down from there!
Drop dead!
I regret having to resort
to vigilante justice.
But for the crime of high treason,
I sentence you to death by explosion.
Shit! Get him!
Charge!
Cavalry now?
What a damn pain in the ass.
Here ya go.
What the...
Damn it.
Let's turn around!
Here it comes.
I can't believe they dragged
you poor horses into this.
Go on. Get going.
Are you kidding?
Xylo, go! We'll distract it!
Teoritta!
My knight!
Help me out!
We're taking them down!
Have you realized the importance
of having a goddess at your side?
Sure. Never been more aware!
Captain! This way!
Rajit!
Can you do it, Xylo Forbartz?
Let's go.
Right.
My knight,
let us end this at once.
Thanks.
You saved us.
Is that the best you can do?
Have you forgotten
the necessity of words of praise?
I seek them from no one else.
Only my knight.
Xylo, I wish to hear you tell me
how impressive you think I am.
You really are one hell of a goddess.
What the hell is going on here?
Do you see now?
Repent for your crimes now,
and I shall grant you all forgiveness.
Who are these guys?
Run!
Don't push!
I can't get through!
What's going on?
How could this happen?
The city my predecessor left to me.
Brother! Don't get separated!
Brother!
Iri!
Hey, sorry.
I really didn't wanna do this.
This real nasty guy
threatened me into it.
I was against it.
Li—
I feel bad about doing this to you,
but I hope you'll just
come along quietly.
I promise not to hurt you.
Quite a commotion over there.
Things have quickly
spiraled out of control.
Lideo Sodrick may already be dead.
What a mess.
I come all the way out here,
and now my employer is dead?
I don't work without pay.
I'm out.
I'll get my money from the
Adventurers Guild and leave town.
Boojum, what about you?
I'm going to go save Lideo Sodrick.
It feels only polite.
Are you serious?
I do owe him, after all.
I won't ask you to help—
No, wait a minute.
Oh, I see. That's the end of that, then.
What a shame.
What is it?
I got new orders.
We're abandoning Lideo Sodrick.
You're here to earn money,
as I understand it.
Would you like to take on a new job?
What?
Who's hiring?
We are.
These things...
Stop that.
It's rude.
Boojum. Are you...
I'll pay.
That's motivation enough for humans
to work for us, isn't it?
I'm fine with it.
As long as I get paid, I'll work for
adventurers, the Demon Blight...
You name it.
So what do you need, boss?
I'm not your employer.
But our orders are to sever connections
between us and Lideo Sodrick.
Literally without a trace.
Okay, sure. That's one of my specialties.
I appreciate your cooperation.
Shiji Bau. What will you do?
I owe you a debt
for all you've taught me.
I'd rather not kill you.
Are you telling me
to turn against humanity?
Is that a problem for you?
Lideo Sodrick taught me
something important.
There's nothing more important to humans
than protecting themselves
and their families,
or securing proportionate
benefits for themselves.
To value other things more than
protecting their race as a whole...
That's human nature. Am I wrong?
No. You're right.
Keep watch in all directions.
To atone, you must serve me
and work for the sake of our people!
Y-Yes, sir! Let's go, you guys.
Xylo.
We'll check the second floor.
It's possible that physical
evidence may remain.
Now, reflect on your wrongdoing!
Repent for all of the
terrible things you've done.
Behold. He is in awe
of my divine glory.
Not sure I'm seeing  it.
Well, it is true!
Now, tell us all you know.
It's true that as leader of the
Adventurers Guild, I tried to kill you all.
But I know nothing about my employer.
Well, that is a problem.
Don't take him at his word.
Listen. You're on a
knife's edge right now.
Under most circumstances,
I'd hand you over to the Holy Knights.
But I'm willing to make sure
that doesn't happen.
Hey, you're not authorized to negotiate!
You want me to use
more base threats instead?
I think he's pretty used
to violence, though.
If you want to negotiate,
will you agree to my terms?
I'll hear them out, at least.
My little brothers and sisters.
Ensure my family's safety.
Oh, those creepy little kids?
If you promise not to harm them,
I'll consider a trade.
Fine.
Xylo! You don't have that authority!
You want to hunt 'em down
and kill 'em instead?
We could do it in front of him,
one at a time. Might make for good torture.
That's not what I meant.
Stay out of it, then.
Lideo Sodrick.
Tell us what you're able to.
Simple enough trade, right?
Our goal was to kill the goddess.
Our employer called
himself a "coexister."
There's that word again.
It started ten days ago.
My first meeting was
with a man in a black mask.
He said he was making me an offer,
but I really didn't have much of a choice.
"Obey, coexist, or die."
I met with intermediaries
just three times after that,
but they have people everywhere.
If you don't want to die,
you have to prove yourself useful to them.
Stabbing humanity in the back
to save your own skin?
A man of your stature
could've put up a fight.
The coexisters plan to yield full
authority to the Demon Lords,
and act as overseers
of the humans below them.
A hierarchy of slaves,
slavemasters, and lords.
They've already spread so much corruption,
and taken so many lives and lands.
Humanity's on the verge
of losing the fight.
It's crucial that I secure
an overseer role.
I had to do it for my family.
I don't want to hear your damn excuses.
I want more useful info.
Otherwise, the deal's off.
The man in the black mask.
He did give me his name.
I'm sure it's an alias,
but spill it anyway.
Mahaeyzel Zelkoff.
Don't be ridiculous.
Mahaeyzel is the name of a saint.
He was a leader of the Temple
during the First War of Subjugation.
And Zelkoff...
"Zelkoff" is...
Wait. Say that—
Majesty! Majesty!
What's going on?
An attack?
This is a way to get paid.
Don't put up a fight
and go down already.
Th-The building.
Run! Get outside!
What, what, what was that?
They've got artillery now?
Xylo! Hurry!
Kivia! You need to—
Wait! He's still in there!
Wait!
Damn.
Run! You want to get killed?
Another incoming! Get down!
What in the world?
Who does this inside a city?
They must be crazy!
Damn. If only we had Neely...
Hey, don't blame this on Neely.
I'll murder you.
I wasn't.
If the enemy has artillery,
we require the aid of Rhyno.
We must break him out of
the cell that's holding him.
Really? I never know how
to deal with Rhyno.
Kivia. We're going after Lideo Sodrick.
Y-Yes. Of course.
I have to find out
if he was telling the truth.
Brother?
Iri? Is that you?
Brother!
Iri!
You're safe!
Yes. Somehow, I am.
We lost the Guild,
but at least we're alive.
Where are the other children?
Those who weren't captured
by the Holy Knights are nearby.
I'm glad.
I did have to give them a few things,
but at least you're all safe now.
A few things?
Brother, did you tell them something?
No, nothing particularly important.
I see.
Iri—
Sorry, Brother. It's out of
an abundance of caution.
Y-You...
Where's Iri?
She's dead.
I'm using her body and brain.
The other children are over there.
I-It can't be...
My... My precious family...
Farewell, my former brother.
It seems we'll need to speed up the plan.
Let's prepare to destroy the city.
We'll kill all the humans
and reduce their structures to ash.
Above all else, we must do
whatever it takes to kill Goddess Teoritta.
Could you give me a bit of time?
I'd like to bury Lideo Sodrick.
There's no need for that.
You have been ordered
to obey my commands.
Forgive me, Lideo Sodrick.
Thank you for buying me books.
I'll need help from all of you,
not just Boojum.
You'll be paid as promised, of course.
Right.
But can I ask you a question?
What should we call you?
Spriggan.
By all means...
Call me Spriggan.