Step right up and have a look...
It's time for Yamishibai.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
Musubime-sama
This is the story of a young man and
woman who recently started dating...
I appreciate you always giving me a lift.
When are you going to
get your license, Toma?
It's on the agenda.
Oh, I heard something from
my senpai at work today.
You ever hear of Musubime-sama,
the Sewn Eye Woman?
Sure have. Yukari said
she tried it before.
Seriously?
If I remember right...
you're supposed to go to a big
shrine in the mountains alone
on the night of a new moon.
As the time passes, eventually...
Musubime-sama will appear.
The ritual with her needs to be
carried out with utmost respect.
You give her a polite introduction,
and then the process begins
with a specific order.
Musubime-sama's hair is really kinked
and tends to get caught on her comb.
If you're not careful about how hard you
go, you can end up pulling her hair out.
If that happens, you need
to beg for forgiveness.
You cannot upset Musubime-sama,
no matter what.
If you do, your wish won't come true.
And after she forgives you,
you resume the ritual.
Once the combing is done,
you put her hair up.
After that, you give your
regards one more time,
and then, for the first time,
you look at her face.
You cannot recoil at the
sight of how horrible it is.
Because the ritual still isn't over.
Last comes the eye-opening.
You have to be careful not
to harm Musubime-sama.
Do that, and you won't leave alive.
Then, once her eyes are open,
you give your final regards.
Then, once Musubime-sama's eyes are open,
you're supposed to end up with
the object of your affections.
You really know your stuff.
N-No, Yukari just likes to talk.
From what I heard,
there's a continuation, though.
There is? I-I don't know about that.
Apparently, Musubime-sama
needs to have eyes.
Eyes?
Like, eyeballs.
Apparently, once her eyes are open,
if the sockets are empty,
you'll never end up with anyone.
No way!
I'm not lying. It's just what I heard.
But that's... Then what I saw...
It didn't mean I'd end up with you?
What are you muttering about?
I can't see! I can't see!
What's wrong?!
I can't see! Why?! I can't see!
I can't see! I can't see!
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
The end.