Mean? Selfish? Or just different?
There are children who are
seen that way by others.
But what if that child could
see something you couldn't?
This is the story of Kaya-chan,
a girl who could see ghosts.
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 6: Shopping Malls Aren't Scary
Let's all draw what we remember most
from the field trip.
Okay!
What's that, Kaya-chan?
A lot happened on the field trip,
but I'm glad we made it back safe.
But I have a lot of questions, too.
If you're going to kill anyone, kill me!
Hey now, Kaya-chan.
Tis foest
This forest
filled with
Don't draw made-up things.
See? What did I tell you?
It's not made-up.
Oh, that! There was a tree
that looked like a ghost.
There was?
Yuh-huh. Wasn't there, Kaya-chan?
Yeah.
Oh, uh, I see.
Sorry about that, Kaya-chan.
But boy, I didn't know
there were ghosts everywhere.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Today's Kaya-sama.
Mommy, what's that man doing?
Shh, don't look at him. Come on.
People like that are dangerous,
so don't go near them.
I got it.
Wow, good job.
Kaya-sama, I'm glad you're doing well.
Mob Osamu.
Occupation: writer and psychic.
His daily routine: stalking a young girl.
I'm looking out for Kaya-sama!
Malls get crowded in the evening,
so keeping an eye on her isn't easy.
I-I lost her!
Where'd she go?!
Despite being the strongest psychic,
Kaya-sama is still only five years old.
Unworthy as I am, I, Mobuo, shall
protect your peace from the shadows...
Kaya-sama!
There you are.
Oh, Mobuo.
Sh-She noticed me.
My daddy's disappeared.
And she's lost.
An unexpected crisis.
This is a problem.
Stare.
While I'd love to assist you,
f-forming a two-person party with me
could be, uh, problematic.
Huh?
The mall was crowded
just a minute ago.
Oh, Daddy.
Oh, uh, w-wait.
Kaya-sama, please wait!
Kaya-sama!
There's no one here, either.
It's disturbingly quiet.
Kaya-sama, where's your father?
Found him.
Over there.
Huh?
K-Kaya-sama!
K-Kaya-sama! Don't open
that curtain so carelessly!
A-A mannequin arm?
That makes no sense.
Whoever beckoned us
was clearly a living...
Wh-Who's there?
L-Let's get out of here, Kaya-sama!
Something's going on here.
A hallucination? The underworld?
I can't tell, but...
E-Either way, I need to
get Kaya-sama to safety!
A-Are you okay, Kaya-sama?
L-Let's get down to the first floor.
We need to get out of the mall.
H-Huh?
Why isn't it working?
I-It's not responding.
We can't leave.
You mustn't give in to fear, Kaya-sama.
I, Mobuo, will make sure you get back
to your father safe and sound.
You can't.
Uh, Kaya-sama?
Once you set foot in here...
you can never leave.
You can't leave.
Kaya-sama? How?
Where'd she go?
Kaya-sama!
Doors opening.
K-Kaya-sama?
There's the missing one.
Don't bully Mobuo!
Kaya-sama!
Let's go back, Mobuo.
Child Assistance Desk
Kaya-sama, you're such a lifesaver!
That was a painful reminder
of how green I am!
Such overwhelming power in that
small body is nothing short of divine!
You're truly miraculous!
I humbly ask that you continue to guide
this unworthy Mobuo with your strength!
Uh, sir?
Mobuo, don't cry.
Child Assistance Desk
Information
Please enjoy your visit.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Is Sato Kaya here?
Yes, she's been waiting for you.
Kaya-chan, you can go now.
Your mommy's here for you.
I'm sorry about that.
Thank you for your help.
They look just like each other.
Stop, Kaya.
I can hear her voice.
Mommy!
I'm very sorry.
But I'm not your mommy.
I'm your aunt, Nana.
Auntie Nana?
Kaya!
Daddy.
Come here, Kaya.
Who are you?
And why did you take my child?
She's Auntie Nana.
Huh? Auntie Nana?
Wait, are you Mirai's...
older sister?
Has my sister said anything
about our home life?
No, not really.
Mirai—um, my wife doesn't
like talking about her family.
I see.
Our family is a little complicated.
I'm sorry for scaring you like that.
Once I found out I had a niece,
I wanted to meet her.
Please don't tell my sister about this.
Yes, of course.
But I have a favor to ask.
I'm sorry for not properly
introducing myself.
I'm Mirai's husband, Sato Shizuo.
Please tell her parents their daughter
is well, and give them my regards.
Thank you. That'll put my mother at ease.
That is...
if she's genuinely okay
and nothing's wrong with her.
It didn't turn out to be the worst-case
scenario, so I guess it's fine.
I need to check out that house.
So it won't be too late
to finish her off after that.
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
The Punishment Room Isn't Scary?
Sensei!
Ken-ken broke the vase!
Hey!
What are you doing, Ken-ken?!
That's the third thing you've broken
by throwing your shoes around.
That's it. I've had enough. Come with me.
No!
Too bad, so sad. He's going
to the punishment room.
The punishment room?
You don't know what it is?
When the teachers get really angry,
they take you to the punishment room.
There's a freaky ghost in there,
and it forces you to be good!
That's what Chihiro-sensei told me.
So you're in big trouble
if you do something bad.
A ghost in the punishment room?
Teehee. I'm counting on you.
Roger that.
Huh? Kaya-chan, where are you going?
I'm gonna beat up the ghost.
Sweet. I'm coming with!
Whaddup, Kaya-chan?
Where is it?
Huh?
Where's the room with the ghost?
Follow me.
Okay. It's this way.
Oh, yeah. Why aren't you scared
of ghosts, Kaya-chan?
Because I can beat them up?
Seriously? That's so cool!
I-Is it?
Even if we run into a ghost,
I'll protect you, Saku-chan.
So don't worry.
'Kay!
Here we are!
Materials Prep Room
This is the room?
I think so.
What's wrong?
It won't open.
Is it locked?
Open, uh, sesame?
Fun Origami
So much stuff.
Saku-chan, what's wrong?
This room kind of scares me.
It's fine.
W-Wait...
Because I'll beat up the ghost.
Uh, no...
That's not what I mean.
It's so dark.
Saku-chan?
No...
No, no... I'm scared of the dark!
I found the light switch.
Do you see me?
Y-You scared me.
Wh-What are you doing?
Stop it, Kaya-chan!
I don't like it when it's all dark!
Do you see me?
Weird.
I can only see you when it's dark.
She sees me?
She sees me. She sees me. She sees m—
You see me.
See? I told you.
Everything will be fine
because I'll protect you, Saku-chan.
Saku-chan?
What's the matter? The ghost is gone.
The door's unlocked?
Is someone in there?
Kaya-chan? Saku-chan?
Chie-sensei.
What's going on?
What happened?
Kaya-chan and Saku-chan are...
Are they fighting?
They're getting a scolding!
Both of you, come with me.
Come on. This way.
Uh-oh. Are they going to...
Conference Room
the punishment room?
Kaya-chan. Saku-chan.
We can't talk if you're crying.
Have a candy and calm down.
Can you go first, Kaya-chan?
Why did you go into that room?
There was a ghost in there,
so I beat it up.
I protected Saku-chan.
We're not hurt at all.
Are you sure?
So why is she crying?
Why?
Uh, because she's scared of the dark.
But I'm not, so I didn't know.
I didn't mean to hurt her.
I know.
I know you have a kind heart, Kaya-chan.
You just wanted to protect
Saku-chan, didn't you?
But if you think about how
the other person feels...
They're scary! The swings are scary!
And so are you, Kaya-chan!
I'm not scary.
...you'll become an even stronger
and kinder person, Kaya-chan.
Saku-chan.
I'm sorry.
Conference Room
It's okay.
Nana, Mirai is dead.
After giving birth to it.
Run for your life. Understand?
Mother. Mirai isn't dead.
I met her child, but nothing's happened.
It must have been your imagination—
Nana.
Mirai is dead.
After giving birth to it.
Run for your life.
Understand?
Nana. Mirai is dead.
My mother is beyond saving.
But that's exactly what's bothering me.
If that girl caused her to take
a sudden turn, that means...
Chie-sensei, I love you.
I love you, too, Kaya-chan.
There's a chance something's
happening around Kaya right now.
Master. To what do I owe the pleasure?
Are you okay, Osamu-kun?
Wait, why would you ask me that?
You're not involved in
anything dangerous, are you?
Eek!
T-True, a lot of things did happen,
but I'm fine thanks to Kaya-sama's—
Kaya? You're still looking
into that home?
Oh! But nothing like what
you're worried about has happened.
Not yet.
You're weak, so you should be more careful
when I'm not around, Osamu-kun.
Don't worry. Trust your student.
Listen. Don't get involved
with that home.
S-Sure thing.
You've been warned.
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Materials Prep Room
In this episode, the specter
in the materials prep room
disappeared when the lights were on,
but showed up when they were off.
It appears this specter only attacked
those who could see it.
Kaya-chan was fine because she can
deal with them, but most of us can't.
If this specter appeared in front of you
when you turned off the light,
would you be able to keep it together?