So, like I was saying.
She will be joining our class,
starting today.
ANNA AKECHI
I'm Anna Akechi. Nice to meet you!
-Nice to meet you!
If you have any questions, just ask!
Ask me, as long as
it's not about studying!
ANNA AKECHI
Okay, that's it for introductions.
Miss Akechi, you can sit
next to Miss Kobayashi.
Okay!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
rinto hirameku
A brilliant inspiration
kitto mitsukeru
datte Precure
I'm sure we'll find it
We're Precure, after all
watashitachi wo yondeiru
It's calling to us
shinjitsu wa doko?
hakken wa nani?
Where's the truth?
What will we discover?
nazo ga nazo wo yondeiru
One mystery after another
Puzzle wo atsume
genzai kara kako, mirai e
Gather the pieces
From now to the past and future
shouko mitai ni
toki wo koe kagayaku mono
Like evidence
Something shining across time
nande? nande? Trick kana?
How? How? Is it a trick?
naze? naze? tachimukau
Why? Why? We'll face it
mitsumete kanjite
himitsu wo tokiakasu no
Look and feel
Figure out the secret
yuuki no ippo ga kiseki made michibiku
One brave step will lead to a miracle
kotae!?
Kizuitenai mono ni kizuita toki
The answer?!
Found when you notice the unnoticed
unmei ne tte daisuki yo tte
chicchana koe
It's destiny, it's love
Whispered in a tiny voice
issho ni aruite ikou!
Let's walk that road together!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
rinto hirameku
A brilliant inspiration
Jewel no kagi ga tsunagaru
tsugi e no kizuna hiraku yo
The jewel key connects us
Opening the link moving forward
nee umareta koto
meguri aeta koto no shinpi
Hey, us being born and having met
Is a wonderful mystery
susume! Meitantei Precure!
Go on! Star Detective Precure!
Yikes! The School is a Maze?
Hey, hey!
Miss Akechi, where are you from?
Uh, the Chairwoman enrolled me.
Were you in a club?
Do you have a phone?
Let's be text buddies.
Text buddies?
Me too!
Whoa! Um, um!
Anna!
Take your time answering!
Sorry, it's just rare to have
a transfer student at this time of year.
Can I call you Anna?
Yeah! Of course!
Do you believe in the occult?
The July predictions?
July?
It's a big story these days!
In the year 1999, the seventh month.
The King of Terror
will descend from the sky.
That story.
Well, it's just a rumor anyway.
Wow.
Oh yeah, I heard you two
live in the same house?
What's the connection?
-Truth be told...
-We are actually...
Detectives!
Here, take one.
ANNA AKECHI
Huh?
Fwip, fwip, fwip!
Detectives?
Wow, Mikuru! Why didn't you tell us?
We gold-star solve any case!
Leave it to the CUREtto Detective Agency.
-And we're also Star Detective Prec--
-Whoa!
The Precure part is a secret!
Oh yeah!
What's that sound?
A mobile phone?
Whoa!
It, it's a--
The bell rang.
Let's talk more later.
Whew!
-I knew it was you.
-Hush!
Hmm.
A Precure from another time...
Maestro Usonoir!
The Tome of Mirages has shown
the next Makoto Jewel.
I, Goemon, should be the one to go.
Newcomers. Come along.
Huh?
Why do we have to?
Yes, okay.
Huh? If you insist.
I'll get a Makoto Jewel for sure!
Lie lie, sir!
This school is huge!
Next is science, right?
I'll get lost when we move classes.
I figured you might!
Ta-da!
Is that...
FIRST FLOOR, SECOND FLOOR
a map of the school!
I made it because I always got lost
when I transferred here!
OUR CLASS IS 2-1
My hero!
What's that?
Pochitan, of course!
Huh...
I see the resemblance!
Go across here, then on the right
is the science classroom...
What a huge cherry blossom tree!
It's said to have been there
since the school was founded!
Wow! That's amazing!
Wait, class is starting soon!
Right!
I didn't expect the Precures!
I'll just quickly get the Makoto Jewel...
-Hang on.
-Huh?
What is it, Newcomer?
The Precure from another time.
Aren't you curious?
Considering what happened to Nijee,
that fairy must have a secret.
Hmm. Then I have an idea.
If the Precures get in trouble,
how will the fairy respond?
I'll find out! With my special talent!
SCIENCE CLASSROOM
Hurry, hurry!
Did we make it?
This isn't the science classroom!
What does this mean?
Welcome to my trick maze!
The Phantom Thieves' Guild!
You've come to take another Makoto Jewel.
What's a trick maze?
I've used my powers to transform
the whole school into a place of mystery!
It's now a trick maze!
You two will have to solve the puzzles.
If you fail to solve a single one,
you'll be trapped in the maze forever.
Forever?
No way!
I'll invite you to the first puzzle.
Huh?
Where are we?
The science classroom?
I can't open it!
That other door won't open either.
Are we trapped?
We have to do something!
A keyhole!
Escape...
A key is needed to open the door.
Obey the warnings in the science classroom
and find the key.
We need a key to get out of here.
Okay! Good to know!
Not here!
I can't find it anywhere!
Obey the warnings in the science classroom
and find it?
The warnings in the science classroom...
Anna, over here!
What is it?
Look at this!
Fire.
It's about fire.
Obey the warnings.
Maybe it's about this?
Yes... Many experiments use fire,
so we have to be careful.
If a big flame comes up,
you have to put it out.
Put out the fire.
We should put out this fire.
The fire on the poster? How?
Like this!
-Huh? This part too?
-Whoa! A key!
Hooray!
Not bad.
But can you solve the next puzzle?
Mikuru!
Yeah!
We'll solve any mystery!
Huh? Again?
Come on... This classroom is...
The music classroom?
MUSIC CLASSROOM, PASSAGE, SCIENCE CLASROOM
The first one was the science classroom.
Now we're in the music classroom.
We're being transported
to different places.
Escape...
A key is needed to open the door.
Press the keys.
Press the keys? What does that mean?
That's interesting.
What are those five lines?
Five lines in the music classroom...
Could it be a staff?
Oh, that thing that music is written on!
If it is, then the keyhole represents
notes. Align this on the staff, and...
Do, mi, so. The key is do, mi, so!
But how can we
press the key of do, mi, so?
I'm not sure...
I feel like I almost got it...
Where is the do, mi, so key?
There! The piano!
Why the piano?
Specifically, that part of the piano!
The keyboard!
KEYBOARD
You write keyboard like this, right?
The first part can be read as "key."
KEY
Oh! So that's what
pressing the keys means!
We play it on the keyboard!
Those notes we saw!
They're in a line like balls on a skewer.
CHORD
That's a chord, and you take
different notes on the keyboard,
DO MI SO
and play them at the same time!
So, using the piano...
We play the do, mi, so chord!
-Alright!
-Mikuru, you're amazing!
I used to take piano lessons!
They got it!
Goemon, you're having fun.
Weren't you watching
for the fairy's power?
It's about time for my entrance.
He's not listening.
Let's just watch.
Yeah.
Okay, ready for the next key!
Escape...
A key is needed to open the door.
I have the key.
He has it?
I guess we have to find
that Goemon character.
That's simple! We just check every place
we think he might hide!
LENDING DESK
Oh, I almost forgot!
This time you have one minute to solve it!
If you don't find me
within the time limit, it's game over.
-Huh?!
-That's not fair!
Start!
W-What are we gonna do?
I know! The Pre-Kit!
Oh yeah!
Open!
Pre-Kit Mirror Loupe!
Hmm?
So that's the Precures'
detective toolset, the Pre-Kit!
Jett-senpai says with the Mirror Loupe
we won't miss any important clues!
Gold-star discovery!
That's the shape of Goemon's sandal print!
So that's one way to use it. Fine.
They call me the master of hide-and-seek.
Will they be able to find me?
The tracks stop here.
Are there any more?
We only have ten seconds left!
Huh?
W-What about behind this bookshelf?
We found him!
Good job, Star Detectives.
Imagine beating me at hide and seek!
Kudos to you!
We cleared the library puzzle!
HOME EC CLASSROOM
KNIT A KEY
ART CLASSROOM
Huh?
The gym?
This was our first location.
This is the final puzzle.
Escape...
Choose the correct door!
To go forward you must go back.
Create a path from nothing.
To go forward, go back?
I think it's a hint.
A mark on the door?
That one, too!
Each of the five doors has one.
A circle, triangle, star,
music note, and an X.
I think they're hints
to help solve the puzzle.
Those marks,
and the meaning of the clue...
If you're stuck, go back to the beginning!
You said that before, didn't you?
We should look back on
the other puzzles we solved!
Okay!
GYM, SCIENCE CLASSROOM, MUSIC CLASSROOM
LIBRARY, HOME EC CLASSROOM, ART CLASSROOM
The rooms we passed through,
and the marks.
We solved a puzzle in the music room,
so maybe it's the note?
Remember what Goemon said.
CREATE A PATH FROM NOTHING
Create a path from nothing.
I think that's important.
A path...
This is a trick maze.
To get through the maze, we solve puzzles.
I've got it!
What is it?
All the places we passed through!
We should connect them!
GYM
First, the gym.
SCIENCE CLASSROOM, MUSIC CLASSROOM
LYBRARY
Then the science classroom,
music classroom, library.
Home ec classroom, art classroom,
and back to the gym.
HOME EC CLASSROOM, ART CLASSROOM
GYM
It should mean something...
-Oh! We overlap them!
-Huh?
The maps!
First floor and second floor!
Separately, they look like nothing.
Put them together, and the paths join up!
I see!
This is the answer!
It's the door with the star!
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
Are we out?
Well done!
I didn't learn much about the fairy,
but I'll take the Makoto Jewel!
Lies, envelop!
Come on, Hanninda!
Hanninda!
-The cherry blossom tree!
-Mikuru, let's go!
Open!
Jewel Cure Watch!
Precure! Wake-up Time!
3! Discover!
6! And face one another!
9! We are the miraculous duo!
Spin around!
And finish off cutely!
Gold-star closing the case on any mystery!
Star Detective Cure Answer!
Jumping towards smiles
with layered reasoning!
Star Detective Cure Mystique!
Star Detective Precure!
I'll show you my answer!
Hanninda!
Nin! Da!
Mystique Reflection!
Cunning!
Get smothered in cherry blossom petals!
-Mystique!
-I've got this!
Nin! Da!
-Let's go!
-Okay!
I won't let you!
I can't see!
Hanninda!
There you are!
What can we do?
It's okay! We got out of that maze!
We can do anything!
Right.
Take that!
They keep running!
Hanninda!
Now!
Jump!
H-Hanninda!
Hm? Huh? My fan is gone!
Hanninda!
-Over here!
-Nin?
Answer Attack!
Da!
Open!
Pre-Kit Mirror Loupe!
Pochitan!
Makoto Jewel!
Look!
Feel!
Solve the mystery!
This is our answer!
Precure! Flying Spectrum!
CUREtto Case Closed!
Hanninda!
Pochi Pochi Cure Cure!
Humph! That was fun!
They've got a tricky power!
As expected.
I'm so glad it's back to normal!
Have we forgotten something?
Science class!
I barely made it!
You're late.
-Where's Anna?
-Huh?
She should be with...?
Mikuru, where are you?
Where's the science classroom?
Oops, I left her behind...
Where are you, Anna?
I've had enough of mazes!
(NaNaNaNa naze? naze? WHY?
NaNaNaNa nazo? nazo! ANSWER?!)
(NaNaNaNa why? Why? WHY?
NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER?!)
ten to ten musundara ara? ara!
Connect the dots, oh? Oh my!
"hanamaru kaiketsu!" kana? kana?
Could it be a "gold-star case closed!"?
Could it?
suiri to nazo wa uragaeshi
niten santen gyakuten
Reasoning turns around riddles
Twists and turns, reverse
kotoba ya shigusa sae wana? wana!
unomi ni shite wa dame! dame!
Even words and behavior are traps? Traps!
Don't just believe them! No!
yoku mite, kangaete, sorekara
fumidasu no yo ippo!
Pay attention, think and then
Take the first step!
komatteiru hito mitara
sugu ni tasuketai
When I see someone in trouble
I immediately want to help
datte nantoka nantoka nantoka shitakute
kakedashiteiru
Cause I wanna, wanna do something
So I go running off
Na Na Na nazo! nazo!
Na Na Na mystery! Mystery!
nazo wo toku no ga meitantei
Solving mysteries
Is what a Star Detective does
uso ka makoto ka mikiwamete
egao no kotae mitsukeru
See through lies and find truth
Find the answer for a smile
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 100 bai
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 100
chikara awasete norikoeru
tomo wa kiseki no katamari
Working together, we can figure it out
Friends are a true miracle
iku yo! Meitantei
Let's go! Star Detective
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 1,000 bai
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 1,000
tomodachi to te ni te wo totte
banjikaiketsu suru made!
Hand in hand with my friends
Until everything's solved!
DATTE Precure
(NaNaNaNa naze? nazo! ANSWER!)
We're Precure, after all
(NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER!)
The Pre-Kits that Jett-senpai
makes are super cute!
I wish even more people could use them!
I know! Let's open a store!
Star Detective Precure!
"Pretty Smiles at Pretty Holic!"
That mystery! CUREtto Case Closed!