Guten Abend.
Ladies and gentlemen, Lynn Reinweiß
here to summarize what happened
in the previous episode
of The Casebook of Arne.
After Little Red Phantom Thief
threatened to steal the Blue Heart,
the latest work by the jeweler Mr. Yelle,
the director of the art museum
went to Lord Arne for protection.
However, both the Blue Heart
and Mr. Yelle himself had disappeared.
We then received requests to find
three other people who had gone missing.
After that, I learned that Mr. Yelle had made
the Blue Heart for someone special,
and he'd also commissioned a portrait
that he never went to pick up.
And then, with Mr. Yelle's whereabouts
still unknown, Lord Arne faced off
against Little Red Phantom Thief
at the museum!
However, her true goal was merely
to deliver another warning—
Before Lord Vampire gets a chance,
I will find the missing Mr. Yelle,
and claim the Blue Heart for myself!
Then, something even more terrifying
happened at the art museum!
I have located the missing humans.
Huh?
Or more accurately, I have located
the corpses of the missing humans.
Will the Arne Detective Agency
be able to solve this mystery?!
What? This intro is too long?
What—
THE CASEBOOK OF ARNE
PART 8: DESIRE AND LOVE
MAKE ALL BURDENS LIGHTER
The statues, the pride of our
collection, are p-people's corpses?
Did I really put corpses on display?
Sir?
In order to make them incomplete,
the killer deliberately
cut off their heads.
That's some twisted taste.
Taking lives for the sake
of art is unforgivable!
The question is, who were they
in the first place?
Can't you already take a stab
at that, Lynn Reinweiß?
Huh?
Oh no! They're the missing boyfriends?
Can a corpse be art? Of course it can.
Art is art because art transcends ethics!
This is no time for laughter.
Director, please pull yourself together.
Art is the f#$%¬@> s#@%!
Aw, yeah!
Director!
Wh-What was I just doing?
Please tell us the name of the sculptor
who made these statues.
The sculptor?
Oh, of course. Let's see.
Frau Silke? Gusteinstraße 3-B?
I'll go there now.
Hold it, Lynn Reinweiß.
Yes?
How many corpses do you see?
One, two, three, four...
There's one too many.
Oh! Mr. Yelle?
It's possible.
No, it cannot be!
Mr. Yelle was turned into one of these?
Sir!
This is Mr. Yelle.
Well then, Lynn Rein—
Lord Arne, please follow up on this clue
and try to find Mr. Yelle.
I'll go visit the sculptor.
This must be the place.
Wait! Wait a second.
What's wrong?
If you ring that, she might run.
Oh, gotcha.
Yup, pretty darn twisted.
It appears she is indeed the killer.
How are we going
to explain this to our clients?
This is so cruel!
Oh, do I have guests?
Are you here to see me?
Or to see my art perhaps?
Aren't they wonderful?
Even if you put all of the greatest
artists in history together,
they couldn't produce
anything close to my work.
Leaving off one part of the body
allows the viewer of the work
to imagine whatever kind
of perfect form they choose.
But that isn't all.
Artists sacrifice their own vitality
to bring their work to life,
but my works are life itself.
Don't you think that's wonderful?
There is no greater art than life itself.
Huh?
Medusa! Don't look into her eyes
or you'll be turned to stone!
Did you turn Mr. Yelle to stone, too?
Who knows? I'm only interested
in their looks, after all.
If this "Yelle" was beautiful enough,
he could very well be up there.
That's awful.
But you know what? You're adorable.
In fact, the three of you are so cute,
I'll turn you all into a work of art.
I'll take care of this. You have to run.
B-But...
Get moving, kid! Uh...
Hurry!
Amy!
You have to run!
But what about Amy?
It's too late! Run!
She let herself get turned
to stone to save you.
A bluebell?
Mr. Yelle's talents have truly
been flourishing recently.
"Bluebell"? Are you sure he didn't
actually say "Blue Heart"?
He definitely said "bell."
A bluebell.
Zisye?
It's Lynn.
Nach, are we going to be all right?
Nach!
Oh, you can't speak because
Lord Arne is too far away.
Turn around and look at me, darling.
I'll turn you into a work of art
that everyone will find beautiful!
Lynn, turn at the next corner.
Zisye!
Go straight, then turn left
down the next alley.
Take the next right.
Now left at this corner.
Oh no.
It's no use hiding.
Found your hiding spot? No, not yet.
Found your hiding spot?
I'm not that naive.
Of course not.
Huh?
You'd never fall for a trap like this.
Wha—
Lynn.
The jeweler isn't among them.
I have to go and tell
Lord Arne about Medusa.
I know just where to find him.
You sure took your time, Lord Vampire.
Game over. It appears
I have defeated you.
Or is that another fake?
It's a pity you have no eye
for marvelous things, Lord Vampire.
This is, without a doubt,
the true Blue Heart.
What proof do you have that it's real?
Why would I need proof?
You're wondering why I have it?
I took it directly from Mr. Yelle himself.
Lord Arne!
Oh, Little Red Phantom Thief.
I didn't realize you were here.
This is a disaster. I forgot to bring
my Lord Arne cheer merch.
Even the most important of all:
the tracksuit.
That's the most important piece?
Is that thing you're holding
the Blue Heart?
Yes, this is the marvelous
Blue Heart itself.
She said she got it from Mr. Yelle.
Oh, good. That must mean he's all right.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Huh?
Yelle said he was making the Blue Heart
for someone special, correct?
Yes.
Do you really think that means her?
How dare you be so rude
to someone as marvelous as I.
Yelle was making it for his lover.
During my investigations,
I didn't find anything about a lover.
He had one.
A lover who was able to lavish him
with startling artistic prowess.
Sounds like something
we heard about earlier.
Ah, that thing before, yeah!
The crest at the art museum.
The leannán sídhe.
The leannán sídhe is the fairy
that's the symbol of this city, right?
The director explained it to us.
A leannán sídhe grants talent
to the artists she loves,
then robs them of their lives.
Their lives?
I'm honestly impressed
you pieced that all together,
Lord Vampire, Lady Lynn, Lady Amy,
and Lord Plushie.
Who are you calling a "plushie"?
You obviously, plushie.
I'll take you to him.
I knew he would be here.
Mr. Yelle.
Lord Vampire, how did you know
you would find him here?
Why are you asking me
when you got here first?
Zisye told me that
when you visited his home,
you uttered the word "bluebell,"
so I came to take a look.
This is the only nearby place like this.
A hill covered in blossoming bluebells.
Leannán sídhe are said to reside
on flower-covered hills.
This very hill might be where
the leannán sídhe and Mr. Yelle first met.
And then, they fell in love.
A little to your left, please.
No, I think I'm fine here.
They must have been very happy
during their time together.
Happy? The human only wanted talent
and the fairy only wanted a life.
It was a transactional relationship,
defined by desire.
It's done. It's finally done.
Leannán sídhe, take a look. Leannán...
Leannán sídhe?
Love is fleeting.
You're giving it back?
I was able to find it before anyone else,
so I believe I succeeded anyway.
That must mean I can do whatever
I want with the Blue Heart now.
Don't you think?
Lord Arne.
Well, wasn't that the museum's request?
For the Arne Detective Agency
to protect the Blue Heart?
Well, I guess it was.
No, it wasn't, Arne.
Zisye?
The museum asked you to protect the
Blue Heart from Little Red Phantom Thief.
But now that the Blue Heart is back
in the hands of its rightful owner,
what is there to protect it from?
You and your stupid semantics.
However, the moon tonight
is exceptionally beautiful.
In honor of that moon, I suppose I could
play along with your stupid charade.
Your painting has been delivered.
I wish Lord Arne could've
attended this with us.
Not a chance. Zwei has
no interest in places like this.
I never imagined the fourth victim
would be one of the museum's guests.
I pray you can rest in peace.
I imagine you're not thrilled
that we're the ones to see you off,
but I guess we're better than no one.
This was such a sad case.
It was the first one Lord Arne
left me in charge of,
so I wanted to be able to celebrate...
But without your hard work, Lynn,
they would've remained statues forever,
and never been returned
to their loved ones.
The clients wouldn't have been able
to move on with their lives.
They too would've
become living corpses.
Neat. Kinda like zombies? Ouch!
Okay, I deserved that,
but I'm still pissed about it.
But what about you? You sure you didn't
stick the heads on the wrong bodies?
Not a chance.
That's right. Amy really put
her heart into her work for us.
I have a request.
What kind of request?
I'd like you to take the heads
and bodies of Medusa's victims,
and carefully put them back together.
When you see a lover for the last time
before being separated forever,
I don't think you ever forget
how they looked. So please...
I did my very best for Lynn's sake.
Good job, me.
Sheesh.
That night...
I'm sure I saw the leannán sídhe
among the flowers.
A lifetime spent stealing the lives of
the people you love must be very painful.
I pray the leannán sídhe
someday finds a reason
to also be thankful for her life.
I'm so bored.
Why aren't they back yet?
Just relax. How about
some nice chamomile tea?
And how about a schneeball, kiddo?
This isn't a café. It's my workplace.
Oh, come on.
Cheers!
Cheers, kiddo!
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
TIMING: HENRY LIN
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: ELISABETH CRIST
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS