Is today Reincarnated in Another
World as a Skill Demon Lord,
I Lead a Cheat Slow Life
While Raising a Villainess day?
It's Reincarnated in Another
World as a Skill Demon Lord,
I Lead a Cheat Slow Life While Raising
a Villainess: Oops, I Did It Again day.
So close!
Should I wake you up
at the usual time tomorrow morning?
Yes, please.
Sounds good. Good night, then.
Good night.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
It's time for torture, Princess!
I surrender!
Your Highness!
Stop trying to set a
new record for the fastest time!
Today's torture is...
Ta-da! Balloon art!
Mama made some for me the other day,
and it was lots of fun.
So I thought you'd like it, too.
Listen well, daughter of the Hell-Lord.
Balloon artists visited
the empire as street performers.
Her Highness has seen
the finest of balloon artistry,
so it'll take an extraordinary
feat to please her.
Isn't that right, Your Highness?
Oh, rats!
She's already thinking up her confession!
Okay, here I go.
Hup!
I can't do it...
What?
I'm scared to twist the balloon.
Y-You can do it, Maomao-chan!
There's still room in the balloon
for the air to escape.
AIR
ROOM
So it won't pop, even if you twist it!
But still...
I'm too scared...
Let me do it!
Your Highness?!
I'll make it and force myself to give in!
You don't see how that's strange?!
What do you want me to do, then?!
Please don't give in!
Maomao-chan's still young,
so she'll run into things she can't do!
But I don't want her to have bad
memories of not being able to do it!
Leave everything to me!
You're...
Mama!
Thank you, Princess.
Maomao-chan, let me see that balloon.
You take this, do this, and with that...
Ta-da!
It's a poodle!
Mama sure is amazing...
Maomao-chan.
Next, it's time to bring
out the big guns.
Huh?
I won't be able to do it all by myself.
Maomao-chan, do you
think you can help me?
Yeah!
I'll be holding onto this end.
Maomao-chan, try giving it a twist.
Yeah, I'll do my best!
I'm still scared.
Don't worry! I'm right here!
I'm here for you, too.
Y-Yeah...
Twist...
You got this, Maomao-chan!
Keep going, Maomao-chan!
Twist...
Maomao-chan.
Maomao-chan!
You can do it, Maomao-chan!
I did it!
Good job!
You did it!
Yahoo!
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Mama, where do I twist next?
Ta-da!
A flower!
What should we make next?
A teddy bear!
A teddy bear? It won't be easy.
Maomao-chan, do you think
you can help me a little more?
Yeah, I'll do what I can!
You too, Princess!
Sure!
They all had fun
What?
Forgot to get a secret out of her?
Yes.
Princess Maomao-chan was
the assigned inquisitor.
She administered balloon art torture...
But after Her Majesty joined in,
they had so much fun making balloons,
that, apparently, they forgot
to ask her for a secret.
I see.
Well, it happens to the best—
What's wrong, Your Majesty?!
His Majesty has gotten a mouth ulcer.
A mouth ulcer?!
His Majesty's mighty jaw and sharp fangs
are said to be able to crush even steel!
An ulcer affecting a mouth like his...
I shudder at the mere thought!
His Majesty can defend himself against
external attacks with near-instant magic,
Lightning Hurricane
but he's vulnerable from the inside!
And healing magic would
most likely harm His Majesty.
So the only way is to let His
Majesty's body heal itself?!
That means he'll need
to get some quality rest time.
Which in turn means...
He'll need to go on
special demonic leave!
Demons with sharp fangs are more
susceptible to mouth and tooth problems,
and demons with many eyes
are more susceptible to eye conditions.
As such, the Hellhorde offers different
leave types based on a demon's physiology.
This is known as "special demonic leave."
Special Demonic Leave
The one upside here is
that today is Friday.
Yes, it won't affect operations too much.
We should manage to hold down
the fort on our own.
His Majesty...
I only hope it's nothing serious...
Mr. Hell-Lord?
Mr. Hell-Lord God Thunder?
That's me.
The Hell-Lord's ulcer-afflicted regimen.
Get some relaxing exercise
to relieve stress.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Is this okay for you to eat?
Eat soft food that's
easy on the stomach.
This savory egg custard is delicious.
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Huh? Papa's home!
He came back early
because he got a mouth ulcer.
Yay!
It really smarts, you know.
Papa! Let's play! Let's play!
Not today.
Once I feel better tomorrow,
we can play all you like.
Sure thing.
Then I'll help heal your mouth ulcer!
That ulcer doesn't stand a chance.
Brush up top!
Remember to keep good oral hygiene.
Brush down low.
Get plenty of sleep.
Saturday
Papa, are you better now?
Yes.
It's healed up.
Hooray!
Okay, we can play lots today!
Yay!
Woof, woof, woof.
Bow wow wow.
Woof, woof.
Bow wow—
Papa?
It's nothing.
So it still hurts a little?
Maomao-chan, how about you
and Papa do some drawing?
Sure!
Done!
Let me have a look.
Watch this, Maomao-chan.
What are you folding it for?
Look, a bus.
Beep, beep!
Can I draw people inside?
Yes, go ahead.
Ta-da!
It looks great.
Let me make more cars.
I know!
What's this now, Maomao-chan?
What?!
A tunnel!
Drawing the landscape?
I was too busy focusing on making cars.
By making a tunnel, the scenery
is suddenly brought into sharp view.
You can practically see the bus
peacefully driving down a country road.
What creativity!
A feat worthy
of the Hell-Lord's daughter...
No, of Maomao-chan!
Look, I made Maomao-chan.
Wow! That looks great, Mama!
Let's make lots more
and turn it into a big town!
Excellent idea.
Create to your heart's content.
Papa, your phone!
Someone's calling?
Papa, your—
Yes, Hell-Lord speaking.
Oh, Your Majesty!
On Duty This Weekend
Chief Battle Officer
Bruse the Destroyer
This is Bruse the Destroyer.
Hard at work, I hope.
Well, what is it?
Oh, well...
I was worried about
Your Majesty's health
and couldn't help but call.
I see, thanks for calling.
But rest assured.
The pain's already gone.
That's great to hear, Your Majesty!
I'm in the middle
of constructing a new town.
Chief Battle Officer
Bruse the Destroyer
What?!
Wh-What sort of town?
A town filled to the brim
with every desire imaginable.
Unbelievable!
I'll see you on Monday.
What does he mean by a town?
Let's get back to building our town.
Yay!
Sunday
One, two, three, four.
There we go!
Well done.
All that playtime with
you made her really happy.
That makes two of us.
When I first got the mouth ulcer,
I was prepared for the worst.
But as a result, I got to spend
lots of time with Maomao-chan.
Isn't that nice?
It is a little tough not being able to
watch late-night anime live, though.
You should stop staying up so late
and get to bed earlier from now on.
That I can't promise.
What?
Instead, I'll cut down
on midnight snacks.
That's for the best.
Lulune, you should watch out
for mouth ulcers, too.
Will do.
Monday
Bus Stop
Hell-Lord Residence
Papa, will you be home early today?
My mouth ulcer's healed up,
so I'm working normal hours today.
I see...
Oh, I know!
You should get lots
of mouth ulcers from now on!
A devilish request
behind an angelic smile.
What? His Majesty?!
Yes!
He's returned from the depths of hell!
Certificate of Health
Attn: Hellhorde
Patient Name: Hell-Lord God Thunder
Patient was diagnosed with condition: (     stomatitis     ).
Following treatment, patient has recuperated and fully recovered from the condition stated above.
The certificate
for your healed mouth ulcer.
Everything looks to be in order.
Please accept my deepest congratulations
on your recovery, Your Majesty!
I'm back to 100 percent!
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
'Tis time for torture, Princess.
Okay, do your worst!
Oh, that's right.
Last weekend, we went through
the ordeal of His Majesty falling ill.
Hey, is he all right?
Your Highness, we're talking
about the Hell-Lord here!
He's the last person
you should worry about!
Fortunately, he was able to
make a full recovery.
Good to hear.
No, not good!
As for me, I work out on a regular basis.
I've never once gotten sick—
Your Highness?!
What's the matter?
This is...
Jinx-eye!
Jinx-Eye
Jinx-eye?!
What in the world is that?
It hurts...
'Tis a disease where part of the eyelid
turns red and swollen from inflammation.
You mean a stye?
So that's what you call it
in the Demon World.
My eye hurts...
Please rest assured.
It'll heal in no time
with some eye drops.
Princess.
Could it be that you
can't handle eye drops?
Are you scared to take them?
Her Highness is Princess and Commander
of the Imperial Third Legion.
The very image of bravery!
Fearless and dashing!
Her Highness would never cower
at the sight of eye drops!
Right, Your Highness?
I'm scared of eye drops.
Your Highness?
I'm terrified of the idea
of sticking something in my eye...
How can that be?!
Through sandstorms and downpours alike,
you would stare down your enemy
without ever averting your gaze!
But eye drops you put in yourself!
And all while staring down
the droplet about to enter your eye...
It's scary!
The sheer fear always makes me
lose all strength in my hand!
It's exactly the same as putting a gun
to your head and pulling the trigger!
It's nothing like that, actually!
I see, so you're scared of
putting in eye drops yourself.
Torture...
Don't worry.
As long as you keep your eyes open,
you don't need to look right at it.
Just look right at the bunny.
Sure...
You're done?
Yes, you did great.
Please keep your eyes shut.
A pleasant feeling
spreading across my eye.
With my eyes closed, a refreshing
sensation floods this world of darkness.
Feels so good...
Thanks, Torture.
Think nothing of it.
I know how painful jinx-eye can be.
Oh yeah, a secret...
I ask you to divulge a secret
only during our torture sessions.
Torture...
You really are such a softie.
There's no guarantee
that I'll fold today, you know?
I'll make you regret not asking
me for a secret here.
I look forward to it.
No matter the torture,
I will never give in!
The princess
confessed
A quirk in the Imperial
Army's marching pattern?
More useless information.
I'm more surprised to hear
the princess can't handle eye drops.
Indeed.
I hear she was only able to
take them with Torture's aid.
Oh?
She managed to take them?
How admirable.
My fever's gone down,
but my throat still feels uncomfortable.
It may be my day off,
but I'll have to take it easy today.
My appetite's returned, so I should
feel better soon with a bit of rest.
I had saved some frozen udon.
Simmer slowly until the broth melts.
Once it does, turn it up
to medium heat to finish cooking.
It's starting to smell great.
Once everything's up to a boil...
It's ready to eat!
Hot! Hot, hot!
That was hotter than I expected.
I should have just used oven mitts.
Shichimi
Pepper
Okay, let's dig in.
Shichimi
Pepper
I brought out
the shichimi by force of habit.
I'll have to pass for today.
It's delicious!
It's soaking right into my aching body.
Next up is...
Oh, the shrimp tempura...
I hate to waste food, but my stomach's
still weak, so I shouldn't eat it.
Still...
It looks so good...
I mustn't!
I am the Hellhorde's grand inquisitor!
My self-control is ironclad!
I won't give in to desire
and behave foolishly!
Oh, I'm powerless!
It's too good!
The soft batter that's
soaked up all the broth.
The undersized shrimp that still asserts
its presence with its plump texture.
It's perfect.
I'll drink plenty of water
and pray that I don't upset my stomach.
That was great.
My stomach feels so warm.
Thank you for the wonderful meal.
Now to spend the day resting up in bed.
It's a shame that I can't go outside,
but sleeping all I want while the
sun's still up is a thrill in itself.
Torture got plenty of sleep
and got better.