SAKUNA: OF RICE AND RUIN
I cannot write.
I knew Koushi Oborozuki could do it.
They're a real genius.
Why are you laughing?
No reason.
Anyway, has Koushi Oborozuki
put out a new book?
Unfortunately, I've been
busy with my duties...
Duties?
I-I mean, I'm sure the author
Koushi Oborozuki is busy as well.
I see. I'd love to meet them.
I am the one and only Koushi Oborozuki.
I took up the pen once more
because it's what Sakuna wants, but...
I can't write anything at all.
SHIKI ZOUSHI
Would it be better to write based on
my experiences, like this Shiki Zoushi?
UKETAMA
If I'm to write something based on my
experiences that Sakuna would enjoy,
then...
Lady Uketama!
Please, don't push.
Don't push.
That's...
No need to rush. I won't run away.
How did you write a book
as marvelous as Shiki Zoushi?
Oh, I didn't do anything special.
I simply wrote what I perceived
with my own eyes and ears.
Yes, the key is experiencing
things for oneself.
It allows one to write the truth,
unlike stories that are
the product of imagination.
You're familiar with
The Unrequited Love Story, aren't you?
That story is pure fantasy.
It's nothing like my own works.
Oh, you're not familiar with it?
You should compare our works.
KOKOROWA’S RICE-FARMING DIARY
PART ONE
Sakuna is looking forward to more works
from me. I must write something.
But I can't publish anything as
sloppy as Koushi Oborozuki...
Kokorowa! Kokorowa!
Kokorowa!
S-Sakuna and Tama.
I've been calling you.
Lady Kokorowa, you seem rather tired.
N-Not at all. Anyway,
you've returned to the capital?
Indeed. I was on my way to your place.
I even brought you a gift. Look.
You have my gratitude.
What is that, Sakuna?
I came to purchase Koushi's
new book, but it's not out yet.
These were on display,
so I bought a copy.
What?
It's a journal called Shiki Zoushi.
I've only read the beginning,
but it's interesting.
I must experience it
for myself after all...
What's that?
Sakuna, I have a request.
Why so formal?
May I help you grow rice this spring?
Really? But you must be busy.
I'd like to experience everything,
from planting to harvest.
I see.
I don't think you should.
What?
You've never performed farm work
before. You can't do it alone.
Just let us handle it.
Anyway, let's go to your place.
These pickles are exquisite.
What's wrong?
You, too?
You don't think I can do it either?
Kokorowa? Why are you so upset?
I'm not upset.
You're definitely upset.
I am not upset!
I've made my decision.
I will grow rice on Hinoe Island.
I'll do everything from harvesting
to planting—no, to tilling.
Tilling? But you can't.
You have work to do in the capital.
There you go again, telling me I can't.
It's just growing rice! I can handle it!
"Just"?
Growing rice is far more
difficult than you imagine.
Even I struggled at first.
I couldn't harvest any rice.
I still struggle sometimes.
Don't underestimate it.
I'm not.
I just want to prove I can do it, too.
Why don't you both calm down?
Fine.
What?
I won't say another word.
Do as you please.
Your Highness.
Oh, I will.
I will.
Kokorowa?
Kokorowa!
What are you...?
Forgive me for not
notifying you in advance.
I came to fulfill my promise.
About growing rice?
Yes.
I shall prove I can successfully
grow rice by myself.
Anyway, could I borrow
a field you're not using?
Your situation seems rather
complicated, Lady Kokorowa,
but we'll do everything we can to help.
Thank you, Tauemon.
And you, Sakuna.
Uh, sure.
You can use one of
the unused fields here.
Haven't you begun work on this one?
Uh...
I'd prefer a field that's
had less work performed on it.
Then perhaps an abandoned
field would be better.
I'm not sure that
I've seen one around here.
In that case...
Oh, Ashigumo.
There should be an
abandoned field east of here.
It's rather neglected, though.
Oh?
Lady Sakuna and Lady
Kokorowa, take a look.
This is it, huh?
Looks like it hasn't
been used in a while.
There's even a stream.
You'll be able to irrigate it right away.
It's cold.
It's not perfect,
but the soil seems fertile.
It should make an adequate field.
Lady Sakuna!
This shed has all
the equipment she'll need.
With a little dusting,
it should be usable.
I'm worried about weeds, though.
They've taken root, so it
won't be easy to prepare the field.
Sakuna, may I use this shed
and abandoned field?
Kokorowa, have you been listening?
That's why I want to use this field.
It'll be worth the effort.
But how are you going to
remove all this wilted grass?
Don't worry about that.
What are these?
They're only prototypes,
but when equipped with farming tools,
they can till, plow, and irrigate.
You've made something
rather convenient again.
I wish we had one of our own.
I have the scroll on agriculture
and my automatons.
I'll be fine.
Okay. Kokorowa, I leave
this field in your hands.
Thank you.
I shall grow some fantastic rice.
Where's Kokorowa?
I invited her,
but she said she'd have food brought
from the capital on the regular ships.
But I put in extra effort
to welcome Kokorowa.
That is a shame.
I see.
She could at least eat with us.
Yeah.
If I can successfully grow rice by myself,
then surely Sakuna will admit...
It's done.
It's time to plant the rice.
Are those bags of seed rice? What?
They're putting them in hot water?
What are they doing?
Looks good.
They've taken on more strain
and muddy water than expected.
I can't believe how
little progress I've made.
My body feels so heavy.
Tauemon?
What?
My seedlings...
Did Tauemon do this?
I'll never be able to write
a new book for Sakuna like this.
Kokorowa.
Sakuna?
Everyone...
I see. You were stressing the seedlings.
They were looking spindly.
Lady Sakuna told me to do it,
but I should've told you as well.
It's quite all right. You crushed
my seedlings to help them.
I'd like to ask you something else.
Why did you dunk your
seed rice in hot water?
That makes the seedlings
more resistant to plague.
I had no idea.
I assumed I could
easily grow rice as well,
but it's not something a novice can do.
You did well, Kokorowa.
What? But I haven't
accomplished a single thing.
Still, you've been working hard.
That's commendable.
But I...
Kokorowa, I'm sorry
for what I said at the capital.
For assuming you couldn't do it.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
I should be apologizing to you.
It was arrogant of me to think
I could grow rice on my own.
However...
I'd like to learn more about
growing rice on Hinoe Island.
So please, Sakuna,
will you help me grow rice?
Of course.
I, Sakuna the harvest goddess,
will help you for the next year.
Thank you.
Lady Kokorowa, here.
Is this for me?
You seemed to be struggling in the
kimono you brought from the capital,
so I made it for you.
Try it on.
Thank you, Yui.
You should eat with us from now on.
That will make the food taste better.
She's right.
We'd be glad to help
you grow rice as well.
You will?
I appreciate it.
Kokorowa!
What?
You're crying first?
I missed you!
We haven't spoken in forever!
I missed you, too.
We'll be together now!
Sakuna.
Kokorowa, you came.
Yes, since you offered.
I shall prepare dinner right away.
PEST CONTROL
I had no idea my mother's scrolls
were in that shed.
Yes.
Sakuna, may I read these scrolls?
That's fine, but are they
legible in this state?
I shall decipher Lady Toyohana's
precious scrolls on agriculture.
Lady Kokorowa.
The automatons in the capital
are acting strangely?
They'd like you to return
as soon as possible.
But I inspected them
thoroughly before I left.
There shouldn't be
anything wrong with them.
Besides...
Don't worry about the rice.
I promise we'll look after it.
Yes, you can count on us.
Very well.
Then I will leave my rice
in your hands for a while.
They're all leaking oil.
There isn't a scratch on any of them.
Once their oil is replenished,
they're back to normal.
What happened here?
Steamed yokan and green tea, please.
I knew it.
Long ago, I used to write my stories
and enjoy them by myself.
TEA SHOP
I forgot one of my books at the tea shop.
Alongside my book,
there was a strip of paper.
It said, "Why don't
you publish your books?"
I responded saying I wouldn't,
but we exchanged messages
several times after that.
Eventually, I gave in.
That's how I came to publish
The Unrequited Love Story
that Sakuna loves under
the name Koushi Oborozuki.
You must be waiting for me, too.
But I can't do two things
at the same time.
This year, I'll focus on growing rice.
What?!
Oh, forgive me.
Are you hurt?
Lady Uketama...
Isn't that my new book?
What? Oh...
I shall sign it for you.
Scribble, scribble.
Here you are.
Do you read often?
Yes. Well, only a little.
I see.
Then have you read
The Unrequited Love Story?
The author, Koushi Oborozuki,
must be a dreamer.
It's quite different from my book.
They haven't published
a new book recently.
Perhaps they've given up writing.
I'm sure...
I'm sure Koushi Oborozuki
will publish a new book soon.
She's overflowing with determination.
It will be different
from her previous works.
What do you mean?
That's just what I've heard.
When the Amahoho arrives
from Hinoe Island,
her new book will be published.
N-Now, if you'll excuse me...
I will publish a new book for Sakuna
while growing rice by the end of the year.
I must resume growing rice
and begin writing right away!