You Can't Be in a Rom-Com
with Your Childhood Friends!
The four of you mean the world to me.
It would be weird
for childhood friends like us
to be in a rom-com situation, right?
I have a childhood friend.
He usually acts cold,
but he actually has a big heart.
It was an accident,
but we even k-kissed...
S-So...
I have a childhood friend.
He's a bit full of himself and stubborn,
but he's dependable when it matters.
I want to be more honest, too, but...
Onii-chan is my childhood friend.
He always treats me
like his little sister...
But he must know how I feel about him!
So...
I have a childhood friend.
He's competitive and stubborn,
but he's a precious friend.
I said I'd support his love life,
but at this rate...
Will this turn into a rom-com
with a childhood friend?
All right! I'm gonna dedicate
this one to all of you!
Not even close?!
Up next is the coed three-legged race!
Will it develop into a lovely romance?!
Good luck everyone!
Thanks, Akari.
The person I was paired with got hurt,
so I was looking for a sub.
Yeah, whatever.
But why did you choose me?
There's a gap in height and you know
I'm not the best... runner...
What do you mean?
You're my precious
childhood friend, remember?
Teehee!
Gross!
Enough with that face!
Stay away from me!
All right! I'm gonna give it my all!
twist
Gross! Don't move like that!
I'm so excited!
Why didn't you ask Shio?
She's a childhood friend, too.
Shio's busy with committee member duties,
Executive Committee Member
Haru's White Team,
White Team
and Runako's in junior high.
Junior High Student
So it's only because
there's no one else.
No, it's not.
I want to run with you, Akari.
You are my precious
childhood friend, after all!
So gross!
I'll do anything you want
to return the favor!
Anything?
All right, participants,
please take your positions!
Dummy! What am I thinking?!
H-Hey!
Come on, Akari. Put your hand on my waist.
Gosh, I can't stop thinking about it.
My heart is...
What's going on, Akari?
Are you nervous?
Huh? What do you care?
Your body feels stiff. Are you okay?
Too close! Too close!
Too close!
Calm down and take a deep breath.
S-So annoying.
He's acting like it's no big deal.
It would be weird
for childhood friends like us
to be in a rom-com situation, right?
So he's telling me
I'm not even on his radar?
Ready...
Shoot! I'm not mentally ready yet...
Set...
Akari, start with your right foot!
Let's go!
All right! Taking the lead at the start
is team Sakai and Hiodoshi!
Huh? It's easy to run...
Those two are totally in sync!
Amazing!
Is Eiyu... matching my pace?
Oh no! But they aren't
picking up the pace!
I'm really bad at running!
They're behind now.
What is he doing?
They're perfectly in sync, though.
Onii-chan...
Eiyu...
It's okay, Akari.
Let's keep going at our own pace.
Step by step, okay?
It's all about having fun!
Maybe it's okay like this...
If Eiyu's this kind,
I can be more honest...
It doesn't have to be all about winning.
Ugh! Darn it!
One more! One more time!
Gosh, not this again!
Your mom will get mad!
Gotcha!
Eiyu!
I don't care!
I'm gonna keep going until I win!
You may not win till you die!
Then I'll keep going until
I win, even if it kills me!
Gosh!
Not a chance!
You brat!
What a dummy.
Wow! Team Sakai and Hiodoshi
have suddenly ramped up the pace!
Akari?
What's going on?
They're totally out of sync now!
But...
They're totally out of sync, but they're
moving up steadily from the very back!
Could this be a big comeback?!
They're so fast!
Akari, you've got so much energy!
Stop it...!
Stop laughing and keep up!
Akari?
What's with you?!
Usually you'd say, "Don't start running
all of a sudden," or, "Match my pace"!
Don't you have anything to say?!
I'm just being my usual self.
No you're not!
You never just agree!
You're so full of yourself and so cocky!
Always acting tough, stupid,
short-sighted, and ridiculously stubborn!
Akari, you sure know a lot about me.
But!
Even after all that...
I like you!
A-Akari...
Oh my!
Team Sakai and Hiodoshi
have fallen to the ground!
They're totally behind now!
What are you doing?
Get off of me.
I'm not letting you have this
as you are now.
Akari-chan, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Come on, get up already.
Let's finish this run!
Gross mode!
GROSS MODE
The pair that went down is back up
and sprinting toward the goal!
Goal!
The pair reached
the goal together, in sync!
This concludes the morning event,
and it is now lunchtime.
The afternoon event will begin at 1:15PM,
starting with the girl's obstacle course.
Good job, Akari!
Participants, please gather
at Tent #1 by 1PM.
But are you sure you're okay?
That was quite a fall.
I'm totally fine!
Don't worry about it.
Hey, my childhood friends!
You all worked so hard this morning!
Come on, let's all eat lunch together!
Cringe... cringe...
cringe
I'm gonna go eat over there.
Huh? Akarin?
Aw, is Akari embarrassed?
Sorry, I'm out.
Hey...
Haru too, huh?
You're all so shy.
grin
cringe cringe
Cringe, cringe, cringe, cringe,
cringe, cringe, cringe...
I-I'm gonna join Akarin over there!
Shio too, huh?
Well, Onii-chan's gonna go
wash his hands now, okay?
O-Okay...
Pulled it off!
Jeez, what's up with them?
All I want is to be normal, but...
Even so...
I like you!
Hey, your desires are showing!
Huh?!
What's this balloon thing?
I'm you.
Me? What?
No way... Are you an illusion?
More like your other personality.
I came to snap some sense
into you, you hopeless fool.
Sense?
You're getting way too horny
for your precious childhood friends.
I'm not getting horny...
You sure?
Huh?!
You kissed me and got horny.
Wha—?!
Now you're getting horny for me.
H-Hey!
You're even getting horny for me, too.
Whoa! H-H-Hold on! W-W-W-Wait!
Hey Eiyu, don't you want to...
Hey Onii-chan, don't you want to...
Kiss them all?!
Don't ya?!
I-It's not like that!
Liar!
Your dirty little grin is proof, you fool!
Even if it's fantasy, don't do that
with your childhood friends, you idiot!
Th-This thing's got some nerve!
Come on, you must have
realized it by now.
If you hadn't fallen in love,
if things hadn't gotten awkward,
if your heart hadn't been racing...
You could have been more
honest and cherished them!
Love is a nuisance
between childhood friends.
Yeah...
I know that!
Boom!
Onii-chan, there you are!
Runako...
Keep it together!
Shut up!
Is something wrong?
YIKES!
Oh, it's n-nothing.
What?
You're not in Gross Eiyu mode anymore!
Gross Eiyu mode?
That's how you've been acting all day.
What?!
We've all been calling you that.
R-Really?
shocked
Gross...?
Anyway, see?
I brought lunch! Let's eat!
Ta-dah!
Wow!
Did you make this yourself again?
Yup! I woke up early to do it!
Wow, thanks so much.
Yup, delicious!
Oh yeah!
I'm especially proud of these.
Fresh spring rolls!
Let's try it!
Here, say "ah."
Hey! Runa—
H-Hold—
She's in junior high.
She calls you "Onii-chan."
You're her guardian!
I know that.
So? Is it good?
W-Wow... That was freaking delicious!
Are you okay?
Huh?
You're acting strange today, you know?
Um, well...
Onii-chan?
No, it's nothing.
But your face is red.
Don't get horny! Don't get horny!
Horny, horny, horny!
C-Calm down, Gross Eiyu!
Looks like you don't
have a fever, at least.
Horny, horny, horny!
Hey! I'm not!
Horny, horny!
I-It's not that I'm getting horny!
Horny?
No, I wasn't—
Are you?
No!
There's no way I'd get horny
for my childhood friend!
That can't happen. No way.
Game over... You're done!
It doesn't bother me.
It actually makes me happy.
Right? That'd be gross—
What?!
I'm happy with your naughty feelings, too.
B-But why?
You're my precious childhood friend...
There's no way that works.
Onii-chan, you know...
Now it's time for the final event!
The obstacle course and scavenger race!
The current standing is 286-291.
White Team is just barely ahead.
Red
Team
White
Everything will be decided in this event!
Darn it! I want to participate,
but I did too much earlier.
Well, it's a boy's event anyway.
White Team! We better not lose!
Eiyu?
This is it! It's the last event!
Yeah.
I wonder how Eiyu will do...
Huh?
He's not...
Gross Eiyu anymore?
Now, all participants
have taken their positions!
Ready...
And they're off!
Leading with momentum is
a first-year of the Red Team...
Sakai-kun!
I... I...
Will we be just childhood friends forever?
To be in a rom-com...
When will you take me as your wife?
with them...
I love you, Onii-chan.
M-My childhood friends!
D-Does this not count either?
Right now... I...
Sakai maintains his lead
and reaches the last obstacle,
the box containing the instructions
for the scavenger hunt!
Now, what will it be?
What will it be?
What the heck is this?!
There it is! The red slip!
Pulled again this year!
Oh my gosh! It's the red slip!
I wonder what it says?
Wh-What's that?
Now! What is this year's
impossible challenge?!
Find someone you really,
really, really, REALLY love
really, really, really love!
Someone you love?
Hey, I don't remember that challenge.
I snuck it in there to spice things up.
Whoa!
Sakai-kun, who was
in the lead, is not moving!
Everyone else is moving ahead!
How will Sakai-kun
respond to this challenge?
I'll just choose someone as a... joke...
"Someone you really, really,
really, really love!"
Who will he choose?
Sakai-kun is running!
Did he make up his mind?!
Runako...
Akari... Shio...
Haru!
I choose...
Runako! Come with me!
Onii-chan!
The one he really loves...
Is Runako?
No...
H-Huh? Why am I disappointed?
Let's go!
Okay! But wait, Onii-chan?!
Onii-chan, you know...
Squeeze!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Is your heart racing?
Or do you feel at ease?
What?
Feeling naughty, yet
wanting to cherish someone...
It's okay to feel all of that!
You too, Akari!
Huh?
You too, Shio!
What?!
Haru, you too, come with me!
What? Me too?
Wh-What's going on here?
Sakai-kun has selected
four beauties from the crowd!
They're all heading for the goal!
That's just how it is...
with childhood friends.
I see...
So it's okay to both have horny feelings
and to want to cherish them.
It all makes sense now.
I was confused and
didn't know what to do...
But!
Shio!
Akari!
Runako!
Haru!
I've known the answer for a long time!
My childhood friends are...
Goal!
Sakai-kun of Red Team makes
the goal with four beauties!
Now, the final judgment!
N-Now, I'll check your slip.
U-Um...
Do you really, really,
really love everyone here?
I don't know!
But!
They're all my precious childhood friends!
Now, what's the much-anticipated decision?
Accepted!
Victory goes to Red Team!
An incredible last-minute victory!
Thanks for your help!
I got first place!
You gotta be kidding me!
White Team lost!
That was really misleading!
Congrats on first place!
Gosh, you scared me!
You're okay with that, Eiyu?
Gross Eiyu.
You're sure, right?
I wouldn't say I'm sure.
But I want to be honest with my feelings.
Even the horny feelings...
Okay.
Then, good luck.
Onii-chan? What's wrong?
Nothing. Thanks, Runako.
See ya, Gross Eiyu.
What?!
I can't eat anymore...
Onii-chan, wake up...
You two!
Cut it out!
Hey, let me go!
Huh?!
A-Akari?
Wh-What?
Don't get the wrong idea.
I wasn't waiting for you at all.
Haru?
H-Hey, what a coincidence!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
A coincidence?
Where's your bike,
Haru-kun?
Oh, um, a flat...
I got a flat tire, so...
stare
A-Anyway, you're all going to school
all lovey-dovey as usual, huh?
What?
N-Not at all!
That's right!
Then you must be feeling
all horny already, right?
Eiyu?!
Y-You're all my precious
childhood friends.
A-All I'm feeling is bliss.
What?
Gross!
Are you going Gross Eiyu again?!
Please don't!
Before he does...
Let's run!
I have four
childhood friends.
Huh? Oh, hey!
The childhood friends
in fiction are all fake.
I know what real life is like!
You can't be in a rom-com...
with your childhood friends!
Now what?
Look at him.
Onii-chan...
What's he doing?
He's so flustered!
Look at him, he's so flustered.
Or maybe you can! Who knows?!
Episode 12
Did the Three-Legged Race and Feel a Little Naughty?
Then Doing the Scavenger Hunt Still Won't Start a Rom-Com
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com
with Your Childhood Friends!