m 0 0 l 0 102 32 102 b 3 75 3 32 32 0
OSHI NO KO
Strawberry Productions, Inc.
Saitou
True Showbiz Weekly
Let's discuss what to do about the
upcoming True Showbiz Weekly story.
Wow, she's visibly down in the dumps.
Who wouldn't be?
Can't believe our first romance scandal
came from Senpai, our crazy cat lady.
There was no romance involved!
And who cares
if I become a crazy cat lady?
I swear nothing happened
with Director Shima.
But it's true that we talked
in a private apartment.
I stayed indoors all night with a man.
The fans will be rightfully pissed.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize to me.
If you feel bad for these two,
that's all I need.
You know...
I don't believe getting photographed
by a reporter makes you unprofessional.
These tabloid reporters
will do anything for a scoop.
They'll try to manipulate you
into getting careless
and use all sorts of barely legal tactics.
They were a thorn in our side
when Ai was around, too.
But...
True Showbiz Weekly
Scoops on idols aren't even moneymakers,
so publishers don't usually feature them.
Huh?
Not unless your group
is big enough to perform on Kohaku.
B-Komachi shouldn't be at the point
where tabloids want dirt on you.
Then why?
Take a look at this photo
the publisher sent over.
It was taken outside Director Shima's
apartment building, see?
Most entertainers bring dates home
instead of going to love hotels.
So the reporter was
staking out the building.
Wait, doesn't that mean...
The original target
for this piece was Director Shima.
Considering even I've heard
rumors that he's a playboy,
he's probably gotten himself
in quite a few messes.
I'm betting a woman he dumped
tipped the reporter off.
You just got caught up in the mess.
Hey, so the leaker girl set her up!
That would be the natural assumption, yes.
Ah...
It was Mako.
An insider leak? Talk about ugly.
It happens all the time.
Anyway, in the future, stay clear
of men likely to have a history.
For now, make sure to be polite
and respectful with the reporter.
Those guys tend to write brutal articles
about subjects who are hostile to them.
Sorry.
I wanted an acting gig, so I was trying
to get in his good graces.
I got tunnel vision.
I'm really sorry.
I...
It's okay.
We get it.
We're just living our lives,
and we can get depressed
and stop thinking straight at times.
Nobody's perfect 100% of the time.
It's okay.
What do you think happens to Senpai now?
This will affect
her future career for sure.
I feel so bad for her.
Kana-chan's probably only being
an idol for you, Aqu-tan.
She believed in and took this path
because you asked her to.
She became an idol
because that's what you wanted.
Ruby.
Even if it meant making a terrible choice,
one that would bring you pain...
If there was a way to help Arima,
would you want to?
Do you even have to ask?
She's one of us.
I see.
Thanks.
Could we bribe the reporter
into burying the story?
Too late for that.
Isn't there some kind
of trick we could use?
Technically, there is one way to stop it.
There is?
Major agencies use it sometimes,
but there's no way we could.
What is it?
Tell me! Tell me!
What you'd need is...
True Showbiz Weekly
Writer Kazuhiko Itano
Hello. You're Hoshino-san?
I'm sorry for asking to meet so late.
Don't worry about it.
If it boosts the value
of my article, I can't complain.
And I can still make
the deadline at this point.
Now, according to your email,
you wanted to talk about Arima-san
as a good friend with the same agency?
Before that, could I confirm a few things?
Go ahead.
Are you not able to redact
the name "Kana Arima"
and go with something like
"Member A of a famous idol group"?
I don't think so.
Why's that?
This is the issue's top story.
Arima-san is a grown woman
who has name recognition—
a public figure
with considerable influence.
There's no reason for the press
to conceal her name.
Arima's still in high school.
But she's in showbiz.
She puts her name and face
out there to do business.
It's hardly fair for her to turn around
and claim to be a private citizen now.
I disagree.
The stalkerish photos taken without her
knowledge won't hold up to scrutiny.
Well, you're free to hold that opinion.
But this concerns two public figures—
Kana Arima-san and Director Shima.
We're only reporting the fact
that they went into an apartment together.
There isn't a single word
about what happened next.
That's for the readers
to judge for themselves.
Even if nothing happened,
the readers will assume Arima is guilty.
Doesn't it hurt your conscience
to saddle a high school kid with that?
It does, but that comes with
the territory of being a reporter.
You may think we're a tabloid rag
that runs worthless articles,
but our readers are the ones
who want to know these things.
Supply meets demand, plain and simple.
Compared to irresponsible
posts on the internet,
our stories hurt the subject less
since we talk to them beforehand.
Most tabloids employ
twenty to thirty writers.
They're not assigned beats
such as politics or entertainment.
As long as they meet their story quota,
they're free to cover whatever they want.
And yet, there are those that go
out of their way to cover showbiz.
Some feel guilty about it but pursue
entertainers to put food on the table,
while others get a kick out of being
the one to take down somebody famous.
This guy here is probably the former.
He zeroed in on the story in front
of him because that's just his job.
In that case...
Can we get down to business now?
My deadline is coming up.
Tell me about your friend Arima-san—
I've got nothing to say
to you about Arima.
Wha?
So, what, you came here just to complain?
This is hardly respectable behavior.
I do have something else for you.
A story that people will care about
a hell of a lot more than Arima's.
A story that'll hurt
the feelings and pride of many,
and one that'll pique
the morbid curiosity of the public.
A story that, if you write it,
will be an abomination in print.
True Showbiz Weekly Street Date
If I turn on the TV, they're going
to be talking about the scandal.
And if I go online,
I bet I'll see a barrage of abuse.
Screw it!
On to our latest story.
We have shocking news regarding the idol
who was tragically taken from us too soon.
She left a profound mark on
the hearts of many, including our viewers.
What...
The Legendary Idol
True Showbiz Weekly
According to today's issue
of True Showbiz Weekly,
Breaking: Ai of B-Komachi's Son Comes Forward
Ai Hoshino-san, the idol
who was murdered 14 years ago,
had two young twins
and was killed by an enraged fan
who'd found out about her children.
Technically, there is one way to stop it.
Both of Ai-san's twins are
currently active in show business.
They've overcome tragedy
to follow in their mother's—
A barter story—replace one
scandal with another one.
Had Twins at Sixteen
Who was B-Komachi's Ai?
Lawyer A
Children born to a de-facto marriage
are also considered illegitimate.
Had Twins at Sixteen
Who was B-Komachi's Ai?
Lawyer A
Children born to a de-facto marriage
\h\hare also considered illegitimate.
I remember being devastated.
She was one of my favorite idols.
The problem is with
the entire entertainment industry.
Agencies aren't supervising
their minors as they should.
I still listen to B-Komachi's
songs sometimes.
I used to do the "my sign is B"
thing all the time.
My sign is B!
Breaking
Murder from 14 Years Ago
Son Speaks
Historical Footage
Ai of B-Komachi's Secret Child
Her Son, Aqua Hoshino, Reflects on Past
Ai-san was murdered in her home
by a fan fourteen years ago,
sending all of Japan into mourning.
[Chat] Discussing the Recent News
Hiro's Room
1.62 million subscribers
What do you make of the news
about the idol who gave birth
to twins at sixteen?
Becoming an idol
is a gamble with awful ROI.
It's not something
an intelligent person would do.
So, yeah, stupid people do stupid things.
But that's just, like, my opinion, man.
For You      Trending       News      Sports
Trending in Japan
1. Ai
2. B-Komachi
3. Chainsaw-san
4. Ruby Hoshino
5. Aqua Hoshino
The culprit took his own life
right afterward,
so the incident was never fully resolved.
The revelation of her secret children
has cast a whole new light on the case.
B-Komachi's Ai
Aqua Hoshino-san, Ai-san's son,
told the magazine the following.
Reporter: "Why did you choose
to reveal this information?"
B-Komachi's Ai
Aqua Hoshino
Ruby Hoshino
"I wanted to explain the matter
in my own words
before it became public knowledge."
"I wanted to explain the matter in my own
words before it became public knowledge."
Wait, so the guy
who killed Ai knew about this?
Aqua Hoshino? Wasn't he on Love for Real?
She had twins, right?
Who's the father?
I read the wiki page about the murder...
No wonder.
Some genes, huh?
Yeah, she's super cute.
Way to promote himself.
So Ruby's working under the B-Komachi
name to carry on her mom's legacy?
That's so touching!
Frankly, it ruined things for me.
Ai was a legend, after all. I feel like
my beliefs have been shattered.
Should I just forget everything
and try to live my own life?
Or should I...
Oh...
Aqua-kun decided to do things that way.
In that case...
I'll do things my way, too.
Aqua-kun.
Once this is all over,
let's go have parfaits again.
Let's eat lots of good food,
go traveling,
and spend our lives together...
Forever.
Aqua-kun?
I'm sorry!
I wasn't looking!
Are you okay?!
I-I'm fine.
I'm truly sorry, really!
It's all right.
That startled me.
I thought someone had pushed me.
You're my hero, huh, Aqua-kun?
Whenever I'm in trouble,
you're there for me.
But...
Given what's in the news now,
you shouldn't be out and about.
Akane.
Please don't do anything dangerous.
Why do you say that?
Why...
Why are you here?
You don't have work today.
If you just got out of school,
why aren't you in uniform?
What do you mean,
"Don't do anything dangerous"?
You're talking like you
know what I'm doing.
You really are too smart
for your own good.
Aqua-kun... This isn't okay.
You've crossed the line.
When did you start bugging me?
Not long after Love for Real.
I thought you might find
a lead of some sort,
and I wanted to track you if you
made contact with the mastermind.
I guess I made the right call back then.
I thought we were building
a good relationship as equals.
But I was wrong, wasn't I?
I thought you trusted me more than this.
I know about your situation.
I've always said I'd help you, haven't I?
If you'd just asked me,
I would've worn hundreds of these for you!
I'm not an object or your sniffer dog!
I'm a human being!
But this shows that you
don't see me as one!
If you'd only asked, I would've gladly...
That's a lie.
Akane, if you'd known about this,
you definitely would've done
something to counter it.
This says it all.
You found information about my dad,
but you were intending
to settle things yourself.
I wasn't! I was just...
Explain this, then.
What exactly were you
going to do with this?
I was planning to talk to him.
It's just, anything could happen.
He's a murderer and all.
I was only going to use it
as a last resort.
I brought it to protect myself—
Akane.
Stay out of this.
I'll stop GPS tracking you.
And I'll get out of your life forever.
So stop putting yourself in danger.
You say you were only using me,
yet you're letting me down gently.
If only you'd asked me to go with you...
I'd even follow you into hell.
I would never take you there.
I'll go on my own.
Oh... You've made up your mind, huh?
There's just one thing
I want to say to you.
You chose the wrong path, Aqua-kun.
Trust me, I know.
So there's no stopping you anymore?
So I couldn't save you.
I don't care if it was arrogant of me.
I wanted so badly to save you!
This is for the best.
Now Akane won't be in harm's way
or have to get her hands dirty for me.
The happy times are over.
There's no going back for me.
I'll have to follow this path
to the bitter end.
Hikaru Kamiki!
I know exactly how
to make him suffer the most!
Episode 31
Breakdown
Translation
Sriram Gurunathan
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check
Gabriella Alabanza
Translation Check
Michelle Tymon