It's fine. There's nothing to worry about.
Luida and Brad and the others
will protect us. Okay?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Maybe you don't have to fight now?
Thanks.
But I've already made up my mind.
I'm protecting this ship
and everyone on it.
Despite being a softie
who can't even kill his enemies?
Undertaker, are your eyes okay?
Yeah. I can see, more or less.
More or less?
What's all that?
Flash-bangs I found in the warehouse.
Better than nothing.
Oh, we found a motorcycle, too!
I wanted to try riding it. Vroom, vroom!
Here!
I hate to admit it, but I have no chance
against the blue-haired freak.
That goes double for Mr. Softie here.
According to your explanation,
this "Legato Bluesummers" fellow
can use telekinesis to control
other people's bodies. Is that right?
How do you even beat someone like that?
I will... do the best I can do.
Even if that results
in you getting carted off?
So then they wake up Knives and...
I see.
Maybe it'd be best just
to kill you here and now.
Wait, what?!
Without this idiot running amok,
Knives won't be able to come back.
Noman's Land can safely await
the arrival of the colony fleet.
But...
I'll make sure your funeral
is dignified and solemn.
What do you say, Needle-noggin?
That's "keeping it in the house."
Huh?
Oh, wait, no! It's "self-serving."
The Undertaker killing someone
to do their funeral is very self-serving!
Ammo! Come on.
Oh, right!
I was just kidding.
Of course you were! Hornfreak said it all.
"I see. Now you're Vash the Stampede's
sworn ally, are you?"
Right, Meryl?
That's right, Milly. The Undertaker
wouldn't harm his own friend.
Of course not! He spent more than
two years looking for Vash because...
Indeed, because they're friends!
I never said a word.
Stop wrapping this up without me.
Thanks, Wolfwood.
For what?! I didn't say anything!
They're here.
Nai...
Target in range.
Fire!
Beginning assault.
That didn't do anything!
As expected, missiles are useless.
We'll have to take out their SSG.
SSG?
Their storm shield generator.
I hope they've taken shelter.
SSG down! We're losing shields!
Incoming flying object identified!
Signal: July!
The tower of JuLai?!
That's the Ark!
Intercept them!
It takes 30 minutes to recharge.
Our shields won't last long either.
Then get us close already, Doctor.
That's what I had in mind.
Look! Here they come!
Listen up, everyone!
We're taking them down!
To protect Noman's Land!
Right!
Shields down.
Okay, give me control!
Don't push it too far.
All right, time to play!
All units, spread out!
Time to move.
You go on ahead.
Vash...
Vash the Stampede.
The fool who voluntarily
gave up being a god.
The fact that we need the likes of you
to bring Lord Knives back is...
offensive.
Let's go. Don't waste my time.
I can't go with you.
You get it, don't you?
Oh?
And what is Vash the Stampede,
the man who can't kill, going to do?
You're going down!
Sorry about that.
I'm a naughty boy, aren't I?
Always up to no good.
I guess that's how I ended up here.
Even if you've had enough,
you never get out of this hell.
Damn it all. What a shitshow to put on.
I'm pulling the curtains on you,
you lousy ham!
Damn it.
I guess not being able to see
is kind of a weakness after all.
So it goes.
Well? Aren't you going to shoot?
Stop.
Stop or I really will.
If you truly want to stop me, aim here.
I knew you couldn't do it.
Playtime is over.
I will take you to our god.
Two, for now.
Doctor, can you hear me?
Come get us already.
Amazing! This is incredible!
You really are Lord Knives's
little brother after all!
How much can you resist? Can you move?
Let's try it out!
Nice! Very nice!
Vash...
Meryl, is that...
Just like in JuLai.
You're not getting away.
I told you not to push it!
If we take a direct hit,
not even this ship can...
Shut up, pops.
"Pops"?!
That's what they're targeting!
Not a chance!
That's nothing!
What?!
That idiot!
Nice! I knew you could do it!
More! Show me more, Vash the Stampede!
Ow...
What are you doing?
Who said it was playtime?! Ugh!
Thanks...
I almost crushed something
precious to our lord.
Don't ever forget that you're a pawn.
Get in.
We're leaving.
We still only have two!
That's enough for now.
With Vash, we have enough to awaken him.
The Ark has also been hit.
There is no further need to fight. Get in.
Needle-noggin...
Captain! Main guns are online!
Do we shoot?!
Vash...
It's gone quiet.
Is it over?
Nicholas the Punisher.
Traitor to our god.
Are you here to get killed?
I've never betrayed anyone. I did my job.
The contract is done.
Now I'm Nicholas D. Wolfwood.
He's right, Bluesummers.
This is no time to start a fight.
Then why are you here at all?
Huh?
Dunno. I just kind of followed.
What an idiot.
And what about you?
Do you want to work
for Lord Knives again?
No way. I already did my fair share.
I just want to watch.
Will humanity survive, or perish?
Will the paradise of plants
come to be, or will it not?
An observer, then.
Fine. Keep those eyes peeled.
How much longer, Doctor?
It's ready.
Hurry! Wake Lord Knives up!
Let us begin.
Gate connected: Vash the Stampede.
We did it!
Welcome back, Lord Knives!
Lord Knives, are you okay?
Does anything hurt?
Let me be alone with Vash.
What's up with his hair color?
The same thing happened
to Needle-noggin. I mean, to Vash.
The black represents fatigue.
The Independents don't
have infinite power.
Here.
No need.
You must be running low.
Don't push yourself too hard.
No need.
Let me know when that changes.
What happens when they get tired?
Their bodies will shut down,
the same as yours would.
As Knives and Vash
continue to use their powers,
at some point, their hair
will be completely black, and—
They'll die?
Death is inevitable for all living things.
The only difference is
when and how it arrives.
Can you hear me, Vash?
The Big Fall of 150 years ago...
That was a failure.
This time, I will succeed.
I will destroy the humans and
create a paradise for our brethren.
A do-over of the genesis.
In the distant past, humans
on Earth forgot their god
and enjoyed a hedonistic life.
To cleanse them, god sent a massive flood.
A select few humans and animals
boarded a ship to survive.
And that's the Ark.
Knives will wipe out
all humanity on this planet.
The only ones to survive
will be those aboard the Ark and...
The plants.
But he's got no way to summon
a huge flood on this planet.
What's Knives trying to do?
I will call rain down
upon this dry planet...
A rain of a thousand immigrant ships.
A "Genesis Flood" Big Fall.
I...
I will stop you.
As many times as it takes.
I will stop you, Nai.
I see.
Keep your eyes on my brother.
No rest, no sleep.
Yes, on my life!
Stay there. Until the last moment.
Stay by my side, Vash.
The darkest hour is just before the dawn.
Our dawn is nigh.
My brethren. Tesla.
I will take in your power...
to fulfill our greatest aspiration!
What's going on?!
Comms are down?
The world is being disconnected.
Even if there is no answer there.