Step right up and have a look...
It's time for Yamishibai.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
Following
This is the story of a certain woman
who runs a tailoring shop...
Musubu Tailor
Excuse us.
Welcome.
Do you need something patched up?
Well, I was hoping you could make this
kimono into a necktie or something.
Isn't the pattern wonderful?
I know it'll look great on you, Ryuuta!
Let me just take a look.
This is a fine piece,
but I do see holes and stains.
Oh... the price isn't a concern.
And I'll wait as long as it takes.
It's a kimono with... a lot of history.
There are lots just like it
at your place, though.
In that case, I'll see to it.
Thank you very much.
I wonder if it belonged to
someone important to him.
This material really is gorgeous,
now that I get another look at it.
The dying and pattern, too.
That's an odd place for all these seams.
They're very sturdy...
Please... Please... Please...
I want to follow him.
I can't stop worrying about him...
He always attracts the
wrong kind of attention...
This kimono... belonged to you?
Yes.
All of this... is my own hair, and that
of someone I care very much about.
All of my kimonos contain hair
from the both of us.
Please... include the hair, whatever
you do, so we won't be separated...
It's my bond to him...
Here you are!
This is the finished product.
It looks fantastic!
I'm glad you like it.
That's so nice! I want something like it!
There's plenty of material left,
so can I have something, too?
Ryuuta? Ryuuta, pay attention to me!
I hope you don't mind me asking, but
that kimono belonged to your wife, yes?
She must've really loved it.
I can tell it was handled with great care.
That's right.
My Kimiyo loved kimonos...
But I was bad at storing them,
and now they're all worn out.
I feel so guilty...
Ryuuta? Behind you!
There's something behind you!
No! Don't look at me!
Go away. He can't even see you.
No way... No way!
I'll take better care of this.
That way I'll always have Kimiyo with me.
That's right, Ryuuta. I'll be
following you forever and ever...
I subtly sewed some of the hair
into the back of the necktie.
That our little secret, ma'am.
Forever and ever and ever...
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
The end.