Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
Smooth as ever, I escort you
And this voice, seducing you
Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
I am your ace darlin'
Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
Please Please
Whisper just to me, call my name
You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
Hey, girl
Look this way!
I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
So take my hand and let's roll
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
It's a spell that makes your heart race
We can't go back
You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
Sweetie honey
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
The overwhelming desire
to make people happy.
When that feeling that's usually
aimed at thousands of fans
suddenly gets directed to one person...
Fans Are Terrifying Creatures
I'm sorry. I just reacted.
Eep...
After that happened, I...
You can't be serious.
Do you know how many gazillions of yen
a single karat of Tamon-kun is worth?
And here you are basically
giving it away for free.
Church of Tamon
You're destroying the market!
Unconditional love for Tamon Fukuhara
Rawr
Please have more respect for Tamon-kun!
I totally lost it.
Tamon-kun belongs to everyone!
Menacing
And then I bizarrely made Tamon-kun
review the 100 Tamon Articles of Faith.
Tamon-kun belongs to everyone...
Tamon-kun's dreams must be
prioritized above all else!
prioritized above all else.
Okay! Bye!
Please excuse me!
I let my rage take over me
and ran right out of there.
Maybe I should be happy about the fact
that he personally showed me
full-on fan service...
Hnnngggghhhh
But I really think that someone who's
supposed to be a world-famous star
shouldn't be handed out so easily!
All of humanity needs
to respect Tamon-kun!
Tamon! Tamon! Tamon!
Why is he doing so much for me?
I hope that Kinoshita-san will
continue coming over forever.
I love you, Kinoshita-san.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
...Hngh!
Thwap
Ain't no
Ain't no way!
waaaaay~
He's just anxious after
losing the competition for center.
And since he's letting all that anxiety
explode in front of me,
it must mean that he
has no one else he can talk to.
Maybe things aren't going well
with the people around him after all.
I'll go give the Gorilla some
cannoli and bombolones!!
I'll go give the Gorilla
some cannoli and bombolones!
Fujita-san seems as busy as ever.
Malice...
Their producer seems super scary.
Go buy some butter sandwiches!
Go buy some
butter sandwiches...
Ouri-kun is less a friend,
and more a rival and a gorilla.
I'll go give the Gorilla
some cannoli and
bombolones!!
Malice...
Go buy some
butter sandwiches...
I'd like to do whatever I can
for him, but...
Plink
Sob Sob
I don't think I can make it today...
I caught a cold...
I'm sorry
What?!
Cool Sheet
That's rough, Yuina.
The King of Elixirs
Yuina
_P Yummy, thanks
Oh, well. I guess I'll have to
spend the day alone.
Goodness!
Goodness! I must admit,
that certainly was a close one!
There were more Kanpyo-chans
in places I wasn't aware of.
If I missed out on the rare official merch
for my oshi, Kanpyo Roll-chan,
I would absolutely never be
able to live with myself!
She showed such bravery as she quivered
in the prize machine enclosure all alone!
I got this close to crying at the sight,
but I gave my tear ducts a stern pep talk
and successfully rescued her
from her glass prison!
Crane games ought to be a cruel mistress,
yet I was grabbed one after another
as if it were an AYCE, and as a fan,
I do feel a bit conflicted about this.
I must be the one to let the admins know
just how in demand Kanpyo-chan is!
The world desires Kanpyo-chan!
The seven seas desire Kanpyo-chan!
Have I ever experienced
such a fruitful day off before?
Actually, I may well have.
But that doesn't matter right now.
I must spend every last second rescuing
Kanpyo Roll-chans from glass prisons.
Relaxed
Hustle
That is my sworn duty for today!
Pull
Onward ho! Until my time
of leisure comes to an end!
Pull
Knowing that all of the other Kanpyo fans
are also acting with happiness
and gratitude in their hearts
naturally gives...
I get you... The love
that we have for our oshis.
Kappa Rolls
Gloomyhara-san?!
What are you doing here?
Huff...
Kinoshita-san...
I'm so happy to run into you
in a place like this...
Huff...
Kinoshita-san...
Inch...
H-Hello...
Do you have the day off today?
Inch...
Er, yes...
Because... You think I'm hot.
If I get too close, he'll start giving out
Hottiehara-kun for free again.
Wobble
Kinoshita-san, please wait...
I'm in a hurry!
Kinoshita-san!
Vrooooooom
Huh?!
His paper bag turned all fancy
and he suddenly got faster!
He caught up...?!
Konk
Craaash
Drench
I-It's so hot...
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
It's a sauna under here
Huff...
How could you run around
in midsummer heat wearing that?
What're you going to do
if Tamon-kun gets heatstroke?!
I'm sorry. I'll be more careful.
Do you have the day off as well,
Gloomyhara-san?
I have some downtime
from work right now...
I'm sorry that someone like me
was having fun.
Oh, no. I'm actually glad that
you have some hobbies.
Sometimes there're kappa
wrapped in really unique ways...
Roll...
They're rare ones.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Rare
Super Rare
Those are the figures that're
at his place, aren't they?
Tamon-kun's using the money we offer him
to buy himself Kappa Rolls for self-care.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Rare
Super Rare
Moved...
That makes me happy.
I just wanted to give you one
because I got a dupe...
Why did you run away like that?
You're actually about 100 cm taller
than we think you are.
So having you run at me when you're
that big is extremely intimidating.
Image 80 cm
Wait, I shouldn't be talking to him!
I shouldn't be interacting
with my oshi outside of work!
This is a
crazy otaku
I'm sorry for
what I did
I'll be paraded around town,
guilty of crazy fan crimes.
It's a crazy fan!
She's guilty!
Well, I'll be going now!
Make sure you properly recharge
and good luck at work!
Step
Ah!
Um... would you like
to have lunch toge...
Absolutely not.
Ruthless
I guess you really do
just see me as trash...
I got too cocky. I guess I'll die now.
Please stop!
Only love, acclaim, and cheers are allowed
to be pointed at Tamon-kun!
Limp
Not this!
Eek
Today's my oshi activities day!
I'm making my pilgrimage
and going to places you've
already been to, Tamon-kun.
That sounds even better.
I'll give you a tour!
Bang!
Boom
He doesn't get it at all...
This is...
The place we had a location
shoot at the other day.
Yes. It's a very popular shop
right now thanks to you.
One bite of a sandwich here helps you feel
that Tamon-kun is real and in this world.
When these two worlds that would usually
never intertwine hit your tastebuds,
Swoon
what fills your mouth is never-ending love
and just a little bit of guilt.
O-Oh, I see...
And what are they doing over there?
I feel the aura he left behind.
You can feel the negative ions.
They are respecting
the ground Tamon-kun stood on.
It's just so cool.
The ground...
Every single spot our oshi has been
becomes a power spot.
I don't really get it,
but if it makes everyone that happy,
maybe I'll crawl around on all fours
at the next location shoot.
I love you.
But please don't.
Ta-daaah!
Let's eat.
Okay.
Click
Is it fun taking photos of me
with the sandwiches?
Click
It's the funnest thing in the world.
Would this make it even more fun?
You can take as many as you'd like.
Tamon-kun
So many Tamon-kuns?!
They're all Tamon-kun?!
So hot! I'm fizzling out!
Fizzling Out
Huh?
Kinoshita-san?!
Kinoshita-san?! Where'd you go?
If someone who wants
to express themselves is an artist
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Utage's remains
and someone who wants
to entertain others is an entertainer,
it goes without saying
which group Tamon-kun belongs to.
Japanese Instruments
The F/ACE section's gotten even bigger!
The world is catching up to F/ACE!
Congratulations, world!
Tamon-kun is so hot!
Huh...
And yet, this is...
Boom
Hey, that's cute.
This...
cannot be allowed!
Staaaare
Hey, are you having fun?
Er, y-yes.
Boom
How can I make him understand?!
That Hottiehara-kun mustn't be handed out
just to sate one girl's personal desires!
Oh, I know!
Gasp
I have an extra ticket
since Yuina wasn't able to come along.
Center Competition Documentary
Yuina
Gloomyhara-san! Let's go see a movie!
Huh?!
If you don't mind me
coming along, of course.
Oooooooh
Center Competition Documentary
Siiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiigh
They were given the name "F/ACE" so they
could become the face of a generation.
I've seen this movie ten times
and cried ten times,
but it might be torture
for Tamon-kun to watch it...
Our coverage covers
the announcement of their new song...
But even then, I want him to know...
This competition to choose the center
is a challenge that'll
take F/ACE to new heights.
That I like the Tamon-kun who tries hard
for everyone. Not just for me.
Bring it on.
Acting cool isn't
the only part of our job.
Come at me with everything you've got.
That he's that cool.
The title of the new song is "RAIN."
It takes the regrets a man feels when
he realizes the weight of what he's lost
and turns it into a lyrical melody...
a ballad about heartbreak.
And for the first episode...
I was honestly surprised
that we were repicking the center.
But F/ACE is a group
that's forever evolving,
so this is just a hurdle
that I need to get over.
Great job.
RAIN starts falling
Washing everything away
Why couldn't I realize it back then?
The sky in a morning without you—
so carelessly clear
The RAIN won't stop
Even if you're suffering,
please don't ever forget...
Under the sky, I start running
That your dream
is right there, Tamon-kun.
I want you to see that.
Gah! That was
the absolute best of the best!
Waaaaaaaaah!!
Were you watching carefully,
Gloomyhara-san?
Now do you understand
how valuable Tamon-kun is?
Er, no...
I honestly barely looked at the screen.
It was too much torture.
What?!
It's no use...
But...
It looked like you
were having a lot of fun...
and you seemed really happy.
You weren't making those expressions
before seeing the movie.
Well, that's because... um...
It's just because
I love Tamon-kun so much.
I'd love to see that again.
If I make my dream come true,
would that make you as happy
as you are right now again?
I'd be the happiest girl in the world!
Maybe he does understand a little bit...
Oh, yeah. I forgot about this.
You can have this.
Oh, thank you very much...
Dash
What?! Wait, isn't this the rare one?
Gloomyhara-san!
Decorate your bathroom with Kappa Rolls.
You're in top form today, Tamon-kun.
He's exploding with sexiness.
I can feel my collagen
replenishing itself just watching him.
I thought he'd be dwelling about the fact
that he lost the center position more,
but he got right back onto his feet.
He's not even scared to work. Actually...
This is your next job.
Here comes another nervous breakdown.
Okay, I'll do it.
You'll be fine! You don't need
to be so scared...
Wait, what?
Thank you for everything
you do, Fujita-san.
I need to thank Kinoshita-san.
Because of her,
I've got one less bald spot.
Huh? He's not answering?
Huh?!
Good evening.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
You're Kinoshita-san... right?
You're Tamon's housekeeper.
I was just trying to go
to Tamon-kun's place as usual,
and then Keito-kun greeted me
for some reason.
I-It's a pleasure to meet you.
Tamon-kun
National Treasure
So hot
Tamon-kun is a national treasure!
Keito Tachibana-kun.
Trusted by the Church of Tamon followers,
he loves his group mates and has
the friendliest, most relatable persona!
What is F/ACE's leader
and current center doing here?!
I mean, he probably lives here,
but what's he doing in front of me?!
Want to come over to my place right now?
Er, I don't mean anything weird by that.
Tamon and Ouri are also over right now.
You know them, right?
Will you let me thank you for
taking care of the others all the time?
I wouldn't say I've done that much...
It's not like I could just go
into Tamon-kun's place so...
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Tamon-kun's
Apartment
Here we are. I'd like to thank you,
but I can really only offer you tea.
Um...
You live next door to Tamon-kun.
I never even realized...
Well, we do usually go home
at separate times.
Come in.
Oh, thank you...
It's dark. It's immediately dark.
Poverty
Wow, the layout of his place
is exactly the same as next door.
Gloomy, gloom.
I can tell which belong
to whom in a single glance.
Time Is\hMoney
A Yen Saved Is a Yen Earned
Okay, everyone have a seat.
Work Hard and
Practice Frugality
Huh?
What the hell are you doing here?
I bet you came to see me—
Absolutely not.
I'm sorry I couldn't answer the door.
I called everyone over.
First, could you take a look at this?
Do you mind explaining this?
This is from yesterday?! When did he...
The last time I spotted you two,
it was at our apartment building,
so I let it slide...
But are you really just a housekeeper?
You guys met outside again?
Who do you think you are?!
Wait. What do you mean, "again"?
W-We just happened to run into each other!
It really was a coincidence.
Though I had fun.
Wha—
Well, I invited her over
to my parents' place twice.
Hey.
Seriously?
Work Hard and
Practice Frugality
She's got you both wrapped
around her finger. How pathetic.
I guess things are worse
than I suspected.
Kinoshita-san.
Yes?
We're trying to become world famous.
Our first album was a hit
and our Dome performance being
a success put us in the mainstream.
Our appearances on TV have
also been growing steadily.
This is our moment of truth.
I'm absolutely going to make F/ACE
a group that represents this generation!
Keito-kun...
He really is a leader that cares
for his group like we thought.
We're gonna swindle
the fans out of all their money,
and I'm gonna go down
in history as a millionaire.
Shock!
Ke
Keke
Kekeke...
As you know, these two are
the dual poster boys for F/ACE.
Frugality Is a Virtue
These two can make or break our group.
Flash
Stop deceiving our precious
golden geese, you wicked fangirl!
Wicked fangirl! Wicked fangirl!
Golden
Golden... geese?
Golden...
Geese
Really? This is what he's like?
Fans like you need to stop meddling
and just quietly act as our sustenance.
A fan that doesn't know
their place is worthless.
I'm not gonna let that slide,
you old scrooge!
Who're you calling old? I'm only twenty.
Excuse me...
Could you not...
speak to my fan like that?
I know there are certain people
that you dislike, Keito-kun...
But you really shouldn't
say things like that.
I actually agree with him for once.
I always thought that was rather
shitty of you, you shithead!
What?!
Don't act all surprised!
I never say the same thing twice.
You literally just said "shit" twice.
So I guess things weren't going well
with the other members after all...
I only said the truth.
Actually, they're not
getting along at all.
Shake
Quiver
Is that seriously the extent
of your vocabulary?
There's no way Tamon-kun can be
mentally stable in this situation.
You guys, violence is ba...
Shut up!
You stay out of this.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm sorry that
my whole existence is a burden.
But it's not like an outsider like me
can butt into their problems...
Not to mention...
Fans are terrifying creatures.
They're ruthless beasts who engage
in bloody quarrels with each other.
Waaaaaaaaah
Rumble
They rival the CIA in gathering intel...
Keito-kun!
Stick...
and tailing others.
They're insane!
Tremble
Wait, I have heard that a certain part of
Keito-kun's fandom is off their rockers.
Are there actually fans like that?
Shake Shake
There are!
Point
As a prime example, this woman has
clearly infiltrated your private lives!
Point
She's an evil fan who will
lead you both to your demise!
As proof, you both failed
in the competition for center!
You two should've been able to...
Keito-kun?
If you mean well at all,
never come near these two again.
Hey! You don't have the right
to enforce anything like that!
This is an order as the leader.
It's true that Tamon-kun
wasn't able to become the center.
Tamon-kun realizes that...
more than anyone else.
It's true that I'm a Tamon-kun fan.
I can't blame anyone
for thinking that about me.
Under One Sky, We
Strive for the Same Goal
Thinking logically, he's 100% right.
I should back away.
But...
If I make my dream come true,
would that make you as happy
as you are right now again?
Even then...
Tamon-kun's worries,
his smile, his hard work...
I can't imagine they're for nothing.
It's true that I'm a fan.
And I'm always conflicted about whether
it's actually bad for me to be around him.
But...
Blackfin Sea Bass
Stingy and Frugal Are
Not the Same
Constant Dripping
Wears Away
the Stone
Whenever I'm around Gloomyhara-san,
it's solely as his housekeeper.
And as his housekeeper,
I've done everything I can for him.
Ugh, what am I even doing?
I had just decided that I'd keep
my distance from Tamon-kun.
Maybe I am just a crazy fan after all.
Um... And your manager is
the one who officially hired me, so...
Our manager authorized this?
What the hell is Fujita-san thinking?
Kinoshita-san!
Fujita-san?!
Oh, there you are. Thank goodness.
Hm? What are you all doing here?
How did you know I was here?
I found this in front
of Keito's apartment.
Tamon-kun
How do you keep dropping that thing?
I actually have a request
for you, Kinoshita-san.
Will you participate in
F/ACE's training camp?!
What?!
Training camp?
It's going to be for a show.
To hit the ground running
as the new F/ACE,
we're going to have them
strengthen their bonds.
I wanna watch that.
We call it "F/ACE's Super Exciting
Summer Trip (TBD)".
Talk about lame.
Stop picking your ears
in my damn apartment.
Hey!
Wait a minute.
I have a ton of questions...
But let's start with what's going on here.
The part-timer we hired to help
with the show won't be able to make it.
And as you know, the real F/ACE is a mess.
Don't call us a mess!
And we don't want others
finding out about our mess!
Grawr
So rather than hiring someone
who you don't know temporarily,
it's safer to bring this woman along
because she's in the know already?
Exactly.
But this is too sudden!
I have no idea how to do
talent agency work.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
I'll make sure to contact your parents
and it'll just be supplementary work,
so we can't pay much,
but we'll definitely pay you.
It's summer break, right?
Blackfin Sea Bass
You have time, don't you?
Time Is Money
You want money, don't you?!
W-Well, yes, but...
This is bothering Kinoshita-san...
Tamon.
If we hire someone new, you won't be
able to let your guard down for a second.
Today's Savings Is
Tomorrow's Happiness
Are you okay with that?
I guess we don't have a choice, then.
Tamon's true personalty hasn't been
revealed to the rest of the world.
That must mean
you've kept your mouth shut.
I guess I can trust you there.
I'm also against doing anything risky...
Wait a minute...
But fans are still rotten anyway.
I'll reveal who you really are during
the two-night, three-day camp.
I can't keep up with all of this.
Are you serious?
She'll do fine. Let's take her.
Don't decide for m—
I'd also have you come along
rather than someone we don't know...
Ooh!
Ooooooh
That's that.
Hell yeah!
We'll be in your care.
What?!
I'll fill you in on the details later.
We'll be leaving in three days,
so please be ready by then!
Dash!!
Fujita-san!
Don't go selling private photos of us.
Glare...
I will not!
I'll bring you around
by the time the trip is over!
Super Excited
Around to what?!
A multi-day trip. I'm gonna throw up.
Wanna Throw Up...
Tamon-kun is a god!
This is a mess!
I guess summer's nowhere near over yet.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michelle Tymon
\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
\h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
Translation Check:
Alicia Ashby
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
Uh huh...
Na na na...
I wonder what the world
would look like without you
When I look back,
you've always been by my side
Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
A speedboat sails across the endless skies
An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
Like a wilted flower coming back to life
A light that shines
Through the impossibly dark night
(Light of your soul)
I wanted to grasp it
(I love you so)
So I strived for it
Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom