Aniki, save us!
Sh-Shocker's after you? Why?
H-Hold up!
I'm Shocker t—
Aniki?!
We're on the same—
Dammit. I-I don't know what's going on...
But we're bailing through the window!
Y-Yessir!
Ow, ow, ow...
Get up!
We gotta hurry!
Follow me!
Right!
Sorry...
Go on without me!
Stupid! This is no time
to start wimping out!
He's right!
I guess this is it.
Aniki?!
I'll take them all—
There you are, Shocker!
Wha?!
Y-You...
Dammit!
Rider...
Punch, right?
Punch!
Rider...
Punch.
Punch!
Rider...
And punch.
Punch!
D...
Damn! He really is legit strong!
He's a normal human...
A human who's just
playing pretend, and yet...
Hey.
Whoa! It's me!
It's you?!
Uh, sorry about that.
It's fine. But I was hoping
to ask you for something...
Look...
can we crash at your place?
Why?!
Because Shocker's trying to kill us!
You're in Shocker!
Yeah, but they're the ones
whose lives are in danger.
A-Are you asking me to hide them?
Please!
The Combat Girls are Shocker Combatants?!
Yeah.
But they're the top idol
group at the moment...
I don't know the specifics,
but apparently their
manager-slash-agency head is the Bat Man.
The Bat Man?!
It makes sense. The Spider Man
had a human form too,
and we knew that monsters had
infiltrated society to some degree...
But the entertainment industry?
And why become the head of an idol agency?
I'm not too sure what he's actually after.
The Combat Girls...
I'll have to dig into this.
And so will I.
Yukarisu?
Care for a refill on your coffee?
Oh, thanks.
I overheard what you were saying...
And more and more of what happened
is coming back to me.
I think the Bat Man is the one who
made me into a Shocker combatant.
The sound of his voice...
I'll never forget it.
The Bat Man...!
You're getting a little full of
yourself, you puny human.
What's the matter?
All done fighting?
Excuse me, can I get some more coffee?
Coming!
Well, I need to go.
Okay.
Tojima-san?
During the other battle...
I turned away and ran
from an enemy again.
I'm sorry. If I hadn't...
My desire for revenge overtook me, and I—
We can't defeat Shocker like this!
I don't know how to put this...
But we shouldn't fight on our own.
We need to work together to overcome them.
Tojima-san!
You're right.
Let's beat Shocker, together!
YOU HAVE ONE NEW MESSAGE.
Hate to bug you,
but we're kinda starving here.
Could you bring back something to eat?
What?!
Some smokes too.
Thanks in advance.
Is it from that Nakao person?
This guy...
Why do I have to feed them
on top of everything else?
We do takeout here, y'know.
Don't let up!
That should do it for today.
GOING TO WORK. YOU TWO BETTER
NOT FIGHT! GET ALONG ❤︎
Eat this.
I give thanks for this food.
He's been training me ever since.
I still haven't discovered
the secret to his strength.
You...
You're just a human...
Well, I guess I'm asking,
how are you so strong?
I've just loved fighting since
the day I was born. No idea why.
I encountered Bajiquan at some point,
and poured all that passion into it,
training endlessly.
But...
After mastering my technique,
my battle against myself came to an end,
and then there was no one else to fight.
It felt like my life
had lost all purpose...
when I encountered Sena.
She set fire... to the light of my life!
She lit a fire?
That's right.
From now on, I'll continue to fight
until I can make a bowl of ramen
that will give Sena sublime bliss!
This was my first time
making broth with fish bones...
I think the richer soup I made before
might be more to her liking, though.
Then human strength comes from
the power of the fire in their hearts.
Say, Aniki.
You think he was serious about that?
About what?
What he said.
Where's all your stuff, man?
Now there's nothing to
worry about if I die.
I think so.
I guess he's back.
Damned humans.
Making us chase you around...
H-Help!
Wh-What the hell?!
Idols...
They're all idols.
How'd you find us?!
Because you're part of Shocker!
S-So it's my fault?
Boys, I'm sorry.
Aniki...
You need to get out of here!
Where are you guys?!
A...
...ni...
...ki...
A...
...ni...
...ki...
What is this?
Aniki, this is your chance!
Get out of here!
Hurry!
What's the point of me getting away?!
Just go!
Hurry!
While you can!
No! I can't just abandon you!
Just go, dammit!
You've taken such good
care of us until now...
He's right! This is the least we can do!
Thank you for everything!
Boys...
Just go!
You dumb bastards...
Hey, what's wrong?!
You took too damn long, Rider!
Come on, we gotta go!
Who the hell are you?!
Wh-Who are—
Y-You... are you trying
to ruin the food I bought?!
W-Wait!
Dammit!
Y-You... could you be...?
You're not getting away!
Shit.
Listen. All of you.
Head on back.
He is our prey.
If I can kill a hundred traitors,
I'll be made into a monster.
So, he's mine.
Yeah, I don't think so.
You think there's a point system
to becoming a monster?
Let's see your point card, then.
Wait, you're Thunder Raiko,
the pro wrestler, aren't you?
You are, right?!
This one belongs to me.
And I will become the strongest...
in Shocker!
That's...
Now, piss off! Or you're all dead!
Wh-What are you talking about?
All of you! Get lost!
We'll report you for this!
Are you... actually on our side?!
Okay, now to kill you.
I guess not?!
Why would you betray us,
knowing it means death?
What betrayal?
I never had any orders in the—
Die!
H-He's still standing?!
Kind of... just a... coincidence.
Dammit.
This time...
I'm standing up... on my own!
I-It's you!
Kamen Rider!
All you are is an old fart
that ran off like a coward.
H-How?!
Rider...
Punch!
Looks like she's out cold.
She was damned tough, but you...
You just keep...
I-I... need to tell you something.
What is it?
A...
...ni...
...ki!
Dammit all!
Wh-What's wrong?
I... I... I will...
I'LL FIGHT SHOCKER, TOO!
I'll fight Shocker, too!
Again, you are part of Shocker.
Being the real deal doesn't matter
if you're still too weak.
Please! You gotta train me!
I gotta get stronger!
Ideally someplace out of the way where
Shocker won't find us! In the boonies!
The further away, the better!
You've really got
a lot of nerve, don't you?
Well, yeah...
I'm a gangster, after all.
What? The Bat Man injured Yuriko-san?!
Yes. And there's more to it...
What?!
Do you think... Aniki got away?
Yeah.
I'm sure he's fine...
If the alternative
is dying here, like this...
I'd rather join Shocker, like Aniki did.
Same.
All right, then.
Being in Shocker isn't so bad.
Well... it's technically bad, I guess.
NEXT EPISODE
IT'D BE AN HONOR
TO DIE
AS A RIDER
IT'D BE AN HONOR TO DIE AS A RIDER
ILLUSTRATION BY: BERABOU NA FURAIBOU