Step right up and have a look...
It's time for Yamishibai.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
Dream Connection
This is the story of a high school
student who lives in the dorms...
Someone... collapsed.
Why can't I get out of here?
Yukiya? Yukiya.
Yukiya!
Just a dream...
Dude, you were really freaking out.
S-Sorry. I keep having
the same dream lately...
So you're in the mountains
and can't find your way down?
Yeah. It's the same thing every night.
It's making me not want to sleep.
Wanna do a dream connection with me, then?
Dream... what?
Dream connection.
People who are having nightmares
connect their dreams and help each other.
It's kind of a ritual that
we do back where I'm from.
Where are you from, again?
Look, just humor me.
I've been having weird dreams, too.
I'm in the mountains,
trying to make my way up,
but always find myself back at the base.
The opposite of mine, huh?
That oughta do it.
And that's it?
Yep. Look at mine.
Now our dreams should be connected.
If this works, my dream might help
you make it out of the mountains.
This sure is weird.
But I'd feel rude turning him down.
Maybe this room is
causing my weird dreams.
It's always so dark...
I'm pretty sure it's this path.
So if I go a bit further...
Huh? Animal carcasses?
That's different from how
this usually goes. But it's weird...
Wh-What the...
A different path?
Wh-What?!
It worked! I made it down!
What the...
What?! Who's there?!
What is this?!
Hey! Stay back! Damn it!
No... No...
Yukiya... It's not so bad in that world, huh?
Don't worry. I'll take good care
of you inside my dream.
Hey! First-years! Breakfast time!
Coming!
Man, you guys keep it dark in here.
Huh? Were you...
Kota's the name. Okajima Kota.
Has that always been your name?
Come on, Senpai,
are you still asleep or something?
It's been a while since
I enrolled here, y'know.
Yeah... Yeah, I guess so.
By the way, Senpai,
do you ever dream of the mountains?
Huh? How did you know about that?
Maybe we should connect dreams, then.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
The end.