Wait, not again...
An emergency advisory has been issued
from Liu-An's control tower.
We will now evacuate
from Liu-An. I repeat.
Liu-An?
This is...
EPISODE 18: WORLD WITH A FUTURE
Ready the ship. Immediately.
But... We haven't received clearance
to take off from the control tower.
They issued an emergency advisory.
We'll just have to use our own judgment.
We really are still on Liu-An.
This is before we took off.
We need to hurry,
or the Gnosia infection will...
Jonas is right. Hurry.
Yuri?
Are your injuries okay already?
Hurry!
But...
You're in the military, are you not?
Take the appropriate measures.
As the captain and Yuri just said,
we're going to have to force our way out.
Hey, is this gonna be okay?
We managed to escape onto the ship,
so no bad endings where we
crash in midair, thanks.
But if we wait too long,
the Gnosia will infect us.
Exactly.
Worry not.
The D.Q.O. and I have been companions
on the raft of destiny for centuries now.
She won't sink so easily.
Increasing output. Takeoff underway.
Looks like we made it out okay.
We don't know that just yet.
Whaddya mean?
LeVi. Do you detect any Gnosia on board?
Scanning for Gnosia...
None found.
Yeah! Woohoo!
Confirming that we have
safely escaped Liu-An.
That's great. That means
we're all safe now.
Had we been infected by the Gnosia,
we'd be unable to dock at any port.
B-But where are we going to head to now?
I personally would like to get back
to Glyze as soon as possible.
If you'll entertain a foolish old man's
idea, I believe we should first
alert the military as to the
happenings on Liu-An.
Th-The military?
Is there any point to that?
Well, why don't we all work
this out over some food?
We have time to relax now, don't we?
I need to calmly sort out what's going on.
This is one day before the day
that I kept looping back to.
Essentially, this is day zero.
The real me who was injured and carried
on board should be asleep in the sick bay.
And I'm probably going to wake up
after my treatment is done tomorrow.
Once I wake up, it'll cause a dual
existence, destroying this universe.
But that means I have an extra day to
work with compared to the previous loop.
Wait. The first thing I need to do
is figure out why I'm here at all.
It's still not full.
Then the answer is simple.
There must be some information
here that the Silver Key desires.
Setsu...
Could you bring me that wrench?
S-Sure...
Here.
Thanks.
You're Yuri... right?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Sorry, but I can't see what I'm doing
with your shadow in the way.
Could you move?
Huh? Sorry...
This ship is so old
that there are a lot of things
that bother me as a soldier.
Are they just pretending
not to know...? But...
Er, sorry. I've actually only
looped a few times so far.
Right. There shouldn't be
any Gnosia on this ship.
There'd be no reason
to stay quiet about the loops.
Can I help you?
Er, no...
Setsu.
What's that?
Huh?
We'll be passing through
a debris field soon.
I have a number of checks I want to do
before that, so you'll have to excuse me.
What's going on?
What do we have here?
It's practically bursting.
Huh... I never thought I'd get to
study a living sample like this.
How does it feel to be entirely
at the Silver Key's beck and call?
You never change, Racio.
Huh?
I-I know! Can I give you
a problem to solve?
You're challenging me?
Oh, how you've underestimated me.
Does that mean you accept?
Heh. It does sound entertaining.
After how smooth this leg of the journey
has been, I've grown bored.
That said...
If your problem isn't worth my time,
you'll pay an appropriate price.
I see.
Setsu is supposed to
be looping, and yet...
Right. Either they've lost
their memories...
or they're acting like they have
for some reason.
Hmph. This isn't a problem to be solved
at all. You're merely seeking advice.
I figured you wouldn't
hear me out otherwise.
Well, whatever.
I was bored, so I'll make an exception
and give you your answer.
That said, the answer is quite simple.
Surprisingly so.
Is it?
Indeed.
Let's say that Setsu genuinely
doesn't remember anything.
In that case...
Perhaps Setsu was never
looping in the first place?
What?
Setsu was actually lying
about looping all this time
in order to deceive you.
To win you over to their side.
Setsu... was lying this whole time?
Did you actually take that seriously?
Consider it payback for
what you pulled earlier.
It's quite obviously impossible.
The truth is actually even simpler.
Just think about it.
We're currently in the period of time
before the start point of your loop.
Before...
That's right. Setsu doesn't
have the Silver Key yet.
The Setsu in this world line is the Setsu
from before they started looping.
Ergo,
it's highly likely that the information
you're supposed to obtain lies here.
It's information that can't be gained
on day one or later.
You're amazing...
What?
No matter the world line,
you're always amazing, Racio!
I never could've gotten this far
if it weren't for you.
Thank you!
Hmph.
That's why you're a fool.
If you've realized that much,
you should be able to figure out
that something is still lacking.
Information that I can only get before
Setsu obtains the Silver Key, huh...
Setsu...
Whoa!
Warning. There is an
abnormality in the hull.
Shield damage detected.
Ow...
Setsu...
Setsu!
Hurry up... and run...
Damn it!
It's too late for me... So please...
Setsu... No!
No!
Hurry...
That's what you told me long ago.
Racio!
You're going to need
to use this, aren't you?
I figured I'd save you the trouble
of looking for it. Be thankful.
Racio...
Yuri?
I need you to repeat the following words.
Words...?
Just do it!
Doubt not.
Doubt not...
Fear not.
Fear not...
And know.
And know...
Knowledge...
will save all.
will save all...
Yuri...
With this,
Setsu will be pulled into this mess.
But... I want them to survive.
Looks like we ended up here again.
Setsu...
And the fact that we're here means...
Yuri, take out your Silver Key.
This is...
Well done. The Silver Key is finally
filled with all the information it needs.
Now, the loop can come to an end.
I can finally... pay you back.
Pay me back?
For letting me survive...
For saving me even though
I was fated to die...
I owe you a debt that I want to repay.
That's why I've been
looping all this time.
Now, let's end this.
Open the door.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Now... it's party time!
Party...?
And to get things properly started...
let's hear from Captain Jonas!
Shut yer mouths, shut yer mouths, yeah!
Hey! You're louder than
everyone here, bud.
Shut yer mouths!
Is everyone here?
Then without further ado...
I believe all of you know who I am,
but allow me to introduce myself anyway.
I am Jonas. Yes, Jonas,
the captain of this very ship.
To all of you who have taken refuge from
the turmoil in the Liu-An star system...
There were no Gnosia infectees
when we left Liu-An...
That means I must have
returned to day one again.
We gather here today to celebrate
your safe arrival aboard this ship.
It's okay. You don't need to worry.
But as I humbly stand before you,
I cannot help but think that for all
of us to come together like this
Setsu...
can be nothing short of a miracle.
What?
However, there is one other way
to think about it: this was fate.
Your speech is too damn long!
Yes, our encounter here
was simply meant to be.
Okay! Let's skip straight to the toast!
Cheers!
Hmph... A celebration, eh?
It's probably too early for us
to let our guards down.
There's no guarantee that the other
star systems are safe, is there?
We can worry about that when we get there.
Let's just have some fun for now.
Yeah! You should eat, too, Racio! Here!
You as well, Yuri.
You're pretty thoughtful, Jina.
You like devoting yourself to others?
I just like fattening people up.
Wait, like, as a fetish thing?
No. I just like fattening people up.
O-Oh, I see...
But let's be for real for a minute.
The only reason we're able to relax
like this is because of Setsu.
Yes. I also... look up to Setsu.
They were just amazing
when they saved us in Liu-An.
Thank you. Though I was only
doing my duty as a soldier.
Not to mention, someone also helped me
when we were running away.
And who was that?
I'm not sure...
Anyway, you're a lifesaver, Setsu!
I need to repay you someday.
You can just forget about it.
Actually... I'm pretty sure you will.
Um, excuse me, Yuri...
Huh? Me?
It's hard for me to ask this
with everyone around, but...
Don't tell me...
"Why are there two of you?"
That's what you want to ask, right?
Setsu... Y-Yes, that's exactly right.
Two? What's that supposed to mean?
Don't worry. That problem's
about to be solved right now.
I'm not sure how it even can be solved...
Don't worry, Stella. Just trust me.
All right.
Hey, bud! What's going on here?
Everyone, just stay here and continue
enjoying the food. I'll be right back.
Yuri.
Come with me.
All right.
Aren't you going to eat?
Save some for us...
Well, for Yuri.
Do you remember
what is said to happen
when the Silver Key is filled
with knowledge and information?
It leaves its host and goes to another
dimension in search of a new one.
Yes. And I'm sure that I told you that
it's also the key to solving
the problem you're facing.
First, I need your Key. Make it appear.
Th-This is...
It's just as I thought.
This is a door that allows passage
into a different universe.
A different universe?
The world is the result of
countless branching choices.
Those choices are what shape the future of
the world and the individuals within it—
even fate itself.
The different universe on
the other side of this door
is an entirely separate world
that doesn't affect this universe.
Regardless of the choices made, their
causality will never influence the other.
Think of the save data
files in a video game.
It's basically like that.
Each has the same characters
and the same story,
but they can never
interact with each other.
Do you understand what this means?
If one of me is taken
to the other side of the door,
we won't be able to interact anymore,
and the issue with the dual
existence won't happen.
This is where we say goodbye.
W-Wait!
I know what you were probably thinking.
That both you and I would be
able to escape our loops here.
Am I wrong?
I thought that at first, too.
But we can't.
Because my Silver Key...
isn't full yet.
You understand now, don't you?
It's obvious. Because I—this me—
hasn't given you the Key yet.
Once I take this through to the other
dimension and shut the door behind me...
your loop will end for good.
Don't they always say
to close a door after you open it?
No!
Move your hand.
What's going to happen to you
once you go through there?
I don't know... But it has to be me.
I have to keep looping on the other side
of this door until I'm done—
until I give you the Silver Key
in that other universe.
No...
Please, Yuri.
I don't want all the loops we shared
together to be for nothing.
Setsu...
I'm only here right now because of you.
You saved me.
I was able to live this long
because you were there for me.
So...
It's time for me to repay you.
Setsu...
With a world that you can keep living in.
Because you're precious to me.
Thank you for everything.
Ooh, you're back.
The party ain't over yet!
AFTER DISEMBARKING, SQ LIVED WITH JINA.
AFTER SPENDING SOME TIME AT SCHOOL,
SHE BECAME A PRIVATE DETECTIVE FOR SOME REASON.
Why do you look so down in the dumps?
I don't know what happened, but why
don't you get some food into you?
AFTER SELLING HER "SLIME" TO A BLACK MARKET DEALER
THAT CHIPIE INTRODUCED HER TO, COMET WAS ABLE TO BUY
THE SHIP OF HER DREAMS. ON A PLANET NOW COVERED IN SLIME,
THE BLACK MARKET DEALER'S ADVENTURE BEGINS...
Thanks for everything
you did back there, bud!
You know. When you
saved us all back in Liu-An.
Wait, am I wrong?
"I'M TELLING YOU, BUD! I'M A LITTLE GREY!"
WITH THOSE MYSTERIOUS PARTING WORDS,
SHIGEMICHI WAS NEVER HEARD FROM AGAIN.
There was... someone...
Someone who helped us
all escape, but... I'm sorry.
I can't remember who they are.
AFTER RETURNING TO GLYZE WITH RACIO,
REMNAN BECAME THE LEADER OF A GROUP OF REBELS.
HIS ENEMIES FEARED HIS UNDYING TENACITY AND UNWILLINGNESS
TO PROVIDE EITHER QUARTER OR FORGIVENESS.
Setsu?
Uh, who was that again? A woman...?
Wait, no? Then I don't remember.
SHA-MING WENT ON TO BECOME A FAMOUS ZOOLOGIST.
THE ANIMAL COMMUNITY HE CREATED, AND HIS AMAZINGLY
INTRUSIVE METHODS OF "EXAMINING" HIS SUBJECTS DREW
EXTREMELY MIXED REACTIONS FROM THE SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY.
Perhaps you were dreaming.
Yes. Dreams are reality,
and reality is a dream.
JONAS CONTINUED TO WANDER THE GALAXY. HE DIED ALONE.
Huh? Setsu?
I'm terribly sorry. I'm afraid I don't
know who you're referring to...
AFTER GIVING JONAS HIS LAST RITES,
STELLA ENTERED A SLEEP OF HER OWN,
TOGETHER WITH THE SHIP.
SHE AWAITS THE KISS THAT WILL AWAKEN HER...
Where does the door that the
Silver Key opens lead to?
That I don't know.
AFTER RETURNING TO GLYZE, RACIO GREW DISILLUSIONED WITH
THE AUTHORITARIAN GOVERNMENT AND STARTED A REVOLUTION
TOGETHER WITH REMNAN. THE GLORIOUSLY NUDE STATUE
OF RACIO NOW STANDING IN THE GLYZE REVOLUTION MEMORIAL
PLAZA SERVES AS A POPULAR MEETING SPOT.
Please don't make that face.
I'm sure that if this
is someone you really
want to see again,
you'll be able to, Yuri.
AFTER LANDING, JINA RETURNED TO HER JOB AS
A SPACE TRAFFIC CONTROLLER. SHE LIVED A SIMPLE,
HONEST LIFE AND WAS LOVED BY MANY.
Hey, let's just take it easy.
There's nothing we need
to worry about anymore.
We can go wherever we want
and do whatever we want.
CHIPIE UNDERWENT FELINIFICATION, COMPLETING HIS TRANSITION
INTO A CAT. IT IS SAID THAT THE ADVENTURER COMET ALWAYS
HAD A BLACK CAT BY HER SIDE WHEREVER SHE WENT.
Would you like to come to Nada with me?
I will introduce you to my friend!
AFTER RETURNING TO NADA, OTOME PARTICIPATED IN
MANY RESEARCH PROJECTS. KNOWN AS
THE "MOTHER OF INTELLECTUALIZATION,"
SHE BECAME A SYMBOL OF HUMAN AND ANIMAL INTEGRATION.
KUKRUSHKA WENT WITH OTOME TO NADA.
AFTER SPENDING SOME TIME THERE, SHE SUDDENLY DISAPPEARED.
NO ONE KNOWS WHERE SHE ENDED UP.
Your story has come to a close,
and now the curtain will fall.
However...
I have to wonder if there
will be a curtain call.
UNKNOWN.