Now, for real this time.
We shall manifest the Armor
of the Supreme Emperor!
Um, can I ask something first?
Didn't, uh, Inmei
from the Divine World say
we all have to be in sync for that?
So, what's the point of the ritu—
How many times must I tell you?!
Yikes.
You need to strengthen your armor first,
or you'll never be able to pull it off!
Sorry!
Nomaku sanmanda, nomaku sanmanda,
nomaku sanmanda, nomaku sanmanda,
nomaku sanmanda, nomaku sanmanda.
Now, Armor of the
Supreme Emperor, rise again!
VOID OF THE FIVE SKANDHAS, LIGHT BEAM FLASH,
MIND CLEAR, UNPARALLELED, VIGOR AND VITALITY
What's all this?
"My Uncle Ear"?
You read it "Mind Clear."
It's probably your supreme art.
My what?
VOID OF THE FIVE SKANDHAS, LIGHT BEAM FLASH,
MIND CLEAR, UNPARALLELED, VIGOR AND VITALITY
Mastering your element's supreme art
will unleash your armor's true power.
Oh no! They're fading out!
Crap! I haven't memorized mine yet!
Mind Clear. Void of the Five Skandhas.
Vigor and Vitality.
Unparalleled. Light Beam Flash.
Okay, so if we master those moves,
we can summon the Armor
of the Supreme Emperor?
Probably.
No.
Don't summon the
Armor of the Supreme Emperor!
Someone here is deceiving us so they
can steal the armor for themselves!
Commander Nasti Yagyu.
LISTENING IN
We've collected all of
the Three Sacred Treasures.
I've followed your instructions
all this time.
Now it's your turn to keep
your end of the bargain.
Who are you talking to?
What do you mean?
Don't try to play dumb.
The Jewel of Conquest can communicate
with other worlds, can't it?
Who are you working with?
If you won't say, I'll answer for you.
The one pulling your strings...
is Demon Emperor Ramaga.
EPISODE IX
OUTBREAK
What does she mean
about you working with Ramaga?
Would you give us an explanation
that makes sense?
It all started more than five years ago.
Yoshie Uesugi brought this to the DST.
My granny did?
She said she'd found it in front
of her home, along with a note.
"For one chosen as a Samurai Trooper."
"Chosen"? Granny said something
about that before she died.
Yoshie read that note and realized
you were no ordinary orphan.
But she didn't want
to put you in harm's way.
So that's why she was against me
being a Samurai Trooper...
Then the Sword of Domination
was sent to me.
When I investigated, I learned
they were two of the Three Sacred
Treasures revered in the Divine World.
And so Ryo searched for the remaining
one, the Mirror of Supremacy.
Going by Kaito's and Shion's pasts,
I suspected the Forest of Truth.
That was probably when Ryo
saved you two brothers.
But then the barrier against
the demons failed...
And the original Samurai Troopers
went to the Demon World.
While there,
Ryo was possessed by Ramaga,
and his comrades were captured.
Some time afterward, I suddenly
heard a voice through the jewel.
If you wish to save your
friends, do as I say.
From that day on,
I followed Ramaga's orders
to get Ryo and the captured Troopers back.
Hang on.
You mean you sent us to the Demon World
three years ago on Ramaga's orders?!
He needed to seal the Sword
of Domination's power
until Gai could wield it.
So Ramaga temporarily stripped
the sword of potency himself.
Don't give me this crap!
You sacrificed them all for that?!
Stop it!
I had no other choice.
I wonder about that.
What are you doing?! Give that back!
Do you still not get it?
The jewel is possessing you.
Maybe you started out trying
to save the original Troopers,
but when it cost so many lives
and pushed Tokyo to the brink of ruin,
you became dependent
on the jewel's magic.
Touching it put your mind at ease.
Then, when the Divine World told me
"those I trust" would be cursed,
they meant Nasti?
Hey, old man. Say something already.
I'm not letting you get your way.
You got that?
I don't need any "Armor of the
Supreme Emperor" to kick your ass!
Gai remains lacking.
Who will be the next sacrifice?
The Last-Namers are sacrifices
to make the prince stronger?
Why didn't you tell us, Saizo?!
Hold your horses. Don't blame Saizo.
He was only following
Emperor Ramaga's orders.
And that makes it okay
to stab us in the back?
It makes no sense to divide Last-Namers
and First-Namers in the first place
E-Easy for you to say, Sei.
You're in the First Name Group.
What?
W-We Last-Namers always
felt inferior to you guys.
We were different from the start.
Mochizuki... I didn't know
you felt that way.
Enough.
I'm more worried that Kakei and Mochizuki
will be sent after the prince next.
We've got to help them without
Emperor Ramaga finding ou—
Mind your own business.
We of the Last Name Group are sinners.
Our crimes in the Human World
made us demons.
This is part of our fate.
Supreme Art:
Vigor and Vitality!
Unparalleled!
Void of the Five Skandhas.
Where's your spirit?!
Shion! The least you could do is try!
You're the one who said that most things
work out if you shout loud enough!
I'm telling you, it's nuts to think that
will help us master our supreme arts.
What's your problem?!
We haven't got time to think,
and you know it!
We've got less than ten hours
till the deadline!
That's ten days in the virtual world.
Oh, shut up.
What are you doing, Shion?
I'm taking a break.
Whatever, old-timer.
Hang on. Where'd Gai go?
He's holed up in the dojo.
He said he wants to master
the Sword of Domination.
Speaking of Gai,
something's been bothering me.
Yeah?
What if the sword possesses people
like the jewel and the mirror do?
If you've got time to dwell on crap
you can't think your way out of,
spend it working on your supreme art.
Let's go!
Vigor and Vitality!
Unparalleled!
Void of the Five Skandhas.
You phoned that in
even more than last time!
Hey.
Did you get a weird feeling when you
used this thing in the Demon World?
I did.
I was strangely elated.
But then my memory grows hazy.
I blacked out.
Shun! Tadayoshi! Seiun!
The next thing I knew, my teammates
were on the ground in front of me.
I thought so.
I saw you guys fight back then.
What?
Anyone could tell you humans were losing.
We're not up to this!
Fall back for now!
What's come over you, Shion?!
I'm guessing this sword
possessed you and...
What are you getting at?
Are you telling me it was my fault
that my teammates died?
Like hell it was!
Hey, what's up?
You guys fighting?
Soon, the day of my reunion
with Gai will be upon us.
Kakei and Mochizuki,
bar his entrance to my Demon Castle.
I cannot accept that order.
What is the meaning of this?
Here's your answer.
Kakei!
You'll suffer for my fallen comrades!
What?!
Kakei!
I see you lack what it takes
to hone Gai's edge.
Allow me to assist you.
Wh-What?!
Emperor Ramaga, please forgive them!
This fate awaits all who defy me!
Someone save me!
Splendid.
Gai...
I am now prepared to welcome you.
The date's about to change. It's almost
time for our showdown with Ramaga.
White Blaze should light our way
into the Demon Castle.
Where's the commander?
I put her in room 15,
where Jun was living.
I'm not letting her out for a while.
So, for the time being, I give the orders.
You?!
What? You got a problem with that?
No objections! I know I can serve you
with all my body and soul!
Whatever. This is just a joke anyway.
Oh, no, it's not!
Is this really gonna work?
What he said.
I'm with them all the way.
What's everyone's problem?!
I'm way more qualified than any of you!
So get going!
Thanks. Your comedy act
really lightened the mood.
I told you, I'm not kidding!
You'd all better come back in one piece.
SEVERAL HOURS LATER
The seven days I promised you have passed.
Gai, tell me your thoughts.
Like scorching heat,
I'll incinerate your mortal shell!
White Blaze!
White Blaze, get back!
What's that thing?
Kakei and Mochizuki!
He's been messing with the Ten Warriors.
We'll kill you!
They pack a punch.
Damn it.
No way...
Shun! Tadayoshi! Seiun!
Who are they?
Second-generation Samurai Troopers.
Shion....
Please...
Save us.
Guys!
You're yourselves?
They're still attacking us!
They don't want to!
They're being controlled!
What's the holdup?!
They're Puppets!
They're already dead!
You can't save them!
You're wrong! I heard their voices!
Sorcery's just making it seem that way!
That's not true! They're alive!
Sh-Shion!
Shion!
Shun!
You still think they're alive now?!
I'll save you this time!
Snap out of it!
Shion!
Shun, Tadayoshi, Seiun, tell me...
Did you end up like this...
because of me?
Gai...
Go help Yamato.
On it.
Why did you kill them?
Why did you murder them?!
I know. It's all my fault.
Because of me, they...
It wasn't your fault.
It's because this sword drove you mad.
I need a favor.
Mimic Arrow!
Crusher Bullet!
Follow Blade!
How are they so tough?
How are three of us
still no match for them?
You guys...
I need your help.
Die!
This feeling...
Come on.
A barrier?
Why?!
We'll be crossing Emperor Ramaga
if we go out there.
They want to make sure
we don't go down with them.
Those idiots!
Kakei! Mochizuki!
Nice one, Gai!
How'd you get so strong all of a—
Don't tell me...
The Sword of Domination's taken over Gai!
What do we do now?
Shion!
I need a favor.
I might lose my mind
wielding this sword, too.
If that happens, kill me.
Why?
I don't want to hurt
the first teammates I've ever had.
Shion! Are you all right?!
Excellent...
My teammates saved me.
Gai!
Are you back to normal?
Did I... make it?
Sorry I couldn't finish you off.
Humans really get me fired up.
Jeez.
You had me worried there, you dopes.
Huh? What?
A malfunction now?
Jun, are—
Do you have a moment to spare?
Translation\h\h\h\h\h\hWilliam Varteresian
Timing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Editing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRiley Dalton
Quality Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSMR
Translation Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMichelle Tymon
You can have my life anytime.
Mirei!
No way. How?
Supreme Art: Mind Clear!
EPISODE X
SACRIFICE
Armor races through your heart.