Episode 7
"The Night of the Promotion"
You're back early.
Our trip went well.
It's good to be back, Stud.
How was Marcade?
It was interesting.
Are you familiar with the Forky Gang?
It's a stupid-sounding name, but I've
been hearing it a lot recently.
I don't know about stupid-sounding...
Actually, never mind.
Were you attacked?
I see. I'll rally the whole
guild to wipe them out.
That's all right. We dealt with
the people who attacked us.
Anyway, what kind of
organization are they?
They're an elusive group without
a set base of operations.
I bet it's hard to learn anything about
them if they have that much fodder.
Well, I don't plan on traveling far for
a while, so I doubt I'll see them again.
By the way...
Is something wrong?
No.
I simply thought you could raise
your rank since you've defeated
a subterranean dragon.
Gil basically defeated it by himself.
You contributed enough to its
defeat to receive credit for it.
Contributed?
Fighting isn't the only
way to contribute.
You're also not picky about the jobs you
do, so broadly speaking, it's about time.
I suppose. If I've met the conditions
for a promotion, then I gladly accept.
Very well. I'll get that
taken care of right away.
Now you're rank E.
Up to D should be easy.
Is C difficult?
You'll probably be fine.
And B?
You're not ready for that yet.
Can I join your party?
You want to join us?
Of course.
Could you introduce yourself and
explain why you want to join?
My name is Eleven.
My adventurer rank is solo C.
My strengths are my poison
resistance and honesty.
My weaknesses are mornings and the cold.
I want to join a party capable of
beating a subterranean dragon.
Your strengths and motive
are conflicting. Try again.
I'll be back.
That boy is charming
in all sorts of ways.
He has a distinct personality
and aura about him.
Stop wasting time on what
seems like a pain in the ass.
I was just curious.
So you rejected him because
he seemed to be lying?
No, that was probably
him selling himself.
He's honest, but he's willing
to lie if it benefits him.
I wouldn't call that honest.
Stud, what do you think?
I agree with your assessment.
He's strong enough to be rank C,
but he accepts few jobs.
His appearance...
Is he perhaps a snake beastman?
Poison resistance and weakness to
cold must be traits of his species.
Probably. You don't see
many of them around here.
Will you let him join your party?
I'm not sure I can.
Now then.
Adventurers go drinking to celebrate
promotions, don't they?
Will you join me today?
You can't drink.
No, but I can soak up the atmosphere.
May I join you as well?
Of course.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Stud, can't you be a
little more, you know...
Since we're celebrating my
promotion today, I'm paying.
Why would you pay?
Is that odd?
You would like to play host.
Um, I can cover this.
No, I'll pay. Keep your
mouth shut, dullard.
So mean...
Look at you drink.
You can't drink, Mr. Lizel?
I'm a little surprised.
It's simply my constitution.
I get drunk off a single sip.
What kind of drunk are you?
Unfortunately, I don't recall.
The first time I drank,
my father, who was with me,
laughed and said I didn't
do anything odd.
But when I next drank with a former
student, I was told to never drink again.
He said I was the opposite
of my usual self.
You demand to be spoiled?
You become terribly cold?
You turn into a horndog?
Gil will be paying today.
Don't hold back, you two.
I'd like something filling.
Let's order some small plates, too.
Hey.
How did the escort job go?
I imagine it was more comfortable than
most, traveling with this dullard.
Stop calling me that.
You didn't do anything
to bother them, did you?
If anything, he took care
of us the whole time.
Literally.
Is that not normal?
I've heard of people being treated like
cargo and stuffed into tight spaces.
They say experience is everything.
Perhaps I'll try escorting someone else.
You can't!
I couldn't bear to see
you treated like that.
But I have to accept all kinds
of jobs to increase my rank.
I'm against it, too.
If you're looking to complete more jobs,
this dullard will submit
as many as you need.
You can take those.
That's not something I'd expect
to hear from a guild employee.
If that's what you want, I'll
submit as many jobs as you need!
It's all right, you two. Calm down.
Come on, drink. Eat.
By the way, I have something
to brag to you about, Stud.
What am I supposed to do with that?
I slept next to Mr. Lizel like family.
Next to him? How close were you?
I got a good look at him sleeping.
We ran into trouble on the way
back, so he even held my hand.
Don't you think you're trying
too hard to charm him?
Merchants are such
black-hearted creatures.
That's discrimination.
Well, you behave yourself when
you're around Mr. Lizel.
I'm simply honest with myself.
Anyway, may I stay in your room tonight?
What?
I don't mind, but it's a single room.
There's only one bed.
I'll sleep with you.
Perhaps there's an available double room.
He wants to sleep with you. Let him.
But it'd be so cramped.
I'll sleep with you.
I guess we'll sleep together, then.
Stud?
He's just asleep.
This is what happens when
he drinks to his limit.
I'm surprised you can hold your liquor.
Thank you.
Come on, Stud. Let's head back together.
I'm going with you.
Let's go, Stud.
I know.
Shall we have Gil carry you?
No.
Well, I'm going this way.
Are you sure you don't need an escort?
Yes. Um, I'd love to
go out again sometime.
As would I.
You really are soft on younger guys.
They're cute.
I don't see it.
By the way, Stud,
you've been particularly
belligerent towards Gil today.
Oh, uh...
I expected this to happen,
but not this soon.
The reasons he picks fights
with me are simple.
He doesn't like that I'm
accompanying you, and...
He hates men like himself.
I don't know my own origins.
For as long as I could remember, I was
living in the slums of the royal capital.
I killed who I was told to kill and
lived off the money I made doing that.
I didn't even realize what
I was doing was wrong.
Then one day...
An adult I didn't recognize
appeared before me.
You don't have to kill anymore.
That adult was the current guildmaster.
I'm grateful that he didn't
turn me over to the police.
I've worked for the guild ever since.
I haven't killed anyone
like I did last night.
I'm sorry.
Could you start over from the top?
You have the day off, don't you?
Yes.
You could've slept in a little longer.
Actually, I always wake
up at the same time.
Gil says the same thing. I'm jealous.
Is something on your mind?
Well, won't last night's events
be detrimental to you somehow?
He was clearly a bandit of some sort.
Even if he's found, I can't
imagine it'd be an issue.
I hope not.
If it would harm you in some way, I'd
rather you not get involved in the future.
You'd rather I stand there and watch?
I can defend myself. I have Gil, too.
I'll be careful not to
inconvenience you in any way.
Would it be better if I said losing
you would be more inconvenient?
Very well. I'll avoid doing anything
to inconvenience you or myself.
Good. I appreciate that.
Would you like to get breakfast together?
Yes, please.
Is Gil in his room?
No, he left early this morning.
Good morning, Mr. Lizel.
Good morning.
Did that boy stay overnight?
Yes. Forgive me for not getting
your permission beforehand.
If necessary, I'll pay for my stay.
Oh, it's no problem at all.
I'll throw in breakfast, too.
More importantly...
That's an adventurer's guild uniform.
You really are an adventurer, Mr. Lizel.
You still didn't believe me?
That was good.
Yes.
Stud?
The Blade seems to have
returned. I should go.
I'm impressed. I couldn't tell at all.
That man last night was
clearly targeting you.
I don't know why, but please be careful.
Thank you. You, too, Stud.
What?
Nothing.
Don't say we're alike, battle junkie.
Then don't make me say it.
If you want to stay with him,
protect him with your life, Blade.
Well, he was definitely
connected to those bandits.
They were using identical bows.
I don't understand why
they're targeting me.
Do I look like an easy target?
You're the one who shot
the guy who got away.
Maybe they resent you for that.
But we didn't
hear a peep from them for the three
days it took to return after that.
Either way...
It's going to continue.
There was another one.
Yesterday?
Yeah. More skilled than the archer.
Then they deliberately
chose to use the same bow
and send an obvious bandit to attack me.
Some guys can be really assertive.
But I don't see what they're after.
They don't hate me, and they
don't want to kill me either.
Do they want to weaken me?
Then it's obvious.
They want to ruin your composure.
I see. They're doing this for fun.
It probably would've
worked on anyone else.
How do you feel about running errands?
Don't choose anything weird.
Oh.
This one looks good.
Helping an acting troupe?
Will you let me join your party?
Oh, you're yesterday's boy. Go ahead.
Solo C.
My strengths are my
handsome voice and face.
My weakness is my gangly and
distinctive appearance.
Does he think that'll work?
The two of you stand out,
so I'd receive a comfortable amount
of attention if I joined your party.
You didn't sell yourself as
an adventurer. Try again.
No good, huh?
Are you planning to accept that?
It intrigues me. Do you not want to?
No.
No matter what?
A little more this way!
Thanks!
Excuse—
It's not enough!
This isn't enough, damn it!
Love!
Excitement!
Thrills!
Excuse me...
What is it? Who are you?
Are you the troupe leader?
Yeah, that's me.
I'm here about the mana
replenishment job.
You'll replenish our mana? For
two weeks while the show runs?
I have to see what I'm dealing with.
Then look!
That's impressive.
It's passion itself.
I see they're performing an original
play called "The Phantasmal Traveler".
Incredible. The setting is unique,
but it's simple and easy to follow.
You could tell all that from skimming it?
Here's the magic item.
With this single item, we can project
rain, snow, or even thunder.
Can you do it?
I think so.
All right!
I'm counting on you.
Don't run out of mana.
I won't.
Move it!
What's going on?
You can't be serious!
Looks like the captain's
fighting with the troupe.
Get this out of the way!
We can't! It takes time to move!
They've got a wagon, so they're probably
being told not to block the street.
Just do it!
Why do you have to come this way?
We've got permission to be here, damn it.
I'm going to complain.
Why are you stopping me, damn it?
It'd be unfair for me to say I'm looking
forward to your performance, wouldn't it?
Let me make the first move.
Let's go, Gil.
Why?
I was just hoping to say hello to him.
Don't you recognize that crest?
You can just go around us.
We're not embarrassing
ourselves like that.
It's good to see you again.
What?!
That's the viscount in there, isn't it?
I'd like to say hello to him.
Yes, sir!
No, wait. You're an adventurer.
Huh? No, a noble.
No, an adventurer.
Honestly.
If you can just go around
them, then do it.
You've become so stubborn since
you were promoted to captain.
It's good to see you again, Viscount Ray.
It's you, Mr. Lizel.
How was Marcade?
It was a lively city.
I delivered your letter, so don't worry.
I'm glad you managed to find him.
We didn't just find him.
He made him buy us dinner.
Gil.
You made that cheapskate pay? Marvelous.
That said, I think that only
put him more on guard.
Did he say something to you?
He's a rather cautious man.
No, nothing like that.
I wanted him to meet you for his sake.
I'm afraid you overestimate my abilities.
Modest, aren't you?
Ah, yes.
Last night, the body of a possible
bandit was found in the city.
Do you know anything about that?
I'm not sure. I haven't heard any
rumors from other adventurers.
I see. I think the bandit was
a member of the Forky Gang.
They can be a difficult
bunch. Be careful.
Gil.
Make sure you protect your companion.
Yeah, I've been told already.
Good. If you'll excuse me.
If they know who it was,
they should do their jobs.
Knowing doesn't make it easy.
After all, the gang is elusive.
Still, asking you about it won't
help them catch any bandits.
And catching bandits isn't
an adventurer's job.
Let's let the professionals do their job.
You don't care even after
they attacked you?
Shall we continue replenishing
the device's mana?
There.
It's done.
Thanks for the help!
All right. It works.
I see. Rather than projecting weather, it
converts mana into snow and raindrops.
It's beautiful.
Next Time
"The Midday Attack"
Next time: "The Midday Attack."
Illustration by: levin aoi