Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
Smooth as ever, I escort you
And this voice, seducing you
Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
I am your ace darlin'
Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
Please Please
Whisper just to me, call my name
You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
Hey, girl
Look this way!
I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
So take my hand and let's roll
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
It's a spell that makes your heart race
We can't go back
You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
Sweetie honey
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
Is It Really Okay For Me to Be Here?
Last time, during my job...
Say that line again.
I couldn't give Tamon-kun
what he asked for, and as a result...
So you really do think
I'm creepy, don't you?!
That happened... and now we're here.
Oversized Garbage
Fukuhara-sama.
Eek!
The only thing Tamon-kun is allowed to
throw away is his lack of confidence!
Oversized Garbage
Seeing you act so normally somehow made me
want to be thrown away even more.
I'm begging you, please don't let one
mere fan's behavior affect you so much!
Please don't say "mere fan."
All of my fans are very important to me!
Squee.
Squee
I'm sorry. I'm going on and on
about myself again.
It's fine.
Kinoshita-san, are you doing okay today?
I am.
That's good.
Squee.
Squee
Calm down... whatever this is!
I feel like everything you say
is correct, Kinoshita-san.
I can tell that you're trying
to keep your distance for my sake, too.
But even then...
Keep the distance!
I feel a bit lonely.
Because you're the closest person
to me right now, Kinoshita-san.
No matter what, I'm just a fan.
The most important thing to me
is Tamon-kun's dream.
Even if he tells me he's lonely,
I can't just go, "Okay, I understand,"
and change how I feel.
I don't know what to do.
Please give me some time.
Huh?
Right now, I just...
I'm not exactly sure what I should do.
I don't even really know
what I'm thinking,
so I don't want to casually say anything
while I'm still trying to figure it out.
It's no use.
There's the me who reveres
Tamon-kun as a god...
and the me who's realized that
he's the closest to me right now.
And I'm currently straddling the line
between the two.
I'm sorry.
I realized that I didn't know you
at all, Kinoshita-san.
So... I wanted to know more about you
and ended up coming on too strong again.
I'm sorry that I ignored
your feelings, Kinoshita-san.
I'll wait for you.
It'd really hurt if you hated me,
Kinoshita-san.
Are you two datin' or what?
Natsuki-kun. How long have you been here?
Somewhere around it'd be okay
to throw you away or whatever.
Oh, I see.
So he basically heard everything!
Not bad, my dude.
You guys been together long?
For about three months.
No! That's how long
I've been his housekeeper!
I won't tell anyone.
No, really! You've got the wrong idea!
What brings you here today?
They turned off my power,
so let me hang out here.
Didn't Pay
Huh? You didn't pay?!
The agency pays for our rent,
but utilities are on us, so you know...
"So you know"?
Weren't you going to work?
By the way, I guess you had to
see somethin' weird earlier.
You can just forget all about that.
Right...
Something weird?
Ishibashi-san was mistaken
for a creeper near my school.
What? Really?!
It's all right.
It didn't turn into a big deal.
So Natsuki-kun's ex-girlfriend
is Asuka-sensei...
But she was acting really weird.
Gotta jot this down...
A rare sneak peek of him writing a song!
This is my first time seeing it, too.
He's so cool...
Please wake up!
Don't wanna. I'm tired. This sucks.
But what about the song?
It'll get done. It'll get done real soon.
Please wake up!
I sense a negative aura
different from Gloomyhara-san's.
You wanna write it instead? You could
pull it off with yer rarin'-to-go persona.
I've never even managed
to rip toilet paper on the lines!
How could I ever pull off writing a song?!
Aw, but are you interested?
I mean, I can't say that I'm not...
I do love music, after all.
I see, I see.
Writin' songs is pretty great.
You aren't very convincing.
Not to mention,
why did you run away again?
You were finally motivated.
Hmm, well, you know.
I just felt like...
I stole someone's life, so I probably
shouldn't be writin' an anthem.
Huh?
Ya see, my ex-girlfriend...
Her name's Asuka,
and I destroyed her life once.
Man, this sucks.
It's cold today, so if I fall asleep
like this, I might just freeze to death.
I mean, it's not like I have anything
I wanna do in life, so whatever.
Here. I brought you a tip!
I want some dak-galbi instead.
Quit your whinin'!
You're just a dumb middle schooler.
Go back home already.
Not like my parents
are around even if I did.
Where've you been sleepin'?
Pretty much at a friend's place
or a manga café and such.
And such?!
What are you doin' about money?
This.
Thank ya.
All right. Lemme sing a song.
My parents had zero interest in me.
It didn't matter what I did
or how hard I worked.
They never paid any attention to me.
Which is why I ended up sucking
at working hard at anything.
He's got such a cute face.
For real. He looks like a girl.
Asuka was two grades above me
and in high school.
I'm so jealous!
She'd always bring me takoyaki
instead of some loose change.
Here's your tip.
Why do you keep comin' 'round every night?
You like me or somethin'?
Not a chance.
You're gloomy, irresponsible,
and they say you're a looker,
but I prefer guys with softer features.
But I do like your songs.
Also, for all your complainin',
you are waitin' around for me every night.
Do you like me?
Nope.
You nag too much
and can't mind your own business.
What?! Then gimme back that takoyaki!
Nuh-uh.
But...
the fact that you work
so hard is pretty cool.
I couldn't do that.
Osaka High School
Judo Tournament
We were complete opposites,
but we somehow got along great.
Huh? But don't you wanna become a singer?
I mean, I do like music, but I was
just doin' that stuff to make money.
Becomin' a singer is pretty impossible.
Only a small fraction
of people ever succeed.
Takoyaki               Kodama
Takoyaki
What're you gonna do
after you graduate middle school?
Well, I'll probably find a random job.
Then you can just work at our shop.
Dad!
I was just thinkin' 'bout
puttin' a listing out.
We'd love to have ya, Natsuki-kun.
Like this?
Wow, good job.
Not bad!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You've got a cute face, sonny.
I'm home!
Can I get an order of cheese yaki?
Kansai High School
Judo Tournament
Great job, Asuka!
That's it!
You might just think of me
as a younger brother,
but I don't see you as a sibling.
I want you to be my girlfriend.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Received Messages
After careful consideration,
we regret to inform you
that you have not been selected.
The names of the participants
who passed the audition
will be listed on our
homepage on 6/25.
How'd it go?
Takoyaki               Kodama
Takoyaki
I failed again.
There's always next time!
Quit treatin' me like a kid!
How'd it go for you?
Heh. I got through the Kansai Tournament!
Ooh!
We're gonna have a feast!
Is that your song, Natsuki-kun?
No, no. It's just a cover.
Hey, when I win the inter-high,
sing me an original song.
Why, though?
Well, you said you wanted to
try writin' songs!
Come on, please?
Ooh, I definitely wanna hear that!
We wanna hear! We wanna hear!
Okay, I guess.
I guess I'll work a bit harder, too.
When I was with Asuka,
I naturally wanted to give my all
doing something, too.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
After careful consideration, it has been decided
that you will be moving onto the final round.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
final round
Heck yeah!
Yes! This is amazing, Natsuki!
I finally saved up some money, so I'll be
able to buy Asuka a birthday present.
Natsuki.
Dad...
How've you been?
What're you doin' here?
I'm doin' an audition right now,
and things are goin' well.
Next week is the final—
What about money?
You're workin', aren't ya?
You need to pay your family back.
You're absolute trash.
Who the hell do you think
you're talkin' to, huh?!
Don't! That's...
for Asuka—
Are you okay, Natsuki?!
A-Asu...
Are you hurt at all?
What about you?!
Y-You little...
Asuka!
We bring you the girls' team matches
of the National High School
Judo Tournament today.
The semi-final is about to start.
There was also a promising athlete
who had to withdraw due to injury...
Asuka...
Oh, you came to visit me, Natsuki?
Are you okay?
Oh, I'm totally fine! Just look at me!
This is all my fault...
So, how'd the audition go?
The final round was yesterday, wasn't it?
I've been curious since you didn't contac—
I didn't go.
What?
How the hell was I supposed to go
in this situation?
But why...
What the hell're you doin'?
Are you stupid?!
Seriously, what the hell?
This is the worst...
Asu—
Get out!
I don't wanna to see your face.
After that accident,
all my motivation completely left me.
All of Asuka's hard work
ended up for nothin'.
And it was all my fault.
I quit my job at the takoyaki shop
and went back to
the aimless life I used to live.
All I cared about was
having fun in the moment.
That was just easier.
Later, I randomly did an audition
my friend goaded me into
and shockingly debuted.
I was happy, but honestly,
it felt really weird.
I was in limbo and felt
a bit guilty toward the fans.
Natsuki,
throw me a kiss!
Natsuki
Shoot me!
Natsuki!
Show us your angel smile!
Sorry, everyone.
And I can't help but wonder...
I love you!
if it's really okay for me to be here.
Is it really okay for me to be here?!
Er, yes. You don't have power, so sure.
Please don't worry about it.
You drank too much, Ishibashi-san.
Have some water—
And he fell asleep!
Natsuki-kun usually seems a bit cold,
but I guess he talks a lot when he drinks.
He does.
This goes for Keito-kun, too,
but I didn't know anything
about Natsuki-kun either.
I never tried to find out
how he felt being an idol...
We're in the same group and yet...
I feel pretty pathetic.
I feel so pathetic that I could die.
Can you not go under too, Gloomyhara-san?!
I'm sorry.
The reason Natsuki-kun can't give his all
has to do with this Asuka-san person?
Let's try asking her about it, too.
But how are we supposed to do that?
Asuka-san...
Rather, Asuka-sensei... heh.
She happens to be my homeroom teacher!
What?!
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Security Camera
Beware of Suspi
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Midoriyama Tailor
That person is
Ishibashi-san's ex-girlfriend
and my homeroom teacher, Asuka-sensei.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Midoriyama Tailor
Um...
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Security Camera
Beware of Suspi
I know it's a bit late for this,
but should we really stick our noses
into someone else's relationship?
This seems completely insensitive!
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Security Camera
Beware of Suspicious Individuals
What if I get arrested
for sexual harassment?!
Please calm down!
When I was a bit exhausted,
it made me really happy when
you noticed and said that I wasn't okay.
Squee
Some people don't like being meddled with,
but some appreciate being cared for, too!
We won't know how they feel
until we ask them.
Great Sage Kinoshita...
Let's just have you be my friend
from middle school!
Badump...
A friend!
Ah! Asuka-sensei!
What a coincidence.
Kinoshita-san...
A creeper!
Tamon-kun!
Don't just push me down like that.
You're his housekeeper?!
I had no idea that you actually
knew Tamon-kun, Kinoshita-san!
Not to mention, Tamon-kun
in the flesh is too intense!
It's nice to meet you.
He spoke!
You need to get used to
this already, Utage.
He said my name!
Does the air around here
taste really good?
Whoa! Kinoshita-san?! Are you okay?!
Yeah, something's different.
Kinoshita-san!
We wanted to talk to you about Natsuki.
I was also curious about
what happened the other day...
Ah...
Did Natsuki tell you anything?
He mentioned that you two
used to be a couple.
Yeah, well...
That's true.
You see, Natsuki's not doing
too well with work lately.
Huh? Why?
He's having trouble writing the song
he's on right now.
He said that he has no right to write
this song since he destroyed your life.
Natsuki said that?
It might annoy you two that we're sticking
our necks into this private matter,
but I just couldn't leave Natsuki alone.
I'm sorry.
Um...
Sensei, you said you
were a Natsuki-kun oshi,
but then the other day you
said you didn't know him...
That's because...
The world never needs to know
about an idol's ex, right?
True.
Besides, if people found out
he was still meeting with his ex,
his career would go up in flames, right?
Yet he keeps casually coming to see me!
That idiot!
Facts!
To be honest, Natsuki thinks
that you hate him, Asuka-san.
Really?
If anyone's hated here, it's me.
I regretted what I did,
so when I found out Natsuki did
another audition, it made me so happy.
Isn't that Natsuki?
What?
I want to be your happy, pretty angel!
I'm Natsuki Ishibashi!
What the?!
This guy even found existing exhausting,
yet he was singing and dancing
and full of smiles.
I'm so proud of Natsuki.
I truly am.
There's no way I could ever hate him.
Because I love Natsuki
when he's doing his best!
Is there... any way you'd be willing
to tell Natsuki that directly?
No way!
Now, Natsuki's a celebrity.
He lives in a different world.
It'd just be a nuisance
if a regular ol' person went to see him.
I understand what Sensei
is saying so much, it hurts...
But that's not how Natsuki feels at all.
What?
Natsuki has a ridiculous amount of talent.
But he drinks too much,
he won't quit smoking at all,
and runs away all the time,
meaning he has flaws, too.
That's why...
You may think idols are amazing
or that regular people aren't,
but that's absolutely not true.
That's all I really want to say.
You're so nice.
But I'm sort of surprised.
I totally thought you were the
"I'm an idol, so I can do anything" type.
Gulp
I say stuff like that at work,
but no, wait... uh... huh?
What am I saying?
Hottiehara-kun is panicking!
This rare footage should be saved
for future generations!
But it's just not that easy.
Instead...
I was hoping you'd show
something to Natsuki.
Huh?
Natsuki-kun! Please look at this account!
Man, your handwriting sucks ass!
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Posts
Followers
Following
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Grownup E/YES (20+)
Natsuki Ishibashi
Guardian Angels
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Follow
Chat
What is this?
Tamon
Take Your Clothes Off
Natsuki
Say Something Funny
It's Asuka!
Huh? Since when?
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Congrats on your debut
You made it into third place right after Ouri-kun!!
I've been waiting for this day for so long!!
I'll continue supporting you!
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Congrats on your debut!
You made it into third place
right after Ouri-kun.
I've been waiting
for this day for so long.
I'll continue supporting you!
She's been closely followin' me
ever since my audition!
What the hell? Why didn't she tell me?!
Why'd she run from me?
This makes no sense! Hello?!
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
assu_0000 commented
An update?
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
I'm watching you. Get it together, already!
I look forward to working
with you again today.
What's gotten into Gloomyhara-san today?
He's like an overexcited grade schooler
the night before his field trip.
Probably because he's never gotten
to go to a cultural festival before.
Wow...
His high school has
a cultural festival coming up, too?
Er, I'm talkin' about the one
at your school.
Huh?
Well, you know, Keito's an alum
of Hanagaya High School.
And F/ACE has a shoot
at their cultural festival—
Whoops. I just spilled the beans.
Sorry, forget I said anything.
Tokyo Municipal Hanagaya High School
And that wraps up the outline
for the new show, "F/ACE School",
and our plans for security that day.
We don't want any chaos,
so we hope the teachers and staff
will help keep things under control.
Yes, sir.
Natsuki's...
Tamon-kun is...
...coming to our school?!
Tokyo Municipal Hanagaya High School
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michelle Tymon
\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
\h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
Translation Check:
Alicia Ashby
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
Uh huh...
Na na na...
I wonder what the world
would look like without you
When I look back,
you've always been by my side
Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
A speedboat sails across the endless skies
An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
Like a wilted flower coming back to life
A light that shines
Through the impossibly dark night
(Light of your soul)
I wanted to grasp it
(I love you so)
So I strived for it
Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom
Kinoshita-san's high school!
The cultural festival!
I'm so excited!