Ashiya?
Oh, sorry. Did I wake you up?
You can't sleep?
No, I just had this kind of scary dream.
Then want to sleep with me?
What? U-Uh, Sano...
Um?!
Just get in already.
My bed's getting cold.
Why the hell are your feet so cold?
His feet...
His feet are so toasty!
Er, S-Sano...
I think I'm just gonna sleep alone—
Stop yapping.
There's not a lot of room.
Is that the problem here?!
If you sleep like this...
I'm sure you won't have
any more... scary dreams...
Wait, he was still half asleep?!
I might not have any scary dreams,
but I can't sleep like this!
Whatever!
Gotta take what I can get!
I can hear his heartbeat...
It's so reassuring.
Good morning!
It's a new day!
Oh, right! We have the
early shift this morning!
Wh-Wh-Wha?!
Why the hell are you two sharing a bed?!
I had a scary dream,
so I ended up sleeping with Sano.
I'll get ready real quick.
Oh, he wandered into my bed
again while sleep-drunk, huh?
O-Okay, I'm just gonna wait outside.
Yeah, sorry!
A guy in his second year of high school
sleeping with another guy
because he had a bad dream
is not normal, right?
Yikes, Nakatsu. Your aura
is the color of jealousy.
I Was the Same
Wow, look at all the people!
Outside visitors are allowed in today.
Oh, Kayashima, you're doing
something independent too?
This individual is authorized
to vend independently.
Kayashima Daiki
Yeah.
What's that?
This?
What do you do with that thing?
You want to know?
Here, a spirit photo.
I'll photograph your ancestors
(or guardian spirit) Low price
Well, it's a business
profiting off my hobby.
Sekime and the others were all excited
about girls from other schools,
but there sure are a lot of them.
So cute!
He looks like a real girl!
Thank you.
All eyes are on the dorm showdown,
but the rankings remain unchanged!
Dorm 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 2\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 3
Still, it's neck and neck!
There's no room for mistakes.
Which team will be the one
to take the win?
Oh, this is Nanba-senpai's class.
Mystery Show
Who really did it?!
Senpai!
This is for you.
Oh, thanks.
I can't believe the line!
Yeah, we've been lucky.
This was no suicide.
It's a murderer's trick.
Who are you?
I am Akechi Kojiro,
the great-grandson of the
renowned detective Akechi Goro.
B-But what evidence do you have
to say this was a murder?
You there, lovely lady.
May I ask for your assistance?
Huh? Me?
The victim was practicing a dance
with a partner in this very spot.
Just like this.
Would a dancer drink poisoned wine while
practicing for tomorrow's competition?
Just like this?
Nakao-kun?!
Hey, what are you doing?
I was wondering where you were!
But I didn't get to see him
at all yesterday.
I'm sorry!
Wait, wait.
Please let me take a picture
with you! Just one!
Please!
Uh, sure, just one.
While you were gone,
we used him to bring in customers,
but the girls are just fawning over him.
Must be nice.
Okay, now a twofie!
Huh?
Hey...
Hurry up and take it!
Ashiya?
What are you doing?
We're short-staffed,
so get back to work already!
Thanks, Ashiya.
You're a lifesaver.
I didn't know how to get away from them.
Ashiya? What's wrong?
Nothing.
What's his problem?
Oh, it's Alice! How cute!
You'd never know you're a guy!
Hey, hey! What grade are you in?
Can I take your picture? Can I?
Why are girls so crazy
about guys in girls' clothes?
To be more precise,
hot guys in girls' clothing.
Be on your guard, you sweet thing.
The night always has you in its sights.
That voice...
Yikes, Himejima Masao!
What comforts this dweller of the night...
is your sweet blood.
I invite you to 3-B's haunted house,
produced by Oscar M. Himejima.
Do come along.
Haunted House
Anyway, so sorry for poaching
all of your customers!
Farewell!
Wh-What was that about?
Damn you, Masao!
Not only did you poach our customers,
but you also put your grubby
mitts all over Mizuki!
Paging all beauty pageant contestants.
Please gather at the special stage.
Come on. That's our cue, Ashiya!
Gosh, it's one thing after another!
Damn you, Masao. I'm gonna beat yer ass.
I deliberately missed
with the flower pot I dropped.
Good.
He's that first-year on the karate team.
And?
How did Ashiya Mizuki look after that?
I think the threat was received.
The hell?!
Listen here.
This year, Dorm 1 has to win the
grand prize no matter what.
Um...
What?!
Er, it's nothing.
Hang on, that means the incident
during the chicken fight was also...
You've got nice legs.
Go!
It was just a compliment.
Don't jump out of your skin.
I'll do what I want!
What do you think you're
doing, you idiot?!
Kujo.
I heard everything.
From your little friends in Dorm 1!
Wait, huh?
There's nobody here.
Either way,
I don't care how dirty you guys play,
I'm not lettin' you lay
a finger on Mizuki!
And don't you forget it!
Nakatsu, where the heck have you been?
It's showtime in five minutes!
Izumi!
What is it?
Mizuki's in danger.
Ladies and gentlemen!
It's what you've all been waiting for,
today's special event:
Osaka Academy's famous beauty pageant!
We of the broadcasting club and the
executive committee will be your hosts.
Now, over to our on-stage commentary!
Yes, comment.
Only the twelve you see here made it past
the rigorous elimination round, comment.
I want to go home!
Now let's introduce the top four who
currently have the most votes, comment!
We'll begin with contestant number 15.
A favorite among the first-years,
it's the fresh-faced Kadoma Shotaro!
Moving on, we've got contestant number 18.
You already know him
as last year's winner.
It's Nakao Senri!
Next is contestant 23,
the talk of the town
who's back from living abroad!
Ever since he transferred here,
he's seen a stellar rise in popularity!
It's Ashiya Mizuki!
Then we've got contestant 34, who made
the cut despite being a last-minute entry!
It's the shy "I'd Like to Stay Anonymous"!
And now, on to the talent program!
Contestant number 5 will be singing opera.
I knew it was the Dorm 1 guys.
Let's go.
Go where?
The pageant's already
in full swing, right?
If they're going to make a move,
it'll be now.
We'd like to thank all of our finalists
for their unique performances, comment!
Now let's get to voting, comment!
You know what to do, Kadoma
Don't screw it up
Okay...
Nakao, your personality sucks,
but you sure are cute.
Can't fault me for anything else,
so I'll give you that much!
I can't wait for this to be over.
Ashiya-senpai.
You're Kadoma from Dorm 1, right?
Yes.
A-Actually, I'd like to talk to you.
To me?
Yes!
Please.
So you're on the karate team, right?
Oh, uh, yeah.
What made you join?
I mean, you don't exactly
look like the type.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
It's fine.
I get mistaken for a girl a lot in town,
and I'm the only one of my siblings
who's small and weak.
But then I saw Kujo-senpai's kumite.
Kujo?
It was just so... How should I put it?
It was beautiful.
I was moved.
I know that's probably weird.
I get it.
I have a similar story.
Ashiya-senpai?
Senpai, um, the truth is—
Good job, Kadoma.
Kadoma, you can go back now.
Oh, come on!
They're about to make the announcement
at the stage... Where'd he get off to?
Let go of me!
Stop resisting and come with us!
I said let me go!
Ashiya?
Hey, you there!
Unhand him!
What do you think you're doing?
Nakao-kun?
Shut up! Stay out of this!
Ignore him! Let's go!
How dare you...
do that...
to my face!
You bastard!
Do something about him!
R-Right!
What, you wanna go?!
It's finally time to announce the results!
We'd like to invite our twelve finalists
back to the stage, comment!
Give it up for them!
Mizuki!
Mizuki! Where are you?
Nakatsu!
Nakao! What's happened?!
Ashiya got kidnapped by guys from Dorm 1!
What?!
Where'd they go?!
I don't know!
I barely got away myself.
Hey, Izumi!
Hey.
Where did you take Ashiya?
What are you talking about?
Stop playing around.
W-Wait, what's this?
Where's contestant 15, Kadoma-kun, going?
Please wait!
Kujo-senpai had nothing to do with this!
Kadoma, tell us everything you know.
What are you guys trying to pull?!
We must win at all costs
for Dorm 1's honor.
Kitahanada!
This isn't personal.
We just can't have you running
in the 2,000-meter race.
Does Tennoji know about this?!
He doesn't have the slightest clue.
This was all my idea.
Watch him!
Yes!
This way!
Don't tell me it was
Kitahanada and the others...
It was.
It's always like this.
Whenever I think something's happening
to him when he's out of my sight,
I get sick with worry.
Why can't you just...
stay by my side?
Let me out of here!
Behave yourself.
This brat!
Naniwabushi Kick!
Oh shit!
Hold it right there!
Who the hell are you?
Sano!
Wh-What's gotten into you?
Please don't move.
Sano...?
It's me... I'm the one
who wants you at my side.
Captain, about the 2,0000-meter race...
Before that...
Since our top three
contestants left the stage,
victory goes to "Contestant 34-kun" of
Dorm 3 who wished to stay anonymous!
I'll get you back for this, Nanba Minami!
Why isn't Kadoma up there?!
What? That can't be...
Senpai.
Kadoma, you...
Kitahanada, such stunts
aren't going to please Tennoji.
What does he mean by that?
I'm so sorry!
Well, the captured princess was freed,
and the mastermind was caught.
All's well that ends well.
As for you...
What happened to being in the pageant?!
Wah!
I'm so sorry.
This was all my fault.
Hey! Why aren't you apologizing?!
We are so sorry!
Their crimes fall on my head!
The responsibility is entirely mine!
As our dorm RA
and captain of the karate team!
Ashiya, what do you want to do?
Uh, well... they've apologized,
so I'll forgive them.
Then I've got nothing to add.
Nanba, you're unbelievable...
But you lot will take responsibility
for sullying the name of the karate team.
S-Sir!
Good. Now get going.
Sir!
I'm sorry, Kujo-san.
I was convinced you were
the person behind this.
I mean, whenever we made eye contact,
you'd give me this grin.
Oh, he literally only thinks about karate,
so if he sees someone with potential,
he always wants to go and scout them.
You mean that's why you felt up my leg?
The 2,000-meter relay race is about
to begin on the main grounds.
All participants, please gather there.
You're up, Ashiya and Nakatsu.
No rest for the weary.
Let's go, Nakatsu.
Yeah.
Ow!
Are you okay?
I was thinkin' my leg felt weird...
I guess it's from doing
that flying kick earlier.
Looks like I sprained it.
This is bad.
What do we do about the relay?
I guess we have no choice.
And now, our final event:
the 2,000-meter relay!
The team who comes in first
will receive 50 points.
Second place will get 30 points,
and third place will get 10.
There's still a chance for an upset!
Dorm 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 2\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 3
Hence, I'll be covering for you.
Are you sure you can do this?!
Now that I've decided to enter,
of course we're going for the win.
Eyes on the prize until the very end!
And once this is done,
I'll be ready to get over it.
I've finally decided to accept it.
I'll even send a bouquet to her wedding.
Senpai...
All teams, on your marks!
Ashiya, I'm counting on you as our anchor.
Okay!
Let's go.
Good luck!
We're rooting for you!
Good luck, Senpai!
Sano...
Ashiya!
Y-Yeah!
I'm going!
We're on the third leg,
and Dorm 1 is in the lead!
Dorm 2 now passes
the baton to their fourth runner!
And there's the hand-off!
Their fourth runner, Nanba,
has just rounded the third corner!
And he's fast!
He's overtaking people
and closing the hundred-meter gap!
He's now in second place!
Ashiya!
The baton switches hands!
I'm counting on you, Ashiya!
He's like the wind!
He's quickly closing in on the lead!
And he's out front!
Ashiya wins!
Dorm 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 2\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 3
Dorm 2 turns the tables
and takes the crown!
Thank you for your patience!
The votes for MVP have just been tallied.
And this year's MVP award goes
to Dorm 2's... second-year Class C!
We did it!
All right!
What a long day.
Yeah...
Come on. What's up with you today?
You seem really out of it.
Got something on your mind?
I was just looking at you.
Huh?
Sorry. The wind was so loud,
I didn't catch that.
Come again?
I'm not telling you.
What? Hey, come on!