Five years ago
How's that guy still alive?
I like it. Let's have a toast.
Don't.
Why not?
He even knows our technique!
I don't know, but...
I'm collecting knives.
Lots of them. Sharp, tough ones.
Don't!
So, would you like to join
my knife collection?
Keep playing your beautiful music.
Perform gigs just for me.
I've killed, and I've killed,
and I've killed, and I've killed.
As his foot soldier, I kill anyone
who stands in his way, just as ordered.
I loved sound ever since a very young age.
That used to be my thing.
I used to keep count, but I no longer
know how many lives I've taken.
How about you? Do you remember?
Nonsense. I've never even
attempted to keep track.
His orders are like sheet music
with no "fine" directive.
An infinitely repeating da capo.
Kill. Kill. Repeat.
What'd you come out here for?
Don't tell me it was to whine at me.
I didn't know you were here.
I only came to see Vash the Stampede.
See him? You're not here
to kill that moron?
I'll take him with me.
Back to Knives?
I'd love to send him off
with a thank-you note,
but that sounds like a recipe
for even more trouble.
So I guess I can't let you have him.
You get it, don't you?
I do.
Then if you'll simply turn around
and walk away, I'll let you go.
Let me go?
Just go ride off somewhere.
Nicholas the Punisher...
I already gave that name back to him.
I'm Nicholas D. Wolfwood now.
I see. Now you're Vash the Stampede's
sworn ally, are you?
Kinda uncomfortable
being labeled his friend.
I guess you've changed,
and not just in name.
What are you even talking about?
Well, what's it gonna be?
This ship will be attacked soon.
And not just for Vash the Stampede.
The whole ark is coming
to take all the plants here.
You're saying Knives is on the way?
Now would be the time to run.
Where in this world would we even run?
You're right. I don't want to spend
even a second near that thing.
Yet there's no place to flee.
So this is how it goes down,
Midvalley the Hornfreak?
It is what it is.
Probably best to beat you down right
quick and prepare for the attack.
I had no plans to gig with you tonight,
but it wouldn't be the worst thing.
Given the current air temperature,
the speed of sound is 340 meters per second.
At this distance, my attack
will reach you in 0.03 seconds.
Will tbe bullets from your
Punisher be faster than that?
Dunno.
Let's find out!
Damn it. Then how about this?!
A lens made out of air? Preposterous.
Got offense and defense, huh? How handy!
A decoy?
Nice try.
I know how good your hearing is.
Guess it wouldn't be that easy.
You really have changed.
Before, you wouldn't have
tried to get me to leave.
You would've gunned me down,
no questions asked.
Even now, you're only aiming at my
saxophone, trying to disarm me.
You can change, too.
Anyone can change, whenever, wherever.
You...
You can only say that because
you were able to leave him.
All I can do is follow
the score I'm given—
Really, though? Maybe you
don't have to follow the score.
I thought improvisation
was the heart of jazz.
Just rip up that weirdo's score.
Play the sound and the music you want.
If I could do that, I would!
But I can't, so...
You've changed too, you know?
If you'd used your
omnidirectional sonic attack,
I wouldn't have been able to dodge it.
But you're only using focused attacks.
Because I need to capture
Vash the Stampede—
Given your abilities, you could easily
fire an attack that excludes him.
But you won't... because you've changed.
You can change.
Perform gigs just for me.
I can't. I...
You can. Nothing is impossible.
I can't!
Weakling!
Shut up, traitor!
I was waiting for you to launch
antiphase sound waves.
Shoulda known it wouldn't be so simple.
You're still alive. You really are tough.
When did it get so dark?
Did all the moons set?
I gave your brain quite a rattle.
You won't be able to see
anything for a while.
Impressive. I guess they don't call you
the Ruler of the Sonic World for nothing.
Hold it.
Where are you going?
I'm going to go pick up Vash the Stampede.
Not on my watch.
Impossible. You can't aim in that state.
I know where you are. That said...
This time, I might end up killing you.
Don't take it personally.
Right back at you.
Tch!
Damn hunk of junk!
This next note is the last thing
you'll ever hear.
Feedback?!
Did you think that
would interrupt my gig?!
This won't change your fate!
Gig's over for the night.
Hornfreak is here?
Indeed, Emilio. I was hoping
you would know a weakness.
As things stand,
I can't even get near him.
To defeat him, I'll need to get up close
and destroy his instrument.
He's your enemy,
yet you have no desire to kill him?
You really are...
No, never mind.
If I tell you, will you
take these off of me?
I'd take it under consideration.
Well, he has excellent hearing and
plays the most beautiful notes.
Why don't you let him hear himself?
I see.
A feedback loop! Thanks, Emilio.
Now, about these handcuffs...
Fine. But we can't let you
out of this room for now.
We have a deal.
That feedback was to mask
the sound of your approach!
Are you all right, Wolfwood?
What took so damn long, dumbass?
Shoulda been here sooner!
S-Sorry! I had trouble
adjusting my new arm.
Besides, he wasn't easy to reach, so...
He almost had me. Yikes.
Emilio gave me the tip I needed.
The puppeteer did?
Wow, you really do change everyone.
Huh?
Never you mind.
Er, a little to the right.
Oh, uh, a little to the left! Or... down?
What do you mean "down"?!
Mind the gap!
You're too slow!
Are you doing this on purpose?!
N-N-No, I'm not!
Kill me.
There's no need for that. It's over now.
Nothing's over.
Oh, right. Knives is on the way.
Nai is?
Yes.
It'll be a massacre.
Vash!
Can you take care of Wolfwood?
Undertaker! Are you hurt?
What about you, Vash?
It's not bad.
I'm fine.
Where?
It's fine.
First aid first thing!
What? It's no big deal.
That won't do! Prompt care is important.
Nobody's going to kill anybody.
Enough already.
I'll protect everyone.
Including you, Midvalley the Hornfreak.
Huh?
I promise.
Protecting your enemy?
You really are soft.
But that's a good thing.
There's nothing good about it.
Though it is kind of infectious.
Huh?
Never mind.
What do we do?
We can't give up Vash.
Nor the plants, nor our lives, of course.
According to Hornfreak, Knives isn't
able to do much of anything right now.
That's why they want Needle-noggin.
The ones carrying out the attack
will be Knives's knife collection.
This is no joke.
Hm...
How are the ship's armaments?
Sixty percent of our guns are operational.
We have plenty of ammunition as well.
And our interceptors?
We have ten ready to fly.
Okay. Then let's take them on.
Luida...
We might be able to take them out.
We have to try.
Initiate level 1 combat preparations.
Noncombatants, retreat to the shelters.
Understood!
Got it.
Initiating level 1 combat preparations.
Noncombatants, retreat to
the shelters immediately. I repeat...
You don't have to stay aboard this ship.
Now is your chance to—
No, please let us see this through.
Yes, to the end!
How nosy.
We're not nosy.
This is our duty as journalists.
Also...
Also?
I consider you people my friends.
When my friends are in trouble,
I want to do my best to help them.
I see.
Is that going too far?
No, not at all.
I agree. Thank you.
That was so cool of you, Meryl!
O-Oh, don't tease me.
Still, if you feel in danger,
get to a shelter immediately.
Right!
Keep your eyes on the radar.
Let me know the instant you see anything.
Understood!
Vash, are we going to die?
I won't let that happen.
I'm going to protect you.
Everything's all right, Jessica.
Okay.
That's right. I'm here to protect.
I'm going to protect everyone, Nai.
I guess Midvalley couldn't deliver
Vash the Stampede to us.
It's fine. He wasn't capable
of pulling it off anyway.
So you sent him into Ship 3,
just thinking maybe something
funny might happen?
The star always arrives last.
The star? Are you talking about yourself?
Who else could I mean?
I'll bring him here myself
to make him kneel before Lord Knives.
And we'll take all the plants from Ship 3
and bring Lord Knives back completely!
Exactly.
Soon, Lord Knives.
The time to awaken draws near.
And then, with your gaze,
you will...
Are we really doing this?
Kind of late for that now, Doctor.
This vessel is now entering combat.
I hope you're ready for me,
Vash the Stampede.
Target in range.
Fire!
Beginning assault.
Our dawn is nigh.