I was wondering, Shio and Akari...
What do you two think about Eiyu?
Why the sudden question?
Seriously.
Sudden? Well, because Eiyu—
She's still mistaken about us dating.
Haru, over here!
I told you to stay out of this!
What? I just wanted to help out!
Just watch over us, okay?
You know you wanna know, too.
I-I don't!
In any case, don't ever bring it up again!
Fine.
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
Sorry about that!
What's going on, you two?
Oh, nothing. Don't worry about it.
But this really feels
like old times, doesn't it?
We always used to bring snacks
to share, remember?
Just play it off for now.
Yeah, we did!
Remember how we made
the losers play the Pocky Game?
Yeah, I do!
You and I kissed for real one time!
Bleh! So gross!
CRACK
And then...
Haru, that's a touchy subject!
Oh, whoops!
Oh, a kiss, huh?
A real kiss...
But hey, look! They're getting jealous!
You've got a chance!
I think they're more
disappointed than jealous.
W-Well, it happened when we were kids,
so it doesn't count. Right?
Yeah, exactly!
Plus, it was with Eiyu!
It was far from romantic!
Sure, we "kissed,"
but it was just for a second.
And we bumped teeth, so it hurt!
It seriously wasn't anything special!
Cut it out! That's too graphic!
Th-This is hell!
Oh yeah.
Someone gave this to us as a souvenir.
Wanna try some octopus rice crackers?
Smooch Smooch
Octopus Rice Crackers
So Good,
You'd Want to Kiss It!
"Smooch, smooch,
octopus rice crackers"...
"So good you'd want to kiss it!"
M
ME
MEN
MENA
MENAC
Someone, help!
MENACI
MENACING
I'm back!
Oh! Do we have guests?
Runako!
Just in time!
See? It's Haru! Remember Haru?
Runako! How many years has it been?
Oh my gosh!
You've grown so big, Runako!
No!
Runako?!
I'm scared of frogs! I'm scared of frogs!
Frogs?
I was traumatized
by Haru-kun way back.
Kero-chan, Kero-chan, Kero-Kero-Kero-chan.
Ribbit, ribbit.
Runako!
Haru-kun!
I brought you something cool!
ribbit
wriggle
You love frogs, right, Runako?
No... Just Kero-chan...
Come on, give it some love!
Slimy! Gross! Slimy! Gross!
Huh? Runa—
No!
I really thought
she'd like it at the time.
I'm sorry, Runako. I really am.
I said I'm sorry!
Don't run, Runako!
Frogs! I'm scared of frogs!
Get away from me!
I told you, I'm sorry!
Stay away!
I feel bad for Runako,
but she helped me big time.
Runako!
No!
Wait up!
I'm not mentally prepared for this!
Whoa! Whoops!
D-Does this not count either?
Y-Yeah, please don't count this.
I-I'm exhausted...
Bye!
Bye
See ya!
Damn it, they're totally fine!
And I'm over here, freaking out!
They kissed... they kissed...
They... kissed...
Haru-kun, too?
Does Haru-kun also...?!
Haru-kun, I envy you.
It was no big deal back then.
"Kiss"!
Kisu
Kiss!
I can't stop thinking about it!
Does Haru-kun have feelings for Eiyu?
Hey! You good?!
Oh, yes.
Oh! Shio?
Haru-kun...
What are you doing?
You scared me.
I just tripped.
You're so clumsy.
All right, well, be careful!
Haru-kun.
Can I join you?
Want me to slow down?
I'm okay!
That's the spirit!
You're totally different from Eiyu!
Eiyu?
We played one-on-one the other day,
and he couldn't move at all.
When I teased him, his face went
completely red, I couldn't help but laugh.
Do you... have feelings?
For what?
I'm talking about Eiyu.
What?
You seemed happy when you kissed him.
Wh-What?!
What are you talking about?
Of course not!
I bet you're the one who likes him,
since you're so worried.
I'm right, huh?
Come on, Shio!
I won't tell you!
Hey! You'll run out of breath
if you go too fast!
Come to think of it,
you used to say, "It's not fair
you're always playing with Haru-kun"!
It's our turn to play with you!
You're jealous of me, aren't you?
I'm the one he held hands with first!
What?
The first one to take a bath, fight,
and share spoons with him was all me!
I'm not jealous at all!
Come on. You're getting all worked up!
Am not! You're the one
getting worked up!
What?
You've been running with all your might!
This is my usual pace!
Your usual?! That's stupid!
Shut up!
Why don't you just admit it already?
Right back atcha.
In my case, I'm his childhood friend.
I'm his childhood friend, too.
Jeez, it's not like that.
D-Does this not count either?
Shio?
You're drenched in sweat!
What are you doing out this early?
U-Um, nothing really.
How about you?
I'm about to have break—
Whoa.
Th-Thanks.
Hey, whoa... Are you okay?
S-Sorry...
I have to go take a bath.
See ya!
Okay.
See ya.
La la la, so soft and fluffy
ANGEL'S
KISS
It's like an angel's kiss
Kiss.
Kiss
You dropped your food.
Up next, discover kissel,
a European dessert.
KISS
Kiss.
Kiss
Onii-chan, you keep dropping your food.
Please watch out for "akisu" this season.
Kiss
You did it again!
Huh?
We just kissed... right?
We did, right?
Is this really gonna turn into a rom-com?!
Onii-chan?
It's been two days...
I wonder...
I wonder how she's been feeling...
I mean, how am I supposed to
act when I see her?
Do I look presentable?
All right! Good!
Morning, Eiyu!
Shi...o?
H-Hey, morning.
You're not going inside?
Come on, the teacher's coming!
Morning, everyone!
Hey, did you do your homework?
Sakai!
Not fair!
You two sure are close!
Huh? Well...
Yeah, yeah. And also...
Huh?
Huh?!
Hey, Shio, so...
Can we t-talk after...
All right! We're going home now!
See ya!
O-Okay.
Huh? Huh?!
Runako!
Are you going home, too?
Didn't expect to run into you!
Eek! Please let me go!
I'm getting goosebumps! Goosebumps!
Oh, come on!
Let's rewrite your memories...
No! Please stay away from me!
with fun... ones...
No!
Hey, isn't that Eiyu?
But something feels off.
His back's wide open!
Kiss... kiss...
I know we kissed for sure.
A girl friend kissed me
A Girl Suddenly Kissed You?!
The Psychology Behind It and How to Handle It
Why's she acting like nothing happened?
Did it mean nothing to her?!
Huh?
Hey! What are you two doing?!
Well, uh...
Never mind that, Onii-chan.
Why are you reading about k-kissing?!
Oh, um...
Is this about the other day?
You said it didn't count!
Huh?
Onii-chan... Don't tell me
you like Haru-kun!
No, you dummy!
This isn't about Haru!
Huh?
I-It's not about me?!
What a relief.
Then...
Who kissed you?
Who was it?
It was someone besides me, right?
If you're looking it up,
then it must've been recent.
No! Stop!
It was nothing!
I know! It was Akari, right?
Huh?!
You were talking
about her the other day!
No! It's not!
It was Shio!
N-No! Not Shio!
I mean, cold shou-lder!
My friend got the
cold shoulder from a girl!
Your friend?
You seem pretty emotionally
invested, looking things up.
Th-That's because...
He said a girl friend of his
kissed him out of nowhere,
but then she acted like nothing happened
the next time they saw each other.
I was curious about what it meant.
She wouldn't kiss him
if she didn't like him!
Just hold her close and kiss her back!
Wh-Wh-What? Are you kidding me?
Wait a minute!
Doing that without making sure you
both like each other is just gross!
You don't get it.
Momentum is key
in this kind of situation!
You're wrong!
Feelings matter most!
You have to verbalize them first!
Hey, you two.
What do you think, Onii-chan?
Do you have feelings for Shio-chan?
Huh?
If you do, then you have to tell her!
You're her childhood friend!
No, this is about my friend...
It doesn't matter!
Momentum! Momentum is especially key
when it comes to childhood friends!
What?!
Quit overthinking and just go for it!
No!
You have to communicate, Onii-chan!
Do I have feelings...
for my childhood friends?
I-I don't know!
I can't imagine being in a real rom-com
with my childhood friends!
Whine, whine, whine, whine.
You're on your way to
being rejected by everyone!
I might get annoyed too
if you keep acting like that.
Hey, we agree on something!
It doesn't mean anything!
They're annoyed... by me...
To make a decision...
and just go for it...?
No way, that sounds terrifying!
Sports Day
Executive
Committee
Team
Anyone want to take on this role?
I'll do it!
Then, the second person will be...
I-I'll do it!
These two are this year's sports day
executive committee members.
clap
We've got this, Eiyu!
Y-Yeah...
Whoa! There's a lot of equipment!
I wonder if we'll finish
inspecting them all today.
Y-Yeah...
But you know...
Since it's just... the two of us...
Are you okay?
ba-dump
Y-Yeah...
Go, go, go, go!
We're alone!
We're alone right now!
This is my chance!
This is my chance
to ask her about the kiss!
But what if she wants
to treat it as an accident
hesitating
and pretend that it never happened?
What if it was just a dream...
Hey, Eiyu.
About this kiss...
What?
This...
This can't be an odd number, right?
It should be an even number.
Yeah... right...
This Kiss
An odd number would be odd...
Right?
Don't mess with me like that!
This is so awkward!
We did k-kiss, right?!
It was our first kiss!
So why is Eiyu acting so calm?!
Calm
Why am I the only one
getting all worked up?!
We really did... We really did it!
W-W-We kissed! We kissed!
Eiyu
I-I'm sure he didn't like
that I kissed him out of the blue.
But what if he's actually...
happy about it?
Maybe it was a bother after all.
But, but, but!
What if by some tiny chance...
This turns into a rom-com...
Just act like I always do for now!
Morning!
Eiyu!
Shio.
Hey, morning.
Huh? Huh?!
I counted four obstacle
course bags over here.
O-Okay.
What's the heck is up with him?
What is he thinking?!
I want to ask...
About the kiss!
Oh no!
Huh?
I feel dizzy.
Oh! Sorry!
The obstacle course bags
kissed each other!
Shio?!
How about that?
They're such good friends!
Smooch, smooch!
He went along with it?!
I don't get what's going on!
Whoa, they're loving
on each other so much!
Is he saying that a kiss with me
isn't a big deal to him?
They really are so lovey-dovey.
Is she mocking me?!
You have no idea how I'm feeling!
Tension
Let's quit messing around
and get this over with.
Eiyu, did you not like it?
When we ki... ki... ki...
Ki... ki...?
Oh, nothing!
Let's finish this up!
Huh? Okay...
Then, you take that side.
You have to communicate, Onii-chan!
You're... You're talking about what
happened three days ago, right?
Wh-When you...
Ki... Ki...
Ki...?
Ki...
Ki?
Ki...?
Watch out!
Kiss!
All right, let's really
get this over with.
Yeah.
Sports Day
Event Selection
I'm so excited for sports day!
Tomorrow's the day. It came up fast.
All right, I'm going home now.
Okay, I'm gonna stay a little longer
to make sure everything's good.
Okay. See ya.
Isn't she from Class 2?
That's Minamo-san.
She's going all out!
Is she?
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
What do I do?
I'm having a hard time talking to Eiyu...
I shouldn't have kissed him.
Akarin?
There you are, Shio.
Huh?
Episode 10
Feeling the Afterglow Kiss After Kiss? Become a Sports Day
I need a word with you.
Committee Member? Still Won't Start a Rom-Com