It's a sealed power!
But your dark, forbidden power
is beginning to awaken!
Rirui will use this power...
to be of use to everyone in the village!
Rirui, keep that power a secret.
Why's that?
Well, a secret power
sounds cool, doesn't it?
True!
I've got some leftover work to do.
Bed for me!
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
There one goes!
Get around behind it!
Got it!
This is a lot of work...
but it has to be done.
Unbelievable.
You little brat!
Get back here!
Like you clowns could ever catch me!
Damn, now I'm really starving.
Man, you been raising hell again?
Ricky! Booby!
EPISODE 12: A HOMETOWN AND FRIENDS
You really oughta knock it off, Hajime.
He's right. And if you're gonna
cause trouble, give us a call!
All right, all right.
Honestly...
Your rat meat's done.
Hey, don't eat the whole thing!
That has to feed us all, okay?!
Aw, damn, I'm still hungry.
That was nowhere close to enough.
Well, talking about it
only makes it worse, so stop.
At times like this, we should
talk about our dreams.
Like what we want to do in the future.
Like what, exactly?
'Cuz I don't have a clue.
I guess I just want to be able
to eat my fill for once.
That sure sounds like you, Hajime.
How about you, Booby?
I'd love to get married someday.
M-Married?
There's this cute girl named Veronica...
That sounds real nice!
What about you, Ricky?
I wanna become a resident adventurer.
A resident what?
It's an adventurer who lives
and works in a village.
What do you wanna do that for?
So I can have a hometown.
Not a rundown cesspool like this.
Somewhere with lots of nature!
A place where people
help each other out.
Imagine a group like us, a bunch of
friends, except it's a whole village!
That's what I want!
Wow, that sounds great.
I don't really get it.
That's right! Which is why it's
bound to be a huge success...
It'll be the best stall ever!
That does sound impressive.
Better get those skewers ready, then.
Someone! Help!
Gotta pee...
If I do this, no one will notice.
That was a close one.
Was that...
Hajime!
What's up? You're up early.
Can we talk? I had some questions.
Sure. Whatever you wanna know.
It's about Rirui.
She had this marking I'd never
seen before glowing on her arm...
I don't know a lot about ancient species,
but is something going on with her?
Seems the same as usual, to me.
The village elder asked everyone
to report anything out of the usual!
Could it be related to the magic
beasts that keep attacking at night?
Rirui has nothing to do with that.
If he knows that Rirui is
the cause of the attacks
and Hajime is keeping it a secret,
he could be worried that
if the village finds out...
Chasing off troublemakers for us, huh?
Good work, little fella.
How can you be so cruel, Dad?!
Can't we all get along?!
B-But mice are pests.
Good morning. Is Mr. Shinonome around?
Olive! Um...
Hajime's still sleeping!
That makes sense.
Is it that bad at night?
Yes. And we're still trying
to figure out the cause.
That's rough...
Come on, Rirui.
Oh, right!
Getting ready for the festival? Good luck!
Be sure to come eat at our stall, miss!
Of course. I'm looking forward to it.
Nice!
I'll come by again later.
Um, why did you want to speak to Hajime?
Something's been worrying him lately.
And considering all he's done for us...
It'd be nice if we could pay
him back for it, you know?
I mean, when he lost his arm,
he had every right to be mad.
He might not even realize it,
but he's too kind for his own good.
U-Um, Olive?
Yes?
Give it a damn rest!
Tomorrow's the full moon. Must be
why there's even more of them!
They're getting more aggressive too.
Damn, they just keep coming!
Hajime.
Why didn't you ask for help?!
Did you think I'd forsake Rirui?
Do you really trust me so little?!
I know when you lost your arm, I...
When you have issues with Rirui,
I should be the first one
to hear about it, idiot!
I know you've always liked
to play things your own way,
but you're looking after a kid now!
Time to grow up already!
What is this about?
I'm sorry. I told the others about Rirui!
And we all decided together...
We're going to protect her as a village.
Ancient species losing control of their
powers happens every now and again.
Usually calms down naturally after a time.
Is that true?
Our focus needs to be getting through
the night of the full moon.
Once we do that, her power will be
back under control for a while.
Today's the deer god festival!
That means the whole village will come
together so Rirui and the other kids
can have a good time, little Hajime!
Imagine a group like us, a bunch of
friends, except it's a whole village!
That's what I want!
Hey, it's morning.
Time to...
Rirui?
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
Rirui's gone?!
We've gotta look for her too!
Right.
Hang on.
Could you two handle the stall instead?
Why?! There's not gonna be anything fun
about the festival without Rirui!
Hajime is going to find Rirui.
He's our resident adventurer, after all.
Still...
And if the stall isn't lively when she
gets back, wouldn't that make Rirui sad?
All right then.
Cocko...
Rirui!
Damn it. Did she leave the village?
What am I going to do?
I'm going to be the first one
to the festival!
The resident adventurer's kid?
Yes, it seems fairly certain.
Rirui's ancient species
powers will make it likely
that magic beasts may approach the
town as early as this afternoon.
I understand that the nightly
attacks have been troublesome,
but I'd like to ask you all to be on
alert during the afternoon as well.
Every night, the village is...
And Hajime has been in
trouble because of Rirui?
Is it that bad at night?
Yes. And we're still trying
to figure out the cause.
She said they'd come this afternoon!
And if magic beasts show up,
it'll ruin the festival!
Rirui can't stay in the village!
Anya, Cocko... I'm so sorry.
I should be there to help you.
But if I'm around,
it'll cause trouble for everyone.
Rirui...
Ow, ow, ow...
No! I can't give up yet!
Rirui... Adventurers never give up!
Dragon?
Everyone...
You little goof!
We were all worried about you.
You should've asked for my help!
I thought we were on the same team!
If you're going to join
my team, stop crying!
Hajime...
What do you wanna do, Rirui?
Rirui...
Rirui wants to go to the festival with
you and the rest of the village!
Well, if you're my partner,
then quit crying.
O-Okay...
Good work.
The moon's starting to wane.
We should be good now.
I am so damn tired.
I've been up all night.
Hajime...
Is the festival still going?
Yeah. Don't sweat it.
Let's head back to town.
Everyone's waiting.
Let's go, Hajime! Come on,
hurry! We need to go!
H-Hey! Quit pulling!
Have fun!
Be safe!
Anya! Cocko!
I'm sorry I'm late!
Took you long enough, Rirui!
That looks delicious!
You take care of the rest.
Come on, Rirui! Get grilling!
Everyone's waiting
for some of your skewers!
Can I get one?
We've been waiting!
One for each of us, please!
I want one too, Rirui!
Step right up!
Hi, everybody!
GUIDE TO THE DEER FESTIVAL
DEERIO
Check it out! It's Deerio!
Thank you so much for all your dancing!
I can tell you all shared
a lot of your power with me!
And next year, I hope you'll all be
able to eat plenty of yummy food!
What a busy year it's been...
Those are called stars of fortune.
They come raining down
at the end of the festival!
I should get one for Hajime too!
I don't really get it.
This stuff about a hometown
or a bunch of friends.
You guys are all I need.
Thanks, man! You guys are
my best friends, too!
Hey, why don't we all go, then?
We'll become resident adventurers,
find a hometown! All of it! Together!
I bet every day will be fun that way!
Ow! Who the hell did that?!
Chair.
Yes, ma'am!
Hey, Rirui.
Thank you so much!
Are you having fun every day?
Yeah! A ton of fun!
Have a safe trip!
All right.
Rirui, let's get a move on.
Right! Off we go!
Time for another round...
of the daily grind.