What is life?
What is hope?
What is despair?
Living things live
Living things live.
And they also always die.
And they also always die
When people face this destined
process, what do they imagine?
What hopes do they hold?
They live, distracting
themselves from despair.
And this man...
Dragon.
Dragon
No matter what it may be, for this man,
life carries no meaning.
For Dragon, life is nothingness.
However...
even for that life of
nothingness, death exists.
Which means all that exists is despair.
And before this invincible Dragon...
someone who is driving
himself to death appears.
Wounded, sensing death,
and through the nearness of death,
he tries for the first time to take
hold of that which is called hope.
Amidst the despair known as death,
he is trying to obtain hope.
But nothing is certain yet.
He still harbors doubts.
Is this man truly someone who is capable
of pushing himself to his utmost limits?
This man... Arthur Boyle.
He has imagined, he has dreamed,
of things that never happened...
of things that never existed.
He fantasized about castles in the air,
and he dreamed.
Everyone who saw him called him a fool.
But he is enjoying himself.
Enjoying life...
the fear of spontaneous
human combustion...
the past in which his
parents abandoned him...
In his imaginings where he never once
hung his head, he simply enjoys himself.
Is he truly a fool in
the most literal sense?
Is it simply that he is good at living?
And he...
is trying to enjoy death, as well.
This place where he is
dying, outer space...
He enjoys comparing it to the paradise
where the Knight King sleeps, Avalon.
Dragon and Arthur.
At first glance, they seem like opposites,
but they share something in common.
Both of them carry hopes for death.
A shudder that seems to
set the world smoldering.
Arthur understood
what it was intrinsically.
In that moment...
the horizon burned!
The source of the flames that dyed
the horizon crimson was, of course...
the Great Wyrm of Despair, Dragon!
Nothing has changed since 250 years ago.
There is no one left worth vanquishing.
Pathetic.
Truly pathetic, humans.
As though it were a display
of Dragon's despair,
volcanoes rise from the sea floor...
and erupt!
That's the boy from another time.
Is he here to challenge me again?
This will stave off boredom
until this world ends!
Give it a try, whelp!
I am right here!
I'm coming.
Hurry up!
Episode 21
"Dragon and Knight Surge Toward the Heavens"
What is important in this world
are the World-Builders who can
guide people's imaginings.
Even among these World-Builders,
the particularly powerful
Dragon's despair is unique.
If Arthur-kun can't wipe
away Dragon's despair,
the Great Cataclysm won't stop.
The outcome of their battle will
influence the Great Cataclysm.
Dragon's despair is immense.
It isn't possible for
some boy to dispel it.
This Great Cataclysm will not be stopped.
The belt of volcanoes that suddenly
appeared along the Tama Riverfront,
the volcanoes where the Great Wyrm
waits, boom with thunderbolts.
I've kept you waiting.
Are you good enough now
to stave off my boredom?
Since you defeated me, I have
experienced a great number of things.
A supremely complex underground labyrinth!
A darkened temple rampant
with evil spirits!
The land where I was born and
raised was burned to the ground,
and in a battle with numerous
devils, I lost many a comrade.
Through overcoming this epic journey,
I have become the Knight King!
There is little time before
the world is destroyed.
I do hope you last that long.
This world will not fall.
I will defeat you, Dragon,
and stop the Dragon's despair!
Despair no longer.
I am here!
I decide what's true or not!
Impressive.
So this is pain, is it? Interesting.
Don't disappoint me, whelp!
The wyrm's roar split the heavens.
You're in the thunderclouds, aren't you?
You're scared of this Dragon,
so all you can do is hide, is it?
Don't get the wrong idea!
Lightning from the thunderclouds
gathers in the holy sword.
Violet Flash,
Reverse Plunge!
It passed through!
Since ancient times, seeing a sea
of clouds ringing with thunderbolts
has made people imagine a particular
immense creature within them.
The land crumbles with the
start of the Great Cataclysm.
Long, long ago, the land
was called Babylonia.
There, a solitary young man appeared.
Unscathed, where he walked,
he left nothing but ashes behind.
The young man could be called a
calamity, but people called him...
Dragon.
Pathetic.
After years of walking and
trampling everything in his path,
he began traveling to
destroy all that remained.
It was, in actuality, an act
akin to a natural disaster.
Heaven and earth shook.
The man was like a catastrophe that
bestowed despair upon the people.
But he despaired more than any other.
No... all he had was despair.
Such things as optimistic
thoughts and hopeful thinking
are only granted to the weak and foolish.
For Dragon, with his absolute power,
there was no optimism or anything else.
That which was called
"hope" did not exist.
Nonexistent hope.
Dragon had lost even his purpose.
And contrary to his huge physique, he was
like a lost child with nowhere to turn.
Once this man of ultimate
power fell into despair,
that despair only grew
stronger and stronger.
And with that despair,
the powerful man's boredom tore
through the continent once more,
becoming a calamity that
burned a lake into nothing.
And who are you?
Lightning that flashes across the heavens.
An earthquake that shakes the land.
A natural disaster spreading far and wide.
The people have no means to resist,
and they are swallowed up.
I am Faerie.
In the eastern lands, 200 years from now,
the Great Cataclysm will begin once more.
To that purpose, your despair is required.
It's tedious to live with
no purpose, isn't it?
Am I wrong?
Come with me, great wyrm.
Come to Tokyo, and together we
can destroy this entire planet!
Though it was hopeless,
he had found a purpose.
Gnat.
But now!
The lightning that flashed
through this great wyrm's body
showed him a glint of light!
Blood flows through me, too.
It flows thickly through me, like magma.
Whelp! No, Arthur! Well done!
What we begin now will be no
mere trampling, but a battle!
This will be my first battle.
Let your thunderbolts peal.
They set the heart racing.
The lightning sent shivers
racing through him.
The great wyrm unleashes a beam of heat.
Lightning and sword flash.
The impact of it pierces the heavens...
and shatters the land.
Lightning races.
The great wyrm reacts.
This is the first time I've raised my
arms for anything other than destruction.
The battle between these
two powerful fighters...
knows no stopping,
not over land, sea, or air.
With my claws, my strength...
I rend the heavens, sunder the land...
and cleave the sea!
Violet Flash, Octo-Strike!
You're pretty good!
But this is not all that I am!
What about you?
To live long is a good thing indeed!
A wonderful thing!
It's too constricting, Arthur.
This planet is far too small
for the two of us.
Don't you think so?
But that will not be enough to stop me!
Unhand me! Just how far
do you intend to go?
The atmosphere of outer space
is very close to being a vacuum.
The temperature there is
roughly -270° Celsius.
Normally, Earth's living creatures
would not be able to do anything
without protective suits.
If they were to step out into
space without protective suits,
all the heat in their bodies would be
lost, and they would freeze completely.
However, these are things...
that these two neither
know nor care about.
The one thing that the
Violet Flash knows is...
He can't breathe! It's suffocating!
Darling, did you see something again?
Yeah. Outer space, like usual.
A sky full of stars.
Is that what was happening?
I wasn't predicting the
future of the world.
It was Arthur's future that I saw!
You mean our son's?
Yeah.
Our son is fighting in that vast sky.
What's wrong, Arthur?
Though you may be the Knight
King, in the end, you are human.
How fragile.
Once you've left the planet,
you can no longer act?
It seems that even you could not
drive away my despair, whelp.
I thought you were someone who
would hold out until the last moments,
but I see that this is the end.
Are you releasing your weapon
to beg for your life?
I have a high opinion of you.
Don't disappoint me.
I have no final blow for a weakling.
Die here alone, in obscurity.
Arthur has equipped the Star Ring
I see that it was for this moment
that the Star Ring exists.
Thank you, Yu!
I will not allow you to despair!
Then, here, in outer space...
Arthur has equipped the Star Ring
let us decide the future of the planet!
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Thanks to the Star Ring,
I can fight even here in space.
Arthur has equipped the Star Ring
Just because you can breathe
doesn't mean you can best me.
That isn't the last of
this ring's effects.
It can transform the thoughts of
the people of Earth into strength!
It seems you've got a
grasp of Adolla, as well.
I can still fight!
Then show me!
This time, I ask that you hold
out until the world is destroyed!
The world will not be destroyed!
Why, you ask? Because you will
find hope in my strength!
You talk big, don't you?
As long as I am alive,
it is no mere boast!
Aren't you glad I exist, Dragon?
I've started to want to see your despair.
I will destroy you!
This is the first time
I've felt this sensation.
I can tell that for both you
and me, death is very near.
Don't disappoint me here at the very end!
You will not be disappointed!
Rest assured of that!
I will defeat you!
If I cause you to despair,
the world will disappear!
The Knight King will never be defeated.
I cannot allow this to be the end!
If the world disappears, he'll have
nothing left to protect after he wakes!
I will save Yu, defeat Dragon,
and do something about him.
That's what I promised.
Knights keep their promises,
no matter what!
My name is Arthur Boyle.
...Arthur Boyle!
I am the Knight King!
You think you can vanquish me
when my body is still perfectly sound?
I should have promised
that I would return alive.
That would be greedy.
There is no one who can
face me and return alive.
I have known that from the start!
Resign yourself. You will die here.
Yes. That may well be true.
The Press of Death.
I learned of it in Asakusa.
But that won't be enough here.
If I want to defeat Dragon,
the Press of Death only makes me aware
of my death. It won't let me reach him.
In order to unleash the
ultimate flash of light...
I need the Readiness for Death.
"Readiness for Death"
I will end this now, Dragon.
Will you cut off my despair, which has
continued for so many years, Arthur?
The Readiness for Death.
It allows for, of course,
but a single strike.
It will be the last strike I ever unleash.
But it will be a strike that
will connect to what comes next.
Well, then, you won't be able
to hit me from over there.
Be grateful that I was here, Dragon!
With this one strike,
you will discover hope!
Let's have some fun!
Die!
With this one strike!
Ah, so this is...
Violet Earth Cleaver!
"Violet Earth Cleaver"!!
What's that light?
It's cutting the planet in two.
It's Arthur's light of hope.
Arthur did it!
Is Arthur all right?
With Arthur showing him
something like this,
he's not gonna be able to just sit around!
That was brilliant, Arthur.
Well done. So you've vanquished me.
Here, at the end of my life of
boredom, you showed me hope.
Thank you!
I'm glad you were here, Arthur.
Dragon lost?
Th-That's impossible.
Hey, Shinra!
How long are you going to play the devil?
I have become the Knight King!
I suppose I may have overdone it a bit.
I believe these repairs are
likely to take some time.
It's so much brighter than
what you see from Earth.
I'll leave the rest to you...
Hero!
To Be Continued
Fire Force Chapter 3
Settling things with the saint
Haumea and the Evangelist.
Next Time
It's something only my
brother the Hero can do.
Let's protect the world, Sho!
This is the final battle in this story!
Next time, "Hero Resurrected."
Episode 22
Hero Resurrected
Return to the great flame of fire. Látom.