THE CASEBOOK OF ARNE
PART 5: ONE SWALLOW
DOES NOT A SUMMER MAKE!
First, let's go over your alibis.
Before the master of the house
called for Lynn Reinweiß,
the only people moving about
were the two maids, correct?
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
1ST FLOOR
After that, Diana left her room and went
to the guest room on the second floor.
That's what Zisye...
uh, wh-what the mirror showed.
The mirror?
I rigged the mirrors so we'd know
when someone passed in front of one.
Huh?
As such, in order to get to
the master's room on the third floor,
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
2ND FLOOR
you'd be seen by the second-floor mirror
or the guard in the dining room.
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
1ST FLOOR
Around that time, Kai climbed a ladder
to meet Diana in the guest room.
The figure Heinz saw outside
must have been Kai.
We also know the gardener didn't continue
into the house from the guest room.
The mirror confirms that.
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
1ST FLOOR
Next, Elise made her way
from the kitchen to Father's room.
She got as far as the door before
returning to the second-floor hallway.
She remembered he didn't want any water,
so she poured it into the vase of flowers.
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
1ST FLOOR
By that time, my father had called for me,
so I was on my way to the third floor.
As I passed the second floor,
I heard Elise break the vase
and the glass,
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
2ND FLOOR
but I continued on up to Father's room.
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
3RD FLOOR
KLAUS'S ROOM
BEDROOM
That's where you were struck by the killer
and left pleasantly unconscious.
What do you mean "pleasantly"?!
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
2ND FLOOR
Anyway, Elise cleaned up
the mess in the hallway,
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
3RD FLOOR
then went to the third-floor storeroom
to look for a replacement vase.
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
1ST FLOOR
Around the same time,
Gordon left his room to go talk
about meals with Heinz in the kitchen.
On the way,
he saw Bernd in the dining room.
A short time after that,
the guard headed to the master's room,
where he'd been summoned.
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
3RD FLOOR
Elise took a vase down to the second floor,
but the two didn't cross paths.
Then, Bernd used his spare key
to enter Father's room.
He saw me unconscious
next to the corpse and cried out.
The only other people with spare keys
are the old butler and the taller maid.
That pretty much it for what we know.
Huh?
SUSPECT: THE MAID, ELISE
This maid visits the master's room
to give him the water for his medicine.
She enters the room, knocks out
Lynn Reinweiß when she comes to visit,
then shoves the master into the basement,
where he falls to his death.
The storeroom next door holds weaponry.
It wouldn't have been hard for her
to remove the impostor's head.
Impostor?
The headless corpse was not Father's.
His actual body was in the basement.
Huh?
B-Basement? But I never—
After the act, she locks the door and
escapes to the storeroom via a route
only someone of her size
can squeeze through.
She crawls through the air vent.
It's extremely narrow, but this petite maid
could have made it through.
That ignores one thing!
Elise could not have used the air vent.
When I crawled through the air vent,
it was dust paradise in there.
If Elise had already crawled through it,
there would've been much less dust.
You are correct.
This maid is not the killer.
Elise!
Miss-tress Lynn!
What a relief. I'm so glad.
I am, too.
Now it's your turn, Lynn Reinweiß.
This is the moment of confrontation.
I have to identify the killer?
SUSPECT: THE COOK, HEINZ
H-Heinz leaves the kitchen before the time
of the crime to go to Father's room—
To get out of the kitchen, he'd have to
go through the dining room or backyard,
FLOOR MAP OF THE REINWEIß ESTATE
1ST FLOOR
but the guard was in
the dining room the whole time.
Th-Then, he goes through the backyard...
There are guard dogs in the yard.
What else do you have?
Nothing.
Then, that means Heinz
isn't the killer, right?
Even if you're just trying to use me
to get off the hook,
I'd appreciate shrewder
theories than that.
Right.
So that's what that was about.
Thanks, Lynn.
SUSPECT: THE MAID, DIANA
SUSPECT: THE GARDENER, KAI
Given how you were
coordinating with each other,
I hereby deduce you were accomplices.
If they'd found a way
to break into the master's room,
they could've easily done it.
If the gardener doesn't enter
the mansion through the guest room,
he must use the ladder to get in.
The ladder may only just
reach the second floor,
but if he pulls it up with him once there,
he has access to the third floor as well.
Sure, but isn't it too heavy for that?
He can't lift it alone,
but the maid is there,
waiting in the guest room.
So they pull it up together,
then the gardener climbs up
to the third floor.
Next, he scrambles onto the roof
and heads to the master's room.
The maid goes to
the master to distract him.
Meanwhile, the gardener
enters from the balcony,
and they commit the crime together.
The gardener could then take
the head and weapons outside,
while the maid locks the door
with her spare key.
Clearly, these two are the killers.
You can't...
It's not true! We were simply...
That ignores one thing!
The two of them couldn't lift
the ladder together!
Oh?
Diana has an extreme fear of heights.
She could never go out onto a balcony.
As they didn't leave the guest room,
they couldn't have committed the crime.
Hmph. Fine.
Mistress Lynn.
I wanna hear all about
you two later on, okay?
Sure.
Well, that leaves two.
Which one do you want to take?
It looks like you've already chosen
the one you think isn't the killer.
Wait, so whoever
she doesn't pick is the killer?
You'll pick me then, won't you?
I'm not the killer!
Stop being so disrespectful.
Who gives a damn about respect now?
Gordon!
Bernd, yeah. Pick Bernd.
Bernd. Bernd.
Then, I choose...
Gordon.
Huh?
Oh? How would he get from his room
on the first floor to the master's room?
I don't know.
Which means it's impossible
for him to have done it.
Ergo...
Wh-What the hell?
I'm the security guard here!
Why would I want to kill—
SUSPECT: THE GUARD, BERND
Huh?
No! I'm not the killer!
Mister Bernd?
But why?
I knew it.
So it was you.
No! This doesn't make any sense!
Is Bernd really the killer?
Of course not.
Huh?
Hey, guard.
I don't care what you say. I'm not the—
Hmm. It's even worse than I heard.
Oh! Bernd faints at the sight of blood!
The accomplice cut off the corpse's head,
and attacked you in the bath.
That'd be impossible for him.
We carried out this investigation
under unusual circumstances.
We had access to information
we normally wouldn't,
and ended up relying on it too much.
The mirror?
You mean Zisye's information
about everyone's whereabouts?
You haven't figured it out yet?
Huh?
Well, fine.
But I'm sure you noticed
something. Right, Zisye?
Huh? What do you mean?
I was doing everything I could to help.
Hmm, I wonder.
They didn't escape through the air vent.
They can't work in high places.
They were observed by witnesses,
or they pass out at
the merest sight of blood.
If we disregard the alibi
created by the mirrors,
there's one individual who could
have moved around freely.
But you can't just disregard
an alibi, can you?
You can't... as it applies to humans.
No...
No, that can't be right!
Zisye, you saw him, didn't you?
I mean, he's been the butler here forever!
Butler?
Huh?
There's the tall maid and the small maid,
the gardener, the guard, and the cook.
Those are the five servants
who work here at the mansion, right?
You know, Lynn, there's something
I've been wondering about this whole time.
Who is this "Gordon"?
Should I reveal the truth now?
No, I will.
Lord Arne and I have deduced
the murder would've been impossible
for any human in the mansion to commit.
But allowing mirrors to serve as alibis
presumes that the culprit is human.
You're a vampire, aren't you...
Gordon?
Please, Gramps. Will you read to me?
This is the third one, Mistress.
I don't care. Keep reading
to me until I get sleepy.
I suppose I cannot refuse.
Hurray! I love you, Gramps!
You believe I am a vampire?
This is not the time for jest.
Then, please stand in front of the mirror.
If you're not a vampire,
you should have a reflection.
But Miss Lynn, Gordon and I
were both assaulted by the killer.
I'm the one who assaulted you.
Huh?
But I never touched the old man.
He probably played the victim for show.
There was one thing that bothered me.
So the broken vase was
your doing after all, Elise?
If you hadn't been up
to the third floor, Gordon,
when did you see the broken vase?
What a shame. I was hoping
to play this out to the end.
So there was no point in watching
the mansion through mirrors at all.
You were in Father's room
the whole time, weren't you?
After you knocked me out,
you killed Father
and walked back to your room,
passing in front of the mirrors.
But why did you kill Father?
I am still very fond of you all even now.
I had hoped to enjoy serving this house
and living secretly amid humans.
However, perhaps about a month ago,
the master acquired a certain item
in a black market auction.
It was the heart of Lord Nachzehrer,
the one king I truly serve.
The master and I had finished
gathering the necessary bodies.
The only thing left was to perform
the reanimation ritual.
However, I preferred to revive Lord
Nachzehrer rather than the mistress.
That is why I did it.
What?
But fear not, for I was able
to grant the master's wish
and reunite him with his wife
as pieces of Lord Nachzehrer's unholy body.
I see. That's why you left
another body in the master's room.
With my king revived and the master
and his wife living on within his body,
and with Lynn serving as
a worthy mistress in her own right,
I wished to continue
residing in this mansion.
"Mistress"? Don't make me laugh.
You wanted to control her like a puppet.
I saw the bite mark on her arm.
A noble title would have helped
facilitate Nachzehrer's return to power.
That must have been part of
the reason you killed the master.
You intended to manipulate Lynn Reinweiß
to take over the mansion.
Very well played, Lord Arne Neuntöte.
Oh, so you know me?
I never expected the mistress
to have already been bled.
No wonder she wouldn't
follow my orders, let alone die.
It appears she was already not human.
But I still hadn't... not yet...
Yet I never expected
any of this to happen,
including her calling the police.
So that's why you attempted
to murder Lynn Reinweiß.
If the master hadn't called Bernd
and started all of this commotion,
I would have already succeeded
in reviving my lord.
But now? None of that matters.
I suppose you didn't need
a weapon with arms like that.
Use every part of me.
Right here, right now.
All hail Lord Nachzehrer!
I'm back, baby!
Man, I haven't had a body in a while.
Can ya even imagine how it feels
to end up inside some old geezer?
Can ya, Neuntöte?
What, did I scare you speechless?
Of course you look exactly
as stupid as you sound.
Huh? You were dumb enough for me
to get that heart out of you.
So who's the stupid one?
How do you suggest we two vampires
settle our differences?
I see. A blood duel.
Yup. The blood you lose during
a blood duel goes to your opponent.
I'm gonna slurp up all that blood of yours
and become Neuntöte myself.
Interesting.
Yeah! Now, let's see who devours who!
You might wanna try paying attention!
How reckless. Are you planning
to use up all of your blood?
When I take all of yours, it won't matter.
Get him!
I suppose that's what
you call a death wish.
How delightful.
D-Damn you.
I win.
Why?
You and me each have one heart.
How could I lose?
You fight far too inefficiently.
Ah, no kidding.
You still refuse to yield?
You ain't gonna get me
to roll over that easy!
I'll be taking that heart back now.
You piece of shit.
What are you doing?
Oh, Lord Arne. I'm glad you're safe.
Um, is Gordon...
He's dead.
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
I see.
What happened to the other servants?
I told them to get to safety.
TIMING: HENRY LIN
EDITING: SMR
I said I'd wait for you.
QUALITY CONTROL: ELISABETH CRIST
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS
What a hassle.
Look at that.
The shining moon makes
everything look so beautiful.
It's nothing but dirt and dust.
It almost looks like the end of the world.
Are you an idiot?
Lynn Reinweiß, are you an actual idiot?
Huh?
The world you live in is far too small.
How did this mansion
appear to you from the sky?
It looked very insignificant.
And that is essentially all this is.
The choice is up to you.
I want to see other worlds.
The worlds I've learned of
in the last few days...
The world outside of the mansion...
Your world, Lord Arne.
Then, should we really be wasting time
here gazing up at the moon?
Let's go, Lynn Reinweiß.
Yes, Lord Arne.