In Front of Saegusa Academy
Harmonia Building Collapses! Caused by a Mysterious Giant Rock Pillar?!
Oh man, the news has spread
all over the world.
Accelerating Collapse
Will the existence of XENOS finally
become public knowledge?
I hope it doesn't cause panic.
I'm worried about people's reaction, but
there's something even more concerning.
Where the heck are Kyoya and Soji?
I'm sure they're safe!
Not only them,
but the rest of SI-VIS, too!
All we can do right now
is believe in them.
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
It's Show Time
The price of living in the time of freedom
"So, what do you want to do?"
Just standing there with my empty body
Like a calling to protect the world
I craved an unequaled gift
Lost in night's darkness
Until a voice called out to me
Like the light that declares the dawn
I'll take you with me at
any cost (I pray and wish)
Beyond the Echo-verse (To the future)
Just being with you makes me strong
It's not an exaggeration
That encounter was a supernova
(Our eyes were locked)
In an instant, everything that I am
(In an instant)
Will be changed forever (Just to be)
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
Destiny is Calling us now
Just to be who we are
Just to be by your side
No remains have been found
at the accident site.
The survival of the fourteen
members of Harmonia Entertainment and
Harmonia Building Collapses!
Caused by a Mysterious
Giant Rock Pillar?!
SI-VIS, who were believed to be inside
the building, has not been confirmed.
Here at Saegusa Academy, where
Saegusa Seina serves as the principal,
I feel bad troubling the students like this.
the staff members are busy
gathering information.
But we can't have you back
in the public eye right now.
If you do, then domestic and international
governments, the media,
and XENOS will come after you.
It would cause serious disruption
to SI-VIS activities.
I had no idea Harmonia
had a secret base like this.
It was the president's idea.
It also functions
as the backup center for Metis.
I see. Since it's located in countryside,
there's almost no threat of the Mirage.
That's smart.
We escaped by the skin of our teeth, huh?
We can still resist XENOS's attack!
By the way, where are Rui-san
and the members of SI-VIS?
Entertaining our savior.
We weren't supposed to
survive that attack.
But μ said she saw something.
You saved our lives.
With a mysterious power.
It's called Elpis.
We XENOS are endowed
with two powers from Priest Archon.
One is Pandora.
It has tremendous power,
fueled by enormous Idea.
It's a power to conquer the earthlings.
The other one is Elpis.
This doesn't require much Idea to wield.
All you need is to release
everything that's left in you,
and it will grant your final wish.
You mean it's
a self-destruction technique?!
Is that what Lukos used?
Yes, to simultaneously strike each other
with that knight over there.
Not that it worked, in the end.
Talk about being unflappable.
You're a scary bunch.
Yes. I used Elpis
knowing that I would disappear.
So I really shouldn't have
survived like this.
We don't care why you survived.
Wow, scary.
It's your fault for telling Rui-san
that she and Yosuke had
a complicated relationship!
Why did you help us?
You're XENOS, after all.
Do you have to ask?
I'm sure you know already.
About our comrade who
gave his life to try to save you,
even though he was
from a different species.
Oh, a counterattack!
Hey, aren't they kind of similar?
Whose side are you on?
XENOS? The earthlings? Or...
If you're on Yosuke-kun's side,
then that's all I need.
Medea-san, is it? I'm—
I saw you in Orphe's memory.
The knight who protects the Diva, Kyoya.
Yeah. I'm a wing
who protects Nagi, our center.
Well, I failed to protect her.
There was nothing you could do.
Because compared to Orphe,
you're not enough.
Your individual strength, your
leadership, your resolution, your wishes.
Nothing about you is enough.
Hey now—
It's okay, Rui-san. She's right.
So, Medea-san, please help me.
I'm not enough on my own.
What was Yosuke-kun trying to do?
What did Yosuke-kun want
for XENOS and the earthlings?
Tell me.
I'm not enough.
I may never catch up to Yosuke-kun
for the rest of my life.
Even then, I'll protect Nagi.
I have to figure it out with who I am now.
Please give me a hand, Medea-san.
Lord Archon.
Please take a look, Lord Apollo.
Lady Eden looks
even more rejuvenated today.
Ah, so that's what the blood can do.
What?
Is she the Diva of XENOS?
Yeah, Lady Eden. She might be your mother.
My mother?
S-So this girl is...
The video I'm about to show you
is the record Orphe left behind.
This is Nagi?
Hold on a minute!
You say, "the daughter
of the Diva," but this is...
Right. It wasn't Lady Eden's fruit
of love, nor a blessed child.
Who would do such a horrible thing?
That guy? He did this to Nagi?!
Right. Now we know who our true enemy is.
Yosuke did that to me?
It's rumored that Lord Orphe raised
a baby who was the Diva's kin in secret.
Not "raised." He created it
in an unethical manner.
When Lord Apollo discovered what happened,
Lord Orphe took you and left this land.
In a strange land, you were
constantly deprived of Idea,
being forced to teeter
between life and death.
That's not true.
Orphe... Yosuke truly cared for me.
He was a strong and kind man.
You believe it was Orphe
who made that girl?
Who else could've done it?
Who's to say?
I can't say that my suspicion of you
is completely clear.
But since the president says
she believes in you,
I have no choice
but to allow you to be here.
It's not that I believe her.
Kyoya-kun said he needed her help.
As always, this company's
too soft on the talent.
Hayama-san!
That's the story.
Would you consider lending me your hand
for the sake of our
precious talent, Medea-san?
I saved you. You're going to
trust me on that alone?
I was just in a deadly battle
against you.
The current leader of our group
is that kind of kid,
even if he may
not be enough in your eyes.
I'm sure it'll be a tough
decision for you.
Choosing to betray your homeland
and the person you've served
all these years,
I'm sure you'll need a good—
You saved me.
After using Elpis, the only thing
left for me was to rot away.
But you carried me here and healed me.
I have no reason not to help you.
We'd say, "We're in the same boat."
Then let's both do everything we can.
Your Orphe loved XENOS dearly,
and our Yosuke loved Earth so much.
We'll save both of his homes.
So it's not just Earth?
Are you saying you'd be
willing to save XENOS, too?
I'm not, but my talent is.
Then I will believe....
in your talent, and in you,
who must have indulged Orphe.
Team formation for the next concert
Center! Soji
How about I be a solo center
for the next battle?
You've got no flare.
Your key's too low.
Too niche?
The heck, guys?!
But if Soji isn't the wing,
then it's unbalanced—
I can be the wing, too!
I know I can do both perfectly!
Chase two rabbits, and...?
Say what?!
Your physicality is essential in
breaking through the front line.
You're a godsend wing.
Please understand that, Soji.
Yeah, I know that.
Too easy.
Here!
Center! Soji
Kyoya
μ
June
Hey! What are you doing,
taking advantage of this mess?!
But when you think about the balance,
that's the only option for now.
Purely from the process of elimination.
You trying to pick a fight with me?
Which means,
we can have Soji in front
and Kyoya and June on both sides
to surround μ in the center.
Front
Soji
μ
center
Kyoya
Looks like the princess
of an otaku circle.
June
But you know, if Siren learns
I'm the center of the group,
she may not stay quiet.
She'll either scoff at you or hit you.
What was that?!
Rui-san, where's Siren?
She discharged herself without permission,
and she's not answering my calls or
checking my messages on social media.
Who knows where she is
and what she's doing?
Either way, we can't rely
on Siren right now.
We'll have to take the plunge.
For now, yeah. I know that.
But when can we start relying on her?
It won't help to
dwell on that now, will it?
Exactly. Now's not the time
to be hung up on that.
Even if we don't have Nagi or Siren,
we'll put on the best performance we can.
That's the goal of SI-VIS, right?
I don't care if it won't help.
I want to dwell on it!
I want to be hung up on it!
You selfish, spoiled brat.
You're seriously new here.
I get where Medea is coming from.
Um...
The double centers, Siren and Nagi.
That's the final form of SI-VIS.
I'll never give up on that
version on SI-VIS.
I'm going to take back
both Nagi and Siren!
Not giving up on both women?
I smell a total schmuck.
As the members, I mean!
Kabukicho Ichiban-gai
Hey, is SI-VIS still missing?
That was a crazy accident.
I hope Kyoya-kun is okay.
Siren got badly hurt, right?
Even a superstar
can't beat an injury, you know?
To you, my dearest, I'll sing a song
of hope that leads to eternity
Feuding in search of peace
For these heroes in prayer
This irony cannot be erased
Learning to cherish solitude
The front and back sides
of this world always overlap
Hey, what's that?
A mirage?
Why would it be here though?
Hey, what the heck is this?!
Impossible!
What happened?!
It's the Mirage.
Where?! Let's get SI-VIS ready—
That's impossible.
It's not impossible!
They were defeated once,
but their motivation isn't—
That's not the problem!
Six locations in Japan alone.
Forty-eight all over the world.
Are these the Mirages exudating
simultaneously right now?
What's that?
A sudden torrential rain?
Is it related to the disaster
at the Harmonia Building by any chance?
None of the estimated values we had
like the speed or the range of
the exudation are helping!
Exudation completed in
thirteen locations already.
There are 35 more to go!
How could this happen?
Apollo must have made up his mind.
You mean he wasn't serious until now?
Exudation of the Mirage
requires a lot of Idea.
A few million people's worth of Idea.
I can't even imagine how much Idea and
XENOS lives he's sacrificing to do this.
A-Anyway, we should send SI-VIS
to at least a location—
That would be a pointless operation.
After allowing 47 locations to be invaded,
what strategic value is there
in protecting only one location
at a high cost?
How can you—
No, she's right, Rui.
President?
I can't deploy SI-VIS right now.
In order to take back this land
Orphe tried to protect...
Mirage.
Rui.
I didn't bring my phone.
Then I'll have to do it on my own.
The world veiled from sight
Touch once and you'll never awaken
from the nightmare
The days that are swallowed up
Everyone has forgotten
Remembering you,
I'm flooded with a symphony
Let it out
No matter how the truth
becomes unrecognizable
I want to protect this undying wish
With every ounce of my being
Let it sound
My voice and your voice
The moment they turn into a song
Our hearts become one
with resonating fantasia
Oh, man. What the hell?
Even if tomorrow never comes
Wasn't I supposed to be a superstar?
With all the wishes in my heart
I'll fight on MELODEA
If only you were here.
Kyoya.
To gain the Idea of
100 million earthlings,
you sacrificed the Idea of
100 million XENOS.
Lose everything or lose 100 million.
Someone had to make a decision.
Well, I admire your decisiveness.
But don't you think that your tendency
to shoulder everything yourself
without relying on anyone
invited Medea's defection?
There's only a few of us left,
and we get a traitor.
That's the work of our
highly esteemed leader.
I don't care how you evaluate me.
Once XENOS is revived, then those who
are restored to life are free to judge me.
I have no intention of complaining.
But aren't you sad to be hated
by those you have saved?
Is that why you didn't finish off Medea?
You can't stand to be loathed
even by a traitor?
Will you purge me?
I can do that anytime.
As long as you bare fangs
to the earthlings, I'll keep you alive.
Listen, Adam, Logos, and Lilith.
This place is probably colder
than the place where you sleep.
Why did you wish for me?
The person named Apollo
said he wasn't interested in me.
But he said you were looking for me.
If you are Lady Eden's kin,
then I thought if you stayed by her,
she might not be lonely.
But I'm lonely.
It makes me sad to be away
from the people I love.
I see.
Are you her...
Her priest, her chamberlain, and...
Do you feel lonely?
No less lonely than
you're feeling right now.
No matter how many years may pass,
I swear your loneliness
will never catch up to mine.
But coming from me,
who's stolen everything from you,
that might be hard to accept.
What happens to me?
What happens to Earth?
Lord Apollo only thinks of saving XENOS.
He will sacrifice everything else.
The Earth, people who live there,
the heart to love others, and...
How can I stop him?
If both Earth and XENOS can be saved,
will you let me see Kyoya again?
Is that what you...
You understand it, right?
You understand my loneliness, don't you?
If you wish strong enough,
if your wish to save everything
calls for a miracle...
But how?
Follow me.
0.02% of Earth's surface area is gone.
The population is even worse.
3% of the population, gone.
Over 100 million people disappeared.
It can't be!
But... But no one has noticed it.
The world has yet to see
the same nightmare that we are.
Hey, you.
You said you'd cooperate with us.
Then bring back the people
who disappeared.
Restore the Earth!
Hayama-kun.
Is it your wish to watch me
cry and apologize?
Blowing off steam by watching me
be tormented by regret.
Is that what you want?
What we want is your knowledge
and skills as XENOS.
Tell us, Medea.
What can you do?
What can we do?
I will invite SI-VIS to a certain stage.
And you will hold a live concert that
involves the entire world on that stage.
A live concert? Where?
Our home world...
where the people of XENOS sleep.
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Tomoko Takedani Sater
Krzysztof Kunc
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Michelle Tymon
In the musical stave
WOW, I let my feelings play
My bright future
WOW, started to shine
Unparalleled
With a smile on my face
I feel like I can even change
the world with you
(3, 2, 1, Singing over)
Intertwining harmony (Harmony)
I wouldn't have believed in miracles alone
This breathless heartbeat (Heart Beat)
I'll let it resonate in
the night sky with my voice
Our dream at full blast
Singing over, forever
Lan lan la la la