Step right up and have a look...
It's time for Yamishibai.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
Sleeper Train
This is the story of some women who have
taken a sleeper train on a vacation...
Wow, so this is what it's like!
Looks more comfortable than I thought.
Staying an extra day and taking the
sleeper train might be worth it.
What do you want to do once we get there?
Oh, I forgot to make sure
we could check in early...
Well, a free-wheeling vacation where we
don't plan everything out could be fun.
Come in.
Sorry to bother you
while you're relaxing.
Thank you for riding with us on
the Evening Star sleeper train.
May I check your tickets?
Oh, sure. Here're both of ours.
Thank you so much.
I'll just check these.
There's one thing I need
to caution you about.
We will be connecting with another
car during a stop tonight.
Connecting?
Right. It'll be dangerous,
so we'd like to ask you not to leave
your car or open your curtains.
We can't even open the curtains?
We ask it for your own safety, miss.
Also, a lot of tickets
have gone missing lately.
Be sure to hold on to yours at all times
until you reach your destination.
Okay.
Well, I hope you enjoy your journey.
"At all times" seems a little extreme.
True. I'm gonna go buy some drinks.
What is that?
Talk about creepy.
Y'know, over by the part of
the car that connects...
And she's asleep. She must've been tired.
Oh, we need to close the curtains, too.
Is this the stop he mentioned?
I'm going to the bathroom.
But we're not supposed to leave the car.
No way. Do you want me to pee in here?
Unbelievable.
That's the car that connected to us?
And it's not a sleeper car.
Man, it's super packed.
What?
It won't turn on? Is it a power outage?
Who are these people?!
Miwa?!
Who are you?!
It's me, the conductor.
I'll need to check your ticket again.
Forget that! My friend...
I think she was screaming...
You let go of yours.
No!
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
The end.