This is...
Oh, Yuri. Morning!
Comet...
How's the party going?
Party?
It's been over since yesterday.
C'mon, get a grip.
There's no doubt about it.
The looping has ended.
Setsu used the Silver Key that I had and
disappeared into the other dimension...
in order to save me.
There's no more Silver Key.
I'll never loop again.
Ooh, Yurinchy!
Wanna get something to eat together?
SQ...
Is Setsu...
"Setsu"?
You good?
Huh?
I guess your memories are still affected.
Well, you'll eventually get it.
That person doesn't exist IRL!
EPISODE 19: EPILOGUE
After Setsu went through that door,
they disappeared from everyone's memories.
The different universe on
the other side of this door
is an entirely separate world
that doesn't affect this universe.
Once they went over there, all trace
of Setsu was erased from this universe.
It's as though they never existed at all.
What's wrong?
The military has issued a request
for us to dock at port.
It must be because we escaped from Liu-An.
But LeVi already confirmed that
there were no Gnosia on board.
They probably just want to be sure.
They're pretty wary
about that kind of thing.
We'd better do as they say.
You don't want to be on their bad side.
If we ignore the request, they will
take us into custody as per space law.
So it's not a request.
It's actually an order.
A military port... They'll check
our identities, won't they?
They're just intimidating us.
I doubt they'll follow through.
We can simply ignore them.
I concur. We have no time
to play along with their farce.
But if they do follow through,
we'll be in a lot of trouble.
We just got outta Liu-An
by the skin of our teeth, bud!
I don't wanna just end up in the slammer.
Hm... What do you think?
Huh?
You're a soldier, right?
Yes. I came from Base 52.
The military...
I think we should stop by.
What shall we do?
Willows bend, not break,
beneath the weight of snow.
Let us follow their orders.
We are changing route!
Call sign sent!
Let them take control of the helm!
As you wish.
Approach confirmed.
The military requests that we disable
all of the ship's defense systems.
Shall we accept?
Yes.
Request accepted.
All defense systems will now be disabled.
So, are we gonna be able
to get off the ship at port?
Apparently, we can disembark
if we fill out the proper paperwork.
We might as well kill some time.
I doubt this will be over quickly.
Though I think anyone with a reason
to be anxious should stay behind.
A-All right.
Knock it off! I said I'm not going.
C'mon, man. Don't be such a drag.
Oh, hey, Yuri!
You should come, too.
It's party time! Right?
You seem rather excited.
Well, duh! This is a
military base, ain't it?
Is there something here?
The red-light district.
Huh?
Some things just don't change,
even after a few millennia.
Honestly... There's nothing more foolish
than letting your desires rule over you.
Man, y'all suck.
C'mon. Let's go.
Wait!
Base 52?
Yes. There's a person
I'm looking for from there,
so I was hoping someone here
might be familiar with it.
Ring any bells?
Base 52... 52...
I think...
He's from there.
Thank you very much.
Um...
Can I ask you a few questions?
Sure. But not for free.
Huh?
Nah, I'm just messin' with ya.
So what did you want to ask me?
Hm... There's no one named Setsu there.
I searched the last hundred years'
worth of personnel records, too.
I see... So that really is what happened.
Huh? What happened?
It's nothing. Thank you very much.
I hope you can find them.
They must be very important to you.
As I thought, their whole
existence is just gone.
The person known as Setsu was
simply never born in this universe.
I'm Setsu.
That never happened.
Or that.
No...
Let go of me!
Hey, now. We're not gonna bite.
It'll be our treat. Come on.
Jina!
Yuri!
Oh? Who the hell're you?
We're under quarantine
after arriving from Liu-An...
because of possible Gnosia infection.
Gnosia?!
L-Let's get the hell outta here.
I guess everyone's pretty scared
of being infected by the Gnosia.
Yeah.
I mean, if they just used
their common sense,
it's pretty obvious that the military
wouldn't have let us into the city
if there was any chance we were infected.
Well, your acting was very convincing.
I guess I just got really good
at lying at some point.
This...
seems to be a navigational record
of historical space voyages.
I see.
It contains about a thousand years' worth
of records for the Allacosia star system.
I never knew something like that existed.
Want to take a look?
Wow...
You can see how the ships
passed through certain areas.
Space traffic controllers
need to know these things.
There are a lot of asteroids
in Allacosia, right?
I'm surprised you knew that.
Setsu told me.
Setsu?
Er, never mind.
Is that the person you
mentioned yesterday?
Yeah.
Everyone says it's because my
memories are messed up, though.
I'd like you to tell me about them.
What?
If you talk about them,
you might feel a little better.
So they went to the other side...
Yeah.
I think that because they went
through the dimensional door
and transferred to another universe,
now they just never existed here.
I see.
I'm sure this must be hard to believe.
I can't even imagine it.
I see.
But I also can't imagine that
you're lying about all this, Yuri.
Jina...
So this Setsu person is
alive in that other world.
Yeah.
But my looping is over,
so I have no way of confirming it.
Ended?
Yeah. That's what they said
when they went through the door.
I have to keep looping on the other side
of this door until I'm done—
until I give you the Silver Key
in that other universe.
So I think they'll give me
the Key in the other universe.
Really?
Huh?
I'm not really sure, but...
Setsu's already gone,
but don't they still have to give the Key
to the you of this universe?
Sorry. I'm just rambling.
It probably doesn't work that way.
Racio!
Sorry! I just remembered
something I need to do.
The Silver Key...
Hmph. Taken an interest to it, have you?
Some use the Key because
they wish to return to the past,
but the frightening thing about it
is that you can't even choose
to end things on your own.
End things?
Indeed.
This thing won't leave its host until
it's filled with the
information it desires.
The loops will continue
until it's satisfied.
You could end up looping for all eternity.
Racio!
There's something I need to ask you.
Hm?
I see.
What do you think?
Will Setsu be able
to close the loop over there?
Hmph. That's what you
call wishful thinking.
I'll be blunt. What Jina said is correct.
In order to connect cause with effect,
Setsu needs to give the you
in this universe the Silver Key.
But...
I'm assuming that Setsu went to the other
universe, knowing this would happen,
in order to save you.
Setsu has to keep looping
in the other universe?
And they knew this would happen?
Run.
Chipie?
Just run, damn it!
Oh? Well, if it ain't Yuri.
Sha-ming?
Perfect timin'.
I was out drinkin' with Chipie
until he ditched me, the bastard.
But you'll do just fine.
Huh? Hey, where are we going?
Heaven!
Our new source of fundin' has arrived!
Now keep those bottles comin'!
Here, have a drink.
Wait, but...
Oh, by the way, here's the current tab.
So pay up, if you could. Thanks.
What?! Uh, I can't pay all this.
Come on! I'm beggin' ya!
Okay, open wide.
So that's why Chipie told me to run...
That bastard really told me that
he was only interested in cats.
Man, he's annoyin'.
I wouldn't say that...
Are you gonna say the same thing?
No point puttin' on airs.
I'm sure there's at least one or
two chicks you wanna take to bed.
There isn't.
Hah! I hate people who try to act
like they're above it all.
Not to mention...
But...
Oh?
But there is someone precious to me.
So, ya bang 'em?
It's not like that.
Hah! So what? You're just gonna stare
at them with your thumb up yer ass?
"Oh, but I'm just too scared!
What if I get hurt?" That it?
What? You got nothin' more to say?
Guess I hit the nail on the head.
That's not true...
If I could go after them, I would have!
But there's nothing I can do.
There's nothing...
There's just nothing...
Are they crying?
How adorable.
Stop!
Is there really nothin' you can do?
Are you sure you're not just lookin'
for an excuse to give up?
Huh?
H-How'd the military inspection go?
It just finished.
No traces of the Gnosia were detected,
so we're free to leave without issue.
Thank goodness.
Where's Racio?
Racio? I believe they just returned...
Racio!
I knew you'd show up.
Where'd you get that Silver Key?
This is my valued experimental subject.
I had to buy it.
Just calm down for a bit.
Huh?
You want to let this Key make a host out
of you, fill it completely, open the door,
and go after Setsu, right?
That's the only way.
Do you think you can pull it off?
I have to!
Setsu is stuck over there,
unable to close their own loop.
If I don't, they'll keep looping forever!
Huh?
Again, calm down.
Why do you think they did
all this to begin with?
Because...
So that you could live.
Because you and the real Yuri
can't exist in the same universe.
That was why the only solution
was for Setsu to go through the door.
So what's going to happen
if you go after them?
You're just going to cause
the same problem again.
All of Setsu's hard work
and your efforts filling up the
Silver Key that opened the door
would be for nothing.
It's quite obvious,
if you think about it logically.
Then what should I do?
Setsu is still over there,
unable to close their loop!
You need to forget them.
This Setsu person doesn't
even exist in this universe.
There's no point in thinking
about someone who doesn't exist.
That's a universal truth.
But that's...
But if you don't like that answer,
I have another.
This is what Setsu wanted.
I couldn't argue with that.
Every single thing Racio said was correct.
What Setsu wanted...
Setsu wanted me... to continue
living in this universe.
And... they wanted to disappear from it.
Um, Yuri...
Otome...
This is a lovely café.
Yeah.
Did Setsu like being here?
Huh?
Was I wrong?
No, you're right.
I'm surprised you figured it out.
It didn't seem like your kind of place,
so I thought that might be it.
But you don't remember
anything about Setsu, right?
No. I'm very sorry.
It's fine. That's how it's supposed to be.
Because in this universe...
That said...
I can't remember their face,
voice, or appearance, but...
Whenever I hear that name,
I feel a little twinge.
A twinge?
Wight awound hwere.
Yuri?!
I knew it! They wouldn't
just disappear so easily.
They wouldn't just cease to be.
Even if they went to another dimension...
A whole other universe...
Their heart...
Their feelings... are stronger than that!
Racio?