The party can't last forever, Zanka old pal.
Guess I'd better offer you up
to the trash beast now.
Good ol' Jabber carried out
his mission like a champ!
Can't wait to get my reward from the boss!
The hell?!
Crap.
Crap, crap, crap, crap, crap...
People might be finishing
their fights already.
I-If I don't hurry, I'll end up dead last...
But... Does that mean I have to start?
I don't know how to start a fight.
Wh-Wh-What do I do?!
H-Hey...
S-So, m-mi-mister...
Mimister?
My name... um...
What was it again?
Ah, um, Fu Oros...tor...
Umfuoros?
Got it. I'm Enjin.
M-Mr. Zodyl... m-my boss...
told me this thing...
"We've gotta make the other Cleaners
we brought here into offerings."
Offerings?
I know I can do that...
but he told me to get it done
before the other Raiders do.
If... I end up in last place...
S-So... I gotta get our fight started already!
Y-Yeah!
So anyway, could you
please maybe hit me first?!
That'll be a no.
A little while earlier...
Episode 18
Oh Zap, Totes Legit
Using wind to throw my hair off
without touching it?
But how long will that work?
You wretch! Don't you turn your back on me!
You're trying my last nerve!
You think you can sneak around
and catch me unawares?!
You slippery little snake!
I truly despise women like you!
Come out this instant!
Are you not also a warrior
who chose the path of battle?!
A true warrior would face me head-on!
I was right on the money.
Your little zappy-zap mode...
It's got a time limit, doesn't it?!
She dodged it?
I wasn't about to let you cut my hair twice.
Just as one learns to perform
fiery Latin dances in heels,
I can move my hair
as if it has nerve endings.
How long do you think I've had this long hair?
Don't take me lightly!
You're pretty legit.
I've never met someone
with such pride in their long hair.
But you're right...
The static electricity charged
by Milet here does have a time limit.
I can willingly put it out as well,
but I can't get it to last longer
than a minute or two.
It's not all-powerful.
Well, hey, I'm glad to hear that.
I thought maybe wind
might be your weak point...
I was getting kind of nervous I might
have to get these windmills working!
Nice to know the time limit
is your weak point instead.
You're optimistic, Riyo.
I know how to compensate for my weak point.
That's what makes me a warrior.
The way she moves...
Noerde! What was your last job?
I lived in a village of women
in the southern lands...
The warrior tribe, Sileia!
Sorry! Never heard of it.
That's unsurprising.
It was destroyed a long time ago!
The way you move isn't suited
to a large weapon like that.
Nah, it totally is.
But I'll admit...
I'm much better fighting alone.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Riyo.
You weren't a kitten after all.
But...
You're still just a kitty-cat.
Hey.
No one could hear a cry
for help from here, right?
No. There's no escape from here.
I see.
No one can hear, huh?
Don't worry. Once this is over,
you'll be offered up
alongside your companions.
Hey...
Why...
Why do you have that thing?!
Enjin said I can't kill people anymore.
So I was trying really hard
to fight without killing you.
But you're just too strong,
so I ended up having to use it.
Thankfully, it seems like nobody can hear it.
I want to finish things here
so I can get going.
I have to protect my team from the enemy.
Don't worry. Those scissors
are my only vital instrument.
I'll never stain them with blood again.
That's a promise I made a long time ago.
This is an ordinary gun I got
from my boss at my last job.
A parting gift.
Don't tell me, you're...
a professional killer?!
That's going to have to
be our little secret, okay?
Lucky for you, Enjin's got me on a leash now.
That means you get to live.
You can't move now,
but I made sure it was a flesh wound.
Make sure that manhole kid saves you.
I'm gonna go look for the rest of my team now.
You know where they are?
I just assumed the Cleaners
would like to keep their hands clean...
There's some real dirty bastards there.
Only the manhole kid and the Raiders' boss
know where they are, huh?
And she said these pipes link
together like blood vessels...
Won't be easy to find them.
I wanna know more about you.
Okay?
I still don't know how Rudo will end up.
But...
Enjin.
Why don't I go and ask her what's what?
Let's you and me learn
to hold our hands out to others.
Together.
Could have just let her be.
Back to the Present
The hell?!
You're too stubborn to die, I'm sure.
Zanka? You okay?
Hey.
Oh, you're alive. Awesome.
Looks like he hit you
with a pretty nasty toxin.
Guess we'd better get you out of here.
We need to get back and get you patched up.
Jabber won.
Noerde lost.
Fu's still waiting for the umbrella-wielder
to make the first move.
Bundus is talking to the "father-son" duo,
trying to get info about the Cleaners' leader.
Rudo.
You Cleaners are tougher than I expected.
What's that supposed to mean?!
What are you doing to them?
We should get moving.
Dammit... You...
Quit tossing me around!
You still haven't told me where we are,
why you're here, or what you want from me!
I'm gonna pound you, asshole!
You just can't do anything
without cursing and flailing, can you?
I made you an offer.
"Want to take the Sphere down with me?"
It's not your mouth
you should be working right now.
It's your brain—considering whether to accept.
Are you the kind of person who can't
do anything unless it's all laid out for you?
Should I prepare a picture book?
Well, I've got one thing worked out!
You're just the kind of asshole I hate!
I wish a more level-headed Sphereite
had fallen down here instead.
I doubt you have anything to contribute
regarding a plan to reach the Sphere.
Allow me to show you, then.
The Watchman series—
Your gloves.
My coat.
And these boots.
I was trying to create my own entries
in the Watchman series.