Heya.
We're home!
Welcome back, Hajime, Rirui.
We brought you something!
Why, thank you! What is it?
I wonder what this is.
A shachihoko walker!
From Yanago, I believe.
Huh. You know your stuff.
Well, I'm something of a scholar, you see.
Rirui beat it up!
My, that is most impressive!
You two must be most
competent adventurers.
Yeah, we are!
I see. In that case...
I've actually been compiling
data on monsters.
Would you be willing to accompany me
into the dungeon, as my escort?
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
EPISODE 7: RIRUI AND COCKO
Thank you for accompanying me today.
Yeah, our pleasure.
Is the kid coming with?
I'm afraid I asked her to stay
behind and wait, but...
What?
The dungeon is dangerous for kids.
You're a kid too!
You never know if
adventurers are any good!
And I know Papa won't say a word
if you two don't do your job!
So I'm going myself!
Cocko! Don't be rude!
Hajime works real hard!
Hmph! We'll see about that.
Hajime's awesome. What a nasty girl!
I hope she trips a trap
and learns her lesson.
TRAP
There's a trap ahead. Watch your step.
I know.
Look. These are trap-detecting glasses.
They'll reveal anything here
on the less-dangerous levels.
You can save your concern for yourself.
Although I guess I'll raise
your trust level slightly.
No differences from my last
observation, it seems.
He's even taking notes
on common monsters like this?
Hey, couldn't you just ask the guild
lady about monsters like this?
Why go to all this trouble yourself?
Aah, yes. A fine question!
There's still so much that
we don't know about dungeons.
There are cases where the monsters
that appear within suddenly change,
or the same monsters
are suddenly a different size.
These changes can cause
much trouble for adventurers.
However, we can sometimes
anticipate these changes.
Have you ever seen a slime quivering
in the corner of a room?
I don't think so.
Well, if you do, instead of killing it,
check back on it the following day.
You should find that its eyes
have turned into gems.
Bwah?! A gem slime?!
Is that true?!
Indeed, it is.
And periodic observation is required
to learn about such changes.
Do you mean to tell me
you didn't even know that?
That's a famous example.
This is what makes
you adventurers so stupid.
There are plenty of other cases too.
Oh, it seems my tongue slipped!
Are you serious?! "My tongue slipped"
doesn't mean you can spit like that!
Now, now, do try to keep
quiet in the dungeon.
No bickering in the the
dungeon, you little goofs!
Shall we take a break?
Why, yes.
Is she drawing or something?
If she sucks, I'll make fun of her!
What is it?
N-Not a thing!
Have you been in this line of work long?
Oh, no, normally I help with farming.
I only pursue my scholarly interests
when I've saved up enough...
If this data proves valuable, I'll be
able to make life easier for my family.
And hopefully make up for the trouble
I put my wife and daughter through.
Mind if I take a look?
Please, go right ahead!
It's adventurers who I hope will gain
the most from my work.
That's certainly impressive.
The stuff in his notes really would
come in handy to adventurers.
I'd love to see his data for myself.
Yeah? I bed it'd prove
useful for the guild too.
By the way, Mr. Shinonome...
Remember when you were away in Yanago?
Looks like I got quite a few requests.
Well, I guess I was gone for five days.
I hate to dump that on you after
the lovely souvenir, but...
I hear you.
Welp, I'll tackle them as they come
like I always do.
Then we'll be counting on you.
You got it.
Excuse me. Pa— er, my father is working,
and I'd like to take
him something to eat.
Not a problem. Just give me a second.
But talk about impressive.
Your father's a scholar, right?
That's amazing!
Oh, no, it's...
Huh? A scholar?
You're a chicken beaster, right?
Your old man's probably
dumb as a brick, then.
A literal birdbrain!
Some dumbass calling himself a scholar?
What kinda joke is that?
You told her!
What do they know?
Nothing about Papa, that's for sure!
My papa's not stupid!
You adventurers are the stupid ones.
What an annoying day!
That birdbrain can't even hit the dungeon
on her own, but she acts so snobby!
What a pain in the butt that Cocko kid is!
You're just a kid too.
She kept making fun of Rirui!
I really hate her!
Her old man may be cool and smart,
but she's no good at all!
She's probably stuck up just
'cause her dad's so smart and all!
Man, I'm hungry.
Are you even listening, Hajime?!
Yeah, yeah. Sure I am.
No, you're not! Even though I'm so mad!
Pay attention!
Dummy...
Rirui, for today...
Mr. Shinonome! I had the the guild
clerk take a look at my data,
and she purchased my research!
She even agreed to buy more
of my notes going forward!
Oh, I am most grateful to you!
Glad to hear it.
I shall be ever so busy from now on!
That being the case...
We'll be staying in this
village for a while.
S-So I wouldn't mind being
friends with you.
What is that face supposed to mean?!
If you have something
to say, just say it!
I want you gone.
Do you have to be so rude?!
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
Why does Rirui have to stay behind?!
Think it over, Hajime!
I'm busy today, okay?!
So what?!
Look, Rirui, Pops is behind on
his work in town, so...
He needs our help because he's so busy!
Man, you really are something.
I swear I'll be of use!
Take me with you, Hajime!
Whoa! Look, a flying slime!
What?! Where does he get off doing that
when Rirui doesn't get to fly?!
Where'd it go, Hajime?!
H-He actually left Rirui behind!
Well, that's how the cookie
crumbles sometimes.
Dang it! Get back here!
Settle down, Rirui!
Release me!
Come on! Easy there!
Don't try and stop me!
Quit struggling!
Why, if it isn't two
bronze-rank adventurers.
Would you be available
to help me out today?
You have work? For us?
You came to the right adventurers!
D-Dragon slaying?
It says ore collection.
You can read, Anyango?
In that case, I'd like you to handle
posting the job listings.
What about Rirui? What should Rirui do?
Could you please clean the floor?
Consider it done! It'll be spotless!
Anyango, could you hand me the
listing for the mountain wolf hunt?
Sure.
Let's see...
Now, you move these two down
and make a note of the number.
Got it!
Let's see... Were these supposed
to go by the entrance?
Rirui can manage!
Rirui! You all right?!
Rirui?
Rirui...
Rirui is useless.
Why would you say that?
You did a great job cleaning!
Anybody can clean!
Aw, come on...
I can't read... I'm weak...
And I'm not cut out to be an adventurer.
I'm so sorry for being
a useless party member.
Don't say that!
You're making me sad!
What happened here?!
I see. It's true you were only doing
chores that anyone could have today.
But seeing you tackle them impressed me.
Now I understand why
you're Mr. Shinonome's partner.
Adventurers who stay local often
end up taking care of jobs
that are effectively leftovers
on relatively short deadlines.
The kind of work where the pay often
doesn't match the effort required.
A lot of it is tiresome,
not to mention boring.
But if you don't take the work
seriously just because it's dull,
it could put the village at risk.
The most important thing
for a resident adventurer
is how earnestly they tackle their tasks.
And that's a major tool that
both you and Mr. Shinonome share.
I'm finally done.
Good work.
They helped me out
with some of my guild work.
Rirui worked hard to tidy
things up around here.
I see.
There's something I want
to ask about, Mr. Shinonome.
Reading and writing, huh?
Well, I don't have any jobs today.
I guess the timing works out.
Hurry up!
Hey, it's Rirui!
Oh, Anya!
You're coming to school today?
School?
You wanna study, right?
I'm stoked to have you in class!
Just go and have a good time.
Come on, let's go!
Meet Rirui and Cocko. I hope you'll
all give them a warm welcome!
Okay!
What is she doing here?
So, Rirui, what should we study today?
Rirui is... bad with writing.
Well, okay then. We'll work on
reading and writing today.
You can read and write, can't you, Cocko?
Could you help Rirui with that?
Understood.
I don't mind teaching you,
but I expect gratitude.
I'll make it simple enough that
even an idiot like you can follow.
You're actually taking this seriously.
You're an adventurer.
Why worry about anything
other than killing monsters?
That's not good enough.
Rirui wants to be able to read the job
postings and look up monster data.
Rirui wants to be like Hajime!
I see.
Well, that's fine.
My dream is also to be
a scholar like my papa.
Stare...
What? What's the problem?
A dream... That's it!
Rirui's dream is to become
an amazing adventurer!
Come on. If you hold it like that,
your handwriting is going to be a mess.
Put it between your fingers.
Like so.
How's it going, Rirui?
Anya!
You're Rirui's new friend, right?
I'm Anyango! Nice to meet you!
W-We're not exactly friends...
Let's play dodgeball, Rirui!
Yeah! Let's do it!
Are you coming?
I'll pass. I want to read a bit more.
If you say so.
Come on, Rirui!
Yeah, okay!
Hey, sorry about the wait!
Hurry it up!
You're in for a whole new Rirui today!
Oh my! A giant armored dragonfly!
Wow! That's awesome!
We don't have this variety in my village.
Let me join you!
Yeah, you want some of this?!
Are you all done reading?
Oh, if it isn't Cocko.
And she's playing with friends! How rare.
Pass to Rirui! Throw it over here!
Now you're gonna get it!
They seem to be getting along.
All of this beautiful nature
and its variety of creatures...
Even Cocko seems more energized.
This is a wonderful village.
NEXT TIME: A RESIDENT OF THE VILLAGE