Four
Where am I?
Adolla?
A pillar...
Where's Sho?
Where's everyone else?
What's happening with the Great Cataclysm?
If I don't stop the Great Cataclysm...
Two
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Episode 19
Those Who Fight Back
There's no end to them.
Hinawa! We're out of time!
We have to hurry. I have
a bad feeling about this.
You lose, Company 8!
Our victory is telling the whole story!
It says that the source of this
world's imaginings is death!
And the response to that
is the Great Cataclysm!
There's a limit to how much
energy you can absorb!
I will end this!
As you say, I'm nearing my limit!
Sorry I've kept you waiting, Haumea!
Haumea?
Hey!
Where are you, Haumea?
I look away for one second,
and she's gone.
Haumea!
Haumea. Are you all right?
My head... is splitting.
Everyone's bad feelings...
are coming into Haumea's head...
Haumea.
Haumea!
Haumea! Haumea!
Haumea.
Don't worry about Haumea!
Haumea can hear inside your head!
If it will make your burden
even a little easier to carry,
then hit me until you feel better.
She wore herself out, eh?
Did Haumea give you those wounds?
Your face looks awful.
Even in sleep, there
is no rest for Haumea.
All of humanity's emotions
pour into her little head.
The only escape available to her
is to enjoy the madness and malice.
You're Charon the Reflector, aren't you?
Why don't you absorb the damage?
Her violence is her pain.
If it helps me to understand her pain
even a little, I will accept all of it.
How pointless.
Haumea's pain is my pain, too.
If you become a Guardian,
you'll understand.
Continuously receiving the
collective unconscious...
Anyone other than Haumea
would have broken.
She was born to be the symbol
of all female saints.
She's always had the goodness of heart
necessary to accept people's wickedness.
Even now, after taking in all
that malice, she's still alive.
She's swallowing all of humanity's evil
with that little body of hers.
Lady Haumea, it's time for mass.
Curiosity
It's been ten years since the saintess
awakened to her Adolla Burst.
Desire
Interest
Fear
Taboo
Respect
Wickedness
It's changed her so much.
Growth
Interest
Temptation
Curiosity
Respect
No.
I must not think about anything.
Lady Haumea knows all.
Still...
Desire
Respect
Curiosity
Fear
Temptation
She's grown so beautiful.
Wickedness
Taboo
Interest
I wonder what lies beneath that crown.
All right.
Thank you!
Hate
Deceit
Nothingness
Cunning
Evil
Humiliation
Desire
Despair
Hate
Futility
Regret
Depravity
Indolence
I can't break yet.
Hate Futility Despair Regret Malice Humiliation Fear Desire
Indolence Desire Futility Despair Humiliation Fear Hate Regret Malice
Let's enjoy all this wickedness.
Calm down, Haumea!
But it's hilarious! Isn't it?!
It can't get any better! Just
disappear! You're getting in my way!
Are you all right?
I went on a little rampage, that's all.
Of course I'm all right.
Is that so?
Hey, Charon?
Charon, how do you feel about me?
What? How do I feel about you?
I've never thought about it.
You can see inside people's heads, right?
Why don't you tell me?
Unconditional Love
Haumea has battled this
world's darkness all alone!
All in order to burn this planet
and purify it with flames!
Charon?
To bring salvation to this planet!
Charon. Charon. Charon. Charon? Charon!
Illuminate the saintess's
darkness and be purified!
Charon. No!
You can do the rest on
your own, right, Haumea?
No!
What's that?
What a shame.
Moon!
SILENCE
What happened?
An eye?
This world and Adolla are connected.
This world and Adolla
are connected.
Images
and
reality...
Images and reality...
are fusing into one
...are fusing into one.
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Year 198 of the Solar Era.
One hundred and fifty years after
the previous Great Cataclysm.
And now...
We've been waiting for this!
We've been waiting for this!!
The Great Cataclysm!
The Great Cataclysm
Episode 19 "The Final Imagining"
Can you hear me?
This is what I have heard all this time...
Humanity's collective unconscious.
All the hope in this world,
what might also be called optimism,
is no more than giving up.
Madness
Madness.
Passivity
Passivity.
Indifference
Indifference.
Rage.
Rage
Destruction
Destruction.
Fear
Fear.
Hate
Hate.
Despair
Despair.
There is no such thing as true hope.
In all of creation,
from the moment of birth, all living
things are headed for destruction.
People and stars alike.
Please try to imagine it.
Imagination gives rise
to every possibility...
and it erases every possibility.
One Two Three Four Five Six Seven Eight
Two Three Four Five Six Seven
Now, let's move forward...
toward the end of this tale.
Despair...
is nothing special.
Large fires have broken out
in every area of the Empire!
It's impossible to know
the number of casualties!
What is that eyeball in the sky?
So this is the Great Cataclysm?
The horizon is burning.
It's the end of days!
Please save me!
Captain Huo Yan!
Your orders!
Konyango! First, guide the
civilians to a safe area!
A safe place, you say? Does a safe
place even exist on this planet?
It's just like the holy scriptures said.
Long ago, humanity angered the planet,
and the world was enveloped in flames.
That was the day of the Great Cataclysm.
And the flames rose up ferociously.
The places where humanity
lived, the words they spoke...
The flames raged with a force to burn up
all the culture that mankind had built.
It's divine punishment!
The world is already...
Rekka wanted this?
This is the world he strove for...
This is the path he believed in?
What is that huge eyeball in the sky?
Is this what everyone is seeing?
Please let it be something
that only I am seeing.
Captain Hibana, the state that
you have been researching
is occurring within the 5th, as well.
What?
Doppelgangers.
5th Angels Three! Hurry up
and help us with the rescues!
This world is already done for!
That's right. Shall I trade
places with you, then?
The world is burning.
Is this despair?
I can see it, Burns.
Through your eyes, I can
see what Adolla looks like.
I understand the world's rules.
The thing that will stir
everyone to action is...
I've been waiting for this moment!
Striking the stone bridge over and
over and over and over and over!
I've waited for this moment.
At last, I will see
Adolla with these eyes!
At last, my dearest wish will be granted!
Evangelist! Hurry!
Please show yourself to me here!
You can't be serious,
Giovanni! Give Yu back!
It's no use now.
I'm already a parasite inside Yu's
brain, and I've fused with this body.
It's impossible for you
to do anything to me.
I wouldn't mind returning this body
to you... after I've seen Adolla.
Though the world will already
be destroyed by then!
Yu!
Why?!
Why do you always...
So this is the final floor, is it?
I wondered who it could be.
It's the plasma user.
You're quite late, aren't you?
There's nothing you can do now.
Yu? No.
I have already achieved my goal!
Will you still try and cut me down?
Along with this body?
People like you, who only look
at the surface and make a fuss,
will leave nothing behind
and will know nothing.
Begone, you cowardly, vulgar insect!
Yu!
Arthur, you...
He's fine.
Wh-What did you say?
Yu? Yu!
Vulcan? Lisa-san?
And Arthur-san, too?
Yu.
Yu, is it really you? It's you, right?
Thank goodness!
Vulcan.
Wh-What happened?
Arthur, how did you do this?
Oh. I burned the monster that
had made its nest in Yu's brain,
Giovanni, and nothing else.
Like with a gamma knife.
I'm sorry I took so long.
It took longer than expected
to acquire the crystal rod.
Huh?
Could it be that you're advancing in...
But with this event, my EXP has maxed out.
Vulcan, everyone, it's thanks to you.
Oh! That's right!
What is it?
Arthur-san, here.
I didn't get the chance to give it to you.
I made it with the leftovers of
a star fragment Vulcan gave me.
It's a Star Ring!
So you finally finished it?
Yeah.
Is this proof that I cleared the event?
Yes! Please keep it with you, Sir Knight!
Drago
I accept with gratitude!
Thank you, Arthur.
I'm not sure how I should
describe you now.
Now, I have mastered what
it is to be Knight King.
Indeed.
Please don't hesitate
to refer to me as such!
He truly is a Knight King!
Vulcan! Is everyone safe?
Somehow, thanks to Arthur.
I'm sorry we couldn't come to you.
No, it seemed like it was
rough out there, too.
Yeah.
What is all this?
The end we strove for.
The unification happened.
Images and reality became one.
It seems that half the planet is burning.
Inspector Licht!
Is there anything we can do?
Given the scope of these flames...
If we don't know where they originated...
It's hopeless.
Joker!
Did you figure something out?
The thing that's burning the world right
now is humanity's negative emotions.
Basically...
Madness
Madness.
Passivity
Passivity.
Indifference
Indifference.
Rage
Rage.
Destruction
Destruction.
Fear
Fear.
Hate
Hate.
Taken all together,
they are human despair.
The flames of the Great Cataclysm use
the image of humanity's despair as energy.
Which means that human despair is
destroying this planet through fire.
According to Arrow-san,
the White Clad feared Shinra-kun's
transformation into a hero.
Was a hero an impediment to
causing this Great Cataclysm?
So the image of despair is important
to kickstarting the Great Cataclysm!
It's a total shocker!
It's a total shocker
Then that means... What does that mean?
Despair
The fuel for these flames
is human despair.
If that's true...
Great Cataclysm
then hope is the thing
that can put them out!
Commander Sho said not to abandon hope.
Hope? Are you sure?
I know it's odd for a scientist like me
to say something so fantastical,
but in the eyes of people
from previous eras,
the world we lived in would have always
looked like some made-up fantasy.
Okay. The 8th is going
to trust you, Licht!
Despair doesn't suit us in the 8th!
Of course not!
Captain Obi, you are humanity's light.
Please show us the way!
We will follow you anywhere!
Don't abandon hope!
I guess I didn't need to say it, huh?
To Be Continued
Fire Force Chapter 3
Now, into battle.
Next Time
Is that the man who kept
following Tamaki around?
Assault, again, you're...
If you say it that way,
then yes, but... Nay!
Next time, "Where Hope Is."
Episode 20
Where Hope Is
Return to the great flame of fire. Látom.