I'm sad.
I'm so sad.
They erased Akari@Hospital
so soon after she was born.
It's too sad.
My heart is breaking, truly!
You've spent eight days being sad.
I beg you, come to your senses!
When one door is closed, another opens!
That is the way of the world!
After all, you finally found him!
You're right, Garan.
I'll permit you to hug me.
I am truly honored!
Master K...
Maybe I'll pay the onibi user a visit.
Sad Boy K
Um, isn't this...
Pig Camera
Pig Camera?
Yep. This is the scene.
It's where you'll be exorcising
ghost accounts.
Uh, do I know you?
C'mon, man, it's me! Azaki!
I'd stand out in monk's robes
in the city, right?
This is a disguise!
Okay, let's get down to business.
Inside this building—
Excuse me!
Do you know how attractive you are, sir?!
And so tall!
What? I, uh... Um...
W-Would you mind grabbing dinner with us?
Er, I'm actually on the job right now.
A-And as it just so happens,
I've cut ties with the world.
Sworn poverty, chastity...
All that good stuff!
He's adorable!
What's he talking about?
He was staring at my tits! He's down bad!
C'mon, let's go!
What'd he come here for again?
He's utterly hopeless.
We began detecting spirit signals in
the Pig Camera building a few hours ago.
Kakiko Itabashi
One customer was badly injured.
We think it might be
a ghost account nexus.
A nexus?
Do ghost accounts swarm or something?
Ghost accounts are digital beings.
They need to periodically "charge up"
inside electronic devices or they die.
Electronics stores are inevitable
hotbeds of paranormal activity.
Can someone explain...
why I have to team up with these two?!
This feels like a personal attack.
For once, we're in agreement.
Azaki-sensei loves mocking us.
You know that.
Look, you've got me all wrong.
Kasubata's one thing,
but I'm as normal as they come.
Normal guys don't cackle
when they go berserk!
I wanna ditch so bad.
My fave's livestream
starts in just two hours!
How will he remember me if I'm
not sending superchats? He'll forget me!
Hang on, is your fandom
more important than a mission?
What's wrong with that?
You want a face full of goo?
I never wanted to be an exorcist
in the first place.
Wh-What's with this girl?
Your mission is to clear out
all the ghost accounts in the building.
The staff and customers
have already evacuated.
Our intelligence division has determined
that only low-level accounts are present,
but don't let your guard down.
Closed
We apologize for any inconvenience. Thank you for your understanding.
Pig Camera Headquarters
Please, you three...
Do your best to stay alive.
All right, let's do this!
You're not in charge.
Unlocked Smartphones
I've never been in an empty
electronics store before.
It's neat, but it's creepy.
Let's take out the trash and get going.
H-Hey, shouldn't we be doing
this a bit more cautiously?
Wh-What's up?
You wanna chat, girlie?!
Uru—
Cyber out.
Parasocial Pistol!
Parasocial Pistol
Her goo became a gun?!
Kiyomi Urusugawa is a clingy fangirl.
She stalks a musician.
That's awesome—
Say what?!
She's a clingy fangirl stalker.
Yami Kenpi-chan
YAMI
ilu ilu ilu ilu ilu ilu ilu ilu
These bitches don't deserve you
Reply
Nerima Ward, huh?
Don't you dare date anyone
love love love love love love love love love
She loves a guitarist or bassist
or something from some band,
and she does things like zoom in
on his social media pictures
A woman took this, right?!
to look for women reflected in his eyes
or find out where he's living
based on background details.
She's made countless new accounts
to evade various bans.
She's a delusional
piece of extra-clingy shit.
Beg pardon.
First of all, it's not "some band."
Their name is Yami Ichigo Union.
Kureha-kun is their bassist.
And I'm not a stalker! My love is pure!
In short...
How you use your smartphone
has a major effect on the way
your cyberkinesis manifests.
Everyone with offensive cyberkinesis
has a terrible personality.
Of course! That's why I have fire powers!
Kasubata!
H-How did he suddenly...
They've been going at each other
this whole time, but now...
No, wait.
They've been doing this forever.
Exorcism is about teamwork.
This is real exorcism!
Close call, huh?
Talk about teamwork!
A close call you caused, asshole!
You nearly killed us with your onibi!
My teamwork...
Pig Camera
Awesome!
Man, talk about a lucky break!
Yeah.
Dunno what the fuss is about,
but the evacuation cleared out
all the customers and staff!
Once we resell all this stuff...
Totes annoying.
Like I said, I never wanted
to become an exorcist.
It's lame, it's dangerous,
and I'm a lover, not a fighter.
But I didn't have a choice!
It's what I'm good at!
Plus, I need money to support my fave.
Yami Kenpi-chan
YAMI
YAMI ICHIGO UNION
To express my love for him as a fan.
Imo-kenpi
That's why I'm doing this!
End of story!
Why are you acting so put off?
You wanted to know why
I came to Miden Academy, right?
Got a problem?!
Hey, watch where you point that thing!
Get to work, you two!
I really don't have a problem with you!
You're just not how
I pictured an exorcist.
Man, I'm just incompatible
with you attackers.
All the times I've had to ban-evade
after some loser reported me...
You only have yourself
to blame, Urusugawa.
Huh?! I'm talking about you,
you sneaky little skidmark.
Skidmark? How vulgar!
You're plenty vulgar yourself!
Beg pardon!
Y-Yeah, they're incredible!
And arguing all the while!
Anyway, he's a trashbag,
but his skills are top notch.
We don't need any more
attackers in our class.
Especially not with demon flames!
Yeah, it'd be hard to trust your six to
someone who can kill you with a touch.
Still...
Exorcism is about teamwork!
Pig Camera
All right. This is the last floor.
Yami Ichigo's livestream
is gonna start any minute now!
Let's get this over with.
You sit in the corner, watch, and learn.
Damn it.
Gotcha!
And that's...
The end of that!
Wuzzat?
I was just making my dolly photogenic!
Kirika-chan
And now...
I got me some new dollies!
So photogenic!
Her wound is healing?
She's got a curse!
I thought they said
it was all low-level ghosts!
Back off, Urusugawa!
I'm not scared.
My sticky stuff is holding her.
She can't do any—
La, la, la!
So photogenic!
Let's give you some bigger eyes
and more slender limbs!
Get your grubby hand off me!
You asshole!
Totes annoying.
Get outta my way!
K-Kasubata!
I feel like I'm getting
thrown around a lot these days.
What's with that thing?
Is that really a low-level ghost?
Weren't you paying attention
in cyberkinesis class?
Let's snap a pic!
Ghost accounts can have special abilities.
Get off me, dammit! Let me go!
Accounts with curses.
They're powerful foes,
considered mid-level or higher.
Normally, we'd form a plan and create
a strike team to send at one.
If we try to take it out like this,
we're all dead for sure.
Let me go, uggo!
Who are you calling "uggo"?
I'm totes photogenic!
This one's different.
Totally different from the others.
Completely different.
Pics?
Go on without us.
I'll free Urusugawa and
be right behind you.
K-Kasubata...
Don't even think about fighting.
You'll just distract me.
I'd be too worried
about your flame to focus.
She belongs to our class! Give her back!
So photogenic!
It's not working!
She regenerates the second she's hit.
Actually, she's not photogenic at all!
I know! I'll muss her head
until the blood gooshes out!
That'll make it better!
Urusugawa!
He set a doll aflame with onibi to throw?
I've got Urusugawa!
Haven't you ever heard?
Exorcism is about teamwork!
I don't give a shit
if I distract you, dumbass!
I'm a member of class 1-B, too!
Pics?
I'm making things photogenic! Get lost!
Run!
The shutter's down!
Hide!
Nobody told us there
was a mid-level inside.
We need reinforcements—
Azaki-sensei?
Where did that lech run off to?!
At such a critical time, no less.
Where are you? Where'd you go?
Shit. What do we do?
You're dying either way,
so come out and play!
See? I helped out, didn't I?
It worked out this once.
But what if you'd lost control
and hit me or Urusugawa—
Huh? What?
H-Hey, my flame's still going!
That's not safe! If you get any closer...
Hey!
Kasubata?
Th-The demon flame is touching...
It's a cursed flame that steals
life force with just a touch.
Huh?
You're not dead.
I thought so.
Look at that.
She hasn't regenerated
from the damage my flame did.
The concept of yin and yang is integral
to the world of spirit power.
When a human wields
the power of a ghost account,
its effects are inverted.
Y-You're saying...
Get with the program.
I'm saying your demon flame
doesn't work on the living.
Conversely, it's fatally toxic
to ghost accounts.
Like a video game where healing magic
does damage to undead creatures.
Then my onibi isn't a demon flame...
It's a flame that makes demons cry!
Onipien
Demon Sadface
Onipien!
Awesome!
Is it?
Where'd you go? Don't leave me!
Okay, what's the plan, Kasubata?
I came here to get strong.
This is our shot to make something happen.
It'd be stupid to run away, right?
Don't be absurd.
That's a mid-level ghost account.
We can't fight when
we don't stand a chance.
You better come out
while I'm still asking nicely!
And if we do stand a chance?
Then of course we fight it, asshole.
Beg pardon.
Is it okay to leave Urusugawa like that?
She'll be fine. That wasn't
enough to take her out.
You ruined my picture-perfect looks.
Come out, you brats!
I'll give you you photogenic deaths!
You called?
Enishiro, your demon flame...
No, your "Onipien" cancels out
her regeneration.
Make an opening, and I'll...
bash the hell out of her!
So much for being polite!
Is that how cyberkinesis
attackers do things?
Shut up and get heated,
you flamebaiting bastard.
Enishiro!
I-I'm fine.
She just grazed me. I'm good.
I've had it up to here.
I'm gonna find a way to make you
guys into the best pic ever.
I know! I'll tear your arms and legs off
while you're alive and screaming,
then put you back together and
hang you out the windows!
A light show of blood and flesh!
So photogenic!
I feel like such an artist right now!
S-Scary!
Special Episode
Ten Delinquents vs Me
This reminds me of how
my head used to pound
and I'd get goosebumps when
I was raring up for a big fight.
You asshole.
I'll cram your heads into that tramp's
coochie and put you out for all to see!
It'll make the best photo.
Even better than that little girl
I messed up photogenically before!
Yami Ichigo Union [Official] has begun their livestream
Just now
Let's get photogenic!
She's fast! I can't hit her!
Crap!
There's one down!
Screw you!
Okay, time for another Yami Ichigo Union
meet-up with our Little Ichigos.
Hey, it's your boy Kureha.
The stream's started.
I had a streak going of being
the first to make a superchat.
If my fave forgets me, what are you
gonna do to make it up to me?!
Urusugawa!
You worthless little tramp!
Can't move!
Beat her down, losers!
I'll tear through this crap!
Look, we've got a superchat already.
From "Kureha Sukipi-chan-san."
That's a funny name.
"I'm getting front-row seats
next time," she says, Kureha.
Hey, thanks.
Who the hell are you?
Keep your paws off my fave,
you stupid bitch!
She's crazy!
Urusugawa, you've got
a terrible personality yourself!
Looks like you're enjoying
the situation too, Enishiro!
You assholes.
Am I the only normal one here?
Like hell you are!
All righty, then...
Sounds like we're a trio of jackasses!
Don't use such vulgar language!
It's a mid-level. We'll have to send
the second-floor students.
I can't believe the intelligence
division slipped up like that!
If we don't hurry, it'll be too late!
Today
Unread messages
Urgent help requested against a mid-level ghost account
He pulled a mid-level
on his first mission?
Lucky Enishiro, huh?
Or is that unlucky?
Sounds like reinforcements
haven't arrived yet.
How will our Aoringo fare?!
Are you kidding me?
He's in serious trouble, right?
You don't think they're
really fighting that thing, do you?
Those three could maybe handle it.
Nuh-uh! It's too powerful!
But doesn't that get you excited?
Hell no!
I think I'm excited, too!
No way!
A flamebaiter...
A basher...
A clinger...
Mercy!
What if users of the three
most annoying kinds of cyberkinesis,
the worst trio possible, got together?
Nope.
Pics...
I can't believe I lost to these
unphotogenic brats!
Wait, am I totally photogenic
as I'm disappearing right now?!
We got her... right?
Yeah, we beat her.
I-I almost died there.
Man, what a freaking pain!
That felt good as shit!
I mean...
How vulgar.
Anyway, just admit it already.
This is the kind of person you are.
I get it.
I did what I did for Akari.
That much is true.
But it was also my way of venting.
I guess... I enjoyed it.
I'm trash, right?
Yeah, you are.
Total garbage.
But trash tends to make a good exorcist.
Plenty of people have given up
after their first mission broke them.
It's nice when the garbage
is self-aware about it.
Better than garbage who
thinks he's the good guy.
What was that?
You guys...
Want some imo-kenpi?
When we get back,
we'll practice our combos.
I'll bash the hell out of you,
so be ready.
Okay!
All right...
Mission complete!
What a mess.
The merchandise in shambles.
I feel like I'm in shambles, too.
So sad...
Crap! Gotta make a comment
on the stream.
I can't believe Urusugawa is
the most messed-up of us all.
So sad.
I feel bad for the guys
who "Kirika-chan" killed.
They're looters who ignored
the evacuation order.
They got what they deserved.
C'mon, dude.
So sad.
You're sad? About what?
I'm sad.
Another ghost account got erased.
I'm so sad.
You're...