Hayashi-san?
Where are we rushing to?
It's Niimi-san.
He took his own life.
No...
Anyway, get to Gion.
I hear he slit his belly in a party room.
What an awful mess.
Wasn't he a Miburo?
Gives me the creeps.
Let us through!
Excuse us!
Niimi-san... Why?
Blue Miburo
Nio, don't look.
No, I'll be fine.
Don't force yourself.
I'll look. I need to see what happened.
Yuck. It's a sea of blood in here.
He sure wasn't subtle about it.
Pay the proprietor.
Cleaning fees included.
Call some people to remove the body.
No need, sir.
We have already received full payment.
What?
A bit before they found the body,
a big man in a white coat
sauntered out covered in blood spatter.
Serizawa. Who else could it be?
Why would Commander Niimi kill himself?
Beats me.
Maybe he was raising funds in secret
and had to take responsibility?
You dopes. Serizawa got him, obviously.
Oh, you mean Serizawa killed him
and made it look like seppuku?
Stay
out
No
\h\hpeek-
\h\hing
I don't see how that's possible.
Niimi must have slit his own stomach.
He had no other unusual wounds.
Asano-sensei here is an ex-doctor.
We should trust him on this.
I'm sure someone else
beheaded him, of course.
That'll be Serizawa.
He threatened Niimi-san into seppuku.
That's hard to believe.
Whatever Commander Niimi intended,
we have to face facts.
The problem is...
we inspectors have lost
a leader we can't replace.
So what are we going to do now?
Why?
I'll take it from here. This is my job.
The measure of a samurai is his death.
There's more to this.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
Think. What's going to happen next?
What...
I can't defend more than
this mat I'm sitting on.
What can I do?
Don't tell me...
Yamanami, what will happen
is a foregone conclusion.
Interpret it however you
need to after the fact.
What a surprise.
I hold an entirely different view.
Niimi-san, you were an admirable man.
We can't afford to let discord
in our ranks get any worse.
Isn't it time we did something?
I know.
Toshi.
We need to talk.
Somewhere we won't be overheard.
Serizawa-san must die.
I will kill him.
Wh-Why, though? You said to wait before.
The month I stipulated has passed.
If I may ask, what was
that month's reprieve for?
I cannot say.
No.
I won't let you join in.
I need you to stay out of this plan.
Do you want to ruin everything?
What will I ruin?
By losing, you mean?
Would that inconvenience you?
That's not what I mean.
If word gets out you killed him
over a grudge,
what happens to we Miburo
under the banner of "sincerity"?
It'll be all over. No, you can't
be there when it happens.
This is no grudge.
Dueling man-against-man
is the samurai way.
This is about manhood and humanity.
Fine.
Kill me, then.
Otherwise, I'm leaving the Miburo
and going back to Edo.
Make your choice.
Will you let me do this my way?
Or will you do it your way
in a Miburo without me?
Very well.
I realize that I forced you
to delay in the first place.
The matter is entirely in your hands.
But, Toshi, you cannot
defeat Serizawa-san.
I know that.
I'll do it.
I'll kill Serizawa-san.
I see. Very well.
Hold your horses.
Harada-san?
I'm gonna kill that bastard Serizawa.
You couldn't do it.
I said I'm gonna do it!
Hasumukai! Hasumukai!
Thank you, Harada-san.
I'm going to do it.
Come on. We can't fall out now.
We should settle this the Shieikan way.
A duel it is, then.
I don't see why not.
Bring it on.
Nagakura?
I cannot bring myself to do this.
I can't blame him,
not when he's training Taro.
He practices the same style as Serizawa.
That may give him pause.
He just wants to stick to his principles.
That's the kind of man he is.
So you've got a shot but I don't?
Let's put that to the test.
Yes, we shall.
Spears are tricky.
They have an overwhelming
advantage in reach.
And Sanosuke's spear
reaches farther than most.
But you'd only know that
if you'd already fought him.
He usually sticks to a sword
when he spars with us.
No doubt he feels the advantage
a spear gives him is unfair.
So, when fighting a spearman,
it's all about how to get in close.
Even Soji will have a hard time.
That's backwards.
What?
Okita's using a reverse grip.
You see, I'll do whatever it takes
to accomplish my goal.
A far cry from a samurai, I know.
But I'd say I win.
Is that even allowed?
You sure you wanna treat your sword
that way? It'll break on you.
It was already chipped.
I was going to get a new one
from Sakura-san tomorrow.
Hijikata! When do we do it, and where?
Have you worked out a plan yet?
Tell us!
Fine.
We move in five days,
on the 18th of the ninth month.
Why that day?
Our whole force is supposed
to be partying in Shimabara.
The reward for our work during the coup
and mopping up will pay for it.
It's been planned for a while.
Serizawa and company
will be there, of course.
So we get them dead drunk,
then just plain dead?
But what if they don't
drink that heavily?
We give them sleeping powder.
That won't be a problem.
We'll call three litters
to take them home.
Everything before that is set up.
But the Yagis have small children
and relatives in the house.
And Serizawa-san and his friends
sometimes invite geisha or mistresses.
Can you really ensure
there will be no witnesses?
The Hishiya's proprietress, Oume,
Itosato of the Wachigaiya,
and Kichiei of the Kikyoya?
They won't be a problem, either.
We won't let them reach the Yagi house.
I'll bribe the litter bearers.
We'll strike in the middle of the paddies
between Shimabara and Mibu.
We'll have the bearers clear out first.
We can tell them we want
to watch the fireflies.
Then we quietly skewer them,
litters and all.
If that doesn't kill them, a bad wound
will make them easy pickings.
Then we blame Choshu extremists
and call it a night.
So that's why you said
I couldn't pull it off.
Would you hesitate to
kill a drunk in a litter?
I know I wouldn't.
Good thing Shinpachi's not here.
Kondo-san and Nagakura-san
wouldn't take kindly to our plan.
We need to do this
without anyone getting hurt.
Take no chances.
No one can ever know it was us.
Soji and I will kill Serizawa.
Fine. I'll kill Hirayama.
But don't forget Hirama.
We need one more guy.
I volunteer.
Yamanami. Do you understand
what that means?
You need someone prepared
to do what it takes.
Who better than me?
Fine.
What about Noguchi-kun?
We don't need to kill their errand boy.
We'll send him to Osaka
on "official business."
Gen-san, will you take him?
Hijikata, would you mind
answering one question?
I know Serizawa crossed a line,
and there's the secret order from Aizu,
but is that really all this is about?
Are you sure you don't have
a more personal reason?
You don't have to join us
if you have doubts.
We only need you to keep your mouth shut.
I never said I wasn't gonna do it.
You're forgetting someone.
Taro.
He'll stick with Serizawa
to the bitter end.
Hajime, he's your job.
You want me to kill him?
Don't even joke about that!
In that case, you handle Taro!
I'll kill Serizawa.
I don't mean that.
What, then?
I want you to save Taro.
18th of the 9th month, Bunkyu 3
(October 30th, 1863)
It's really coming down, huh?
I've been feeling gloomy all day.
This is a good omen!
A rain of blessings!
Masa-san. Yashiro-san.
Woo-hoo!
Today, we party!
Yeah!
You're going to Shimabara
to celebrate, aren't you?
Yup. With pretty girls.
We might even, y'know...
Whoa there. He's too young
to hear about that.
Kids aren't allowed
in the red-light district.
Numskulls.
I'm glad they're having fun.
Anyway, I bet Commander Niimi
wanted to celebrate, too.
I mean, he arranged the whole thing.
What? Niimi-san did?
Not that it matters now that he's dead.
That's strange.
Niimi-san took his own life,
meaning he could choose the day he died.
So he wanted the party
to be after his death?
What for?
Everyone's going to the party, right?
Yeah.
Except Inoue-san, who took Noguchi
and some other guys to Osaka.
No idea why, but I guess
Hijikata ordered it.
Do something about Serizawa.
I assume you know what I mean.
Kill Serizawa.
That's what they meant.
Is this all a setup?
A setup to help
Hijikata-san's group kill Serizawa?
Planned by Niimi-san?
Is Serizawa-san really
in the dark about it?
Nagakura-san.
Excuse me, but where's Hijikata-san?
No idea.
But look at this rain. What do we do?
Hey.
Man, I've gotta eat something.
I feel like a nap.
Why'd they suddenly...
What's wrong?
You're covered in sweat.
It's today.
If something's going to happen,
it'll be today.
Hey!
Spilled water doesn't come back.
I can't scoop up anywhere near all of it.
Just one mat's worth.
But I'll still do what I can.
The measure of a samurai is his death.
I heard Serizawa-san's position.
If I possibly can...
I heard his wish, too.
What can't I compromise on?
Which way should I steer things?
Steel yourself. Be strong.
Aiming for that and working toward it...
is what makes me, me.
It's really coming down, huh?
I wonder if it'll stop by tonight.
Beats me.
Do your best for Taro-kun.
What do they all think I am?
Fine.
Who's there?
It's me.
Oh? But you always come at night.
We're short on umbrellas.
Give me all you've got.
I'll leave the money here.
Take those.
I may not be able to come tonight.
Is something special going on?
Nothing, really.
I just can't make it. That's all.
And?
And I don't want you
trying to die tonight.
Then tell me a story. Any story.
I won't die if you do.
Let me think...
There's a man called Serizawa.
He's a true samurai, I guess.
Taro.
Give me a massage.
Y-Yes, sir.
What's going on?
He's chewed me out and thrown stuff at me
on sight for the past two months.
But he's so mellow now. Almost as if—
You call that a massage? Harder!
Stomp on me for all you're worth!
You've got some nerve,
stepping on the face of Serizawa Kamo!
I'm dead meat!
Bring your sword.
Huh? Sir?
Remove the pin and hilt and do
maintenance, just like I showed you.
You remember what to do?
Here.
Yes, sir.
That thing will never look right on you.
S-Sorry.
I'm parched. Get me some tea.
Yes, sir.
It's weird.
He's definitely acting weird today.
Manly
Here, sir.
Oh, no! I can't believe I...
You little...
I'm so sorry!
I'll wipe it up and bring a fresh cup.
He's mad as hell!
U-Um, isn't today...
Serizawa-sensei!
Our litters will be here soon.
Right.
Taro, fetch my coat.
Yes, sir.
Guess I'll go.
I... I'll get out of your way.
A party at the Sumiya in Shimabara!
It's like we're rich big shots.
Hey! Mr. Moneybags! Mr. Moneybags!
Shima-
bara
We have reached the main gate
of Shimabara, sir.
Near
Yet Far
Next time
Todo Heisuke here.
The rain's really coming down.
This weather's as stormy
as we feel inside.
I'm at a party,
but I can't let myself get drunk.
We're all trying to shake off our doubts
and run straight down the paths we chose.
But I can't begin to tell what's right.
So I'm just gonna do what I can.
Next time: "The Path of Asura."
The Path of Asura