Kyoya.
Nagi!
I've finally caught you,
my bird in a cage.
A Diva in the Cage
You will continue to sing
the song of hope right here.
Until the universe is no more.
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
It's Show Time
The price of living in the time of freedom
"So, what do you want to do?"
Just standing there with my empty body
Like a calling to protect the world
I craved an unequaled gift
Lost in night's darkness
Until a voice called out to me
Like the light that declares the dawn
I'll take you with me at
any cost (I pray and wish)
Beyond the Echo-verse (To the future)
Just being with you makes me strong
It's not an exaggeration
That encounter was a supernova
(Our eyes were locked)
In an instant, everything that I am
(In an instant)
Will be changed forever (Just to be)
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
Destiny is Calling us now
Just to be who we are
Just to be by your side
What the heck is that?!
So huge!
Kokytos.
You know what it is, Medea?
I have seen it activated once before.
Ten years ago.
Ten years ago. You mean...
It finally awakens once more.
Kokytos, which went to sleep
along with Lady Eden ten years ago.
Ten Years Ago
That's Earth.
That's where he is.
Can you get us there, Priest?
This is going to solve everything, right?
Our planet, our people... and most
importantly, Lady Eden will be saved?
If we can get all of Earth's
Idea, it is possible!
Moreover, he betrayed us and
contacted the earthlings.
They must be annihilated now
or it will come back and bite us.
Saving our planet or defeating Orphe.
Which do you wish to achieve?
What does it matter?
Regardless of the purpose,
the action we must take is the same!
Release the Mirage, and take everything
from Earth with the power of the Diva!
Please forgive me, Lady Eden.
I must borrow your power
one last time so I can save you.
Using the power of the Diva
to control the Mirage?
By being in close proximity to Earth,
the location and range of the Mirage
can be easily controlled.
It was meant to be the ultimate weapon.
Are you kidding me?
Why is he using a bastard cheat move now?
Is there a reason why it
wasn't used for ten years?
There are two reasons.
The new Diva; Lady Nagi's power
reduced its might to a minimum.
And its last use has put
Lady Eden, our former Diva,
into an eternal slumber.
Th-Then why is it activated now?
The Diva of XENOS
is asleep now, isn't she?
Then how...?
It follows that it is the new Diva
who's powering Kokytos.
Let's go, Priest. No, Lord Archon.
This time for sure, we shall
take Earth with Kokytos.
It is not Lady Eden you need to face now.
What you must do is to bind the new Diva.
Give the Idea of Earth to this bird in
a cage and make her sing for our planet.
And what happens to Lady Eden?
Will she continue to sleep
as she has been?
But our planet will come back!
Our people will awaken!
The Idea of the Earth
and the blessings of the Diva
will give us XENOS
the power to regenerate!
The Idea of the Earth
and the blessings of the Diva.
If that power, the blessings
of the new Diva,
are given only to Lady Eden,
then perchance...
What are you thinking, Archo—
Archon, you bastard!
Not only Samael, but you're
sacrificing yourself to Kokytos?!
Not a sacrifice for Kokytos.
Nourishment for Lady Eden!
Lady Eden has reached the end of her life!
Why can't you see that, Archon?!
You can't seriously suggest that you're
willing to dedicate XENOS's everything
to a single individual who
will never wake up again?!
That's what I should have done
from the beginning!
When Lady Eden's power started to
weaken several hundred years ago.
That's what I should have done!
I created her for this day.
From the DNA of Lady Eden and myself.
So that Lady Eden's life
can be saved, nothing else!
Are you saying that the new Diva
is you and Lady Eden's...?
Orphe was right.
He never betrayed us.
That's right, Apollo.
That guy, Orphe, never doubted anyone.
Since that day, you two parting ways...
and XENOS and the earthlings
killing each other...
It was predetermined to happen.
I did that to Orphe.
But you know, Apollo.
It was you who gave Archon the final push.
Ten years ago, out of hatred for Orphe,
you activated the incomplete Kokytos
and consigned Eden to eternal sleep.
Ever since then,
Archon's purpose has changed.
He decided to save one and only one
out of tens of billions of XENOS.
We became part of the sacrifice
to revive Eden.
If you knew that, then why did you...?
Well, nothing he'll do
will ever resurrect Eden.
Then, the true destruction
of all will come as I hoped.
Not just the destruction of Earth
and XENOS, but the whole universe.
Let go. Let go of me!
Where am I?
It's finally mine.
Archon...san?
Copy of Lady Eden.
And our dear daughter.
What are you talking about?
You will now absorb the Idea
of the whole universe.
And give it all to Lady Eden.
Why am I doing that?
So my beloved lady can live on forever.
And you'll destroy everyone
and everything except for Eden-san?
Do you think Eden-san...
the person you love...
will be happy to see that?
Do you think she can smile
from the bottom of her heart?
I will have to ask her once she wakes up.
Take that!
It really is here, Medea-san!
Move up already.
We're waiting down here.
Ugh, Jeez! There's no end to this!
Let's use this spacecraft!
Are you going to go after Nagi?
Yes, I am!
But Kyoya-kun, we're totally
surrounded on all sides.
You think so?
Nagi... Our center was taken away again.
It's the same situation it was
before we got here, that's all.
The people on Earth
are consumed by anger.
We can't have a live concert
like we used to—
It'll be fine.
If they hear our songs up close,
I know they'll regain their good hearts.
Whoa?!
Ow...
It looks like you really
haven't given up yet.
Huh?
If you were going to whine,
I was going to take over as leader.
What?
So you tested me!
Why would I believe you?
Well, I had faith in you, Kyoya-kun.
I smell a lie!
For being in a hurry,
you all seem very relaxed.
She's totally egging us on!
You're pretty lax yourself, you know?
Medea-san has assimilated
as a member of Harmonia.
Nagi, I will follow you
to the end of the world.
She could've smiled
from the bottom of her heart
if only you'd told her that
on daily basis.
Whoa?!
Right.
We'll have the happiest
ending with a smile.
With Siren, of course!
This is Nagi's masterpiece!
Write some awesome music for it!
You're SI-VIS's Diva.
No, their former Diva, correct?
Team Formation for
the Next Concert
Center!
Soji
Kyoya
You are... a friend of June. Yeah?
A friend of June.
That's what you choose to call me.
Not the sworn enemy of the world?
By the way, I'm not a former Diva.
I'm still the main vocalist of SI-VIS.
How did you find us?
June told me.
He wanted me to save his friend.
He disclosed such confidential
information to an archenemy like me.
It's absolutely irrational.
But I heard you also gave every weapon
you had to Asukai-kun.
Aren't you being irrational as well?
And? You came all the way here
to see if I'm doing okay?
Yes, and I knew it at a glance.
You can no longer sing.
Every time you try to sing or play,
Lukos' curse sucks Idea from you.
And eventually, your presence
will not be recognized by others.
Not to mention, one strum of the guitar
must be causing you unbearable pain.
Still, I'm more present in this world
than Nagi was a year ago.
Back then, not even one percent of her
was present in this world.
She was translucent, quiet, and so floaty.
No one could imagine that she'd be
a Diva who would save the world.
But Nagi came back.
With Kyoya, she was able to.
So I won't let Nagi take a lead on me.
I'll come back to SI-VIS once again.
A large XENOS warship has been detected!
What the hell?
They're devouring asteroids
around them as they approach.
That sounds like a black hole.
And how long until
Earth is in that range?
Their speed goes up each time they
devour something, so we can't be certain.
But I'd say one hundred minutes.
And will SI-VIS make it in time?
We received word from Medea-san earlier.
They're not sure either!
Oh, do calm down!
Something similar happened
ten years ago, you know?
And you didn't realize it
until you were attacked, right?
Then we don't need to panic
before it happens.
Now that I think about it,
I can't believe Harmonia grew this much.
I did a good job!
I did such a good job, so I'm
not going to let it all go to waste.
This must be XENOS's final move.
If we can get through this
and defend ourselves, we win!
Yes, ma'am!
This is Nagi's masterpiece!
Write some awesome music for it!
Unfortunately, you're out of time.
XENOS will... Apollo will soon
devour all Idea from the Earth.
Your song will not save the world.
If I wasn't here, that is.
Siren, I am going to remove your curse.
I'll turn you back into a normal human.
A normal human isn't going to cut it.
I've got to be a superstar!
Okay then. I'll turn you back
into a superstar.
With my Elpis.
I'm sorry, Lukos.
Not just the people on Earth,
but my comrades as well.
But it's okay.
I lost you and got caught up in hatred.
I took quite a detour, but...
finally, I've arrived.
Songs are incredible.
They can make people smile.
Give them power.
And... Songs can even save people.
So I want you to save them.
Not just the people on Earth,
but my comrades as well.
Goodbye, June...
I've heard of Elpis.
From your sibling.
So I know what you're
trying to do right now.
And I also know that
it's not the right thing to do.
Let me go!
Throwing away a life
in order to save a life.
That's something you should never do.
It's the only way!
To cancel out Lukos's Elpis
completely, I have to use my Elpis!
Doing that will reduce my
number of fans by one.
I am not your fan...
But you're a fan of June,
of SI-VIS. I know it.
I don't need to be restored completely.
I just need to be able to sing one song.
Five minutes... No, three minutes
to shine is all I ask.
You can do that without
sacrificing your life, can't you?
If you give it your all?
Listen, June's little friend.
Your name's Krios, right?
I want you to embellish my song.
You want me to...?
Nagi recovered her presence and her Idea
by being with Kyoya and SI-VIS.
If Nagi can do it,
there's no reason why I can't.
It's impossible.
She's the Diva of XENOS.
And you're just a normal human—
Didn't I tell you?
I'm a superstar.
Who said a superstar
is inferior to a Diva?
I'm going to get back.
To SI-VIS, to my friends.
And to Kyoya.
You aren't going anywhere.
The whole population
of Earth could disappear.
Why are you so hung up on this?
A live concert is out of the question.
Right now, you're not even capable of
the performance of an average person.
It'll work out somehow.
No, I'll make it work.
SI-VIS isn't here.
Not even Kyoya-kun.
In your condition, there's no way
your solo can stop XENOS and the Mirage—
If I sing, he will come.
So all I have to do is to deliver my song.
To everyone on Earth
and in the universe.
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Tomoko Takedani Sater
Krzysztof Kunc
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Michelle Tymon
On the musical stave
/ In the musical stave
WOW, I let my feelings play
/ I hid my feelings
My bright future / My pitiful past
WOW, started to shine
Unparalleled / Challenges ahead but
With a smile on my face
/ I'll embrace them
I feel like I can even change
the world with you
(3, 2, 1, Singing over)
Intertwining harmony (Harmony)
I wouldn't have believed in miracles alone
This breathless heartbeat (Heart Beat)
I'll let it resonate in
the night sky with my voice
My... our dream at full blast
Singing over, forever
Lan lan la la la