The wall's down?
Emoto...
Damn it. Damn it.
Why... Why does this keep...
You can't create the wall if you can't
focus on your music, I believe.
You haven't conquered your fear.
You haven't grown at all
since the last A-B Battle.
You can't change what you are.
Just give up already and
leave the academy.
And never call yourself an exorcist again.
You disgust me!
I give—
Hasumi?
You don't get to decide what Emoto is!
What do you know about him?!
You don't even know
what song he's listening to!
Very well.
Since you're such good friends,
I'll sever all of your limbs as well.
Wh-Why?
Why are you guys...
Because we're a team.
We're not leaving anyone out.
Class 1-B is the precious family
that Kukuru and I have found.
Sever!
What just happened?
They disappeared the moment I struck.
No... They fell?
Ren...
Where am I?
Wagari! Didn't you know?
Windows aren't just for looking through.
World
Through a
Shutter
They passed through the windows?
They can teleport to places
he's photographed?!
An exceptionally rare
kind of psychokinesis.
And to move them all at once
to protect them from his Sever sttack...
He's quite a treasure, isn't he, Azaki?
I told you he was the scariest
member of class 1-B!
Azaki-sensei! Why didn't you
tell me, your assistant, that?
Oh, did I not?
But will splitting up across such a
large area prove good or bad for class B?
Class A has more attackers, and therefore
the advantage in one-on-one battles.
Emoto-kun...
Bye-bye, Wagari!
Sorry, but we're all still in the game.
Don't underestimate class 1-B.
We're gonna beat the shit
outta ya, so get ready.
What did Hasumi do?
I can't believe he had
this ability and didn't tell us.
We all got split up.
Time to get back in gear!
I... I...
Wagari's strength is truly absurd.
None of us can beat him one-on-one.
We need to regroup and
set up a new ambush.
It's the only way to defeat him.
"Be perfect."
I was born into a family of exorcists and
had that principle beaten into my head.
Always be correct. Always be perfect.
That's why I can't stand them...
The societal threat posed by Sad Boy K.
Enishiro, who wields the same power.
Those who call themselves exorcists
despite having no talent.
And you, Kasubata!
Can you guess why I chose this window?
It's because I hate you, Kasubata-kun!
It hurts to hear you say that to my face.
Don't you think it's rather rude?
I bear no particular ill will toward you.
That's a surprise!
I was sure you hated me, too!
Slice!
Wagari!
You made a mistake picking me.
I'll make you regret it!
Wagari!
Right here, right now...
I'll crush you!
The Banhammer of Civility...
A hammer of righteousness.
Kasubata-kun!
What is "right"?
He intentionally cut
everything but my flesh.
He's toying with me!
To be "right" means to be a paragon,
while your righteousness
is merely a veneer you wear.
Violence and vulgarity...
are your true nature!
Be quiet.
Wickedness should make its nature clear.
Look at our own Dei Surugi.
He's such an over-the-top villain,
it's actually reassuring.
I like that!
Shut up!
Looking at you reminds me...
of the masses who are unable to acknowledge
their own mistakes and weaknesses.
Always be righteous. Always be perfect.
In other words...
Minoru Wagari's Lifestye Advice
"Become someone useful to the world,"
was the command.
Blunt Feedback for Your Problems
Female, 20s
"Just because he has a family, people
are against our relationship. It hurts."
People who cheat on others are feces.
Only flies are attracted to feces. Stop.
Male, teens
"I have terrible marks at school,"
"but my parents won't stop pestering me
to study and enroll somewhere good."
"How do I make them stop?"
If you have time to blog, you have
time to study. Go do that.
Male, 40s
"I'm on the job hunt right now."
"Is there anything out there that pays
a million yen on a three-day work week?"
What you need to do is get out
of the house and face reality!
Kasubata-kun, you're exactly like them.
I'll slice you to shreds!
Your "righteousness" is nonsense.
It's just decorated feces!
Will you stand up again?
It would surely be too sad for you
to leave the game here and now.
But at least drop the pretense.
It should be clear to you
that you can't beat me.
Run away like you should.
Just like you did that day.
You asshole.
Found ya!
I've been wantin' to see ya, Enishiro!
I was wondering when you'd show up, freak.
Hey, listen, I know it's kinda dumb,
but I've been thinking
about it this whole time.
What can I do to bully you even more?
Torture!
I'll burn each finger off in turn.
And I'll seal your mouth shut
so you can't even forfeit!
I've been holding it in
for two weeks just for today!
What's your reaction?!
Everyone said you love it
when people get mad or scared,
so I should just ignore you.
Why would they do that?!
Still, frying you up should earn me
a few good screams!
Cyber out!
Flames of Loathing!
Well, it's not like I've forgotten
how you insulted Akari and 1-B!
Oh, you're that kind of guy?
The kind who hurts more
when the people in his life suffer?
Lemme tell ya somethin', then.
Minoru and Kasubata
are goin' at it right now.
The jerk with the sword?
See, I can sense people's fear
and negative emotions.
Kasubata's scared shitless of Minoru!
Inferiority, frustration...
He avoids him at school so they
don't bump into each other!
What a lamer!
Poor li'l guy!
I bet he's gettin' his ass whooped,
runnin' all around while he sobs,
"Pwease fowgive me!"
Now go on, get mad!
Nah, that ain't happening.
Not with him.
You asshole!
Even if this is a fake set, don't soil
a sacred spring with your blood.
Just admit defeat already.
And then...
Take back your warped ideas
of righteousness!
Whew, that's hot.
I almost lost it for a minute,
but that really cleared my head.
That's the water of Kusatsu for you.
It's great for cuts, too.
You want me to take something back?
Fine. I will.
Wagari...
I hate your damn guts!
I'm the one in the right here!
Kukuru...
Heya, Hasumi.
On your way to help Kasubata out?
Thanks, Gatspi.
All right. Bet you're hungry.
Have lots to eat.
Owada, could you pretend you never saw me?
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
You're a real sneak, you know that?
You've been hiding
your power all this time?
And a teleportation power, at that.
I remember Surugi called you
"a flake whose only skill is peeping."
But he got you all wrong.
I obviously can't let you pass, Hasumi.
You're a problem. I have to take you out!
Then Kusaba-chan's gonna say I'm so cool!
Cyber out!
Cyberbeast Summon!
Teddy Kong!
Teddy Kong! How darling!
Hasumi's cyberkinesis is powerful, true.
But...
There, there. Cute little thing.
You want some, too? Just a sec.
Sorry I can't give you a home.
I've got a big family and
we're barely scraping by.
I see. Is that why you keep
electronic pets instead?
How do you know that?
I've received reports from the monster
trainer app Nikuniku Monsters
of monsters flying around
above your house.
That was you, wasn't it, Ikko Owada-kun?
Teddy Kong!
No!
Sorry to do that so suddenly.
Scared you, right?
He soothed that savage cyberbeast
with a single touch.
I get paid if I join this school
and become an exorcist, right?
Yes. At a rate reflective of your ability.
Owada is also an outstanding talent
with an extremely rare cyberkinesis.
My max-level monster
with the strength to crush boulders
will take you out before you can teleport!
I've got to get to Kukuru!
We met when we were six.
Kukuru Manase.
Nice to meet you!
I'm Renri Hasumi!
And this is my little brother, Rota!
It's nice to meet you.
I want all three of you awakening
your psychokinesis soon.
Yes, sir! I'll try!
Thinking back, our fathers, both caught
up a power struggle within their sect,
invested a lot in their sons.
Hey, Kukuru-kun,
what's your channeling device?
Mine's a trident vajra.
Don't call me Kukuru.
Why not?
It's not cool.
Kukuru! Kukuru! Kukuru! Kukuru!
Don't call me that!
Like most exorcist families,
mine was utterly toxic.
They barely let us out and
tortured us in the name of "training."
For years and years...
Every time I saw Kukuru,
I could tell his family was the same.
It's a bullshit family.
The food tastes like puke.
He gets more vulgar each time we meet.
Years
Later
My sons haven't awakened yet!
Not one of the two. It's pathetic.
Manase's boy and Wagari's
have both awakened.
And they say Yoimaru Azaki
was awakened at birth!
Could we give them
electronic devices? Channels?
Cyberkinesis is heresy.
It's okay.
No food or water
for three days and nights!
Reaching your limits will open the path
to the spirit for both of you!
Look, Brother.
The moon is beautiful.
Yeah, it is.
Hey, Brother.
Let me get a good look at your face.
You should get a good look at mine, too.
Rota...
Look at me.
Don't forget me.
A basic training ritual
was enough to kill him? Pathetic.
He was a born failure.
Renri, don't turn out like him.
You never had a little brother.
Understand?
Everyone in the house
stopped talking about Rota.
It became taboo. Like they
all wanted to forget him.
But I won't forget him.
I won't forget one thing about him!
Hey, Ren.
Let's run away.
K-Kukuru?
I heard about Rota.
This world is a stinking bag of shit.
I'm sick of it.
Come with me.
This is where you wanted to go?
I've always wanted to try one of these!
It's so good!
Kukuru, you try a bite, too!
They sell stuff this good
this late at night?
We didn't know anything about anything.
Hey.
Let's do my big idea next.
Running away from home
and bleaching your hair?
You've always been extreme, Kukuru.
Shut up.
Hey, that's what makes you so cute.
Huh? Don't call me cute!
Cutie-pie!
That's cold! Don't you know
what month it is?
Yeah.
Looks good on you.
I bet I don't look like
an exorcist at all like this.
After I jumped out of that window,
I experienced so much for the first time.
I couldn't believe how light
the popular sneakers were.
How soft girls were.
I made lots of friends and did lots of bad
stuff, like I was blotting out my past.
Man, ain't nothing
Ku and Ren here can't handle.
Yeah, we rock!
And we rule!
Keep your voice down.
Say, how'd you get so strong?
Ku looks like the badass he is,
but Ren's got that babyface...
Good question.
But every now and then,
I was hit with this feeling of emptiness.
Ren. What's wrong?
K-Kukuru... wh-what am I gonna do?
I can't remember Rota's face.
It's only been six months...
but it's already so fuzzy.
I promised I'd never forget him.
I tried every day to hold on
to him in my memory.
Hey, Serina.
You've got two smartphones, right?
Hand one over.
That one's for work!
And I'm meeting a client tomorrow—
Factory reset.
Here.
B-But why?
Take a picture.
Of me.
A picture?
I know you were fighting hard
not to forget Rota.
But human memory's never perfect.
Good memories and shit ones
all fade with time.
But take a picture and you'll
never forget me, right?
So quit cryin' already, asshole.
I could feel something
in my heart start to relax.
I'm gonna take tons.
I'm gonna take so many... from now on.
Yeah. Take a bunch.
My first picture was lousy as hell.
C'mon, Ku!
Don't go making Ren-kun cry!
Shut up, idiot! They're having a moment!
I don't get it,
but that's friendship for ya!
It was out of focus,
and I had a finger in the frame.
But it was an important picture.
We're not friends.
We're family.
When Kukuru decided to
go back to the exorcist world,
it wasn't even a question
if I'd go with him.
If I'm with my family,
I don't care where I call home.
As long as it's a house
without bars on the windows.
Hey, hey, let's take one to remember this!
Huh? Remember what?
I dunno. Anything.
Yeah, go on! Take it!
Wait a minute! I didn't do my
makeup right! Lemme fix it first!
It looks the same as ever!
Come on, get in here.
Gonna take it now! Smile, Kukuru, smile!
No fair! Let me in—
So that I never forget
what matters to me again.
You first, Hasumi!
What the—
My family's in danger!
So get outta my way, dumbass!
Kukuru...
Please, be safe!