Here, use the formula you just used.
Oh! So I just use this.
Yeah. You've got it now, right?
Oh, there's one more thing
I want you to show me.
Wait, which textbook was it again?
You should clean your desk.
I might've left it in my bag.
Modern Torture Studies
Math II
Huh?
Modern Torture Studies
Math II
Here it is.
This is bad.
Is he interested now that
he knows what my job is?
No, it's possible that someone
just happened to give it to him.
No, no. But...
Luc's always been a kid
who likes to imitate me.
Look! It's just like yours, Nii-chan!
Mama did it for me!
Hey, you old hag!
Whaddya think you're doing?!
If I don't handle this right,
he might end up even more interested.
And if I oppose his learning about it,
he might start worrying about me.
Nii-chan, for this problem here...
What's in my little brother's
best interests here?
What a tricky problem.
What? It's that hard?
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
All right! I win again!
You're good at this, Luc.
Nii-chan, you're losing
on purpose, aren't you?
Well, if I play for real, you'll cry.
I only did that when I was a kid.
Now, I'm just happy
you're hanging out with me.
He's so cute!
When He Was Little
Nii-tan, this is for you!
I Love You
He's so cute!
Not Long Ago
I bet you've got work again anyway.
It makes me feel a little
lonely, but he's so cute!
Lately
Nii-chan, welcome home!
He's ultra cute!
You're the cutest little
brother in the whole world.
But I'll still win every
match. Is that okay?
I knew you were holding back.
Hey, Nii-chan?
You haven't told Mom or Dad
you're a torturer, right?
Huh? Uh, yeah.
Are you hiding it?
I figured it's perfect.
They don't ask, so I don't tell them.
Dad would probably worry,
but Mom might be a bit of a pain.
That's why I haven't said anything.
Should I keep it a secret?
Please.
Sure!
Shoes
You're sure you want
cleats for your birthday?
Yeah! Thanks!
Wouldn't Mom buy them for you?
You'll be using them for the soccer team.
Aw, but I want to wear shoes
that you bought for me!
Oh, I'm getting a call.
Look to your left.
Siu-san!
Hey.
Siu-san, what were you doing?
Just shopping.
We were getting Luc's
birthday present and...
Oh, sorry. I'm getting another call.
It's Noe.
Sero!
Your paperwork is completely illegible!
Decipher them on a video
call! Immediately!
I need to step away for a moment.
Sure.
This is awkward.
Are those good?
Yes.
I heard you're interested in
torture studies at university.
How did you—
Sero said he found
materials in your room.
Do you have a problem
with it or something?
I don't have a problem with it,
but I know the anxiety and worry that
comes when family takes an interest in it.
I understand it, too.
When we grow up, we're going
to do the same job as Papa!
Damn. No, they're still
just children, so...
It seems dire.
It's not fair.
You do the same work as my brother,
and you get to be with him all the time.
I want to spend more
time with him, too.
Needy
Needy much?
But you both take pride in your
work as torturers, don't you?
Pride, huh?
Yet you don't want to let your
family do the same work?
Kid.
It's true that our work isn't something
that most people would like.
It's tough, blue-collar work that
wears on the mind and body.
It may be our colleagues
who support us at work,
but who supports us
in our private lives?
Our families.
If you're willing to get into the same
line of work on a half-baked whim,
then you should support him as
his beloved younger brother instead.
You're... right.
That's finally over.
Huh?
It's from Siu-san.
Siu-san
I talked to your brother about
the thing you were worried about.
Siu-san...
He's so smug!
Sorry about that.
That ended up taking a while.
Nii-chan.
I'm going to study
torture more after all.
I just took a casual interest in it
because I wanted to be with you,
but when Siu-san said I need to
think about it more carefully,
I realized...
Both at work and as your family...
I want to support you, Nii-chan!
Why? Why? Why?
How did things turn out like this?
Sorry, okay?
Another Day
Nii-chan!
Easy to understand
The Torture Profession
Contract killers, cleaners...
There are all kinds of jobs, huh?
So, this ragman job...
Absolutely not.
Birthday: 10/19 Age 20
Height: 182 cm
Weight: 75 kg
Blood Type: AB
Siblings: 2 Younger Sisters
Lives In: An Apartment, Alone
Interests: Girlfriend
Skills: Poker
Favorite Food: Baumkuchen
Disliked Food: Spring Rolls
His Type: Someone Adorable
Hey.
Las-kun, you're here.
Just for a little while.
I'm killing time until work.
Nice to meet you.
And who might you be?
I'm Mike!
He's my friend from work.
Huh?
I thought Mike-san from your
work was older than you.
I'm pretty,
but I'm a 22-year-old man!
For real? Please pardon my rudeness.
I'm the one who should apologize
for this criminal cuteness.
I'm Hugh's friend. My name is Las.
No need to be so formal.
So, what were you two about to do?
Go to a lecture on torture studies!
We thought we might be able to
if we hid among the students.
There are so few students taking
torture studies, I don't think...
Don't look at me like that.
Well, that professor would
probably just let you listen.
Maybe I'll go and sit in, too.
Your friend from your
part-time torture job?
I suppose it's fine.
As far as passionate
students go, Hugh-kun...
you're the only one.
And it seems all of my students
are absent today.
What?
It really isn't popular at all, huh?
And that's where we'll stop
on the topic of illegal torture.
Any questions?
Yes!
This is the first one of my lectures
has felt so worthwhile!
It was super interesting!
I'm surprised you keep teaching.
My tummy is so rumbly, la, la, la...
Studying made me hungry.
Want to head to the cafeteria?
I do!
Sorry! I wanted to ask
the professor something.
Go ahead without me.
Okay.
Will do!
Today's Menu
This Month's
Recommendations!
Las-kun, how long have
you been friends with Hugh?
Since our second year of high school.
Really?
I bet he stood out, huh?
Well, I mean, with his
height and that face...
I bet you stood out, too.
Well, I mean, I do have these good looks.
Which of you talked to the other first?
Me.
With a face that pretty, it's a waste
to be looking down all the time, right?
Once we became friends,
he opened up to me,
and it was just so adorable.
SQUEE
I totally get it!
It's just not fair, right?
He's had a rough time because
his face is so pretty, you know?
And he's had trouble
getting along with others.
I was worried about
his new part-time job,
but it looks like I didn't need to.
I was shocked by how
handsome his face was, though.
But his face isn't all
there is to him, you know?
So it just means I have one more
thing to like about my friend.
Mike-san, you're cute,
but you're cool, too!
Well, yes, I am.
I'm glad you're his friend.
Really? That makes me happy!
There was a time when
I thought I might not
be able to do my job because of my build.
Hugh really saved me back then.
So no one's happier to have
Hugh around than me!
Then we'll just agree
that we're both glad!
Yeah!
Hey, Hugh! I can see you.
You were here?
I'm starved. Let's hurry up and eat.
Yeah.
What do you recommend?
I'm glad...
that you're both my friends.
I'm glad!
How long are you gonna cling to me?
Huh?
Oh, not that it bugs me or anything.
But wouldn't it be better
if you had other friends?
There's no one else who'd hang
out with me the way you do.
I don't think that's true.
But if you're fine
with this, then so am I.
I know that's what I said,
but I feel both happy and lonely.
I wonder if this is how dads
with daughters feel.
Next time, I'm gonna ask Sero-san
to teach me how to pull nails off!
I'm going to ask Siu-san
about how to use a whip.
Their work is unsettling, but they seem
to enjoy it, so I guess it's fine.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Sero, you're free tomorrow, right?
Yeah. My day just opened up.
I'll come pick you up at 8 AM.
That's really early.
Are we going somewhere far away?
No.
It's for a recital at
an elementary school.
Oh, sounds good!
Morning.
Hey.
Here.
A video camera?
That's your job today.
You aren't recording it yourself?
I'm going to watch and take photos.
Oh, that makes sense.
Besides, if I watch the whole thing
through a lens, it loses something.
You're such a good papa.
Shut up.
Siu-san, you really don't fit in
at an elementary school.
I'm all about elementary school.
Don't be ridiculous.
Are you fitting in like you should?
Of course I am.
Really? I don't know about that.
Oh, Siu-san!
That recipe you taught me
the other day was delicious!
And that cake you gave me
was delicious, too!
I'm glad.
Well, we'll see you later!
See?
You're fitting in way too well.
Okay. We're all ready.
You seem used to that.
I used to film my little brother.
Nii-chan!
Luc!
Then I'll leave the video to you.
That camera's some
serious gear, isn't it?
What do you usually photograph?
I only photograph them.
Now that's love.
School Recital
They're adorable!
Of course they are.
They're working so hard!
I think I'm gonna cry!
Don't get more emotional than me.
Sero-kun, did you see us?
I did.
What did you think?
You were so good! I took some videos, too.
Yay!
Leu-chan, Nero-chan!
Who's this? Your older brother?
This is Sero-kun!
I'm Sero-kun!
Wow!
Food! Food!
Sero-kun, you'll eat with us, right?
I will!
We're stopping there first.
'Kay!
"There"?
You coming?
I'm not that insensitive.
I'll wait here. Take your time!
Mama, we had our recital today!
We did really well!
Don't worry. We're all doing great.
Papa, what did you wish for?
You don't make wishes at a grave.
I wished for everyone to
stay happy and healthy!
So did I.
So did Leu!
Hey, what are you going to eat?
Omelet rice!
Oh, they fell asleep.
All the excitement wore them out.
And they ate, too.
Their sleeping faces are so cute!
They're lively and honest.
Such good kids.
It must put their mother at ease.
You think so?
I do.
After all, they have a really great
papa named Siu-san raising them!
Yeah, yeah.
I really mean that!
The Next Day
Thanks for yesterday.
It was nothing.
And I caught everything
on video, right?
Well, you did record
everything, but...
They're adorable! They're so good!
Stop commenting on everything.
They couldn't stop laughing.
Why?
Oh, and when I was sorting through
the photos from yesterday...
Huh? Why is Sero-kun
crying like that?
Papa, did you make him cry?
He said he was moved
by your performance.
Really?
I like this picture!
Me, too!
Papa, will you print it out?
Put it in here and frame it!
Frame it!
It's weird to frame a photo
of someone who isn't family.
Is it weird?
It's fine if it's weird!
Because Sero-kun is Sero-kun!
Which is why we have a
photo of you up at our place,
but now it's like I see you all day,
every day, and it makes me sick.
Wow, that's so mean!
Sorry to interrupt!
Let's make sure to
turn off the lights.
Oh, dear. What a scramble.
Fon-san, we don't have
your part ready yet.
Okay, I'll wait!
Still...
it's quite unusual for
you all to be this busy.
There's no way a well-informed
guy like you doesn't know.
Three nearby torture companies went bust,
and all their work came
flooding to you, right?
It's rare, but not unheard of.
Can you take on more cases?
I don't know...
It might be hard to take on any more.
Should I do it? What do we have?
One that'll be a pain,
and the other two are korokke cases.
Please allow us to take those!
Sense of Justice
Spirit of Inquiry
They're so reliable, aren't they?
And we're grateful.
I'll take the rest!
The delivery dates for several
of the cases have been adjusted!
Oh?
Which ones?
These two... and the first ones
that Siu-san is handling.
You're pretty good! That's a huge help.
Well, this did happen really suddenly.
I'm impressed you got
an extension for this.
How did you convince them?
I said I had a Buddhist memorial
service for a family member.
Is this an after-school club?
Let's build a fun,
cheerful workplace together!
Stop harassment!
All that's left are Mike
and Hugh's. I'll go tell them.
I'll leave it to you. Also, hey...
You reek.
What'd you just say?!
Well, do your best, everyone!
I'll be waiting here.
Don't make yourself at home.
If you've got nothing to do,
you could help us out, you know.
Oh, yeah. You used to do this
a long time ago, right?
What? Torture? I could never
do something so uncivilized.
No way! No way! It's too scary!
I don't want to hear that from
someone who disposes of humans.
Everyone works so hard.
You make good money from it, right?
Still...
who'd have thought Spirytus
would ever be this lively?
Siu-kun, I'm happy for you.
I guess.
Yoo-hoo! I'm here!
Could you not act like you're
my girlfriend when you come in?
Are you bored?
You got pretty busy, huh?
That's right.
When I asked the police to investigate
an illegal torture company,
they apparently found some others, too.
On top of that, they asked me,
"Your place is fine, right?"
How rude of them!
This place is a gray that's
as close to white it gets!
We're lily white, I'll have you know!
As someone who's known this
place since you started it,
Spirytus has made me feel
really emotional lately.
Siu-kun and Sero-kun are
as skilled as ever.
Done already?
I'm letting one sweat
and working on another.
Same.
Mike-chan and Hugh-kun have
started to shape up nicely.
Will you do this one with me?
Is it okay if I finish up this one first?
That's been changed,
so we'll handle the arrangements.
And Noe-chan seems like he's
gotten used to everything.
Yes. Thank you for handling all that.
Do you want to come
and torture here with us?
No way! Not doing it!
Being a ragman suits me better!
Besides, you don't need anyone
here who isn't fully devoted.
Spirytus is the best as it is right now!
Yes, I suppose it is.
What?
Come on. You should
deny it at least once!
I'm busy, too.
Go and do some work, would you?
We're done.
I never knew things could get this busy.
Just every once in a while.
Once in a while...
The deadline for my
manuscript is coming up,
but I'm going to sleep
like a log tonight!
And I think I'll do my
assignment tomorrow.
When things like this happen,
it makes a lot of other things harder.
Haven't you thought of quitting?
Nope!
Not once!
I haven't.
Being able to be so useful to others...
No other job is as
worthwhile as this one!
And there aren't many jobs
that are this exciting.
This is the first time I've found work
that I haven't gotten bored with,
so I have no plans to quit.
You're all a bunch of weirdos.
Siu-san! Did you just smile?
I'm not smiling.
What?
That's the first time I've seen it!
Me, too.
I haven't seen it much, either!
You should smile more!
Shut up.
Let's hurry up and grab a bath,
then get some food.
Sure thing.
Okay!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Elanor Sakamato
John Chandanais
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Becky Cottrill