Someday, that child is going to
destroy the family Magecraft!
A child named Flat never
existed to begin with!
Are you Flat Escardos?
Yes!
What's with that face?
Your mimetic muscles are moving in an
order that ignores its intended functions.
Only caring about the ends
while neglecting the means...
That is an immature thought process.
If that's your way of
getting around in this world,
you should alter your way of thinking.
Ow!
I'm telling you, children
should not be faking smiles.
These fashion choices
really feel like you.
Don't they?
It's perfect for an
infiltration mission, right?
Humph.
I would have agreed...
if we were heading into
a disco full of cowboys.
This doesn't really feel like reality.
Are we really being
watched by Special Ops?
Moreover, the American government joining
forces with Mages in a conspiracy?
What is this, a fantasy movie?
Yes. I was surprised, as well.
But it also makes sense.
You kinda look like you're having fun.
I... looked like I was having fun?
Are you not gonna tell them that
there is a vampire in the hospital?
I'd like to keep some cards up my
sleeve, just in case something happens.
Oh?
I believe... they are good people.
But this is how I have lived my life.
You...
that assassin girl...
Quite the troublesome folks.
Only you five showed up, huh?
So? How'd you feel fighting a real
monster and almost being killed?
Th-That's—
First of all, why do you
go so far to keep fighting?
What is there to gain by standing
at the front line of this war...
where people can die at any moment?
I...
We are police officers!
It's our job to save as
many people as possible
under conditions where
we may die at any moment!
You're glorifying things.
Does doing that put food on the table?
I know that you built a giant mansion.
Hah, you sure have got some words!
Are you saying my works
are glorifications?
You're exactly right.
Huh?
An overglorified protagonist who sees
their will through to the end...
sells really well, actually.
There's a special gimmick, so I'll
explain all sorts of stuff later.
But, I—
John Wingard, 28 years old.
The second son in a family of Mages.
Aspired to become a police officer
after losing his mother in
a terrorist attack on an airplane.
Because you didn't want any person to end
up with the same sadness as yourself.
It's nothing like that.
I simply wanted revenge—
It's fine. I'm still going to glorify
it into something like that.
If revenge is what you actually
want, then revenge it is.
I originally had no interest
in plays or novels.
I was just tired of seeing
nothing but boring tragedies.
But one day... I saw a tragedy called
"Hamlet," and that was something else.
I was overwhelmed.
It ended up being one of
my greatest inspirations.
However...
the Hamlet I saw was the
one where old man Ducis
broke the original work into pieces...
and rewrote it with his
own interpretation.
When I later read the real
thing written by Shakespeare,
I got all weak in the knees.
Compared to the real thing, what I
saw was truly just a wannabe Hamlet.
But what changed my life...
was that wannabe.
That is something I won't let anyone deny.
Fake or whatever...
the passion packed in there
was real. That's all!
The Noble Phantasms I create are fake...
but the passion your boss
has is the real thing.
If you believe him through to the end,
you should be able to overturn
as many of those real legends...
as you need to.
Come in.
Chief, there's something
urgent I need to report.
Release me!
I'm innocent!
Sit still!
We're in, Mr. Jack!
Infiltration...
is his intent, perhaps?
When we found him at the park...
the report said a cop and
a woman in a dress...
suddenly appeared and disappeared, right?
Yes.
It is likely an ability of the Servant.
He should be off duty today.
I will gather nearby Clan
Calatin members immediately.
Right.
Also...
who the hell are you?
I thought we had a ceasefire.
I don't trust you.
Where do your beliefs lie?
I don't believe in anything.
Not in my client...
not in Magecraft, not in myself.
You don't have a god that
you send your prayers to?
I...
have yet to receive a god's favor.
The people who raised me
dragged fetuses out of mothers'
wombs to experiment on them.
For the sole purpose of creating
spellcasters that kill people.
They said...
those who commanded our country were gods.
But they were annihilated. So...
I don't have a grasp of
what this god thing is.
I see.
Sorry.
I have made you confront
such harsh memories.
You are different from the other Mages.
Your eyes truly look like they
don't believe in anything.
That is likely because you have yet to
discover what is worth believing in.
I have no right to speak
of faith at present.
However...
I hope that someday...
when it is created within you,
your faith will be of good nature.
I'm surprised, my boy!
It looks like you're quite
the charming swindler.
What's wrong?
It can't be love at first sight, can it?
No.
This is the first time someone has wanted
something from me outside
of Francesca's begging.
What is the meaning of this?
Can I take this as a form
of workplace harassment?
You say things that the real
Vera might actually say.
You still doubt me?
The real Vera...
is currently headed to
the monitoring room.
I was able to read it just now.
An IC chip in the neck.
Something that complicated
cannot be copied instantly.
A machine, huh?
Indeed, something like that...
I wouldn't be able to figure out.
Play Ball.
You tamed the Demonic Beasts?
Game Set.
You took over the police station's system?
Please stand down from
your attack posture...
Police Chief Orlando Reeve.
Roughly 40 percent of the personnel
within this police station...
are all me at this point.
It seems you have gained
the upper hand here.
Oh, I'm glad you understand.
You show just a part of your powers...
to make the negotiations
advantageous to you.
This is just like what the mafia does.
Oh, no. All of the bounded fields
were connected to you, Mr. Chief...
so I was trying to have
him check things out...
but I didn't think we'd get caught.
I'm sorry to have surprised you!
Hah.
To think there'd be a Mage like you...
So, what do you want?
There's no way you're here
to make an alliance, are you?
We came here...
to file a report!
Oh, you mean the fire in
the industrial district.
Don't worry. There haven't been any
injured people brought over here.
Huh? Tsubaki?
On her right hand...
Thank you.
You take care of yourself,
too, Big Sister.
Goodbye, now.
I confirmed it.
Just like what Mr. Escardos claimed...
Tsubaki Kuruoka has
manifested Command Spells.
You're saying that her Heroic Spirit
is the source of the curse that is
falling upon Snowfield right now?
Yes.
However, as we don't know the
Heroic Spirit's identity,
we can't recklessly attack them.
On top of that, the location
is not suitable for that.
I will use the pretext of an accident
and have the people inside
the hospital evacuate.
Um...
We can also use large-scale Magecraft
to blow up the entire hospital.
Those in the government wouldn't
hesitate to use that tactic.
However, I have shackled our position
as representatives of justice
with my subordinates...
through a pact.
Before I deem sacrificing this girl
to be the most justified move...
I'd like to check off
all possibilities and be
absolutely positive it is our only option.
That's good!
I'm very relieved!
Of what?
If you guys had agreed with
my suggestion from the get-go,
I thought I wouldn't be able
to join forces with you!
You tested me?
I'm sorry!
However...
I will say that if damage
spreads any further,
I will point my gun at her.
Yes! You've proven yourself
by telling me head-on,
so I can feel assured in introducing you!
I did a 27-step encryption on my end,
and they've placed measures
on their end, as well.
So, I don't think anyone
will eavesdrop on us.
Who are you?
I am the instructor of Modern Magecraft
Theories at the Clock Tower.
I usually borrow the title
of "Lord El-Melloi II."
However, for you lot, this other name
should be better at ringing a bell.
"Waver Velvet."
I'm just a third-rate Mage
who once participated
in the Holy Grail War of Fuyuki.
I'd like to confirm the combative
forces of each faction.
In terms of sheer magnitude,
the Police Chief and Dumas duo
should be the greatest...
as they can move ordinary
police officers, as well.
What about the clan led by Tiné Chelc?
Fifty-six foot soldiers are
active within the city.
There should be more in
their base in the valley...
but that's outside of
Watcher's observation range.
Though, the number of actual
forces is probably 46.
The others are either spies
from other syndicates
or are being swayed by their propositions.
I see. It looks like they're
having a hard time.
Hold on a second.
Flat Escardos and the police chief seem
to have formed an alliance just now.
They're going to start a secret operation
at the Central Hospital tonight.
Lord El-Melloi II.
He's a greater armchair
detective than rumors say.
I know, right?
Regardless...
I'm relieved both of you
are really good people!
We already had ascertained the
situation about Tsubaki Kuruoka.
Her parents were natural born Mages,
and they used their daughter...
as a subject for Magecraft experiments.
It seems the objective
of their alliance...
is to rescue the Master in the
hospital from her Servant.
Is she captive?
No. That Master is a
comatose... a sleeping girl.
Oh, but...
That expression may perhaps
be a suitable phrase.
The parents raised their
daughter very, very preciously.
As if putting their favorite
bird inside a birdcage.
You could say her current self...
has been set free.
For the first time in her life...
she was able to go to the
outside world that she admired.
However, the possibility of
the operation failing is high.
Why's that?
I told you, there are moles everywhere.
What you'd call "corrupted cops."
The police chief...
surely doesn't think that
one of the Clan Calatin...
is a henchman for the Scladio Family...
of all things.
Is that girl going to be murdered?
You don't like it?
Perhaps so.
My boy, can you actually be hesitating?
Francesca told me to do as I like. But...
doing as I like...
I don't understand it too much.
I'll say this just in case...
but if you value your life,
don't head over there.
I figured out where that vampire is.
I want to talk to you directly.
Is that all right...
Assassin?
There's one person...
I'd like you to get rid of and stage
it like an accident or natural death.
If thou proceed, thou cannot turn back.
Know if thy conviction
degrades into a fake,
the curse in its entirety
will fall back upon thee...
and consume thee whole.
I would sacrifice all of Magecraft
for the United States.
If it is for this nation...
I wouldn't even hesitate to kill citizens.
I see.
Mr. Police Chief wants to use the
Holy Church to his advantage.
Depending on how the operation pans out,
we want you to take care
of one Master. That's all.
By the way, you are?
You don't look like a police officer.
Nice to meet you!
My name is Flat!
I'm the Master for Berserker!
I'm counting on you as the
Overseer of the Holy Grail War!
Oh?
We finally have a Master who
acknowledges me as Overseer?
I'm Hansa Cervantes.
Um, I'll apologize if this is rude...
but Mr. Hansa, is about 70 percent
of your body made of machines?
You can tell?
Yes. It was something I
couldn't understand at first.
Oh, that's amazing! I've
never met a cyborg before!
Can you launch rocket punches and stuff?
Maybe even a drill?
My fist doesn't detach, but
my arm extends three meters.
And a drill? That's a secret.
I'm so touched!
If you don't mind a Mage from the
Clock Tower, can I shake your hand?
You've got some good taste.
If you get bored of Magecraft, you
should convert over to the Holy Church.
Father Hansa is revealing
his hand to a Mage.
Is that okay?
We can't do anything about it.
Hansa is like a kid inside.
I have already gotten rid of
the people in the vicinity.
At the time of the operation's start...
we will use Magecraft to put the
people inside the hospital to sleep
so we may hurry inside.
Our objective is securing
Tsubaki Kuruoka...
a Master. Nothing else.
Please make sure to not
cause injury to civilians.
Nothing less from a survivor
of the Holy Grail War.
Both Lord El-Melloi II...
and his student...
I'm glad we settled things well.
We must be grateful to the police chief.
The theories of Tsubaki Kuruoka's
Heroic Spirit your mentor spoke of...
and the plan he came up with
were both quite marvelous.
Nobody in the Clock Tower
can win against Professor in
negotiations without Magecraft!
Why are you trying to save that child?
It's the obvious thing to do.
That's not true.
Indeed, you have a looseness about
you that's unfitting for a Mage.
However,
it's all too reckless to expose yourself
to someone who is normally your enemy...
for someone else's sake.
It's a simple story.
I just thought if the Professor were
in my shoes, he would save her.
Before I am a Mage of the Escardos Family,
I'm Flat of the El-Melloi Class.
To abandon that child here is betraying
Professor and all of my peers.
I am scared of doing that just as
much as losing my purpose as a Mage.
I see.
If you say you're scared,
I am forced to understand.
And Mr. Jack, why don't you oppose?
Hmm?
In order to survive the Holy Grail War,
we don't have to reach out
and save a girl, right?
It's simple.
I was merely influenced by
you and your mentor, as well.
Then, that makes you a student
of the El-Melloi Class, too!
You harbor within you a great divergence
from the world that you
yourself aren't aware of.
I was terrified of that, as well.
Humans all live with a sense of divergence
from this world somewhere
within themselves.
But upon speaking with your
mentor, I felt relief.
Right. Professor is—
Not for the fact that he is your mentor.
It was because you felt
a sense of reverence
for how the said mentor lives his life.
As long as you have that spirit...
you will always...
be able to overcome the
divergence within yourself.
Something is coming!
What is that?
EPISODE 8