What are you looking at?
This says they can send us
a few on a trial basis.
I can't wait to see what they send.
Don't let Bel-san take advantage of you.
Huh?
She'll send over some
ridiculously expensive devices.
Is that what this is?
Of course, her main objective is...
Right? Isn't the shape
of it just wonderful?
You absolutely must see and touch
and experience it for yourself!
She just wants to show you all
the torture devices she likes.
I see.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
I'm finished with intake.
Yes, good work. You can go now.
Oh! We have a wild rabbit!
What? A wild rabbit?
What an adorable name.
Wild rabbit?
So many spikes.
How is this used?
After you... tie them to the wheel,
you turn this...
and the spikes on the bottom
gradually strip off their skin.
It's like using a grater
over their entire body.
The handle's hard to move,
so it's hard to gauge the tolerances.
Won't they die?
They last longer than you'd think.
It gets messy, though.
These are small, but they're spiky, too!
They look a little like accessories.
There's no point in using
that on your skinny neck.
But...
That's adorable.
It reeks of iron.
This one isn't spiky!
It's a cage to hang people in and
expose them to the elements, right?
But do you just lock them in there?
No.
They can't sit or anything,
so it's pretty rough.
It's a battle of attrition.
I'd rather not be on the
giving or the receiving end.
Me neither.
That's adorable.
It's more comfortable than you'd think.
Were there any that interested you?
There's one that's deeply intriguing,
but it's large, so it may
be a little inconvenient.
Most of the big ones tend to lean
toward long battles or heavy damage.
They're interesting, but they might
not be suited to our daily work.
Right?
Hey, wait! Please let me out of here!
That's true.
You're adorable, so I thought
I'd keep you here as a pet.
Please don't say that with an expression
that looks like you mean it!
Okay, so we'll return all of them.
Okay.
She'll probably come to
pick them up tomorrow,
so we can leave them there and go home.
This is hard to use,
but it does have a lot of impact.
Starting the fear through visuals
is highly effective, isn't it?
Maybe this piece places more
importance on that than usability.
Yeah.
The kinds of devices that
inspire fear are actually...
Well, it's nice that they seem
to have learned something.
Belta can be helpful
every once in a while.
Yes? Hello.
Hi, Bel-san.
Sorry, but we'll be returning all
the equipment you sent over.
What?!
They're not very practical.
Hang on!
There are uses for them
other than torture, you know!
Don't they make great
interior decoration?
All those cold, spiky, magnificent forms!
Just thinking about the sight of them,
all made to hurt people,
even the karma that
casts its shadow over—
I've heard that Belta-san actually
does live with torture devices.
Wow.
'Sup?
Sero-san?!
What happened? Why are you injured?
Shouldn't you take the day off?
I'm fine.
It's not as bad as it looks.
Was it a traffic accident or something?
No, no. This was just your average...
attack.
Attack?!
Some dangerous compatriots
of someone I tortured before.
I guess it's what you'd call...
"paying respects."
You say that like it's normal.
Well, I am famous in the industry.
Yeah, so first I got hit with a
metal pipe out of nowhere...
What?!
Then I went in with a headbutt.
And then, I called the police.
It's all too wild for me.
And, well, looking like this,
my torture targets
wouldn't take me seriously.
So I'll take a supportive role today.
Sheesh. Just don't push
yourself too hard, okay?
Yeah, I won't.
This case... That's already next week.
Then... I'll have Mike take that, and...
I guess I'll give this one to Hugh.
About next week's schedule...
Would you rather do
this one or this... one?
Huh? He's ignoring me?
Hey!
Siu-san!
What's going on?
Those injuries you have.
Huh?
Are you okay?
I'm totally fine!
I went to the hospital, and they
went overboard with the bandages.
This is nothing!
Why are you smiling?
After going off on your own...
The torture session that got you attacked
was one that I was
supposed to handle, wasn't it?
Yeah, but switching cases isn't—
It's what landed you in that state.
And if it is... so what?!
Why do you always try to
take on everything by yourself?
You have so much that
you have to protect as it is!
Please don't include me in that group.
If anything happened to you,
it'd be a problem.
For this job, for everyone...
Well, it causes problems for me
if you're not strong and healthy!
And it's not just me.
You seem pretty angry.
What about you?
You were angry for my sake, right?
Then please understand
why I'm angry, too!
For me, the idea of you getting hurt...
of the people you love getting hurt...
I don't want that.
If the alternative is you
taking on everything alone,
I'd rather get injured!
I'm more useful than I used to be, right?
So let me take on just a little bit...
of everything you're carrying.
Ow!
Moron.
If you drop it, there'll
be no forgiveness.
I won't drop it even if it kills me!
If it kills you, huh?
There you go, talking big again.
Hey! Are you doubting me?
I'm serious! And I'll prove it to you.
I can't go along with this.
Hey, you're the one who said it.
Just make sure you watch me work, okay?
What a pain.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
This is amazing! It's so pretty!
All of you are always
working so hard for us.
I thought it'd be nice for a change.
Oh, right. Where are
Leu-chan and Nero-chan?
You don't need to be
considerate on our accounts.
Moron.
Who would bother being
considerate of you?
I let my brother and his wife
take them out, that's all.
Papa!
Eri-kun said they'll
take us to Lulupii Land!
Lulupii
And that we can stay over!
So you can go to the hot springs!
Oh, my.
Iris Room
Okay...
Sharing
a Room
You're free until dinnertime.
Sakura Room
Okay!
Sharing
a Room
Understood.
Peony Room
Should we hit the
baths before dinner?
Yeah.
Huh?
Don't these pairings mean I'm the
only one who doesn't get to relax?
Sure you will.
Sharing
a Room
I'm a comforting guy, you know.
That's news to me.
This is paradise.
Right?
It feels so good,
it's strange to think that if you used it
a little differently, it could be torture.
You mean like a water chamber
or a boiling cauldron?
Yeah, exactly!
Sero-san!
We don't do either of those
at our place, right?
If they get stubborn, it's a pain
to figure out the tolerances.
You could say it's not cost-effective.
Besides...
using huge amounts of water
isn't very eco-friendly.
Spirytus is a torture firm
that's kind to the planet.
Torture builds a sustainable society
Give the villains
the iron hammer
Now that I think about it,
Hera-san and Noe-san haven't come yet.
Oh.
They're probably relaxing
in a private bath.
Despite how they seem,
they're both shy.
Oh, I-I didn't realize.
You're quite the smooth talker.
Well, it's not my place to say anything.
It's the kind of thing
you say when you want to,
to the person you want to, right?
I'm ready to listen anytime, so...
Yeah, yeah.
I'll be here year round,
no breaks, twenty-four hours a day.
How considerate of you.
Iris Room
I see the scars have faded quite a bit.
Have they?
This is a rare chance.
Are you sure you don't
want to be with everyone?
Those boys won't say anything about it.
I don't think they would.
It's just that I...
I just want to be with you, Hera-san.
In that case...
It's been a while. Maybe I'll ask
you to wash my back for me.
Of course! Just leave it to me!
Okay, all done!
I've always wondered...
Sero-san, why do you
always dry his hair for him?
Oh.
Since it's long, it's faster
if I dry it for him.
Plus, over all the times
he's let me do it,
I've gotten pretty fond of his hair.
That's so creepy.
Frankly, it's a pain,
but if I don't dry it right,
he starts nagging me.
And, I mean, he's not bad at it,
so if he wants to do it that badly,
I figure I'll just let
him do what he wants.
Seriously, though, it's a pain.
That's salon-level service!
There, Siu-san. You're all done.
Right.
Thanks for all your work, everyone!
Cheers!
Siu-san, have some more.
Sure.
Are you eating, Noe?
I don't need you to remind me. I am.
Have you gone on company
trips like this before?
Yeah.
One time,
Sero and Noe got all worked up
and had a table tennis match.
That's right.
We had to keep them company
until they got sleepy.
Really? So, who won?
Which of us was it?
I'm pretty sure it was me.
I think it was me.
You don't remember?
Now that I think about it...
Mike and Hugh are the first ones in
a long time to stick around this long.
That makes me happy somehow.
Maybe I'll make this my primary job.
Just kidding!
You're welcome here anytime!
What about you, Hugh? Do you have
a lot of future career plans?
I... suppose so.
I'm still thinking
about what I want to do,
but my parents are supportive of my
being involved with torture in the future.
What a wonderful family.
When we grow up...
...we'll do the same job as you, Papa!
Don't.
But why?
Should I learn from their example?
They have their rules, you have yours.
Don't let yourself lose heart!
Hey! Who gave Noe alcohol?!
I poured it for him!
You idiot!
When he gets drunk,
he's more of a pain than I am!
So he's aware that he's a pain.
I'm no good at all.
I have to contribute
more to the company...
That's not true!
You're a huge help to us!
But someone like me will never...
I'm telling you, you're
already working hard enough!
Hilarious.
Adorable.
Wait!
Why are you grabbing snacks
to have with your drinks?!
Man, I sure drank a lot.
Don't fall, now.
Who'd be clumsy enough to...
Are you all right?
I told you so!
Be careful, okay?
I'm sorry, Hera-san.
Moron! Idiot!
They make a ruckus
no matter where they go.
What did you just say?
Ow!
Sorry. I didn't notice you were there.
Are you okay?
No, no. I should have been more careful.
My cheeks are bouncy, so I'm just fine!
Um...
Can you not see
out of your right eye?
Oh, yeah.
Haven't I mentioned it?
It's a false eye,
so I can't see out of it.
Sakura Room
Did you know about Siu-san's right eye?
There were some times when
I thought it might be, but...
I never heard anything in particular.
Yeah, that figures.
He seems like he'd tell
us if we asked, but...
It's hard to broach the topic, right?
Yeah. And it seems like
a lot happened, so...
Sero-san seems like he'd know, though.
That's why Sero-san is
always on Siu-san's left side!
Love really does hide in the nooks
and crannies of everyday life, huh?
What does that mean?
Well...
I'll write about it in a novel one day!
Really? I look forward to
the day when I can read it!
Thanks!
Do you see something cool
out there or something?
Oh. Did I wake you?
Not really.
So why are you sitting
here alone, lost in thought?
Did I look like a stunning picture?
Ugh.
I was just thinking
that it's a nice place.
Yeah. The scenery's nice.
Not that.
I'm talking about Spirytus.
I've wandered in and out
of a lot of different jobs.
It's kind of a mystery to me
how I've stayed here this long.
And it makes me wonder
how long I'll be able to stay.
You can stay forever.
You're needed, after all.
You can stay for as long as you want to.
Actually...
stay to make things easier for me.
In that case,
for the company, society, and you,
I'd better give it my best.
It sounds so flippant when you say it.
What?
But you know...
that lightheartedness is
one of your good points.
Mike asked me about my eye.
He did?
Well, he didn't ask for details.
But I wouldn't mind
telling those guys about it.
It's fine to take it slow, I think.
There's still a bunch of stuff
even I don't know.
I'll wait until you're ready
to talk about it.
It'll probably take years.
Then I ask for your continued
good will for many years to come.
And I, the same.
Morning!
Good morning!
What are you guys doing here so early?
We're doing some torture studies.
We want to get better at torturing,
like you and Siu-san.
Right?
I like that attitude.
I read that one, too!
That brings back memories!
The exercises in this book
are really hard.
Oh, yeah, those. These are—
Why are you dawdling in here?
Siu-san?
Didn't you get the message I just sent?
We picked up an urgent case.
Since he's tough to deal with,
they wanted Spirytus to take him.
And that's why you're all coming, too.
Yes, sir!
Well, shall we get started?
Okay!
I'm ready anytime.
This is a highly rare
four-man special course.
Now, why don't you hurry up
and spill what you know?
Torture Outsourcing Firm Spirytus.
Today, for the sake of
a bright, cheerful world...
I will once again devote myself
to my part-time torturing!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Elanor Sakamato
John Chandanais
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Becky Cottrill