What the hell?!
How could something like this stand?!
Chiyo?
I can't believe it...
How could this have been
going on all this time?
I'll never let it go...
Uniform Point Deductions for Female Applicants:
Nitto Medical University Accused of Arbitrary Manipulation
Never! Not ever!
Journal with Witch
Episode 11\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSet Free
Morimoto's absent again?
You mean Chiyo?
I've been meaning
to give this back to her.
Fifty People
You try texting her?
I don't know her number.
We only really talk here.
We've been exchanging books.
Didn't you hear what happened last week?
Hey, isn't this cute?
Looks like something you'd like.
What's that supposed to mean?
I think it's cute.
Library
Yeah, right!
You're good! You're good, I tell you!
Did Shinozaki ignore you just now?
What's up with that?
Who knows?
I heard he and Hashiba broke up.
I couldn't care less.
Ouch.
Chiyo was supposed to go
into medical school, so...
Anyways, now you know what happened.
I think it broke her.
She hasn't been to school since.
Want me to give you her number?
Huh? Oh, sure.
Told ya!
Ack!
Watch it.
You good?
Y-Yeah.
Apologize.
What?
I said apologize to her.
Hang on, Takumi, did you just go "ack"?
No way. Who really says that?
Shut up and apologize already.
Get over yourselves.
Whatever. My bad.
It's like they don't know
how to say sorry.
So annoying.
Huh? You're quitting? Why?
So you're running away?
Is that all baseball meant to you?
So what?
I've been picked on,
punched in the stomach,
treated like a gofer,
and forced to grovel.
And you expect me to just take it?
Is that what baseball should mean to me?
Later.
Band Club
Auditioning for vocals
How have you been? Anything new?
Hmm... Not really, I guess.
Oh.
You know how your leg twitches
while you're asleep?
Yeah, sure do.
I bet that's—
I just wanted you to like me, Natsume-san.
What a void of a person.
Huh?
What's up with this guy?
What's wrong?
I meant the TV.
You're watching it, aren't you?
Yeah, but I didn't think you were.
I was peeking out of one eye.
By the way, you forgot your journal today.
Oh, yeah.
I saw you actually closed
it for a change.
It actually made me a little sentimental.
What? Why?
This is so stupid.
What kind of a plot twist is that?
But you never noticed me.
A void of a person...
Void (pronounced voyd)
Noun; adjectival verb
To be empty or contain nothing,
as in "a boundless void of space."
To be meaningless and of little substance or value, as in "a void
opinion merely echoing others' sentiments" or "days of void."
What's that for? Modern Japanese?
Oh, no. It's just my personal notebook.
It's a collection of my aunt's trash talk.
What? Her trash talk?
Can I see?
Yeah, sure.
Does your aunt talk that much smack?
Not a ton, but it gets pretty
spicy when she does.
Inane
To be shallow without knowledge or thought
Evil
"Inane: To be shallow without
knowledge or thought."
Jeez. Harsh much?
"Evil"? That's hilarious.
When would you ever need to say that?
She said it while watching the news.
Impudent
\hTo be unabashed...
Let's see... "Impudent."
"Folly."
Folly
To be foolish...
"Cowardice."
Cowardice
\hTo avoid being open and fair...
Benighted
"Benighted."
What's that mean?
I can't remember.
"Escapist, deceitful, villainous..."
Man, this is a whole
treasure trove of trash talk.
Wretched (pronounced retch-ed)
Adjective
To possess ugly features. The state of possessing a nasty heart
or acting on meanness, as in "a wretched battle."
I just remembered another one.
Wretched
Ooh, I wanna hear.
Wretched!
I think I'd die if someone
ever called me that.
Stuff like wretched or a void.
I know, right?
Void
\hTo have little value or content
Hey!
Guess what, Dad?
Mom keeps bugging me about my hair.
All because I got it cut.
It just looks too much
like a boy's haircut.
Hear that, Dad?
You're not listening!
Mom apparently doesn't like my hair.
Oh... right.
Well, just do what you want to do.
As long as it's within reason, I guess.
Gone...
They're both gone.
Forever.
I had such a weird dream yesterday.
Really? Like what?
Morning.
Oh, hey, Mori-chan! Mor...
What were you saying?
...ning?
Right, so there's this Samoyed...
Samoyed?
It's a breed of dog.
They're, like, white and fluffy.
Look! Look at that!
Huh?
See? Right there!
Oh, I think I know what
you're talking about.
Yeah.
That's all you have to say?!
I told you, I'm not talking
romance with you.
No, please! Let's talk romance!
Speaking of, it's almost Valentine's.
Are you doing anything, Emiri?
Do you have a Valentine? Well?
Nope.
I'll give you some friendship
chocolates again.
Yay!
I wanna do something for Valentine's too.
What about Makio-san?
You should give her some chocolate.
I doubt she cares about that stuff at all.
That's something to consider given
that it takes place at school.
We'll have to make a decision
by the end of the year.
I'm sorry I never return
the favor with things like this.
Oh, don't mention it. I hope you like it.
Do you buy chocolate this time of year?
I'd like to, but I can't handle crowds.
Makes sense.
Although, my niece mentioned not
having anyone to give chocolates to.
How old is she again?
Almost in her second year of high school.
She loves talking about stuff like that.
It's quite exhausting, actually.
But it's good inspiration.
I'm making chocolates
for my childhood friend.
Are you two going out?!
No, nothing like that.
I get something for White Day in return.
So it's a fair trade.
Ugh, man, I'm so jealous!
Stop shaking the desk.
Want me to make you some too?
I expect payback on White Day.
Yay!
I told you, stop shaking the desk!
Did you get anything?
Some tea. I saw the limited edition
tag and couldn't help myself.
So if I got you tea as a gift,
would you enjoy that?
Well, I'm pretty particular.
But if it's the basic kind, sure, I guess.
I figured. I could never bring myself
to ask in case you thought it was stupid.
I'm glad I finally did.
So, does your job let you
out and about during the day?
Sure it does. I'm on my
lunch break right now.
But it's 3 PM.
I know. Poor me, right?
Want some?
No. I was just admiring
how you savor every bite.
It's a bit embarrassing
to be stared at like that.
Spring can't come fast enough.
Are you even listening?
Who would've thought...
Who would've thought we'd be able
to eat together like this again?
I certainly didn't a year ago.
Yeah.
It's been a year already...
Rather, it's only been a year.
Hey.
Hey!
Huh?
Where's Asa-chan?
Haven't seen her.
I can't do Monday.
I have to make chocolates then.
You mean for me?
Band Club
Auditioning for vocals
Don't get too excited.
They're for my friends.
I'll give you any leftovers.
Nice!
It makes you that happy, huh?
I can't wait.
Whatever you say.
Keep quiet.
Okay. Sorry.
Here. For you.
From Kasamachi-kun.
Chocolate!
Ow, my eardrums.
This one's yours.
This one's mine.
And these are from my editor.
We can share them.
You're that excited?
These aren't the same size!
He played favorites, apparently.
What about you?
Did you give him anything?
Nope.
Actually, I gave him
a good book last week.
That has nothing to do with Valentine's.
Don't expect any typical
feelings or habits out of me.
So you're unapologetically
admitting that now?
Not exactly. I just know myself.
It's like I'm the only person
in the world who's not in love.
Asa, not everyone has to fall in love.
And that's no sign of unhappiness, either.
You're lying!
It's the truth.
There are people like that.
People who don't need romance.
But that's got nothing to do with me.
Of course it does.
There isn't a single thing in this world
completely irrelevant to you.
At the very least, you could take comfort
in the fact that you're not alone, right?
I don't get anything you're saying at all.
Then think harder.
What?
I said to think harder.
You know Makio-chan, you're just...
Hmm?
Nah, never mind.
I'm gonna go change.
Seriously, you think way too much.
Actually, you're too sensitive.
What are you, conceited?
Maybe I am.
Journal with Witch
Takumi.
You know the deal.
Kan-chan! You're the best!
Keep your voice down.
Thanks.
Don't forget next month.
Hey, is Morimoto-san absent again?
Looks like it.
Will she even make it to the next grade?
Sure she will. She's top of the class.
Did you see the news?
About the university docking
points from female applicants?
That makes me so mad!
I wonder what she'll be like
when she's back.
We probably shouldn't bring it up.
Think harder.
There isn't a single thing in this world
completely irrelevant to you.
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Hey, is that Asa-chan?
I wanna see her!
Hi there! I'm Motsu.
Oh, hello to you too.
She's from the same friend group as Daigo.
Glad to finally meet you.
Yeah!
Hey, which do you like better?
Um...
The light blue one.
Told you so.
What's it for?
We're trying to decide what she should
wear for her book signing.
You're doing a book signing?
That's awesome.
Isn't it?
It's all just for show.
C'mon, you're always so cynical.
How about this?
Let me see it on.
I think you're supposed
to step into that one.
Yeah, I think you're right.
My arms are cramping.
Asa, can you zip me up?
'Kay.
You'll need help wearing that.
Asa-chan's gotta lend a hand.
All done.
Thanks.
Hey, I like it.
Yeah? Then maybe I'll go with this.
So, this book singing...
Hmm?
Will you be talking in front of
bunches of people?
I mean, I'll say a few words, sure.
Really? And you're okay with that?
You know, since you're
socially awkward and all.
What?
Actually, you'd be pretty surprised.
She gave a great speech at my wedding.
Although we ended up splitting.
I'm pretty confident I could write
an even better speech for a divorce.
Really? Let's hear it some time!
Makio Koudai Autograph Session
I-I'm a huge fan!
Thanks. What's your name?
What is "marriage"?
Wretched!
You know...
It's just, um...
What is it?
Wait, let me guess.
Are you getting into teenage angst?
I wanna hear all about it.
There you go again, leeching off
the energy of the young.
Is that so bad?
Um...
Yes?
I dunno.
Is standing out a good thing?
Or is it a bad thing?
What?
You know, I'm not the type
to really stand out.
I'm not getting any taller.
I don't have a crush on anyone.
I can't write any lyrics.
Curse
So for someone like me
to stand out feels...
I dunno. I guess it feels wrong.
Like I'm just not the type.
So I guess I keep thinking
it's a bad thing.
What?! Your type?!
Who gives a crap about that?
Jeez, could you be any more blunt?
Oops, my bad.
It was just so silly,
I couldn't help myself.
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
But really, who gives
a hoot about your "type"?
You know, I've carried
a lot of regret about that.
"The type to be understanding."
"The type to avoid confrontation."
"The type to put others first."
"The type to never cry."
I regretted all of those labels.
I got so caught up in the labels
that before I knew it,
I lost sight of what I actually
wanted for myself.
So I got off the hamster wheel.
Asa-chan, wanna know what I think?
I think you should do what you want
to do, right when you want to do it.
Who cares about the rest?
Asa.
If anyone gives you a hard
time for standing out...
Give them hell.
Is that okay?
To give them hell?
No, it's not!
Don't listen to her.
It's what you always say.
Yeah, I'm no novelist.
Be more expressive.
Fine, tear them to pieces.
I didn't mean like that.
Here! I got it!
I'd like to sing!
Huh? Sing?
Sure! I'm not sure I follow,
but go for it!
The scenery I once saw...
In a daze, shooting stars soon shine...
If only I could watch this forever...
Throw away the past and to the future...
Impudent
\hTo be unabashed and brazen
Inane
To be shallow without knowledge or thought
Evil
To have a twisted, bad heart
Void
To have no value or content
With every meeting,
I'd like to turn my gaze away
Wretched
To have a nasty heart or act on meanness
We're all so forgiving
of our own contradictions
from my former self,
from that time and space.
yet show no sympathy for
the contradictions of others.
I didn't realize that
until much, much later in life.
I'd like to reach out
to the sunlight in the dark.
If only I could talk with you right now...
Perhaps we're all like that.
And perhaps I'll have to grapple
with that for a long, long time.
The sunrise seeps into my whole being.
I'm free, I'm free.
But maybe...
My eyes are finally beginning to open.
Just maybe...
Uniform Point Deductions for Female Applicants:
Nitto Medical University Accused of Arbitrary Manipulation
That's not such a bad thing.
If only I could talk with you right now...
This day is one to love. It seeps into me.
"She's really good."
I'm free, I'm free and flying.
"I know."
Okay! That's it!
That was amazing! Bravo!
You know...
Hmm?
Without you, Makio-chan, I probably
wouldn't have joined the band club.
Actually, I know I wouldn't have.
I don't think so.
You made that decision yourself.
I think you would've arrived at that
no matter who you were with.
I wonder what Mom and Dad would have said.
I'm not sure.
Maybe give it some thought.
Makio-chan...
Don't you ever get tired
of thinking so much?
Seriously, you think way too much.
I'd like to sing!
Maybe I do.
But as long as I'm alive,
I might as well struggle.
I don't get what you're saying at all!
Think harder.
Hey!
That was mine!
I was saving it for later!
Oops, sorry, I forgot.