ADAPTED FROM THE STORY OF THE SAME TITLE
BY AUTHOR KU XUAN
FROM CHINESE QIDIAN WEBSITE OF YUEWEN
GROUP THE DAILY LIFE OF THE IMMORTAL KING
How strange.
What anomaly is this?
The treasure left by the Dao Ancestor
seems to have been opened.
Impossible!
The treasure is guarded
by the Dao Ancestor's Martial Soul.
So this is the legendary
Heavenly Dao Scripture Pavilion.
How dare you go into the sacred grounds
of Heavenly Dao without permission!
Oh?
I can handle this intruder alone.
You don't need to step in, guys.
Hahaha!
Such arrogance!
Well then,
you'd better be ready
for Heavenly Dao's punishment.
Bound by my Spatial Chains,
all your Spiritual Energy will be drained.
How... are you still moving?
That's it?
The Heavenly Dao is nothing special.
Let's attack together!
Great Mind Control Technique.
Went into the Heavenly Dao's realm
without permission, you're dead!
Oh no!
The Ancestral Dao's Avatar.
He's been whitelisted by the Heavenly Dao!
Well then, now it's my turn.
Now the whole Heavenly Dao space
is under my command.
What are you trying to do?
Revenge.
THE DAILY LIFE OF THE IMMORTAL KING 5
EPISODE 11:
THE REALM-WIDE WANTED: WANG LING
CANTEEN
Breaking news from our station.
Lately, many kids have gone
missing in the Songhai region.
Spiritual Energy Pay Received:
3 Spiritual Stones.
Meanwhile, lots of masters on the
Celestial Ranking List have gone missing.
Thanks for treating us, Senior Wang!
Now, with the help of the Top Cultivator
of Mortal World, the Seven Star Squadron
has launched a full investigation.
The case is under intensive investigation.
Fellows of Songhai,
I'm Bai Zhe,
the Top Cultivator of Mortal World.
Recently, two notorious criminals
with 10,000-year sentences
have escaped from the First Prison.
They are Wang Ling,
convicted of the Snack Consumption Crime,
and Wang Nuan, convicted of
the Demon Child Rebirth Crime.
WANTED: WANG LING, WANG NUAN,
10 BILLION SPIRITUAL STONES
These two fugitives
are extremely dangerous
and a huge threat to the Mortal Realm.
From now on, the cultivation realm
enters its highest alert status,
a realm-wide wanted is issued
for the two fugitives.
Whoever captures them will get
a reward of 10 billion Spiritual Stones.
LITTLE RACCOON
Wanted criminals?
What is the Top Cultivator
of Mortal World talking about?
Exactly! Senior Wang is only 19 years old.
How could he have been imprisoned
for ten thousand years?
Wang Ling, don't worry.
We're brothers,
and we all believe you're innocent.
CAMPUS STORE
Sun Rong.
Senior Wang,
why did you betray me?
Hmm?
Senior Wang, prepare to die!
- Catch him!
- Stop!
Sword Master, what's going on here?
Stop there!
I've been set up.
Don't let him go.
Damn it! I hesitated.
I should've broken Wang Ling's legs first.
10 billion.
Catching him, I can get
10 billion Spiritual Stones.
Top Cultivator of Mortal World,
Lord Bai Zhe.
We beg for your guidance.
Fugitive Wang Ling is heading
towards Heavenly Paradise.
Senior Wang.
Why... Why are you catching me?
I'm just a dog!
Immortal Master Zhuo,
the demon king has been caught.
The suspect's parents were also arrested
at the vegetable market.
They are close relatives of the wanted
criminals, so they might harbor them.
Did they confess anything?
Nothing.
Don't hit! Don't! Stop!
Keep questioning.
Got it.
The most important thing
is to catch that demon child.
She's just a little kid.
Immortal Master Zhuo, do we really need
to use such drastic ways?
You don't realize
how dangerous this little kid is.
Little girl,
just lay off the sudden moves.
We don't mean any harm.
Oh no!
They were just bubbles.
Everyone, get her!
Yes!
Heh heh...
So Senior Wang was hiding here.
10 billion Spiritual Stones.
If we could catch Wang Ling,
we'd be rolling in cash.
But what if Wang Ling escapes again?
Don't worry.
I asked my grandfather
to activate Paradise's protective barrier.
Senior Wang, are you refusing
to fight back because you look down on me?
Ah! Oh no!
Fire!
Senior Wang, you're not getting away!
Sun Rong.
All the good times we had together.
We released the sky lanterns.
We watched the meteor shower.
The hardships we went through.
The battles we fought together.
And our promise.
Did you forget them all?
Sun Rong.
No matter when or where,
I, Sun Rong, will always have your back.
The way you smile...
No slacking off.
I don't need the whole world's love.
I was wrong.
No matter how much time passes,
bring me to your side...
Are you awake now?
Senior Wang, I'm sorry.
What have I just done?
It's not your fault.
Bai Zhe changed the memories
of the whole Mortal Realm.
That's right, what can you do about it?
I've ascended to the Heavenly Dao.
Don't tell me you can come to
Heavenly Dao to fight me? Hahaha.
Heavenly Dao?
Senior Wang, go for it.
Huh?
Go save the world.
I'll hold them off here.
Ms. Sun, I'll help you.
Senior Sun, have you betrayed
the mortal realm, too?
I won't go easy on you this time.
What's so great about Wang Ling anyway?
Why would you go against everyone for him?
Because
of love!
Did you do all these?
It's time to settle the score.
Hahaha.
Wang Ling, what makes you think
you can challenge me?
The entrance to the Heavenly Dao space
has been sealed off.
How… did you get in here?
The Heavenly Dao,
my wardrobe opens right into it.
What... What kind of joke is this?
I've planned for millennia
just to be here.
But it doesn't matter now.
I've absorbed the Seven Heavenly Daos,
I've become invincible!
Cut the nonsense.
Nuan, will you fight by my side?
Hmm.
Wrath of the Immortal King!
Are you ready?