I attack with two
"Scale-Armored Pack Animals"
and win the game.
Now go work so you can pay off your tab.
Still No Leads on Missing Panda
The body of Fang Fang, the
panda from the Eno Zoo
that died on the 11th, has gone missing.
Zoo director Sato says
that it's likely that
Still No Leads on Missing Panda
someone from outside the zoo
snuck in and stole the carcass.
Eno Zoo Director Sato
Security camera footage has been unable
to confirm the removal of the body.
Fang Fang the Panda
Died of Natural Causes at Age 25
Police suggest the crime was committed
with the use of ether powers
as they continue to investigate.
Why the hell would somebody
steal a dead panda?
Don't change the subject.
You guys again...
Well, one of you.
Yeah.
Just me.
I have a personal request today.
Sara Kashiwagi Pendragon
King Arthur's Only Daughter
It's bound to be nothing but trouble.
Scram!
Hey, don't chase my customers away!
Order something.
A ginger ale, please.
Scum of the Brave
A Brave Sensei
Second-years need to fulfill a period
of public service to graduate...
OO/XX/YYYY
Today I went out
to defeat a slime.
Not "Slay the Dark Lord!"
stuff like before,
but going into dangerous areas
to search for missing people
or taking down dangerous monsters
that Dark Lords left when they died.
I have been beaten.
I couldn't even handle one.
PASS
But to get credit for it, you need
either a teacher from the academy
or an external pro Brave
to act as overseer.
The teachers all say no
when I'm involved.
Whisper, whisper, whisper...
And right now, I'm the
only one missing this credit.
Aw, man!
So what you're saying is...
You're getting picked on by your teachers,
even though you're
the chairman's daughter?
Not exactly!
Well, kinda, I guess...
I know my dad didn't make a
big deal out of it on the phone,
but he's always been against
me becoming a Brave.
And I get the feeling he's
mentioned that to my teachers.
I'd say that means your old man cares
more about you than he lets on.
No one would want their
kid to become a Brave.
No one sane, anyway.
It's not about that. I swear.
My point is, if I can pull
this assignment off,
the school won't be able to fail me...
I think.
Plus, the Brave who acts as my overseer
will be paid by the academy.
How much?
Two doses of E3.
Not even cash?!
There are also cases where the client
with the job pays a separate fee.
Here's a good example.
From the Metro PD.
January 15th, a suspicious gang snuck
into their training facility in Tama,
and they took off with four police dogs.
Three of them were recovered safely,
but from what the transceiver
in the collar indicated,
the last was driven away.
The Kidnapped Police Dog, Komugi-chan (Age 2)
This is a police dog...?
But it's a shiba.
They seem to be used a lot lately.
And the dog's trail ends
somewhere pretty dangerous.
This abandoned building.
Oh, yeah, stray Dark Lords love
holing up in places like this.
To just get credit,
I'd only need to check the place
out and then write a report...
Please save Komugi-chan!!
But if I can recover this shiba,
or the collar it was wearing, there's
a reward of 100,000 yen as a bonus.
So ask the cops for help.
Please save Komugi-chan!!
They don't exactly have people to spare.
Two doses to look for a lost dog,
and 100 grand if we get lucky...
No thanks.
You're gonna find most Braves are
all about making a thorough plan
so they can pull off
get-rich-quick type jobs.
Which does not include this sorta stuff.
Sounds more like a gig for a student.
Well, I'm not gonna force the issue.
I guess I'll ask someone else...
maybe that Joe guy.
Is he coming today?
Actually, he's...
Joe
Sara
Whoops, my hand slipped!
Joe
And after I asked you to
look after my daughter...
You will pay! With your life!
Hold up.
I guess...
I'm willing to help out.
The Next Day
Here's the E3 you were promised.
If you don't end up needing it,
you're free to keep it.
You seem pretty confident.
What's your power, anyway?
Some kinda life form tracking thing?
More like I can tell where enemies are.
I can sense traps and explosives, too.
If they're packing heat,
I can sense them
from over 200 meters away.
How's it feel, anyway?
They always tell us at school not
to give a lot of specifics...
Well, they know their stuff.
Not that it kept Jogamine and
Indo from spilling the beans.
Shocking that those two are
worse students than you.
Anything from the transceiver?
Nothing new.
That means they either
noticed and destroyed it
or went underground.
What do you think?
You can get a passing grade by heading
back and writing this up, right?
Maybe, but I'd at least like
to find the transceiver,
not to mention wanting the reward...
Hey, I'm not saying to give up.
It's your call to make.
From where I stand, it'd be pretty
lucky if we found the mutt,
but I'd also rather not use any E3.
So, what do you think?
I don't sense any enemies.
I think I'd like to keep looking.
Then we've got us a test of courage.
Make sure to keep me safe, milady.
Scum of the Brave
This place...
Reeks of dog in here.
What is this?
A zoo or something?
Hey, look!
Isn't that the shiba we're looking for?
It is!
Heh, look at him wag that tail.
All right, come to me, 100 grand!
Hey!
I have a bad feeling about this.
Will it explode?
No, but...
Hey!
Isn't this...
The panda they were talking
about on the news?
Are pandas usually this big?
No... not usually.
What the hell?
A kid?
Hey, what're you doing here?
Do you know where your mom and dad are?
He must have someone looking after him.
Can we get out of here already?
Hang on a second.
Someone's coming.
From this feeling...
It's a Dark Lord.
This sucks.
Sara, if we end up having
to fight a kid like that,
try not to kill 'im.
R-Right.
You wouldn't believe the
amount of paperwork involved.
They'd want a statement
and for you to go to counseling...
If a Brave kills a minor
under the age of fifteen,
even in a situation where
they have no choice,
there is a mandatory two-week
suspension of activities,
along with compulsory counseling sessions!
Of course, as a Brave,
it's ideal to comport yourself on a
regular basis in a way that avoids—
Hey, are you freaking out?
O-Of course not!
Yusuke?
You left the lights on again.
After him!
Hey, you know that guy?
He's a minion of the
Dark Lord of Kabuki-cho.
And importantly,
he has a bounty on his head!
Gotta take him out!
I fled without thinking at first,
but I must ask, Yashiro the Reaper,
are you here to finally join our forces?
Hell no! This is just a coincidence.
No peons for you
to hide behind this time.
And down here,
you won't be able to get away.
Are you so certain?
What's with the little zoo back there?
You gonna open a pet shop or something?
My job is to create loyal
soldiers for my master.
Which means sampling a wide
variety of candidates.
These take a bit longer than I'd like...
But this is a good opportunity.
I was in the process of abandoning
this facility anyway.
So, before I do,
I can take care of business!
Sara, are there any other
nasty traps in this area?
Not here.
Wait, there's something close, but it's...
Above us!
This is the perfect chance to
test this rare subject's ability!
Bastard.
It feels like...
I don't like this.
It's just like that time
with Amber Thorn.
Back up, Sara!
He's not as tough as he looks.
Don't screw with me!
Three Days Later
Missing shiba found, along with panda carcass.
Credit goes to student from the academy.
Maybe old Pincers'll send
monsters after you next.
If they're anything like the panda, he
could send an army and it wouldn't help.
Here we go.
The debutante who cleaves
a rampaging panda in two.
Thanks for the other day.
Thank you!
Man, I love getting paid for good deeds!
Is this what they call satisfaction?
What did I do to deserve this?!
You mean how you
got yourself into debt?
Shut up!
And get lost, you bourgeois!
Well, I'm glad I turned to you.
And thanks for letting me
handle it, Sensei.
Wait, did she just call me sensei?
My field of vision—
It's nice to meet you, Ishino-sama.
I am a knight of the Round Table.
My name is Kay.
At the command of King Arthur,
I have come to speak with you.
Well, that is a surprise.
How can I help you?
I have a job to offer you.
We'd like you to work along five of our
men to take down a Dark Lord...
Or, rather, take down the Dark Lord that
you've been hunting this entire time.
The official bounty will be split
between you and the five Braves.
However, in addition to that, you
will be paid 80 million as a reward.
In addition to being provided
with as much E3 as you request.
What say you?
It's a generous offer,
but I have to turn it down.
Why is that?
What don't you find agreeable?
Well, being able to choose
what jobs you take
is the best part of being freelance.
In other words...
I have no interest in serving you people.
I see. Well, so be it.
I will respect your courageous decision.
Godspeed to you, Ishino the Musician.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Next Time
There's not a damn thing good
about being a teacher for Braves.
It's the kinda gig
second-rate guys take on.
Right! The perfect job for you
in your current state, Master!
Say what?!
Next time, Episode 6:
"A Brave's Training"!
You mean to tell me I'm
Great Teacher Yashiro?
A Brave's Training