The child lives under constant
violence and fear.
Let me go.
Through his endless suffering
and despair, he finds an escape.
He creates a completely
new person inside himself.
I'm scared, Nico.
He then begins believing
that the one being subjected
to such a horrible situation is not him,
but rather this other poor person.
I have to... catch up.
So this is the "other person"?
Hey, what's up with this treatment?
I thought the Eye of Michael
was supposed to be a friendlier place!
How do you feel, Livio?
Huh? Livio? Who's that?
I'm...
Razlo!
I am Razlo!
Razlo the Tri-Punisher of Death!
Who did this to you?!
Was it Chapel?!
Or was it the blue-haired freak?!
Livio...
Eliminate the traitor!
Wolfwood...
Needle-noggin!
I'm glad your brother is alive.
He's not my real brother.
He's like my little brother.
Say, Needle-noggin...
Having family point a gun at you
is pretty bone-chilling, isn't it?
Is that crybaby Livio who was
always following in my shadow...
even still alive?
Hey, Needle-noggin!
Oh, I can't believe them!
Aunt Melanie...
What's going to happen to us?
What's all this? We're fine.
Even without plants...
Yup, we'll be just fine for a while!
Isn't that right?
Where's the rest of the town?
They abandoned the place
to run off to Octovern
seeking shelter from that so-called "Ark."
They took all the plants from
Hopeland to pay for protection.
I see.
You're...
What? What's going on?
Why are you stopping? Come on!
Oh, no. Hey, back up! Go back!
I guess I wasted my time.
Hey, are you Ni—
In fact, I brought this on you. I'm sorry.
Huh?
I need a favor.
Can you take care of him?
He needs to rest.
Got it.
That's all I've got.
Share with everyone, okay?
Thank you.
If I get taken out...
Hand Needle-noggin over to the man.
He'll leave you alone that way.
Yeehaw!
I heard you were a merciless,
cold-blooded executioner.
Far from the truth, isn't it?
Oh, I see.
It was Vash the Stampede.
He must have gotten into
your head and dragged you down.
No, that's not what this is.
You're wrong!
Hm?
The guy's a real idiot in my opinion.
There's no way I could
ever play along with him.
I know... he's an idiot.
Everything he says is just the
reality-denying prattle of a spoiled brat.
I know all that. But still...
Even so...
He never makes any excuses!
Oh?
This medicine can cure any wound.
However, in return, it causes
your body to mature rapidly.
Within a few short years, your cells will
deteriorate, and you will die of old age.
Well, well. I'm actually surprised
that you're still up to the task.
But by my calculation,
this time, you're gonna die.
Besides, what's the point?
The world is ending soon.
Or... do you think Vash the Stampede
can beat Knives?
Who knows?
But if anyone can, it'd be him.
That relentless sincerity of his...
That, I put my faith in.
You should be afraid of someone
who never gives up anything.
Oh, how funny.
I'll see if you're right,
if I should be afraid...
after I'm done with you!
I'm beating you down.
Take this!
Die already.
Stop that!
Are you talking to me?
Yes, you, Livio.
Why does everyone always call me Livio?
Because you are Livio.
Don't you remember how
Nicholas took care of you?
Nicholas, you're a fool yourself.
Tried to do everything all
by your lonesome again, didn't you?
I swear, you always take the losing side.
You have such high standards
and never compromise.
That's why you get hurt so often.
Being alone must be so overwhelming.
You're all beat up, and you've
been gone for so many years.
Yet you come back when we need you most.
Yeah, maybe I tried to take on
too much by myself.
I screwed up.
I can't move anymore.
I can't save Livio.
I can't show everyone the hope
that leads to tomorrow.
Hang on. This ain't right.
I shouldn't be remembering
his face at a time like this.
Oh, I see now.
I finally get it.
Don't you, Nicholas D. Wolfwood?
The reason I couldn't stop
looking for him.
The reason I keep going after him.
He's my...
I don't really get what's going on,
but killing them first seems like fun.
Don't... you...
I'll take everything from you
before I kill you!
Auntie...
I have a friend now.
Don't worry. I'm Nicholas's friend.
Needle-noggin... If you can move,
you shoulda gotten here sooner.
Er, sorry.
You guys go back up.
Hurry!
Auntie, you guys said "Nicholas"!
Was that Nico?!
Listen, everyone. That man is...
He stopped every single
shot out of my Tri-Punisher?
Oh, wow. I'm getting hard.
That's awesome! So awesome!
I'll dedicate your heads
to the late Master Chapel!
You seem a lot more interesting
than this guy at my feet.
I don't know about that.
You're still playing with me.
You're practically dead. What do you want?
Get lost!
Useless.
That doesn't even hurt— Huh?
My blood?!
You're using it as the medicine!
I'm going for the heart.
This is it, Razlo.
Ow...
My regeneration can't keep up.
Wait... What?
Ow!
Crybaby Livio!
I'm gonna save you!
In that case...
It's over. Stop, Razlo.
Ah, I see. Are you Livio?
Who do you think you're talking to?!
That sounded like an order!
Sorry, then let me put it this way.
I'm ending you now...
Razlo the Tri-Punisher of Death!
Hey! Stop, you idiot!
Without me, you're just a—
I'm sorry. Truly. I forced
everything painful onto you.
But it's fine now.
I can go on.
Yes, I want to live like him.
Don't worry. I'll catch up one day.
This is farewell.
Goodbye, Razlo, my friend!
Mister... Wolfwood.
Hey.
Welcome back, crybaby Livio.
Stay with us, Wolfwood!
Nicholas!
Please don't die. My blood should
fix you up right away!
You're still the same old crybaby.
You'll never catch up to me like that.
Nico! You're Nico, aren't you?
Can you use the toilet by yourself now?
Yeah, I can!
You're all grown up now.
Hey, Needle-noggin...
Take care of everyone.
Nico!
Yeah, I'm home.
Wolfwood?
Nicholas!
Hey, Nico!
Nico...
Open your eyes! Don't die! Nico!
Nico!
Say something!
You're disturbing my rest.
Mr. Wolfwood!
Nico! Are you okay?!
Nicholas!
Thank goodness.
Wolfwood!
I said you're disturbing my rest!
Ow!
We must go and finish
our fight against Knives.