There.
You're all set, Kaya.
Oh, look at the time.
Kaya, do you have everything?
Daddy, my water bottle.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Just a second.
There we go.
I filled your bottle with
that sweet barley tea you like.
Kaya, let's go.
Okay.
Off we go.
Sato Kaya
Mean? Selfish? Or just different?
There are children who are
seen that way by others.
But what if that child could
see something you couldn't?
This is the story of Kaya-chan,
a girl who could see ghosts.
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 5: Trains Aren't Scary
Chie-sensei! I spent
the whole night digging into it,
Mob Osamu
and I think I found
something interesting.
Mob Osamu
So I figured I had to
tell you immediately—
Wait, stop! I don't have time
for that right now.
Tanigoe
Kawabukuro
Shindoba
Shibukawa
Tatehama
Shin-Tatehama
Kanjiro Line
Yamato Korai Line
Bound
Local
Express
Sonandai
Imobukuro
10 Cars
Knowing you, you
probably already know this,
but today's our field trip on the trains.
So I don't have time to listen—
Anyway, while I was looking
into Kaya-sama's mother...
Are you even listening?!
Chie-sensei! You go with the last group.
Yes, of course.
Uh, got it.
Hello, Chie-sensei? Chie-sensei!
So please just save it for later. Bye.
Sheesh.
Okay, the Beetle Group
will go with Chihiro-sensei...
Sensei, I want juice.
You're not allowed.
Sensei, can I go to the bathroom?
I need to pee, too.
We're taking the Sozo Line, right?
So it's the yellow train!
Huh? But my daddy said
it was the blue train.
Akira-sensei, Chie-sensei's freaking out.
Don't just watch. Go help her.
Beetle Group all set
Chihiro
So is the Ladybug Group
Hasumi Chie
Looks like everyone made it on safely.
Wow, really?
I can't wait.
Same!
What snacks did you bring?
Grown-ups pay for this train.
You kids ride for free, don't you?
So get off those seats!
Huh? We paid for the group fare.
Hey, don't say stuff that
might make things worse.
I'm sorry. It'd be unsafe to make
the kids stand, so please take our seats.
Kashiwa
Hachimi
Shin-Kengaya
Funabashi Yama
Bound
Platform
Local
Express
Kokanei
Ofune
10 Cars
Okay, let's all get off.
Do we have everyone?
Yes, we do—
Kaya-chan!
Kaya-chan is still on board!
What?
What's the matter, Kaya-chan?
The door is closing.
We're getting off.
Ah.
Well, the silver lining
is that you're there with her.
The principal said, "It happens once a
decade or so, so don't beat yourself up."
O-Once a decade? And I did it?
We've got things covered here,
so there's no need to rush. Safety first—
Akira-sensei?
We got disconnected.
Maybe it's a weak signal.
Oh well. Let's turn around
at the next stop.
Here. Have a seat, Kaya-chan.
Kaya-chan?
I can't sit there.
You kids ride for free, don't you?
It's okay, Kaya-chan.
Don't worry about what that man said.
Huh?
We paid our fare, and there's no rule
saying kids have to stand.
Hey, you!
Besides, the train is empty.
What? There wasn't anyone
here a second ago.
You can see them, too, Chie-sensei?
A lot of people got on
at the last station.
Huh?
That's why I couldn't get off the train.
We have to run, Kaya-chan.
It's fine. They're not doing anything bad.
That man is meaner.
Y-You think so?
We're stopping.
Let's get off! We need to head back!
Don't get off.
Huh?
M-Move!
Damn. What was up with that train?
But man, that was cutting it close.
Who knows what would've happened
to me if I'd stayed on?
Good thing I—
W-Was that a dream?
A call?
Mob Osamu
It's Mob-san.
I figured something had happened
when the GPS suddenly cut out...
...but ending up at
an underworld station was unlucky.
It's fortunate you had
Kaya-sama with you.
You thought I'd overlook the GPS thing
if you mentioned it in passing, huh?
So from what I'm hearing, you got
separated from the rest of the group?
Well, yes.
Even if we wanted to catch up to them,
there's no train we can take.
AM
48 minutes until departure
So...
We might as well go grab a taxi
to meet up with them.
Hello! Your taxi's here!
What are you doing here?
Aw, c'mon. At least you have
transportation now, so that's a win.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
Are you okay with this, driver?
This guy's being ridiculous!
Yes, my husband's always been like this.
H-He's your husband?!
You're the man who can see ghosts.
Oh, you remembered me this time!
Please call me "Mobuo," Kaya-sama.
Mobuo.
I, Mobuo, will make sure
you reach your destination safely!
But before that,
I'd like to make a suggestion.
A suggestion?
Kaya-sama, would you like to go see
your mother's mother—your grandmother?
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Grandma Isn't Scary?
Kaya-chan's grandma?
What are you talking about?
She's the reason I urgently
reached out to you, Chie-sensei.
Allow me to explain from the beginning.
While I was looking into Kaya-sama's
parents, I discovered something.
A picture?
That is Ebisumori Mutsu-san.
Her eyes have colossal
clairvoyant powers.
It's said she used her psychic powers
to identify the perp of a vicious crime.
For a time, her foresight was sought
worldwide, disrupting her life,
and forcing her to turn down divination
requests from the general public.
But her abilities weren't
limited to clairvoyance...
Here we go again.
Her granddaughter is even said
to wield divine power.
That means...
Huh? You're talking about Kaya-chan?
Precisely. Given Kaya-sama's abilities,
it's hardly a surprise.
As a close relative,
there's a good chance she knows something
about Kaya-sama's mother.
Coincidentally, Ebisumori Mutsu-san lives
where you're going for your field trip.
With her granddaughter there,
she'll be chattier,
so I was waiting for an opportunity
to bring her along.
Huh? Wait. Does that mean...
You planned to kidnap
Kaya-chan, didn't you?!
Oh, no, no. Phrasing it like that
makes it sound terrible.
I naturally intended for you
to accompany us as well, Chie-sensei.
Could you not make me
an accessory to your crimes?!
But when you're up against
supernatural phenomena,
common sense alone doesn't cut it.
Think back to when you first met
Kaya-sama. You should understand.
Given that, what can you do for her?
And what do you want to do for her?
So I'll be the one who
protects you, Kaya-chan.
I...
As a teacher, my duty is to make sure
the kids can live happily every day.
So even if I can't see it myself,
if there's trouble at home,
I'll cross any line to help out!
Yup, that's the spirit!
And anyway...
Leaving you alone with
Kaya-chan is just too sketchy!
Where are we?
It's where your grandma lives.
Let's say hi to her, okay?
Okay.
Front
Desk
I'm here to see Ebisumori Mutsu-san.
Yes. We're her relatives.
Shoo. Shoo.
Huh?
Over there.
Hmm?
I guess those are their pickups.
"Pickups"?
I'm here!
Well, there are a lot
of elderly people here.
Hey, that's inappropriate!
How so?
If they've lived until
their time's up, that's plenty.
Death always catches up eventually.
The pickup phenomenon is seen
pretty often. It won't hurt anyone.
You're oddly calm about it.
Are you impressed?
Shut up!
Okay, let's go—
Shoo.
Oh! K-Kaya-sama!
Oh, my.
What a nice girl you are. Thank you.
Did you see that just now?
She sent it away.
Sent it packing.
They saw!
Huh? What do you mean?
I don't get it.
Let's hurry.
Hey!
What's going on?
She sent the pickup away.
Do mine.
And mine.
Send mine away, too.
I still want to live.
That was careless of me.
It's said people see things
more clearly when death is near.
So what's going on? I don't understand.
The "pickup" is the personification
of one's impending death.
If people learn the looming death that
attaches itself to you can be sent away...
Wait for me!
What's the matter, Yamaguchi-san?
Suzuki-san, please don't push yourself.
You sayin' it's fine if I die?!
A child just sent the pickup away!
I... I refuse to die!
Despite their age, they remain
physically capable humans.
Letting them near Kaya-sama
in their agitated state is dangerous.
Kaya-sama's grandmother's room
is down the hallway.
Go see her before things get out of hand.
What about you?
I'll handle things here.
Mob-san.
Aw, yeah! I've always wanted to say that.
This is no time to joke around!
Mobuo.
Man! Okay, we're going.
Okey-dokey.
I'm annoyed at myself
for giving him any credit.
Now, having said that...
I've never been good at all that rough
stuff, so there's not much I can do.
Enough.
I came to see what
all the noise was about.
You aren't young anymore, you hear?
Sending the pickup away
doesn't mean you live any longer.
Instead, you never know
when you're going to die.
So you live in constant anxiety.
Ebisumori-san.
So this is Ebisumori Mutsu,
one of Japan's top psychics.
Hmm?
That's Kaya-sama's grandmother for you.
She sent all of the pickups away!
For heaven's sake. So pathetic!
Why are you freaking out all of a sudden?
You're old. Accept it.
Pardon me. Are you Ebisumori Mutsu-san?
Huh? I don't recognize that voice.
Who are you?
My name is Mob Osamu, and I'm a writer.
There's someone I want
you to meet today.
I wonder if Mob-san will be okay.
Ebisumori Mutsu
Found it. This is her room.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Looks like she's not here.
What's this?
Maybe an altar?
Tensho
Kotai Jingu
Oh, is this a family photo?
Is the girl at the end
Kaya-chan's mother?
She looks so cute.
Oh.
What's the matter, Kaya-chan?
Kaya-chan?
Her daughter?
That's correct.
She's also your grandchild.
Have you met her?
No. I was never told
she'd given birth, either.
She's such a heartless
daughter, I swear.
And what does this child want with me?
Let's talk about that in your room.
But first, I think it's best
if you spoke with her alone.
So she had a daughter, huh?
Kaya-sama, Grandmother Mutsu is here.
Kaya?
No!
Huh?
I see now!
How terrible!
Ebisumori-san?
Why?
G-Grandmother? She's...
Sato
Kaya
Nana... What happened to Nana?
Sh-She... She didn't do anything wrong!
It's all my fault!
S-So if you're going
to kill anyone, kill me!
Only take me!
Sato
Kaya
Nana is...
How can you say something
like that to a child?!
I beg you!
Are you okay, Kaya-chan?
I-I see now.
K-Kaya-chan!
It's all because of my careless
suggestion. I'll reflect deeply on it.
No, it's also my fault for agreeing to it.
Chie-sensei.
Kaya-chan! Are you okay?
Are you feeling all right?
Yeah.
My grandma.
Yeah?
We couldn't see her?
Huh?
Parking for Authorized Users Only
Standard
Vehicles
Large
Kaya-chan had lost her memories from
before and after meeting her grandmother.
It's not exactly a happy memory.
I think it's better to let it be.
Once things have calmed down,
I'll go see her again.
Um, sure.
Mobuo, bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Something occurred to me.
Kaya-chan!
What took you so long?
Hey. Glad you two made it in time.
I had to take a taxi, so y'know.
A taxi?
Now that we're all here,
let's explore the forest together.
Okay!
What if Kaya-chan
didn't lose her memories?
What if that wasn't her in that room?
Sensei!
Come on!
We won't look for you if you get lost!
Wait up!
But then, who was it?
What did you find?
Look, an acorn.
Wow!
That question would be
answered a little later.
It's so pretty!
Where'd you find it?
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
The specters attached to the elderly
are harmless to humans.
They have no malicious
intent whatsoever,
and merely stay by the side of those
whose time is almost up.
To seem less scary, their masks resemble
people that person was once close to.
So if you see one yourself,
please don't be afraid.