Step **** up and *** a look...
It's ti** for Yami***bai.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
Gathering
Morishima Real Estate
This is the story of an unremarkable
man who works in real estate...
Is this really the talented
psychic that the boss wanted?
Seems like just some young punk who's
paying too much attention to his bangs.
I'm sure you've heard,
but the people who've moved into
this house have been going missing
and dying in mysterious ways...
I have to admit,
this place is definitely creepy.
Oh, I-I guess I was
distracting you. Sorry.
Um, Sensei?
It's done.
Done? You mean... the exorcism?
You're not going to pray or anything?
The spirit is already gone.
I don't really follow,
but as long as it's done...
Well, good work, Ohara-sensei!
Morishima Real Estate
My daughter told me about
how talented you are.
Looks like I made the right
call turning to you!
I didn't really do anything.
The exorcism was a success thanks to him.
Him? You mean Shibasaki?
I oughta change that light bulb.
He's got a unique condition that
seems to draw spirits to him.
He draws spirits in?
Yes. Most spirits will be lured away
from wherever they're
haunting by Shibasaki-san.
For example, the poltergeist from
that house is with him now.
Never thought he had that kind of talent...
He doesn't seem to realize it, either.
Does that mean as long
as Shibasaki is around,
he can clean up any stigmatized
properties we're handling?
I think so, but...
Huh? That's weird...
If anything ever triggers
Shibasaki-san's ability to see spirits,
I don't know if he'll be able to stay sane.
Ow, ow...
N-No way...
After all, there's bound to be
countless spirits that Shibasaki-san
has attracted haunting his
house at this point.
So, my dad told me that
Shibasaki-san is in the hospital.
Really? I figured.
You did? Do you know the reason why?
Maybe.
Don't play dumb! Is this a ghost thing?
Is it? Is it?
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
The end.