What? Mobu-san's gone missing?
Yes, you could say that.
Um, aren't you worried, ma'am?
It's nothing new.
The moment his interest is piqued,
he cuts off all contact.
Where the heck did that punk go?
And if things get hairy,
he can disappear for days.
H-How scary. So scary.
Then he comes home perfectly well,
so it feels silly worrying about him.
I-Is that so?
I'll get him to contact you
as soon as he returns.
Thank you. I'll be waiting.
I couldn't tell her.
I called Mob-san and a voice said...
This is why I warned him.
And it clearly wasn't his voice.
I've tried calling him a few times since,
but he's not picking up.
I hope Mob-san's okay.
Hanamugi... Hanamugi...
Ah, found it.
What's the matter, Chie-sensei?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
No? Well, it's almost time, so could
you get the kids to come back inside?
Yeah, I can do that.
So that's Chie-sensei, huh?
Just as I thought.
Kaya-chan.
Time to put things away.
I'll stop when I fall.
No fair, Kaya. You never fall.
Hurry up and get off!
Kaya. Her name uses the kanji for "God"
and the number "eight."
Sensei! Kaya-chan's not doing what she's told!
It's time to go!
She's the eighth shrine maiden.
I see.
She's a monster.
Mean? Selfish? Or just different?
There are children who are
seen that way by others.
But what if that child could
see something you couldn't?
This is the story of Kaya-chan,
a girl who could see ghosts.
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 8: Reversed Isn't Scary
Family
Fall
Festival
October 24th (Sat)
Central Shopping Street - Station Front Street
Family
Fall
Festival
October 24th (Sat)
Central Shopping Street - Station Front Street
Goodbye, Sensei.
Goodbye.
No!
I like it like this!
Stop being difficult.
It's okay like this! No!
What's wrong?
Oh, Sensei.
He's wearing his shoes on the wrong feet,
and his socks are inside out.
When I tell him to fix them, he says...
It's okay like this!
No, it's not. It means you're dead.
Huh?
Long ago, to signal when someone died,
everything on them got reversed.
So the way you're dressed now means
you died, Takkun. Are you okay with that?
Oh, for crying out loud.
What? No way!
Takkun, you can put
your own socks and shoes on now?
Remember how you were
always asking for help?
Yeah.
You've grown so much! That's incredible!
Aw, I wish I'd seen you
put them on by yourself.
Hey, I know! Could you show me and
your grandma how you put them on?
O-Okay!
You're amazing, Sensei.
Oh, this is nothing.
Good job, Takkun.
Uh-huh.
Bye-bye, Sensei!
Bye-bye.
Any word from Mob-san?
Mob Osamu
Voice Call
Mob-san
Did something come up?
Is it something related
to Kaya-chan's aunt?
Her name is Nana-san
Canceled
Guess not.
Civic Park
I have something important to tell you. Come alone.
Excuse me?!
He finally gets in touch out of nowhere
and asks to meet here at this time.
Man, how long's he gonna
make me wait?
Civic Park
I have something important to tell you. Come alone.
I'm here. Where can we meet?
Where are you?
Hey
I have work tomorrow, you know!
That's it! I'm going—
A boy?
But it's already dark.
When did he get here?
A-Are you here by yourself?
Where are your parents?
You shouldn't be out alone this late.
Oh, I teach at the kindergarten nearby.
If something's bothering you,
we can talk there—
Um...
Toshi-chan!
Mommy!
Is my son bothering you?
Oh, no, it's not like that.
I'm sorry to surprise you.
Mommy!
How embarrassing. I didn't notice them
because I was glued to my phone.
Mommy!
I'm sorry to scare you—
What's this weird feeling I'm getting?
Something's off.
Toshi-chan!
Mommy!
When someone died...
Toshi-chan!
...everything got reversed.
Th-This isn't good!
Something bad's gonna happen
if I stay here!
I-I'm sorry.
Chie-sensei?
Huh?
Mob-san!
What are you doing here?
No, that's my line. You're the one
who told me to come here!
But never mind that.
This place isn't safe. We need to go.
There's a ghost mother and child over—
A ghost mother and child? Ooh, intriguing!
Gimme the details.
We can't chat here!
Everything's reversed!
You know about it, right, Mob-san?
How everything's reversed
for dead people—
tsohG
Oh, so you're familiar
with the "reversed" custom?
You sure know your stuff, Chie-sensei.
Oh, no. My legs gave out.
Clap, clap, clap. Clap, clap, clap.
There you are.
Um, is he dead? Uh...
C'mon, Osamu-kun. Wake up.
Someone'll call the cops
on you again if you sleep here.
Now, that's what I call refreshing!
I feel so light!
As if a curse has been lifted.
Well, yeah. That's what happened.
Huh?
What?!
Wh-What are you doing here...
m-m-master?!
A d-decoy?!
I see. You found Chie-sensei
in my call history,
and brought her to a place
where specters were likely to appear.
Yup.
Impressive, master.
Say what?!
I'm glad you're okay, Osamu-kun.
Thank you for looking after me.
Don't move on without me.
I have a million questions,
but first, who are you supposed to be?
Loom.
My master isn't good with people.
What? And what's all that "master" stuff?
His name is Namu-san.
I gained my knowledge
of spirits from him.
Namu-san?
He's a great psychic whose powers are
so strong, he can't settle in one place.
So he's suspicious person number two,
and he's homeless and without a job.
Have a little mercy.
It doesn't matter.
Huh?
This is our last time
speaking to each other.
I warned you, didn't I, Osamu-kun?
About not getting involved
with the Ebisumori shrine maiden.
Ebisumori?
You got lucky this time
that it was only a minor possession.
Oopsie-daisy.
It might not be so simple the next time—
Hold it right there.
He just said "Ebisumori."
That's Kaya-chan's mother's maiden name,
and the last name of the psychic granny
and the aunt who showed up out of nowhere.
What's this about the Ebisumori family?
What do you mean? You got involved
not knowing who they are?
No wonder you panicked earlier.
In that family,
the eldest Ebisumori daughter inherits
power beyond the ordinary for generations.
The eldest daughter?
That little one is
the eldest, too, isn't she?
Even so, that one's on
a whole other level. A monster.
Because Osamu-kun is
too perceptive for his own good,
he seems to attract
all kinds of spirits now.
Wasn't that thing
supposed to be locked up?
They can't just set
something like that loose.
What the heck is
that old Ebisumori woman doing?
A-Actually, Mutsu-san is...
W-Wait a second!
Sure, Kaya-chan does indeed
possess mysterious powers.
But she's not a monster.
She's an ordinary girl
you'd find anywhere.
Don't say such awful things!
Individual good or evil means nothing
in the face of such overwhelming power.
I bet you know what I'm talking about.
That's...
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
The Sandbox Isn't Scary
Huh?
Oh, hi, Kaya-chan.
What are you going to make?
A mountain.
Nope! That's not how you do it!
Huh?
This is a job site run by my company,
Nakahashi Construction.
You can't join us if you're not
gonna take it seriously.
You heard him!
Listen to what our boss says!
No, this won't cut it. All you
did was pile up sand and that's it.
You gotta pat it down
like this with the shovel.
Hear that? That's the sound you want.
See?
Excellent work, boss.
Boss!
Got it? Now you try.
Wha?!
You're fired! Fired, fired, fired!
Cut her some slack, boss.
Kaya-chan wants to join you.
Well, she can't!
She'll just mess up what I made again!
I did it!
Wow!
Huh?
Your mountain's so cool, Ma-kun.
Here's the tunnel,
and this is the hiking trail.
It's like a real mountain!
You're so fussy, Masaru.
It's called being skilled.
You're number one at making mountains,
Ma-kun. You're so cool!
Hmph, that's nothin'.
Huh?
Mine's bigger.
I'll just add a tunnel now.
The boss is jealous.
He hates to lose.
Hey, don't just watch. Gimme a hand!
Nah. This one's more fun to watch.
Huh?
Is someone digging
from the other side, too?
But who? The mountain's
too tall for me to see who it is.
Well, whatever. Who cares?
Just a little more. Keep digging.
Almost there!
You're so cold! Don't grab me like that.
You freaked me out.
Well, whatever. The tunnel's complete!
What the heck? I can't get up
if you're holding my hand!
Let go!
What are you doin'? You're too strong.
Hey, boss.
Stop being so stubborn and come join us.
Shut up! The person on
the other side won't let go of me.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
You're the only one digging the tunnel.
Huh?
What the heck? Stop!
Let go of me! Hey, what are you doin'?
Stop pullin' my arm!
What the heck?! Who are you?!
Are you okay?
Uh-oh, Kaya-chan. You shouldn't ruin
someone else's mountain.
Don't do anything to mine, okay?
You'll get in trouble for swinging
a shovel around, too.
It felt like something
was inside the tunnel.
He's right, you know.
No way. It was just my imagination.
Kaya-chan!
Huh?
Let's make sand balls together.
Coming.
Huh?
Hurry up, Kaya-chan.
Okay!
How do you explain this?!
How did he get this bruise on his arm?
We should've kept a closer eye
on him. We're very sorry.
You really don't know who did it to you?
There was nobody around you?
Kaya-chan was.
But...
She beat it up for me, so...
Beat up who?
The g-ghost.
Staff Room
We never found out
how he got that bruise on his arm.
I'm sure Nakahashi-san isn't satisfied.
It is what it is. We have to do a good job
going forward to rebuild their trust.
Injury Log
Tamura Asuka — Playground
Collided head-on during tag and got a nosebleed.
Applied ice to stop the bleeding.
Sakurai Rihito — Same as above
Bump on forehead. Applied ice.
Nakahashi Yuki — Sandbox
Unexplained bruise on right arm. Applied ice.
Still, a ghost? That sounds like
something Kaya-chan would say.
Is it the in thing now or something?
Know anything, Chie-sensei?
Huh?
That one's on a whole
other level. A monster.
K-Kaya-chan isn't a ghost!
Oh, c'mon. What are you even saying?
Of course she's not.
That's not what we're saying.
Huh? Oh, of course.
I'm sorry.
Nice People Aren't Scary?
Family Fall Festival
It's time for our annual
Family Fall Festival.
Let the fun begin!
Trick or treat!
Here you go.
Yay!
And one for you.
Thankin' ya!
Oh, it's the teachers
from Hanamugi. Sensei!
Long time no see, Akira-sensei.
You're dressed as a demon?
Wow, look at you!
Getting bigger every year.
I was sulking about giving up our day off
for community service, but...
We can't complain after seeing that.
Sensei! Trick or treat!
Being an experienced teacher
has its upsides.
I guess so.
Huh?
Wait. Just now...
I could've sworn I saw someone
who didn't fit in.
What's up, Chie-sensei?
Oh, nothing.
Huh?
Trick or treat!
Boo!
Kaya-chan!
Hi.
Hello. Here with your dad today?
Yup.
We've been at the hospital
with my wife most weekends.
How is Kaya-chan's mother doing?
She's doing a lot better.
That's great.
I appreciate all the help
the kindergarten gives us.
Oh, it's nothing.
Daddy, I wanna do that raffle.
Huh?
Da—
Oh, what's the matter?
Ah, did you mistake me for your daddy?
Oh, Daddy!
Hm? Oh, you're that girl from earlier.
Looks like you're really lost, huh?
You're in trouble, right? I'll help you.
No!
See?
You came to me again.
I bet you actually want to play
with me. Isn't that right?
What a naughty girl.
You shouldn't hit people.
N-No!
Huh?
Help me! I wanna go home!
Lemme go!
Calm down. These ghosts aren't real.
I wanna go home!
It's okay.
Oh, I see. She's still little.
Must be rough on her father.
Let go!
How cute.
Okay, let's go get some treats together.
I don't want any! Let go!
Just come with me.
You don't like monsters, do you?
Be good and nothing scary will happen.
No... Why?
I'm strong.
So why can't I... How come?
I'm...
Huh?
Has my daughter done something?
Are they arguing?
Wait, he's not her father?
Oh, yuck. He's just some perv?
Could you let go of her now?
She's the one who was following me!
You should watch your kid
if you're a parent.
Whatever, man.
Your powers don't work
on normal human beings.
Oh, but you wouldn't
understand what I'm...
I guess it's no use.
This is exactly why monsters
can't live among humans.
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka