Let's have a flower-viewing party!
Let's do it!
This morning, I saw a spot
where they were in full bloom!
Let's all go see them together!
What?
It doesn't really do us any good to
look at some cherry blossoms.
And it'll be all dusty.
Yes, that's true.
What a shame.
I guess we could go.
I do happen to be free tonight.
Thank you!
I'm not quite satisfied
with how this went...
But whatever! Let's go!
All right!
Siu-san, have you ever been
to a flower-viewing party?
Do I look like a man who likes flowers?
Yes, very much so.
Don't just say random shit.
Papa, cherry blossoms!
I didn't really look at the flowers,
Yes, they are.
Papa, they're pretty!
but my kids pestered me, so we went.
Yes, they are.
That makes sense.
Flower viewing! Flower viewing!
Let's go! Let's go!
I can't wait.
Hey, Hugh, do you like
flower-viewing parties?
I'm not sure.
I've only ever done them as a child.
Same here.
I wasn't particularly into them before...
but when I saw them today,
they were so pretty.
And I thought, "It'd be so nice
to look at them with everyone."
I thought the same thing!
Really? So we're the same!
I can't wait to go!
Yeah!
A flower-viewing party?
Apparently, they're going
after they finish work.
Oh, yes. Well, they will
fall soon, after all.
Do you want to go, too?
No, I'm not interested.
But I'm glad everyone
is getting along so well.
They're such good kids, aren't they?
I'd love to see the
people who raised them!
Shall I bring you a mirror?
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Gloom...
GLOOM
With this much work,
we won't have time for a flower viewing.
Boo.
Don't act like babies.
I'm sorry.
It's not like this is your fault.
We got some urgent cases in,
but Siu-san and I will handle them.
You two can go if you want.
HISS
I wanted to see them
with all of us together.
If just the two of us go,
there's no point.
Mike-kun...
But... I understand how
important this work is.
So let's do our best
and get it all wrapped up!
Yeah!
Seriously...
You've become such good kids!
I guess your big brother here will
have to show what he can really do.
Right, Papa?
Who're you calling "Papa"?
Done
That was fast!
We did hurry, but...
if we change clothes,
we won't make it in time.
It's pitch-black over there at night.
Oh.
There's a cherry tree at the
park near here, isn't there?
The one that has the
street lights on at night.
Let's go there!
It won't be much compared
to the place you wanted to go.
That's totally fine!
Let's try going there.
It's so pretty.
One tree is more than enough!
Well, cherry blossoms
are cherry blossoms.
Yes, they're quite impressive.
Well, good work again today!
Cheers!
Thank you...
you for going along with
our selfish request today.
It's not a problem.
Mike-chan, are you satisfied, too?
Yes! Thank you.
I'd like to see them with
everyone again sometime.
Yeah.
Welcome, everyone!
THRILLED
We've been wanting to
come here for so long!
You can look around the first
floor without a license,
so you could've come sooner!
That's what I thought,
but Siu-san and Sero-san said...
"If you go by yourselves,
you'll be sitting ducks, so don't do it."
I-I wouldn't take advantage of you!
Wow!
There are so many books
I've never seen before!
Wow, this is incredible!
There are specialist volumes here
that aren't in general circulation.
They're all pretty expensive.
Makes it hard to decide which to buy.
What are you deciding between?
We'll take all of them.
They're big brother sitting ducks.
Torture Supply Store
2nd Floor
Your licenses look okay.
You and your companions
can come right this way!
This is amazing!
Right?
Look! Look at this device!
Who gets that excited in
a shop like this? Weirdos.
Wow, that's so cool!
There's a new model of whip out.
Siu-san... you're pretty odd yourself.
It's a garrote! Wow!
It's so cool!
Excuse me, Belta-san?
Hmm? What is it?
Would you mind taking a picture of us?
What?
Peace! Peace!
I like how it's so easy to adjust
the pressure on the neck.
It steadily inflicts pain and fear,
so it'd make it easy
to extract information!
I get a lot of odd ones
among my customers...
but those kids are way weirder than most.
Yeah, I thought they might be.
They're very promising, after all.
How do you use this?
Oh, that?
It's like a crane game.
It grabs onto flesh or skin.
Like... Wham!
Seems painful.
Do we have one?
It's so funny how their
tastes are slightly different.
A license, huh?
Maybe I'll try studying for one.
It never hurts to have one.
If you're going to get one,
I'll give you some gentle lessons.
Just give it some thought.
We will!
Gentle, huh?
He wasn't gentle with me at all!
Because I believed
in you, obviously.
Siu-san!
Don't force me to do this dumb stuff.
So, that's what this shop is like.
Do you feel satisfied?
Yes!
If you want to come again, just ask.
Sero-san!
Can we get a garrote at our place?
I guess I could ask Noe.
If that doesn't work,
just cry until he caves.
Yes, sir!
Oh, right.
Bel-san, are they finished?
They've already arrived!
Wait here just a sec, okay?
Those are presents from us.
Sero-san!
Mike-chan, put it down. Put it down.
Wow! This is amazing!
It's incredible!
It has my name on it!
Mine has mine, too!
Let's use these and work even harder!
Yeah!
It just took one device
to get them that motivated.
Those were good purchases, huh?
Actually, though...
They're just so cute that we
wanted to reward them, that's all.
That's all it was.
Forget love-blinded parents.
They're love-blinded mentors.
We're off to do some torturing!
Hey!
Are you using those again?
Yes.
There's no need to use those
for everything, you know.
But...
No buts!
If you're going to act spoiled,
I'll take them away!
What?!
Keep it to twice a day.
Are you their mom?
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Hiya!
I've come again today
to pick up the dregs!
Are you all happily torturing...
I can see you're not.
Sob, sob...
What's wrong?
Don't get so sad.
You can't change what's already been done.
Sero-san...
Hey, what happened?
It was pretty much fine
if that one died anyway.
Um, hey. What happened?
Safety First
Let's stay safe today!
Oh, dear.
You let someone die
who wasn't a korokke?
Korokke
A target it's okay to kill
That's right.
It's the one you were
scheduled to take today.
Oh, that one?
I'm sure it'll be fine, then.
Right?
Wh-What if we killed
someone and it wasn't okay?
What would happen to us?
License
Revoked
Disbarred
Your license would be revoked.
Fined
And the company would get fined.
That's an unexpectedly normal response.
To put it simply,
korokke cases are ones that
are low on the priority list.
(Worth as a Source of Information)
Must Keep Alive
Unavoidable Death
The scale and number of
the crimes they've committed,
Possibly Unnecessary
Adequate
Not Bad
plus their value as a source,
Pretty Good
Impressive
determines whether
they're korokke or not.
Super Rare
Based on
overall combined
circumstances
such as how
the organizations
are linked.
Let's build a fun,
cheerful workplace together!
Stop harassment!
There's an inherent risk to torturing.
A certain number of accidents
outside of korokke cases is expected.
It's just...
we lose some organs and information
that could be converted into cash.
I see.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Have they calmed down?
More or less. I'm sure they'll be fine.
You seem laid-back about it.
Did you say anything to them?
I did give them a bit of a scolding,
but those two understand
what's important,
so I didn't yell at them.
Well, hearing it from a guy
who can't always keep his
emotions in check around scum
wouldn't be very convincing, anyway.
What?
How to handle the aftermath
in times like that
is a lesson I learned
from watching you, though.
Dunno anything about that.
What?
It still bothers you?
A little.
A bit.
Noe-chan is handling it for you, right?
That's...
...true, but...
Could it be that you
regret killing your target?
No, not in the slightest.
Those who come here are criminals
for whom death is too light a punishment.
You're so stoic.
Would you like to talk about your workplace worries?
Don't take it all on alone. Come and give us a try.
Free consultations
Just when they'd started trusting
us with so many things...
...we made a mistake like that.
I just feel so bad.
Even careful veterans can
have this kind of accident,
so I don't think you need
to worry so much.
Von-san...
Though...
I will be putting in a claim for
the organs that are no longer viable!
What?!
Wh-Where should I go to donate them?
I-If it's something I have two of...
No need. No need at all.
Torture builds a sustainable society
Give the villains
the iron hammer
Isn't holding lives in your hands scary?
Do you two have something you believe in?
It is a little scary. But...
We can't stay scared.
Because this is something
we decided to do ourselves.
As for things I believe in...
Maybe the work itself?
And Siu-san and the others?
And you, too, Hugh.
And I believe in you.
Is that so? I'm glad.
You two... will be just fine.
Is it true, Von?
I heard you're quitting torturing.
Yeah. I'm not suited to it.
Unlike the two of you.
Really?
Yes, really.
You two feel that it's worthwhile,
and you have things
you believe in, right?
You have something to help you overcome
the dissonance of hurting people.
I think torture is necessary.
I admired it, and that's why I started.
But with vague feelings like that...
I haven't been able to fully
believe in what I have to do.
Really?
Well, it'll feel a little lonely.
And so! And so!
I'm going to start working
as a scrap handler!
Turning crimes and lives into money
is so much easier, don't you think?
I'm not using vague ideas
to prop myself up anymore!
I'll take responsibility for the part
that comes after the torture!
For acting all sensitive,
you're certainly bold.
And what are those sunglasses for?
I'll have to connect
with terrifying customers,
so they're, like... a disguise?
You're just too shrewd.
Von-san was super nice
yesterday, wasn't he?
Right?
What?
Just as he was leaving...
You two just believe in yourselves
and keep working hard, okay?
...was what he said to us.
It was very encouraging.
Hey, numbskulls, don't let him fool you.
When Von-san handles the aftermath of
irregularities, he gets to name his price.
He was being nice to you because
he was going to make a lot more money.
Thanks for your business!
What kind of person does that?
Lecture Room F
Mike-san, long time no see!
Are you looking for material again?
It's been a while!
Both looking for material
and studying, I guess.
If you're coming to the lecture,
Russ-kun, does that mean...
you've taken an interest in torture?
Want to come to our company?
I think I'll pass.
I just came because I had nothing
to do and it's interesting.
That's too bad.
When you're all here,
things are so lively. It's nice.
It's usually just me and Hugh-kun.
I didn't know there were classes
with this few students in them.
Even when there are more,
they're just dabbling or
hoping for easy credits.
Hugh-kun is the only one I can
have meaningful discussions with.
It's that bad?
Mike-kun, you work at the same
place as Hugh-kun, right?
Yes, sir!
Spirytus takes very good care of us!
Is torturing fun?
Yes! Lots of fun!
What a great smile.
Given the current rules
and laws around torture,
is there anything
you're dissatisfied with?
There are a few things
I wish were a little different,
but there's nothing we can do about
things that are already decided.
HEH HEH HEH
I think doing everything I can
within those lines is the real thrill!
How very stalwart of you.
Hugh-kun, unlike Mike-kun,
you think there's a need to
change some of the rules, right?
Yes, sir.
I feel that with the
application of more pain,
much more information could be extracted.
You are quite stalwart, as well.
Your sense of justice is very valuable,
but you mustn't go too far.
But there are truly irredeemable
villains among them.
I do understand how you feel.
After all, I worked as a torturer, too.
What?
You were a torturer?!
Didn't I mention it?
Despite how I look, long ago,
I was quite in-demand!
Wow.
Lecture Room F
Do the two of you intend
to continue as torturers?
Well, I'm still planning to
continue in two professions.
If I think about it in terms
of a future career,
I'm a little uncertain.
I love my current work and workplace,
and I'm thinking about continuing
in work somehow related to torture.
But I'm not certain about what
I should be aiming for yet.
In that case, Hugh-kun,
you might as well aim for
the top, don't you think?
The top?
I believe your thoughts about
the rules that should be changed
would do well in the Torture Association,
a group above the workers on the ground.
Oh, yeah, that could be a good fit for you.
I'd never even considered that.
Sounds good. You'd be good at it.
What?
But does that mean I won't be
able to work with you anymore?
What? Oh, no!
I want to cheer you on,
but I'd hate that!
It'd make me feel lonely, too!
It wouldn't happen right away.
And gaining experience
is very important,
so he should continue working for now.
Yay!
What a relief!
Now, let's continue the lesson.
Yes, sir.
You can't use this on a Class 3
torture target, can you?
You're right.
Huh? If you check it against
that law from earlier,
it can be used on some of them, right?
Such an approach exists?!
Stop looking at me like
I'm some kind of genius.
It was just a fluke.
Lecture Room F
Thank you for today.
Thanks.
Is it all right if I come again?
You're welcome to.
Please give my regards to everyone
at Spirytus and to Hera.
We will!
Huh?
I wonder how the professor
knows Hera-san's name.
Maybe it's because he's famous
as the head of Spirytus?
Today was fun, wasn't it?
Yeah. Thanks for coming with me.
No, thank you for inviting me.
It's great that you found
something you can call a goal.
I suppose so.
Hugh?
If I join the Torture Association,
I won't be able to work
with everyone anymore.
Thinking about that makes me sad.
It makes me sad, too.
But I think it'd make me sadder if you
gave up the goal you
just found for yourself.
Mike-kun...
I want you to do the
things you want to do!
So, while you're learning
all kinds of things at Spirytus,
you should find the thing you want to do.
You're right.
I'll think about it and try looking!
That's the spirit!
We'll both keep working hard
toward our goals together!
Yeah. Let's give it our best!
Really?
Aiming for the Torture
Association, are you?
Yes, that sounds wonderful!
You'll basically continue to
do what you've been doing,
but I'll assist you so that you'll have
that option available to you.
Thank you so much!
Still, the professor who
recommended it to you
must have quite the eye for talent!
What's his name?
Yes, he's called Professor Summon.
Are you okay?!
He hasn't done anything
horrible to you, has he?!
He's always smiling.
He's a very nice person.
Truly?
Y-Yes.
Is Professor Summon someone scary?
Who is he?
Oh. He's Hera's...
teacher.
I never imagined I'd connect
with him like this!
What?!
The way Hera-san is reacting...
What kind of person is Professor Summon?
Gulp.
Oh, stop making such a fuss.
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Elanor Sakamato
John Chandanais
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Becky Cottrill