Good work these past three days!
We're heading home.
Okay!
I guess my job's done.
Mister!
I'm glad nothing happened...
The Black Dragon?!
Impossible!
JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES, PARTY OF NONE
Everyone, run!
EPISODE 6: THE JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES
OVERCOMES HIS LIMITS
This pressure...
It's impossible to believe,
but that has to be the real thing.
Why?
There's no way it should be on this floor!
A tyrant who slaughters
helpless adventurers...
That's the Black Dragon.
No doubt about it.
I need to take command, now!
Think! How can we survive?
The boss on this
floor is already dead.
If we can get past it and to
the Teleportation Crystal,
then we can escape!
If we all hurry...
I'm the only one who's even able to move?
Monsters will usually head
towards crowds of people.
The Black Dragon will
probably do the same.
If I run, I'll survive and
everyone else will die.
If I go alone, I can...
No!
I have to fight the Black Dragon!
My job is to make sure that all the
new adventurers make it back alive!
I won't betray them!
I'll protect them, no matter the cost!
I should give up on any ideas of
buying time for them to escape.
There's only one way for
everyone to survive.
Defeat the Black Dragon!
Chaperons!
Do whatever the hell it takes
to keep the rookies safe!
Defensive posture!
Cathy! Magic Ward!
R-Right!
It's huge!
We're doomed!
Impact!
W-We're alive?
We're saved...
What the hell was that?
It felt like the Magic Ward
got stronger for an instant...
Was it Orhun?
Orhun!
It knew what he was doing!
No, that was deliberate!
He's aiming for the one instant
when its eyes are closed!
Impact!
Incredible!
That has to have taken it down!
I should've known that wouldn't be enough.
It's unharmed?
No!
Orhun, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just keep protecting the rookies.
I'll deal with the Black Dragon.
I have a plan. No need to worry.
But...
I'm sure all you rookies may
be scared, but please stay put.
I'll protect you.
Orhun!
Where are you aiming? I'm over here!
He took aggro from the Black Dragon?
To draw it away from us?
Is it really okay to let
Orhun handle this himself?
That thing killed Albert!
If that happened again...
could I stand it?
Reflective Wall!
How do you like the taste
of your own fireballs?
He reflected its attack?
What kind of spell is that?
I've never seen or heard
of anything like it!
Reflective Wall...
One of the original spells I came up with,
which reflects anything that
touches it back on the wielder.
It's still unharmed, huh?
Looks like I'm going to take some risks.
Status Up!
A boost to all his stats...
A high-level spell that does parallel,
simultaneous construction
of all six types of support
magic to increase all stats.
But Orhun's support magic
can only double stats...
That's not nearly enough!
Should I help?
Status Up. Double.
What?
Status Up. Triple.
Quadruple.
Lastly... Quintuple!
Impossible... You can't use
the same buff multiple times!
If you recast it, it'll just reset
the time until it wears off...
And he cast it five times, consecutively?
Orhun!
He moved that far in such a short time?
He's so fast!
Wh-Whew...
That's not just simple support magic.
Nobody's ever seen a spell like that.
Is that another of his original spells?
How many secret powers are you hiding?
I can't even tell anymore...
Five consecutive casts have
increased my status 32 times.
But I can't keep it up for long.
Because I'm basically casting
30 different spells at once.
The burden on the caster is far too great.
I need to hurry and end this now!
No!
Good idea.
But...
He made a stepping stone in midair?
Is that magic, too?
It's not magic. It's a special ability.
Rarely, humans will have powers
called "special abilities".
They're another type of power,
different from magic or sorcery,
that gives us abilities
we don't normally have.
My ability is Magical Convergence.
I can gather magic into a single
point and materialize it.
I can also cause that magic
to propel me through the air.
It's an ability with a great many uses.
Oliver has the same ability, and all
he uses it for is attacks, though.
Sharpness Up!
Durable Up!
Here we go, Black Dragon!
Impact!
He did it!
He got through those thick scales!
You're amazing, Orhun!
Orhun!
Of course he's not okay!
Normally, it's impossible
to chain support magic.
And he's also adding
effects to his weapon.
And he keeps using that original
magic of his called "Impact."
Does he really intend to defeat
the Black Dragon on his own?
But what can I do?
The strongest members
of the Night Sky Silver Rabbits
couldn't beat that thing together.
Even if I join in alone, what can I do?
Wh-What is this shaking feeling
welling up inside me?
Am I worried about Orhun?
No, that's not it.
This is...
I don't understand.
What's happened to me?
Get a hold of yourself!
All I can do now is make sure Orhun
can concentrate on the fight...
by protecting the new recruits here!
No!
Orhun!
At the bottom of distant memories...
When Oliver and I were still young...
While we were training...
bandits attacked the village...
and did this to everyone.
Orhun, I'm going to get stronger.
So nobody can steal from me ever again!
I'm going to get stronger.
So no matter what horrible things
happen, I won't lose anything.
No matter what happens...
I'll be strong enough to
protect what I care about!
That's right. I swore...
that I'd become an adventurer
and seek knowledge and power...
so the horrors of this world
couldn't grind me down.
What I need to do to protect everyone...
is to drive away the
horror in front of me!
There's nothing hard about it at all.
I just need to defeat
the foe in front of me!
Orhun! I'm so glad!
I knew he wouldn't go down that easy!
You're the best, Mister!
When it turns that purple mist
into a weapon and fires it,
that's the Black Dragon's strongest spell.
It's slain so many adventurers
that it's practically fear itself.
How will you fight it, Orhun?
It's probably like my Magical Convergence.
It uses the magical power in the vicinity.
The dragon transforms it
in many different ways,
making it possible to attack
from all directions.
But when I beat it last time,
it had a lot more different types...
Which means the Black Dragon
isn't serious yet.
All right, keep underestimating me then!
Here I go!
Fire Bullet!
It really is tough!
And persistent, too!
Rock Wall!
It changed its attack pattern!
And it's much faster, too!
I can't dodge it!
I'm glad I set a Reflective
Wall there, just in case.
What an incredible fight...
Orhun...
He's keeping up with the Black Dragon!
Can he win?!
No, he can't land the killing blow.
At this rate...
This is tough...
Last time, Derick and Luna
blocked the purple mist.
Anneli kept it pinned down with her magic,
and Oliver's Divine Flash
was our secret weapon.
But none of them are here now.
I'm supposed to do all their jobs myself?
I swore no matter what happened,
I wouldn't let it beat me!
To beat the Black Dragon without
relying on any of them...
I'll...
That's... active defense!
That's how a dodge-type defender moves!
The Black Dragon's pinned down and
can't attack like it wants to!
And he's drawing it away
so it doesn't attack us!
He's protecting us...
Even in this situation,
he's looking after us!
Parallel Construction?
He's doing all those spells at once?
He said there were people
who could do dozens...
So this is how an adventurer who aims for
the bottom of the Great Dungeon fights!
I bet you've never taken
that many spells at once!
I don't expect to defeat you like this.
So I prepared one more spell.
Raise & Repeat.
A trap spell that absorbs magical
power from the surrounding area,
and repeats the same attack from
before at a higher intensity!
It's one of my original spells that takes
advantage of my Magical Convergence!
I had no idea you could use trap
magic to attack like that...
Turning the battlefield
to your advantage...
So this is how an enchanter fights!
Well?
It's every bit as strong
as Anneli's attack magic!
You're strong, Black Dragon.
But when I was in the Heroes Party,
we had one more attacker
to land the killing blow.
Magical Convergence!
It's not gold, like Oliver's...
Taste my pitch-black blade!
Divine Flash!
Someone who can fulfill every
role in the Heroes Party!
That's the kind of swordsman I want to be!
Impact!
It sacrificed its own tail?
Damn it...
Even that couldn't finish it?
No... I should've expected
that of a deep floor boss.
But I've got a reason I can't lose, too.
It's one on one,
and neither of us can retreat!
The real fight's just beginning!
No! My buffs!
He ran out of time?
I'll cast Status Up!
My magic won't work?
I don't need your buffs!
They'll throw me off
from what I'm used to!
Focus on protecting yourselves!
Orhun?
That was Orhun who did that?
He's saying he doesn't need my support?
I know that there's no place for me
in the fight between you
and the Black Dragon.
Status Up! Quintuple!
Thunder Shock!
Impact!
The Black Dragon fell?
Did he finally win?
It's alive!
Even that's not enough?
This is insane!
But that's why...
His sword!
Looks like we're both
on our last legs, huh?
Let's end this.
Destruction!
This pressure...
The magic power is incredible!
What is that?
A pitch-black greatsword...
How is it so big?
"Destruction."
A spell that converges highly
amplified magic into a sword.
Even without Impact, its power
far exceeds a special rank spell.
Reflective Wall!
Weight Up!
Impact!
Wow!
We're saved!
He beat the Black Dragon!