Has it been three years?
Shion! Fall back for now!
Are you nuts?!
You expect me to abandon them?!
Ryusei!
Ryusei! The demons are attacking!
You want to recruit that demon?
He's human. And the jewel glowed red.
Then he must be...
You can't be serious about
making Gai a Samurai Trooper.
I am.
With proper guidance, he'll be
an emissary of Fire like Mr. Sanada.
I think, anyway.
QUESTION 8: A PERSON CUTS AHEAD
OF YOU IN LINE. IS IT OKAY TO HIT THEM?
I don't understand!
I just don't get humans!
Take it easy.
What's this song?
It's getting me all fired up!
Right?
It's called "Samurai Heart."
Hey.
I've been meaning to ask.
What're those marks on your shoulders?
Oh, these? I inherited them from my
role model, the Trooper of Fire.
Fire is more my thing, though.
When you become worthy of being
a hero, they'll appear on you.
I'm... fine...
In what universe?
You can barely even stand.
If we win, you quit being
a Samurai Trooper.
We don't need an old fart slowing us down!
Those sound like fighting words.
Ryusei?
Ryusei!
They got me.
Those stupid brats!
It's not like that.
This is their way of showing kindness.
Where are they now?
Fighting demons with Shion.
Samurai Troopers can't unleash their
full power unless all five stand together.
But if he's with them...
Dad!
You mean that's...
The Demon Emperor...
Ramaga!
EPISODE V
SADNESS
To think that my own child
would betray me!
Don't give me that crap!
You only see me as your next Puppet!
It is a son's duty
to sacrifice himself for his father.
And it's that mindset that
rubs me the wrong way!
Huh? Why'd it go boom?
Was that Ramaga's sorcery, or what?
What's wrong? If you won't come to me,
I'll reach you.
Damn it! Hypnosis?
Guys! Wake the hell up!
Won't you kill them?
Did losing your power reduce you
to human on the inside as well?
Damn it. Your stupid faces are
pissing me off even more than usual.
This fight is over.
Anti-Magic Bullet!
What the...?
What happened to us?
Ryusei...
Now, who's ready to strike back?
Ryusei, you idiot!
You're already way past
your limit, so why push it?
Because he promised Ryo.
Ryo? From the original Samurai Troopers?
Ryo Sanada, the emissary of Fire.
He passed the baton to Ryusei.
But Ryusei's element is Light.
Why would the emissary of Fire choose him?
I think that Ryo sensed
something in Ryusei.
And so he entrusted the future
of the Samurai Troopers to him.
Ryusei has been sacrificing himself
to live up to his expectations.
How can that man dispel a supreme art?
Could it be...
I guess old men really do get up early.
I was so worried about my problem
students, I couldn't sleep.
Did you break the spell on us?
Yeah. It was a gamble,
so I'm glad it paid off.
I mean, I wasn't affected
anyway, but yeah.
You were totally under their control.
Probably the worst of anyone.
What'd you say?!
Why didn't you attack us
when we came at you?
Hurting you guys would
only weaken our side.
You're still a terrible liar.
And you're still a pain in the ass!
Nah, if anyone's a pain
in the ass, it's you!
Oh, you've got a point.
What?!
Hey! Enough with the chitchat!
Run!
Why didn't you tell me about the poison?
I'm not good with words.
Bull. You're in no shape to fight.
You're not fooling anyone.
I love the Samurai Troopers, same as you.
Is that a dig? Are you being sarcastic?
Maybe I'm jealous.
Doesn't this seem weird to you?
Huh?
He ought to know
we can dodge at this range.
Now that you mention it,
this isn't like him.
Sasuke normally goes for a head-on fight.
That's it!
Yamato! Use your secret art!
Huh?!
Just like that?! Easy for you to say!
JUSTICE
Secret Art: Geo Morph!
Whoa! That's the first time it worked!
I see. So that's what
the invisible walls really are.
Hey! Are you gonna just ignore
my debut secret art?!
I saved your butts! The least you
could do is say thank you!
Thanks.
Nice one.
Props.
I want proper thank-yous!
And Gai, all you did was nod!
You'd better not think
that wall will save you!
Yeah! Yeah!
Looks like Kaito's right.
You're strangely determined
not to get out of position.
Explosive Thunder Attack!
Now!
Oh, man. All because
Sasuke's crew got out of position.
So the Ten Warriors really were behind it.
I call it "Operation Move the Ten Warriors
and Bust Through the Barrier"!
Well done. But the true
battle is yet to come.
Anti-Magic Bullet!
Take this!
Did you imagine your
petty tricks would fool me?!
No, I didn't!
When did he—
This is the end!
Think again!
You call this dull knife
the Sword of Domination?
Don't make me laugh!
Shion!
Shion said the Jewel of Conquest and Sword
of Domination were "Sacred Treasures."
That's right. When the Three Sacred
Treasures are assembled,
the Armor of the Supreme Emperor
is supposed to appear.
The what?
A legendary set of armor only
the Samurai Troopers can manifest,
said to banish any evil.
So does this mean Ramaga's invading
to stop them from summoning said armor?
I suppose...
Ridiculous.
To think you dared face me
with such a paltry imitation...
Wait, you mean he tried to open
the Demon Gate with a fake?!
Most likely, he never
intended to open it at all.
He lured us out here by brandishing
the Sword of Domination as bait.
Excellent.
I wasn't sure I could protect
the Sword of Domination on my own.
Where is the true sword?
You know I won't give it up that easily.
Bold words.
Hey, listen up.
Got it?
Samurai Troopers,
I shall now bestow unto you...
despair.
Ryusei!
Ryu!
The demon who struck you
with that poison three years ago
was me.
Ryusei!
Just shut up and go!
That poison does not end life.
It magnifies hatred, making
its victim a hideous monstrosity.
Like hell... I'd give in...
to this crap...!
You'll be the next leader
of the Samurai Troopers.
Why me? I don't even wield fire.
Because I sense the spirit
of Righteousness in you.
Isn't this...
The crest of fire.
I'm entrusting it to you.
I can't let myself... lose here!
Ryusei!
Such is the fate of all humans
ruled by negativity.
Savor it for yourself.
It's your fault!
If I hadn't saved you,
I never would have ended up like this!
Stop it, Ryu!
How would you know how I feel?!
My isolation!
My rage!
My despair!
Ryusei...
I'll wreck everything.
I'll wreck... I'll...
Guys...
Kill me!
Are you nuts?! There's no way!
There must be a way to save him.
But what can we do?
I'll wreck everything
if you leave me this way.
Please... kill me...
I'll...
put you out of your misery!
Gai!
What's this song?
It's getting me all fired up!
Right?
It's called "Samurai Heart."
The heart of a samurai, huh?
Maybe learning this song will
make me a little more human.
What are you talking about?
Anyone can see you're already human.
What the hell?
Is Gai seriously gonna just—
No. He's not thinking of killing him.
How can you be so sure?
After spending a month with him,
even a monkey could tell.
A monkey?!
When you become worthy of being
a hero, they'll appear on you.
Then that'll never happen.
I killed a whole bunch
of humans, remember?
Do you regret it?
Sure, you've done things
you can never take back.
So you'll have to atone by doing
something only you can do. By fighting.
I know you can become an emissary of Fire
with the spirit of Righteousness.
What even is
"the spirit of Righteousness"?
You'll learn soon enough.
You guys...
I'm no monkey!
Huh?
I think Yama's trying to say
you ought to lean on us more.
What do you need us to do?
Pin him down for me.
Will that save Ryu?
Who knows?
But it's his only chance right now.
Hey! Couldn't you put more thought into—
Fine.
Huh?!
Count me in.
L-Listen, you—
Oh, all right!
We don't need a samurai
who's not ready to fight.
I've found some will to fight since then.
WISDOM
Secret Art:
Gale Force Break!
It takes a lot more than passion.
I won't let you say passion's
all I've got now!
I have high hopes for you.
Am I living up to your hopes for me?!
JUSTICE
Secret Art:
Geo Morph!
FAITH
Ice Cannon!
JUSTICE, RIGHTEOUSNESS, FAITH,
WISDOM, GRACE
Don't tell me he's...
Hey, listen up.
You can warp the real
Sword of Domination through this.
The emissary of Fire should be able
to cleanse Ramaga's demonic power with it.
He'll purge the poison from Ryusei
with the sword!
Burn!
Ryusei!
Ryu!
Hey! Wake up, Ryu!
What's going on?!
The demonic power
should have been cleansed!
The power I used on him does
not stem from the Demon World.
It could not have greater affinity
with the Sword of Domination.
The sword rapidly activates it,
reducing any mere human to ash.
No...
You've gotta be kidding.
Gai...
"Samurai Heart" is an
all-time classic, don't you think?
Why bring that up now?!
You're already a worthy emissary of Fire.
This is yours now.
Ryu...
Hey! Don't you dare die on us!
Cut me some slack.
You guys don't... need me... anymore...
Shion.
The Samurai Troopers are... in your hands.
No!
Ryusei...
Humans aren't half bad.
You made me feel that way.
Like scorching heat,
I'll incinerate your mortal shell!
Foolish child.
RIGHTEOUSNESS
Secret Art:
Blaze Slash!
Is that...
Ryo!
Translation\h\h\h\h\h\hWilliam Varteresian
Timing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Editing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRiley Dalton
Quality Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSMR
Translation Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMichelle Tymon
EPISODE VI
RESTART
Armor races through your heart.