Now this gets me fired up!
All is ready for the invasion of Tokyo.
My prince, are we really going
to take over the Human World?
How do you like my favorite song?
I'm not sure what to tell you.
Man, you're no fun.
Guess I'll put something else on.
You know the words?!
My granny liked that song.
I heard it all the time.
Seriously?! Now that gets me fired up!
You're already a worthy emissary of Fire.
Okay, Dad, time for the big finale.
Like scorching heat...
Like a raging wildfire...
I'll incinerate your mortal shell!
Armor of Wildfire!
EPISODE XII
EPILOGUE
Whoa.
But all of our armor was absorbed
into the Armor of the Supreme Emperor!
Won't Ramaga just take over their bodies?
Not to worry!
With the Sword of Domination in our hands,
it will stop us from turning into Puppets.
Oh? You're quite informed.
I got you to share a lot of info
while you had me under your control.
All the more reason not to let you live!
Huh?
How?!
It's Ramaga's Sorcery! Don't fall for it!
Naumaku sanmanda, naumaku sanmanda,
naumaku sanmanda, naumaku
sanmanda, naumaku sanmanda...
Jun, what exactly are you up to?
Back when I was researching
the mirror, I learned
that it acts as a beacon
for the Samurai Troopers!
Sasuke?
Do you intend to defy
Emperor Ramaga's command?
He only ordered us to stall them.
He never mentioned defeating them.
Yeah! Yeah!
What is this, your rebellious phase?!
I've been inside you all this time.
I can read you like a book!
Twin Fire Slash!
You have skill.
Now, see what you make of my next move!
Saizo!
Saizo just turned into a Puppet!
But why?!
Now I can wield the Armor
of the Supreme Emperor
as I see fit!
He wasn't moving like that a minute ago!
Then this is what he can do
with a physical body!
Naumaku sanmanda, naumaku sanmanda,
What's this?
naumaku sanmanda, naumaku sanmanda,
Save our friends! Please...
naumaku sanmanda...
Is that your idea of attacking me?!
I may be incomplete,
but against the likes of you,
this body will suffice!
Mr. Sanada!
You sure about this?
Saizo's body will hit its limit
if this goes on much—
Shut your mouth!
Shut your mouth...
Die!
White Blaze!
What good will one mere animal do you?
We'll see about that.
Aren't those...
Excellent!
It's the original Samurai Troopers!
Thank goodness.
We made it in time.
Is that what I think it is?
Save our friends! Please!
White Blaze!
They're all trapped
in a hall on the fourth floor!
It's up to you now,
Samurai Troopers.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Ryo.
After all the time you've spent asleep,
what can you do?!
You're right that we're in no shape
to fight right now.
So, Ryo, we're leaving this to you.
Rise again, Dawn Armor!
Get him for us, too, Ryo.
All of your hearts...
are now with me!
Enough prattle!
Holy crap...
So this is what Demon
Emperor Arago sought...
The power of Dawn!
Ramaga! Prepare to die!
I see that your body
has reached its limit as well!
Use this!
Flash Slash!
Saizo!
The castle's about
to collapse on top of us!
We're getting out of here!
You're going nowhere.
Sasuke!
Bring me my next Puppet,
and be quick about it!
Sorry, but no one here is going
to give their life to you.
You accursed brats!
Everyone!
Nasti!
You must have been worried, huh?
It's fine. I'm just glad you're all safe.
I need to ask you about my dad.
What happened to that bastard Ramaga?
It'd be a relief if that
finished him off, but...
What's all this?
Look at the Puppets!
So sorry to keep you.
Let the second act begin!
Wait! Are you going
to fight in that condition?
'Course we are. We're heroes.
Hey! That was my line!
Let's leave this to them.
Quit whining and get moving!
Do not think I am the same
Ramaga you just faced.
This body, charged with
the hatred of the masses,
suits me to perfection!
Now this gets me all fired up...
Up till now, as long as I was satisfied,
nothing else mattered.
But every time I think
"I wanna help this guy,"
or "I wanna save that guy,"
I feel the heat building in here.
And now, it's blazing as hot as it gets!
So...
until this fire burns out, I'll keep
getting up as many times as it takes!
If we gave up now,
this would all be for nothing!
For the people who believe in us...
And for all of the victims,
we'll finish this fight!
That's...
...our mission!
Nonsense!
I know this light!
I'm getting a second wind.
Samurai Troopers.
The Divine World supports your resolve
to vanquish Ramaga in the name of good.
Defeat him with the power
we bestow upon you.
Sagume... To think that you
would take the humans' side!
Let's do this!
Oath of Righteousness, emissary of Fire!
RIGHTEOUSNESS
Armor of...
Heat!
Sky!
Wilderness!
Water!
Light!
You may have regained your strength, but the outcome will remain the same!
Supreme Art: Mind Clear!
Now it's time to bring down
the curtain on you!
Supreme Art: Void of the Five Skandhas!
Supreme Art: Vigor and Vitality!
Supreme Art: Unparalleled!
Supreme Art: Light Beam Flash!
Burn!
Lost your grip from the blood, did you?
I've been waiting for this moment!
Jun, ring the staff!
Huh? Oh, right!
How I tremble...
You've surpassed even
my expectations, Gai!
You attained ultimate power
and then became my Puppet!
No way... He got Gai!
Musashi!
Gai...
So this is what my dad's like inside...
I need to ask you about my dad.
How did you break his spell back there?
I heard the ringing of the staff.
I followed that sound.
Crap.
Y-You dare to...
Gai!
How do you like that?
I call it...
"Operation Pretend to Drop my Sword
but Actually Take Over Ramaga"!
Thanks for ringing the staff for me.
You scared me there!
I thought it was all over.
So, you managed to trap Ramaga?
Well, not exactly.
Curse you, Gai! What are you—
Ramaga!
See? It doesn't look like
I can hold out too long.
So kill me with this sword.
Why me?
There's just no way!
Don't worry. The Sword of Domination
can cut my body free of my dad.
Wait! But then—
It's the only way left.
Come on, Kaito.
Cease this foolishness!
You shut up!
Kaito!
Do it!
What gives?
Why...
isn't your body free?
Sorry. I lied about that part.
But the Sword of Domination should
have made Ramaga's Sorcery—
Only the emissary of Fire can nullify it.
When we use the sword, it just...
Why didn't you warn us?!
How could I?!
He'd already made up his mind!
There was no way I could say anything.
It's okay.
I killed a whole bunch of humans.
I'm getting what I deserve.
What are you talking about?!
Don't give us that!
You fought your heart out
to atone for what you did!
So...
don't talk like that.
Don't cry, you big baby.
It makes it harder to say goodbye.
Once I fall into the Demon World,
this'll all be over.
Gai!
I don't know those lyrics.
Not many people do.
I hear the song was originally
supposed to go like that.
Seriously? Now that gets me fired up.
Just finding that out
makes my life worth it.
See you.
Gai!
Gai.
You did magnificently.
Gai! Do you mean to fall into
the Fountain of Annihilation?!
If you land in there,
you'll vanish along with me!
Translation\h\h\h\h\h\hWilliam Varteresian
Timing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Editing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRiley Dalton
Quality Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSMR
Translation Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMichelle Tymon
We did the right thing, didn't we?
Yeah. I'm sure Gai agrees.
Still, it feels lonely
for things to end like this.
He's alive.
How could he not be? He's a hero.
Now, let us begin laying
the foundations for our new land.
EPISODE XIII
A NEW CHAPTER