After we clean up, let's have some milk!
Woah, stop it!
Hey!
I told you I don't have time to play.
Sorry! The paperwork to move
out of my dorm took so lo--
Is it just me, or is it messier?
You're here now, so let's all make this
a gold-star wonderful detective agency!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
rinto hirameku
A brilliant inspiration
kitto mitsukeru
datte Precure
I'm sure we'll find it
We're Precure, after all
watashitachi wo yondeiru
It's calling to us
shinjitsu wa doko?
hakken wa nani?
Where's the truth?
What will we discover?
nazo ga nazo wo yondeiru
One mystery after another
Puzzle wo atsume
genzai kara kako, mirai e
Gather the pieces
From now to the past and future
shouko mitai ni
toki wo koe kagayaku mono
Like evidence
Something shining across time
nande? nande? Trick kana?
How? How? Is it a trick?
naze? naze? tachimukau
Why? Why? We'll face it
mitsumete kanjite
himitsu wo tokiakasu no
Look and feel
Figure out the secret
yuuki no ippo ga kiseki made michibiku
One brave step will lead to a miracle
kotae!?
Kizuitenai mono ni kizuita toki
The answer?!
Found when you notice the unnoticed
unmei ne tte daisuki yo tte
chicchana koe
It's destiny, it's love
Whispered in a tiny voice
issho ni aruite ikou!
Let's walk that road together!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
rinto hirameku
A brilliant inspiration
Jewel no kagi ga tsunagaru
tsugi e no kizuna hiraku yo
The jewel key connects us
Opening the link moving forward
nee umareta koto
meguri aeta koto no shinpi
Hey, us being born and having met
Is a wonderful mystery
susume! Meitantei Precure!
Go on! Star Detective Precure!
Everyone Come
to the CUREtto Detective Agency!
Wow! It's bigger than I thought.
The garden is so cute!
Yeah!
Whoa! I love it!
It even smells nice!
It looks like
the previous Star Detective used it.
Pochitan and I will use this room.
We're neighbors!
The books have an order!
It's prettier if I sort them by color!
That's impractical!
The Importance of Eliminating
Confirmation Bias in Investigations...
Hey! Back to work!
Yes, sir!
So what's on the second floor?
I guess it's just storage?
Is this a map of the area?
Yeah.
The CUREtto Detective Agency is here?
My town will be built here.
Anna?
It's so close! I had no idea.
I'd never come this way before.
I'll come, after I go back to my time.
Hey, I have an idea.
Home decor?
That's not important.
Just a map on the wall is boring!
Please take one!
When we have clients,
isn't it better to have a lovely office?
GET YOUR PHS NOW
SPARKLY / PRE-MAIL
Clients...
Of course we accept all cases as a rule.
But our mission is to stop
the Phantom Thieves' Guild.
We know that!
Hey, I've been wondering.
Back in my time,
the world isn't enveloped in lies.
I'd never heard of the Phantoms before.
It's the same as here!
It's peaceful.
The future is always changing.
If we don't work hard at this, this time
and yours could be enveloped in lies.
It could fall into
the hands of a nasty fairy.
A nasty fairy?
Didn't I tell you?
The Phantoms are all fairies like us.
There's not much time
until the appointed hour
to decode the Tome of Mirages.
We need Makoto Jewels,
but these blunders...
I'm sorry Maestro Usonoir.
To think that
Star Detective Precures would appear...
The Tome of Mirages is indicating
a new Makoto Jewel.
I guess I'd better go this time!
Ageseine, why you?
Your teen girl disguise? So corny. As if!
It was wack!
I can't let that slide!
There they go again!
Yeah.
Maestro Usonoir!
Leave it to me, Nijee!
Go, Ageseine.
Huh?
Purloin it with grace and elegance.
-N-No! Give me a chance!
-Yay!
Lie lie, sir!
-Lie lie, sir!
Whoa!
It's gold-star delightful!
Welcome!
It's full of cute things!
That's cute!
It is!
Is that a turtle?
Don't touch!
It's glass, so it could break!
Jett-senpai, I want it!
Huh?
I'm sorry.
That's not for sale.
SALES CLERK
CHIHO MAEDA
What?
It's the symbol of our store.
Symbol?
Yes! Everyone at the shop
takes care of it.
Like a turtle, we may go slow,
but we go forward a step at a time.
And one day we'll build a bigger,
even more wonderful store.
When I look at the turtle,
I feel like I can keep going.
How lovely!
I can't sell you this, but I can
show you some other things!
Yes, please!
Chiho.
SALES CLERK
TAKUYA NAKATEGAWA
I'll put it back for you.
Thank you, Takuya!
Are you looking for anything?
-Um...
-We want to decorate our new room.
In that case...
Hello!
Welcome!
Whoa! What a cute sofa!
Is cute all you know how to say?
We have a sofa!
Well then, how about some cushions?
You can dress up your sofa.
Cushions would be okay.
I'll bring them over.
Oh! Aren't these curtains great?
They're pretty gaudy.
Well how about these?
It's got Star Detective vibes.
Yes!
You two are having fun.
Is it another case?
What's wrong?
The sculpture! It's gone!
Huh?
It was just there!
Hewp her!
Is this a case?
There might be
a Makoto Jewel in that sculpture.
Every time Pochitan brought us somewhere,
a Makoto Jewel was in danger,
or had been stolen.
I see. That could be it.
Leave it to us!
What?
Open!
Pre-Kit Book!
It gets smaller for carrying!
Aren't I a genius?
We're detectives from
the CUREtto Detective Agency!
D-Detectives?
We'll solve your case!
Please do!
What's going on?
CUSTOMER
SAEKO KAKU
What's happened?
TOURIST
TOM MILLER
This is everyone who was in the store.
Could the thief have snuck in,
stolen it, and snuck out again?
But the door has a bell on it,
and it didn't ring.
Are there any other doors?
This is our loading dock for furniture.
Maybe the thief entered from there,
and carried the sculpture out?
That's possible,
but it's too early to know.
We have to consider
the thief could still be here.
But... nobody has the sculpture.
It might be like the tiara at the wedding!
Oh yeah! Could they have hid it somewhere?
Whoa! Too many hiding places!
That sculpture is glass, isn't it?
Yeah, it had to be hidden somewhere
it wouldn't get broken.
Yeah.
I got it!
Really?
Found it!
Here!
Thank you very much!
One, two, all six are here!
Nothing's broken!
I'll put it back on the shelf.
Thank you, please do!
Case closed?
Not yet! The Phantom thief who tried
to steal the sculpture is among us!
Mikuru! Interrogation time!
Yeah! Now, where were you
at the time of the crime?
Oh, I can't speak Japanese.
English! What are we going to do?
I have just the thing!
My genius invention, Pre-Kit Gummies!
Open!
Pre-Kit Gummy!
It's gold-star cute!
Try one!
Squishy!
Delicious!
That's not all!
When you eat it, you'll be able
to speak and understand any language.
-Yeah? Amazing!
-What's amazing?
I can understand!
By the way, it lasts for three minutes.
Okay, we'd better hurry!
What were you doing in the store?
I was with him, looking for a scarf.
Were you with him?
Yes.
Tom was looking for a scarf
to give to his mother.
He picked out a beautiful scarf for me.
Yes, I chose a print
similar to that sculpture.
He told me his mother likes
growing plants in her garden.
So I thought she'd like it.
A scarf with a print
similar to the sculpture.
The sculpture's print?
Plants?
Where were you?
I've been petting this darling
ever since I entered the shop.
A cat... can't be a witness.
She was.
Huh?
She was petting me.
We can understand cats?
Aren't I a genius?
She's not the thief.
Who's left?
Chiho and Takuya.
Chiho? Surely not...
Um...
My mom is waiting, so I have to go.
Takuya, you forgot to put
a sticker on the wrapping.
Oh, sorry.
We have a sticker service.
Please choose one of these.
Choose one of these six? That's tough...
I'll get one that matches
the color of the scarf.
Scarf...
Six...
I see!
This is the answer!
-The thief is...
-Yeah!
That person!
We found the thief!
The one who stole the sculpture...
Is you!
M-Me?
That's not possible!
No, it can be nobody but you.
The key to this case was the scarf.
The scarf?
You took the sculpture, and went
to go out the loading dock.
Since you work here,
nobody would have noticed.
But when you tried to leave,
Tom asked you to help him find a scarf.
You panicked and hid
the sculpture in the cushions.
In there, it wouldn't break.
You're just accusing me!
Surely not Takuya!
-Tom?
-Yes?
Takuya said the scarf for your mother
had a print like the sculpture, right?
Yes.
Could you show me?
Yes, here it is.
Flowers?
Yeah, just like the sculpture, right?
What?
Yes. Takuya thought it was
a sculpture of a flower.
Even though it's a turtle.
A turtle?
When we found it in the cushions...
All six are here! Nothing's broken!
I found that strange.
You don't usually
count a head, tail, and legs like that.
You thought it was a flower,
so you said there were six.
Like you were counting petals.
Takuya the shop employee
would never make such a mistake.
You're not Takuya!
This is like, so wack!
Yes! I'm Ageseine from
the Phantom Thieves' Guild!
I'll be taking this!
Whoa!
Why are you here, anyway?
A message from Maestro Usonoir.
Defeat them and steal it with grace.
That's it. Make it happen.
What's up with that?
There she is!
Tsk. I'd rather not
but if Maestro Usonoir says so!
Lies, envelop!
Make 'em fly!
Hanninda!
What's going on?
A new Phantom technique!
You're sealed off from everyone!
Now your case will go unsolved!
Open!
Jewel Cure Watch!
Precure! Wake-up Time!
3! Discover!
6! And face one another!
9! We are the miraculous duo!
Spin around!
And finish off cutely!
Gold-star closing the case on any mystery!
Star Detective, Cure Answer!
Jumping towards smiles
with layered reasoning!
Star Detective, Cure Mystique!
Star Detective Precure!
I'll show you my answer!
Hanninda!
It's not a flower, it's a turtle!
Han!
Nin!
Da!
Those girls are interesting!
What are you doing, Hanninda?
This is wack!
Wack?
It means it's really bad.
It was a fad a while ago.
It's a fad now, if you ask me!
Go get 'em! Hanninda!
Hanninda!
Whoa!
Da!
Hanninda!
Yeah!
This is Age. Are you watching?
Maestro Usonoir!
I think this means I won!
Are you mad I took the Makoto Jewel?
The Makoto Jewel is important.
It's the symbol of our store.
It's not just about Makoto Jewels!
You're not seeing the feelings
people put into their belongings!
Huh?
Like a turtle, we may go slow,
but we go forward a step at a time.
We'll get Chiho's precious item back!
We'll keep going forward, too!
Hannin!
This is our answer!
CUREtto Case Closed!
Hanninda!
Pochi Pochi Cure Cure!
This bites!
Precures, huh?
Thank you so much, detectives.
I'm back!
-Huh?
-I'm sure this is the real Takuya.
I couldn't find the hibiscus
you asked me to buy anywhere.
I didn't ask you to do that.
Surely Ageseine transformed
into Chiho and asked him to go.
It's done!
Our detective agency!
M-My money...
It turned out great!
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
Yeah!
I wonder what our first case will be?
I've already decided! My first client.
Huh? Me?
Yeah, Anna.
I'll send you back to your own time!
Yeah! But I decided something!
I want to save everyone!
I can't stand a world covered in lies!
I'll be a Star Detective Precure
together with you, Mikuru!
I can go back later!
Anna!
Hire me, Anna!
Mikuru...
Please send me back to my time!
I'll put the case on my books!
I'll work to become a great Star Detective
so that I can solve your case, too!
Okay!
Let's help each other become
great Star Detectives!
They're so similar. They make a good pair.
Things are about to get busy around here.
(NaNaNaNa naze? naze? WHY?
NaNaNaNa nazo? nazo! ANSWER?!)
(NaNaNaNa why? Why? WHY?
NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER?!)
ten to ten musundara ara? ara!
Connect the dots, oh? Oh my!
"hanamaru kaiketsu!" kana? kana?
Could it be a "gold-star case closed!"?
Could it?
suiri to nazo wa uragaeshi
niten santen gyakuten
Reasoning turns around riddles
Twists and turns, reverse
kotoba ya shigusa sae wana? wana!
unomi ni shite wa dame! dame!
Even words and behavior are traps? Traps!
Don't just believe them! No!
yoku mite, kangaete, sorekara
fumidasu no yo ippo!
Pay attention, think and then
Take the first step!
komatteiru hito mitara
sugu ni tasuketai
When I see someone in trouble
I immediately want to help
datte nantoka nantoka nantoka shitakute
kakedashiteiru
Cause I wanna, wanna do something
So I go running off
Na Na Na nazo! nazo!
Na Na Na mystery! Mystery!
nazo wo toku no ga meitantei
Solving mysteries
Is what a Star Detective does
uso ka makoto ka mikiwamete
egao no kotae mitsukeru
See through lies and find truth
Find the answer for a smile
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 100 bai
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 100
chikara awasete norikoeru
tomo wa kiseki no katamari
Working together, we can figure it out
Friends are a true miracle
iku yo! Meitantei
Let's go! Star Detective
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 1,000 bai
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 1,000
tomodachi to te ni te wo totte
banjikaiketsu suru made!
Hand in hand with my friends
Until everything's solved!
DATTE Precure
(NaNaNaNa naze? nazo! ANSWER!)
We're Precure, after all
(NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER!)
They finally came! Our first client!
-Apples, potatoes, onions...
-Pochi?
I'm checking the evidence!
The manga manuscript turned into food!
Pochi?
Star Detective Precure!
"Exciting! Our First Client!"
That mystery! CUREtto Case Closed!