What a pretty scene.
Thank you. All of our
hard work has paid off.
I bet everyone's delighted to live
in such a wonderful village.
It's been a while since you came
to this village. What do you think?
Me?
Would you live here?
Huh?
W-Well...
I mean, setting aside engagement
proposals, what do you want to do?
It's fine to put your own feelings first.
What I want to do?
I want to get engaged to Lord Van.
But, um...
You want to get engaged?
Should I pretend I didn't hear that?
Please.
I see. I see.
U-Um, Lord Van, you seem
kind of happy all of a sudden.
You're imagining it.
EASYGOING TERRITORY DEFENSE
BY THE OPTIMISTIC LORD
EPISODE 9: THE TIMID GIRL'S
BEAUTIFUL MARIONETTE DANCE
Lord Van! We've returned
from the royal capital.
Welcome back. Did you set up
your trading company easily enough?
Yup. Everything went swimmingly,
thanks to you, Lord Van.
And just as we promised,
30 platinum. Here you are.
Oh, thank you.
Till. If you would.
RICHES
It's my first time ever handling
such a large amount of platinum.
Um, isn't Lady Panamera
coming back to the village?
She said she had to go report
to Count Ferdinatto.
She thinks allying with you will be more
interesting than sticking with the count.
Huh? So she'll be living in this village?
No, she said her plan was to
be given land near this village.
Knowing Lady Panamera, I'm sure
it won't take long for her to get it.
That's true.
That woman's likely to become queen
before anyone realizes.
Also...
We present you with this masterpiece
we found in the royal capital.
I-Is this what I think it is?!
It's a machine bow, capable of firing
up to ten shots in a row.
It's the latest tech in the royal capital.
Thank you! I can create
new ballistae with this!
Yahoo!
I'm so happy!
Good for you, Lord Van.
Is he more excited about that
than the platinum?
Thank you so much, you two!
So pulling this lever causes
the next bolt to slide down?
This is the happiest
I've ever seen you look, Lord Van.
Oh? Is it?
Incredible.
Huh? It's not moving.
So even you fail sometimes.
Huh?
Oh, m-my apologies.
I didn't mean anything by it.
I fail at things all the time.
Aside from my magic,
I can't pride myself in anything.
That's not true.
You have amazing talent
with the sword and with your studies.
I really don't have anything.
Huh? Talent?
If you'd like, I'll introduce you
to my fiendish butler
and the monstrous commander
of my chivalric order.
You'll become just as "amazing"
as me in no time.
That reminds me,
what's your magical aptitude, Arte?
U-Um, Lady Arte?
Lord Van won't force you to answer.
If you don't want to say, that's fine.
No.
M-My...
My aptitude is for marionette magic.
Marionette magic.
Just like my production magic,
it is considered useless by nobles,
so it is equally loathed.
However...
Wow, I've never seen that magic before.
Could you show it to me?
Huh? U-Um...
M-My magic?
Well, people with an aptitude
for marionette magic are rare.
Of course, that's probably
because many people hide it.
Even so, you're the first person
I've met who can use it.
This is fate, Arte.
Can you move this?
This is incredible magic!
There's limitless potential
in this magic, Arte!
That was magnificent.
So, so impressive, Lady Arte.
Can you also perform that dance
you made the puppet do?
Oh, y-yes.
Although I'm a little better at making
the puppet dance than doing it myself.
No, no, that's still really amazing.
Let's get Lord Van to make
more charming puppets.
I bet if you put on a show with them,
the villagers would be delighted.
You're right. That does sound fun.
While we're at it, I can make a puppet
using the mythril ore Arte discovered.
But my magic isn't fit
for showing off to others.
The same could be said for my magic.
Plenty of people have told me that
it's unfortunate I have production magic.
My father even called me a failure.
But I've brought everyone
happiness with this magic.
I'm sure they'll all enjoy
your marionette magic, too.
I've always lived under the assumption
that I'm worthless, but...
If you think I can do it,
Lord Van, I'll give it a try.
What's this?
What's going on?
Did you hear anything?
What's happening?
Lord Van summoned us all here.
I wonder what's going to happen.
Are the people in the back good?
What's Lord Van going to do?
I can't see.
Thank you, everyone,
for gathering here today.
We will now put on a show
using Lady Arte's magic.
Put on a show using magic?
What kind of magic?
Wow. It's like it's alive.
But isn't that...
It's marionette magic, right?
Didn't someone try to take out
the royal family and nobility using that?
You bring me such grief!
What's this?
It stopped?
I hope she's not losing control.
Lady Arte.
Hey, everyone. Don't go thinking
the puppet's going to curtsy to you.
"The magic of vile criminals."
Marionette magic often gets labeled
as such and discriminated against.
You're about to see
what Lady Arte's magic can really do.
How is everyone going
to view her after this?
How will they interact with her?
She must be terrified imagining all that.
But it'll be okay.
What a lovely dance.
Lady Arte's marionette magic
breathes life into lifeless objects.
It is truly wonderful magic.
Bravo!
That was a beautiful dance!
Yes, what incredible magic!
Marionette magic is capable of that?
The way it moved was incredible!
I was so scared.
Lady Arte, move your doll some more!
I always thought
this was an awful aptitude.
Your doll was beautiful!
Do some more!
I've never seen anything so beautiful!
Arte, you did it.
Thank you so, so much.
Lord Van, urgent news!
What is it?
A carriage bearing the royal family's
crest is heading our way.
The royal family?
Hi, young man.
Panamera. It's been a while.
Say, that's an awfully lukewarm response.
Did you find another woman?
Arte and I have grown much closer.
It's been a while, Lady Panamera.
Hey, boy. What kind of trick did you pull?
How has she changed so much
in such a short time?
Well, I wonder what it could've been.
Arte appeared to
lack confidence in her magic,
so I just told her how wonderful it is.
You've got some slick moves.
Your future looks bright.
Whoops. I got caught chatting.
Now, bow your head, boy.
You stand before His Majesty.
Oh, right.
Huh? His Majesty?
So you are Van Nei Fertio?
Raise your head.
I am Dino En Tsora Bellrinet,
king of Scuderia.
And I am his chancellor, Aperta.
You have officially become a baron and
joined the lower ranks of the nobility.
You must dedicate yourself
for the benefit of our nation.
Yes, Your Majesty. I humbly comply.
I expect great things.
Also, I hear you have discovered
a dungeon within your barony?
Someone will be by to inquire about it,
so give them a full, honest account of it.
I will not tolerate lies or falsehoods.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Lastly, defeating a forest dragon
is a truly wonderful feat.
Given the exceptional claim
and location this time,
His Majesty has come
to confirm it in person.
You will answer all of my questions
accurately. No objections, I presume?
Of course. I vow to give you
an honest account of everything.
However, I'd like you
to promise me one thing.
What?
I can show you how everything happened,
but if you don't believe it all,
it might seem like a lie to you.
So I ask Your Majesty
to keep an open mind.
You're every bit as interesting
as Viscountess Cayenne told me.
I can make that promise.
Um, so the small village
you see here is Seatoh.
The ramparts, gates, and moat
are the cornerstones of its defense.
The ballistae atop the ramparts
are the core of its offense.
Aperta, what do you think?
Well, ballistae are good for taking on
certain-sized foes at a limited distance,
but they're quite inconvenient to use.
Then allow me to show you a test.
Khamsin! Fire into the forest!
Here I go!
That was astounding force and distance.
Plus, it fired two bolts in succession.
Pulling off an attack like that without
an elite archer or a mage is astonishing.
I'm also curious about
your star-shaped ramparts.
Oh, our star-shaped fortress?
This shape allows us to attack enemies
from multiple directions.
Those bolts raining down from
every angle would be terrifying.
As it stands, these defenses are perfect
against all but aerial attacks.
Aerial attacks?
I've made several, but I won't be
sure how well they work until I test them.
You speak as if you make
these weapons yourself, baron.
That's because I do.
I seem to remember telling you
I won't tolerate lies and falsehoods.
I swear I'm not lying.
Your Majesty, I understand your
reservations, but please hear him out.
You're in for even more of a shock.
Who came up with the designs
for the ramparts?
Their structure seems awfully unique.
I did.
And the village's development?
This scale of development
would take several years.
I worked really hard to build it all.
And everyone helped out
by gathering materials.
Then how many years did it take you
to erect these ramparts?
Uh, roughly four months, I think?
Do you understand it?
I find it almost impossible to fathom.
Your Majesty. Perhaps it'd be best
if he gave you a demonstration?
Fine by me.
Let's head down to the lake.
Lord Van!
Oh, Lord Van.
Good afternoon, Lord Van.
Have a good day, Lord Van.
You, too.
Let's all enjoy some meat
together again sometime.
Sure! We'll look forward to it!
Baron, were those the villagers?
Yes, they were.
So the lord and his people can have
such casual conversations?
Yes, uh, we can?
Wh-Who are they?
Oh, it's Lord Van.
Howdy! Where're ya goin'?
I have some business down at the lake.
Are you all doing well?
'Course! Right, you guys?
Glad to see you're so full
of energy like always.
B-Baron, who were those men?
They're adventurers. We've bonded while
they're here checking out the dungeon.
I-Is that...
Oh, it's my son-in-law.
Ladavesta, I'm not
your son-in-law, remember?
Unless my eyes deceive me, these
are apkallu. They're incredibly rare.
What a coincidence, Your Majesty.
That's exactly what I'm seeing.
I can't believe there are apkallu
living so out in the open here.
I've never seen a sight like this before.
Esparda, should we build
another tall rampart beyond the lake?
Now, the finishing touches.
So yeah, that's how I make the walls.
What would you like me
to show you next?
Son-in-law, is that man another chief?
Uh, well, he's more like a great chieftain
who coordinates many chiefs.
Gosh. Then I should pay him
the utmost respect.
Those of us who lead tribes
owe each other respect.
Great chieftain.
I am Ladavesta, chieftain
of the Lada tribe.
I am the king of this nation,
Dino En Tsora Bellrinet.
I'm delighted to meet you, Sir Ladavesta.
Indeed. Likewise.
Allow me to present you with a gift
as a sign of our friendship.
No way. Is that...
Orichalcum?
The legendary metal known
as the "metal of the gods"?
I didn't expect to lay eyes
on such a rare resource.
If we forge a sword
with this orichalcum,
it'd cost somewhere north
of a hundred platinum!
Why would the expense concern you?
It would be an instant national treasure.
As such, it would be priceless.
Yup, I think it turned out well.
I-Is that...
What?
Did we just see you make
a sword from orichalcum?
Baron, I told you not to tell any lies.
You can make swords, can't you?
I'm not really sure
what you're talking about.
Boy, answer honestly.
If you have any demands,
I'll hear you out.
I promise to pay what
your honesty is worth.
In that case, please grant me
permanent residency in this village.
No matter what happens,
never send me to a different land.
That's all I ask.
Why?
If you came to the capital,
you'd be treated well
regardless of your status.
Who would protect the people here
if I left this land?
Creating a land where people
can live in peace
without struggling to secure
food, clothing, and shelter...
That's the duty of a lord.
So I have an obligation
to make this land prosper.
All right.
Frankly, it's a shame
to leave your talents out here,
but even if you won't come to the capital,
you'll work with us if I send
an emissary here, yes?
Of course, Your Majesty.
If it's within my power,
I'll offer what aid I can.
I won't be shocked anymore.
I've decided to stop viewing you
as a child, baron.
At least I've managed to avoid
moving to the royal capital.
I'm gonna keep improving this land
so I can lead a life of leisure.
Hooray for the slow life.
Unfortunately, I can't afford to be away
from the royal capital for very long.
Could I confirm the dungeon next?
The dungeon is far enough away
that a round trip takes all day.
So I advise against visiting it today.
Your attitude toward me is
steadily growing more casual, isn't it?
No, uh, not at all!
Emergency!
Lord Van! I-It's a dragon!
Everyone, to the defenses!
Send word to the adventurers!
Yes, sir!
Hey, boy, do you need help?
Yes, please.
Where's the dragon?
R-Right there!
TRANSLATION: JOHN PICKETT
TIMING: ANDY ELLIS
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: RILEY DALTON
TRANSLATION CHECK: REI MIYASAKA
NEXT EPISODE: A SECRET WEAPON'S
VILLAINOUS ATTACK ON THE HOMELAND