Since the beginning of summer break,
Kanata has run the Double Lane
course nearly 200 times.
Despite the tragic news
he recently received,
his motivation for
the next race hadn't faltered.
Oh, Shun? What's up?
Tomorrow? Tomorrow's kinda...
I'm not exactly free.
I'm going to the beach
with some schoolgirls.
What the hell? Don't mess with me.
How'd that happen?
I'm coming, too.
Wh-What are you saying?
You can't just—
Don't be so cold, man.
We pitiful bachelors have
known each other for ages.
Look, I was invited myself.
I can't just bring extra people.
It's the beach. One extra person
ain't gonna make a difference.
Odawara
\hOffice
I'm trying to say the other party
has their own—
Whatever. You'll have to kill me
to keep me away!
Aw, crap. I picked totally
the wrong guy to brag to!
Now I'm bringing Shun along
with Kanata and Ren-chan there...
This sucks.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
The End
of Summer
I feel for the guy,
but I need to ditch Shun.
Closed Today
Whatever happens, I can't bring him along.
If I turn my phone off
the second I leave the house,
he can't contact me.
Forgive me, Shun.
There are other considera—
Morning, Ogata-kun.
Why are you here so early?!
It's not even seven yet!
Oh, I was just so excited, y'know?
And I just woke up early.
Y'know, it's like the day of
a field trip when you were a kid.
I honestly had a hard time
getting any sleep last night.
Thanks, Ogata, my man. I've never been
more grateful to have a friend like you.
What a mess. And I don't have
the courage to say no to him.
What's wrong, Ogata? You look queasy.
Upset stomach?
Cheer up! We'll have some fun
and sun down at the beach.
Uh-oh. It looks like
everyone's already there.
Japanese people are super punctual.
We'd better hurry, Kanata.
Wow, you two are cute.
I'm Aiba Shun. I'm an MFG Driver.
Wow!
Just like Kanata-san!
That kind of reaction is encouraging.
Well, since I'm the adult
with plenty of cash to burn,
I'll cover lunch and drinks
and whatever snacks today.
Really?
Thank you so much!
We're totally broke,
so that's music to my ears.
Ah, come on. It's the natural thing to do.
After all, I get to chill
with a couple of cuties like you.
Dude, who even are you right now?
All this smooth talk
is throwing me for a loop.
Come on, man. These are
sheltered high school girls.
Gotta bring a little class, y'know?
Shun-san seems really nice. And funny.
Kinda like how
you're clean-shaven for once.
Despite seeming kinda scary at a glance.
Sorry we're the last here, everyone.
Hey there, Kanata-kun.
A-A-Aiba-senpai?
What am I seeing right now?
This wasn't in the plan. What's going on?
So this is the girl I heard about.
Something about her face
does it for me.
And do I recognize her from somewhere?
It's nice to meet you. I'm Aiba Shun.
N-Nice to meet you, uh... I'm Saionji.
She's so adorbs.
What is this, Ogata-san?
Other than a nightmare.
I'm sorry. I kinda screwed up.
Well, now we're all here,
let's go change.
G-Good idea. Let's do that.
We'll just have to pray
Shun doesn't catch on.
Considering Kanata and I didn't
figure it out, I'm sure he won't either.
Damn, Ogata wasn't lying.
She's got a really nice body.
It sure is bright out today.
Yeah. I hope the sunscreen works.
That's one sweet peach.
It's every bit as fine as Number Seven's.
It is her!
You're Number Seven of
the MFG Angels, aren't you?
How in the hell?! How did he know?!
W-Well, uh, I-I...
I'm sorry.
You've got the wrong person!
Ren!
Her name "Ren" is written with
the kanji for love in "first love," right?
Th-That's right.
Unbelievable. My angel has descended
upon the beach in Enoshima.
Kanata.
Did you know?
What's going on here, man?
H-Hang on, Shun. Let's all stay calm—
Can it, Ogata. I am calm.
Come with me, Kanata.
I'm really disappointed in you, Kanata.
The fact your host family's girl
happened to be an MFG Angel...
I mean, what other explanation is there?
And that's not your fault.
It's not even the issue.
But why'd you hide it from me?
Why didn't you tell me? Do I really seem
that stubborn and unreasonable?
I liked you, man.
I respect you. And I considered
you a close friend.
I wanted to believe you felt
the same way. But I guess not.
Is that just how it is
with English people?
Well, we're not friends anymore.
My face is probably pretty swollen.
I can't let the others see me like this.
It hurts.
Not where he hit me,
but this throbbing pain in my chest.
You won't even say anything
in your defense?
How am I supposed to know
what to do?
I know he's got good reflexes,
but he didn't try to dodge at all.
I guess I already know
Kanata's not that kind of guy.
I know getting hit hurt him, but...
For some reason, slugging
my favorite junior made my chest hurt.
The three of them sure
are taking a while, huh?
This atmosphere is unbearable.
Please let somebody come back.
Hey there, ladies.
You're cute. You two on your own?
Care to join us?
Sorry, we're here as a group
with some other guys.
You mean the old dude there
who looks like your dad?
You sure about that?
Is that your idea of fun?
We really are. And you're bothering us.
Go pick up girls somewhere else.
Man, you're no fun.
And here we were,
lowering the bar for you.
You know you're not all that hot, right?
Hold it right there, guys.
What?
I happened to overhear your rudeness
towards my friends here.
That's not very nice.
You should apologize.
Huh?
Don't you understand the words
coming out of my mouth?
Maybe you should apologize...
while I'm still feeling nice.
W-We're sorry!
Sorry 'bout that.
Got a little distracted on the way back.
I'll make it up to you
by getting us drinks.
Here you go, Ogata.
You bet.
Talk about great timing.
I couldn't say a single thing
in my defense.
I just didn't have the words.
Do I even have the right to defend myself?
Am I really 100% innocent here?
I made a promise to him that I wouldn't
fall in love with Number Seven.
And I wasn't able to keep that promise.
It's only natural he hit me
because of it. I did something wrong.
Can you promise me?
I can.
You okay, Ogata-san?
Come on!
MF Ghost.
Look, I'm really sorry.
I don't know how to make it up
to you and Ren-chan.
I'm prepared to commit seppuku.
It's okay, Ogata-san. Forget about it.
I think Ren's a little mad, but I'm sure
it'll blow over, so don't worry.
It's only natural Aiba-senpai got mad.
I'm the one in the wrong.
How are you in the wrong, man?
You didn't know it was her.
No. All through summer break after
I found out, I didn't do a thing about it.
I guess I'll keep an eye out
for a chance to explain to Shun.
Nah. I doubt it'd satisfy
Aiba-senpai, anyway.
Please don't do anything, Ogata-san.
You say that, but...
Who's this?
Hello?
J-J-Just a moment, please.
Please talk to whoever
this is for me, Kanata.
It's a woman who started speaking
English really fast at me.
I didn't catch a word of it.
Hello?
Emma? Emma Greene? Is it really you?
Where are you calling from?
Huh? Odawara? Really?
Well, of course it was a surprise
that you ran off all of a sudden.
And that you're an MFG Angel.
Sorry, Yuka.
I'm scared to ask, but how'd things
go afterwards? At the beach.
Well, you see, the thing is...
It was fun. Ogata-san and
Shun-san are really nice,
and since they're adults, we felt safe.
The lunch we had at the shack
by the beach was full of flavor.
And I don't think I've ever had guys
fawning over me like that my whole life.
R-Really? You had a good time?
Yup!
I feel like I kinda missed out.
They even have nice tans. No fair.
Ogata Automotive Ltd.
Wow, an Aston Martin!
And it's a Vantage in
British racing green. Cool!
I'm disappointed.
"Oh, hey, a Vantage. So cool."
That's moron talk.
Emma.
I finally get to see my ex
after all this time.
I was expecting a more
romantic reaction than that.
Your ex? Me? I seem to remember us
only ever being friends.
We were a couple.
Uh, no, we weren't.
You've changed, Kanata.
You don't have that harsh look
in your eyes anymore.
I'm more curious about
what you're doing in Japan.
That should be obvious.
Don't you see the number?
I'm going to be racing in MFG.
Though just for one race.
I'd really rather you didn't.
It's a bad fit for you.
That's rather a rude thing to say
to your old RDRS classmate.
The stuff we learned there won't be
enough to help you do well in MFG.
You do realize I'm a current BTCC driver,
right? Don't underestimate me.
Did Fujiwara-sensei give his permission?
I don't need permission.
I graduated a long time ago.
You might have been top of
the class while I was third,
but I've grown a lot this past year.
After your hiatus,
I won't be outdone by you.
I'm heading off now, Kanata.
I'll be in touch.
I love you, darling.
She was gorgeous. Blonde hair,
blue eyes, and boobs like whoa!
This is bad. She's going
to be racing in MFG.
I could tell. There was a number
on her door panel.
The Aston Martin's a bit of an unknown.
I don't ever recall anyone
driving one in MFG before.
Is she fast?
Yes. She was my classmate at the academy.
She's very skilled
with good driving sense.
And she's not just fast.
She's dangerous.
Good session, Miss Greene.
After just an hour and a half,
you're within two-tenths of
Akaba Kaito's course record.
I question whether the lap time I posted
with the data we entered for the Vantage
will translate to the circuit.
It should be fairly accurate,
given it's the latest version.
It might be an odd thing
to talk about in this place...
but I was curious why seafood back home
is so comparatively dire,
so I looked it up.
The reason is apparently simple.
There's a profound lack of biodiversity
in the species found around England.
But the waters around Japan have a huge
variety of species, and in greater numbers.
The ocean around Japan
has a whole host of currents,
so there's an oceanographic reason
for the large plankton population.
There are also over
35,000 rivers in Japan,
which carry stuff for the plankton
to feast on out to sea.
But the whole world
has coastal areas, right?
Shouldn't there be
a bunch of places like that?
Be it in the Mediterranean or
off the islands around Southeast Asia,
there are fewer varieties of fish.
I'm not exaggerating when I say
Japan is unique in the world.
It's a country blessed
with its aquatic properties.
It's a sea of miracles,
crafted by God.
This country has an almost
unfair share of divine gifts.
MFG's front-runners apparently
come here to train.
Katagiri Kanata is the exception.
He hasn't come here once.
Kanata Rivington
is indeed exceptional.
He's the kind of person who can
conquer a course in very little time.
He's creative and eccentric
to an absurd degree.
He earned himself the nickname:
the "Silent Artist."
Everyone at the academy, from students
to teachers, was astounded at his speed.
I wanna use the simulator every day until
the race to get familiar with the course.
Please make the arrangements, Hayato.
Emma. I'm not sure about that.
Okay. I guess I will.
Ren, a friend of mine from England
will be at Enoshima station soon.
I'd like to introduce you,
if you don't mind.
Really?
Of course I don't mind.
I'd love to meet any friend of yours.
I should probably tell you now
that she's a woman.
But our relationship
isn't anything special,
so please don't get the wrong idea.
She's not a bad person,
but she can come on a little strong,
and she might be kind of rude to you.
If she is, I'll be sure to correct her.
Oh.
Emma, let me introduce you to Ren,
my host family's daughter.
Nice to meet you.
Huh. So you and Kanata
are going steady, are you?
Emma, I won't let you harass Ren.
If you don't stop, I'll leave now.
And go back to the house
where you two are living together?
What a scandalous suggestion.
I can't stand it.
You're breaking my heart.
What do you expect me to say to that?
I almost lost my cool there.
Let's start over.
What a cute body she's got.
Japanese women seem to keep
their thin, girlish figures as they mature.
Let's take a break
somewhere cool, shall we?
Ren, Emma hasn't been
in Japan long, so I'll translate.
Since when were you
such a gentleman, Kanata?
It's a bit different from
how you treat me, isn't it?
Oh, don't mind me, Kanata.
After all, your friend came all this way.
Besides, I should be able to understand
about 70% of your conversation, I think.
I've been taking English lessons
since I was little.
You must be pretty well off. Very clever.
I have to say, this heat should
be wrecking my appetite.
Yet the food here is so good,
I end up eating anyway.
Yes.
You should try the more reasonably priced
restaurants, too, not just hotel food.
I reckon you'll be shocked at the quality.
Don't sound so proud of that.
You're not from here.
Besides, what are you even doing here?
This path makes no sense to me.
If you'd committed to
competing in British FE3,
you'd be in the running for
the Young Driver of the Year award.
Every British driver dreams
of winning that.
I understand what happened to your mum,
and you have my sympathy,
but that doesn't excuse
throwing it all away.
Do you realize how many people
you disappointed?
I'd rather not talk about it, Emma.
What's done is done.
Well, too bad. You still seem
like you're running away.
This isn't where you belong.
I'm saying this because
I care about you deeply.
It's frankly foolishness to waste
your God-given talents like this.
I don't have the kind of talent
you're talking about, Emma.
And even if I did, it would be
a gift from my parents, not God.
Don't give me that atheist crap.
It's unpleasant. I don't like
this version of Kanata.
I can decide what's best
for me myself, Emma.
And I'm 100% sure coming to Japan
was the right decision.
You have no right to criticize it.
Sorry. I need to use
the little boys' room.
You're in high school, right, Ren?
That's right.
And you like Kanata, right?
It's easy to tell.
But you're still just a kid
while you're in school.
You're not independent.
And Kanata's an adult.
Romance should be between two adults.
All you're doing is playing house.
I'm not trying to be mean.
Just stating facts.
She really got me there.
She didn't hold back at all.
Her earnest concern for Kanata
stopped me from saying anything.
I can't compete with someone like that.
Let's head back, Ren.
I'm looking forward to
the fireworks show tonight.
Next time on Turn 32: Sparks Fly.