I'm so sad.
It distresses me to see you
like this, K-sama.
You're all alone again.
I wonder what the
demon flame guy is up to.
You'll see him again, I'm sure!
Though we may need to deal
with those pests around him.
I'm so sad.
Really, there is no need to be sad.
You are steadily gathering the resources
you need to make your dream come true.
Very soon you shall realize...
Sad Boy K
Follow
Tell me about your troubles.
Using Tweeter since August 2016
Following
Followers
the land of dead accounts.
Kasubata-kun!
I-It's not what you're thinking.
He propelled himself with his abs?!
Like a snake!
My abs are every bit as lovely!
Put those away.
Sorry, Minoru.
I can't hold back!
Dei Surugi
Class 1-A
Yeah, there's no telling
a flamebaiter what to do.
Minoru Wagari
Class 1-A
You feel my pain, right, Kasubata-kun?
Indeed, Wagari.
Flamebaiters are all assholes,
without exception.
But our shit stinks slightly less.
Beg pardon.
Title: "Flame vs. Flame."
No, not up to my standard.
Ban Ashina
Class 1-A
Yellow makes me think of bananas!
Kiri Namekawa
Class 1-A
Bananas makes me think of yellow!
Yellow makes me think of bananas!
That hideous class B flamebaiter!
Ikko Owada
Class 1-A
He made the heart in Kusaba-chan's
beautiful body skip a beat!
I'm so jealous...
I mean, disgusted!
Urusugawa-chan! How you doing?
Eru Kusaba
Class 1-A
Don't talk to me, you pick-me freak.
Still sucking up to every guy you meet?
Oh, come on!
You're the one still dressing
like she wants to land a man.
It's really just sad!
Your Onipien Enflame...
One hit from that would do
more than break my bones!
To think that anger's all meant for me...
Cyber out.
Flames of Loathing
Flames of Loathing!
He doesn't use a smartphone?!
That's hot! It's real fire!
Don't get scared. Get angry, Enishiro!
I know! Why don't I tell you the results
of the first term's A-B Battle?
We won by a landslide!
And for one obvious reason...
The blatant superiority
of our individual abilities!
A flake whose only skill is peeping!
A stupid coward!
A little dolly who's
the life of the party!
Hey, I'm no dolly!
All with your anachronism of a teacher!
You're a trash class
full of loser rejects!
When will you stop?
Have you no respect
for people's feelings?!
Don't soil Akari's memory.
And don't make fun of class 1-B!
You grabbed my flame with your bare hand?
That's hot!
That's quite enough.
Enishiro-kun, members of class 1-B,
I apologize for Dei Surugi's
many indiscretions.
I'd also like to say one thing.
You are all...
crap!
Why would you say that while apologizing?
Are you as mad as you are vulgar?
Oh, don't get the wrong idea!
I'm not saying it because you're weak.
Unlike Dei, I don't care about that.
Don't expect him
to listen to anything you say.
The fact that you accepted
a demon flame wielder...
has disgraced the name of class 1-B!
In the A-B Battle at the end of
the month, we'll beat you again.
We'll never lose to a
trash class like yours!
You've got it all wrong, Wagari.
You think we'll lose with him here?
We'll win this time because of him.
Enishiro!
I'm head over heels for you, man!
Let's really put our fuel
on the fire next time!
At the A-B Battle!
Nurse's
Office
Sheesh, I told you guys
to keep it in check!
You kids get banged up too often.
My bad.
Thank you for everything.
Hey!
Nice work today.
Azaki-sensei!
Where's everyone else?
Making preparations
for two weeks from now.
I'd better join them!
Azaki-sensei.
There's something I want you to teach me.
Hasumi
Emoto
Urusugawa
Cardboard?
Kasubata
Soji
1-A
Split up
At last...
the second term's A-B Battle is here.
Class B lost badly in the first term.
Only Kasubata acquitted himself well.
I believe the main reason
for class B's defeat
was that their defender's cyberkinesis
failed to function, yes.
This time, Soji Enishiro's is participating.
Will he bring them good fortune or bad?
Sad Boy K
Today
Your wish will come true very soon
Thank you. I look forward to it
Let's get hype, y'all!
Let's talk about who we like!
I'm a one-Kureha girl.
I'm carsick.
Have some tea. It's good for that.
We're on our way to the A-B Battle.
Should you really be relaxing?
I'm totally freaking out about it here!
The first-term battle was a nightmare!
Who wouldn't be scared?!
Tea.
Was the last A-B Battle in the mountains?
Yeah, chaos in the mountains.
It still haunts me.
They've got too many people
with offensive cyberkinesis!
I ran and ran, but they all
kept chasing me.
They're a group of the worst
people imaginable!
Hey, Emoto.
If you're that scared of everything,
why stick with the exorcist gig?
You just came out and asked, huh?
Why do I do it?
Because...
Hush now! Everyone's got
their reasons!
Master Haijima?
So the real you didn't come along?
What're you talking about?
The real her is right there.
Th-The doll requires less spirit power
when I'm nearby, so...
It's been a while since
I left the campus, but...
I r-really want to win, so...
Itabashi-sensei, we're absolutely
taking this seriously.
We spent two weeks getting ready!
I can't wait to try out my new trick!
Well, we're almost there.
B-But this is just Kusatsu!
Itabashi-sensei, why are we
back at the school?
A-B Battle
This year, it's urban warfare
in the city of Kusatsu.
Victory is yours if the other class is
rendered unable to fight or gives up.
Rest Building
Kochi-sensei the nurse is here,
so you're permitted to inflict harm,
I've got a fully charged battery!
but killing is off-limits.
Killing warrants immediate
team disqualification.
This place is a recreation of Kusatsu
on land owned by the Society.
Th-That's nuts!
A total recreation of the town?
How is that possible?!
A faculty member at the school
possesses "copy-paste" cyberkinesis.
It's a truly incredible skill.
Azaki-sensei will be joining us
via video conference.
Huh? Am I on?
Hey!
Azaki-sensei, we're
getting a black screen.
Hey, we're up his nose!
Sensei, you're too close! Pull away!
H-How about this?!
Now you're too far!
And put some pants on!
This is like Video Calling 101!
I should have just recorded it.
Azaki-sensei, please do this right.
I'm trying, but it's hard!
This isn't even my tablet!
Anyway, do your best.
The teachers, your upperclassmen...
Everyone's got their
eyes on this battle.
It may be a school tradition,
but it means something extra this time.
You're being evaluated for potential
use in the mission to exorcise K.
Watch us, Sensei.
We won't embarrass you this time.
I'm gonna be honest.
I'd be fine if you lost this one.
I mean, I really love you kids!
If you go on an extreme-level
exorcism mission,
there's a good chance you won't come back.
But you've worked really hard
these past two weeks.
You've gotten strong!
As your teacher,
I have but one thing to say.
Get out there and win! That's all!
Sir!
Needless to say, get out there and win.
Show them which exorcist class
does things the right way.
Listen. You're doing one person—
We're doing one person per target!
Welcome
Each of us is far stronger
than each of them.
So let's find them and
take them down quickly.
Right, Nanzo-sensei?
Correct.
All right! Dibs on Enishiro!
I'd prefer to take Enishiro myself.
Blue is my favorite color, after all.
Have you been paying attention, man?
Enishiro and I have a real
love drama developing here.
Well, let's get this over with again.
Wagari-san, who should I go after?
Whoever you meet first is your destiny!
Now...
It's time for the rabbit hunt.
It is now noon.
Classes, please take your places.
Darn it, I gotta get my head in the game!
Don't you underestimate me!
Well, if we can't beat these guys,
there's no way we could beat K.
Hey, Enishiro.
Thanks for getting angry on
our behalf in the mountains before.
It made me really happy.
Hasumi...
Why do you think we didn't say anything
after all of Surugi's trash talk?
That's because, Enishiro...
We were saving it for the big day.
The first-year A-B Battle...
begins now!
That's a fairly weak sound.
Let's start with a bang!
Go, class B!
Right!
Yeah!
A show of force to start with, eh?
A suitably barbaric battle cry
coming from Kasubata-kun.
Wait, Wagari.
Allow me.
It's truly sparked my imagination!
Cyber out!
Millennium Suspension!
Millennium
Suspension
Title: "The Beast of Frozen Beauty"!
Title: "The Beast of Frozen Beauty"
Oh, incredible...
I'm frozen, captivated, once more.
You're amazing, Ashina-kun!
Seems a little over the top.
Ashina-kun, how much
of your charge did you use?
Fifty percent!
You idiot! And keep your clothes on!
Hey, whoa, what the heck is that thing?
Ashina's a freezer.
His taste is as bad as ever.
Easy on the eyes, though.
I guess wiping them out in one hit
would've been too convenient.
Emo up!
Cyber out!
Nirvana Wall!
That was close!
I'm glad we came up with a code!
Awesome work, Emoto! Nicely done!
R-Right. I guess so.
So that was Wagari's response.
He did that from all the way over there?
That's scary as hell.
Minoru Wagari is class 1-A's rep.
His cyberkinesis is "Worry-Cutter."
He can freely change the power
and target of his cuts.
He's only a first-year, but he's been on
multiple high-level account exorcisms.
He's even beaten mid-levels solo.
He's a prodigy.
Wagari's dangerous.
Listen, if you end up one-on-one
with him, flee immediately.
Don't need to tell me twice.
If Kasubata's talking like that...
Piggy Moving Company
Haijima's real body will move separately.
Make sure you're not found.
Ya.
Give 'em hell, Master!
Where should I hide?
Somewhere I'll never be discovered.
One person per target.
Once you find one of them,
inform everyone.
Enishiro! Where are you?
I'll make all the bad stuff go away!
I've longed for this
frozen form for so long!
The peak of beauty!
I wonder where Kasubata-kun could be!
Hello, Owada? I'd like to pee.
Then use one of the bathrooms nearby!
This is strange.
Cyberbeast Summon
I can't find 1-B anywhere.
Where are you hiding, class 1-B?
I'm going to dominate the A-B Battle
and participate in the mission to banish
the extreme-level account Sad Boy K.
It'll be a perfect springboard on
my journey to become a top exorcist.
Slice.
Hiyori Haijima.
The shut-in doll user.
I give you credit for leaving your room
to appear on the battlefield.
Hiding among the souvenir shops
was also a clever idea.
Disguise a cardboard box
among cardboard boxes.
But I'm sorry to say...
I can see you trembling.
Wagari's dangerous.
Flee immediately.
What a fool.
You should have just given up.
Slice!
MISSED ME
Nearly all of class A uses
attack-type cyberkinesis.
They're strong.
So their first thought will be
to split up and search for us.
Haijima, you lure them out.
Bait them as a frightened weakling
separated from the herd.
You fell for it, dumbass!
The real me is hidden
somewhere totally different!
I'm in a narrow alley, vulnerable
in the moments after an attack.
It's a trap!
Ever heard the saying...
that exorcism is about teamwork?
Our first job is to take out your
strongest member, all together!
Teamwork?
Looks more like a dogpile to me!
A pathetic strategy for weaklings.
Instead one person per target,
I'll go for six targets myself!
Emo up!
Slice!
Ren! Where are the other class A members?!
You're good. They haven't seen us yet.
We'll finish you before
the others get here!
A hit!
The demon flame user...
Yeah, that's the way.
Well-planned teamwork.
Class B used their cyberkinesis nicely.
The wall, the goo, and the hammer.
The addition of the flamebaiter Enishiro
has sparked some life into them.
I like you, class B!
And it's so cute to see Denmi-chan
movin' around like that!
Principal, you're forgetting someone.
The scariest member of class B.
We did it?!
We beat Wagari?
Heck yeah! That's one down!
How could this happen?
Stupid class B actually
landed a hit on me.
There goes my flawless victory.
Even though I'm supposed to be perfect.
He's still going!
Pile on!
He can't use his swords while
he's still bound up in the goo!
Suicide?
No, not that...
Crap.
His cyberkinesis lets him
choose his target.
He's cutting only the goo!
Withdraw! Quickly!
With Worry-Cutter, I can choose
my target and my power level.
Normally I use Slice, which cuts things.
I usually wouldn't use my
severing sword against humans...
Because it kills.
Sever!
That monster.
Oh, this is awful!
I actually let anger control me!
I came so close to killing them all!
Deep breaths. Mental reset.
Okay, this time, I'll choose to sever
only your hands and feet!
Get your adrenaline up now
so you don't die of shock!
He's totally crazy!
Our escape route is blocked.
Luring him back here worked against us.
Dummy! We can still use
the wall to block him!
Don't underestimate our Emoto!
The wall's gone?