In the near future, e-Pulse is
generated by human thoughts and emotions,
and used as an energy source
for AI devices called "Sapotamas,"
leading to a new development for humanity.
But from its shadows,
terrifying monsters have appeared.
Monsters that evolve by consuming e-Pulse.
They are...
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
Beyond where no one can stop me
darenimo jama wa sasenai sono saki he
I'll make my way there
As I seek the answer
mayoinagara kotae sagashi tsukisusumu
Carve your emotion
kizamitsukero Emotion
It reverberates
hibiiteiru
The tempo that synchs
tashika ni shinkurosuru Tempo wa
Is a pulse that slowly reveals
The hidden world
sukoshi zutsu
kakureta sekai abaiteiku hakudou
Record on top of the solid Baseline
yuraganai Baseline no ue de Rec
Don't mess up tempo
Normal's not enough for me
futsuu ja monotarinee
Just keep howling, howling!!!
Howling like it's all you've got
Even if what you believe begins to blur
shinjiru mono ga nijimisou ni natte mo
The reality that you grasp
Rings strong and true
nigirishimeru Riaru wa
uso janaku tsuyoku hibiku
Take away the Metronome
For this one and only JAM
Metronome topparau ichido kiri kono JAM
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
The emotional beat that rings out
kanjou no mama narasu kodou wa
Is the BPM that continues on and on
sou zutto hashiritsuzukeru BPM
(Let the beat lead the way)
The Cloudy rain swallows the city
matenrou nomikomu Cloudy Rain
Even if I link and the rhythm warps
I just make it part of my groove
rinkushite rizumu yoretatte
Groove ni shichaeba ii
Ride it like you see fit
norikonase omoidoori
(Let the beat lead the way)
Even if it hurts, I won't stop
itami daite mo tomarazu ni
Keep carving the beat
Won't back down
kizami tsudzukeru kodou
We can overcome anything
bokura nara donna koto mo norikoerareru
Drum to your emotion
tatakitsukero Emotion
Please... No more...
I...
don't want to...
THE PRICE OF FREEDOM
What's wrong?
Is he okay?
Talk about suspicious.
E-Excuse me?
If his stomach can rumble,
he's not dead.
I guess so.
Stew?
I guess I'm on my way to meet my maker
because three heartless people
wouldn't feed me some stew.
That was delicious! Thanks a bunch!
You're kidding!
We bought that food to feed Kyo
when he returns from Nirinso exhausted!
I wanted some, too, ya know!
Hey! You're supposed to stay hidden!
No need to fool me.
That's a Digimon, right?
Huh?
I'm an Owner, too.
Say hello, Commandramon.
A Digimon?
A Commandramon. A Rookie Digimon.
By displaying the surrounding environment
on its body, it can camouflage itself.
Wow, ya know!
So anyhow, if you'll excuse us.
We're not just letting you leave!
Are you wanted?
No. No bounty poster at Maki's.
Then, you're a Cleaner?
That's personal info. I'd rather not say.
The stew was great. Thanks.
Gekkomon.
What are you...
We don't have the money for more food.
You get it, right?
Pull your weight if you want food.
A bet of hospitality, ya know.
Debt. You mean a debt.
We never did things like this.
Yeah.
What do we do...
from here?
Commandramon, do it!
Right.
I got this!
Listen...
at the very least, you should...
What are you talking about!
We're in this together!
What's that, ya know?
Haruomi! Never say that again!
Sorry.
What's up?
Are you fighting, ya know?
It's nothing.
Tell me.
How come you're so poor
if you're Cleaners?
We don't turn over captured In-Training
Digimon to the Ministry.
So we don't get paid in full.
Huh? Why?
We don't delete Digimon.
That's our rule.
Ya know!
Commandramon, stay here with these guys.
Huh?!
Crystal Cannon!
What the...?!
They found me.
Haruomi Sone. There you are.
Tactics?!
You. Tomoro Tenma, was it?
Have you learned to control your emotions?
And are you still Naito's lapdog?!
What's going on?!
What a shabby home.
Sorry if it doesn't suit you.
Hotaruko...
Makoto.
Hand those two over.
We won't say it again! Hand them over!
-No way.
-Ya know!
I never did return the favor
for what you did to Rhamphomon!
Evade!
-Commandramon!
-Right!
Tylomon!
Okay!
Commandramon!
Let go of me!
-Tactical retreat!
-Hey!
Why'd you abandon Commandramon?!
Answer me, Haruomi!
We're on a first-name basis?
They won't risk deleting Commandramon.
Their orders are to bring us both back.
What?
Then you two are...
Yeah. We're former Tactics.
So why are you fugitives?
We wanted to be free.
We got tired of doing
all those shady jobs.
Shady jobs?
Thanks to Commandramon's camo ability,
we were sent around the world
on special missions.
And...
our hands got dirty.
Can't you wash them?
You're hilarious!
So, I wanna ask a favor.
Could you help us get our freedom?
First we get Commandramon back.
Wait, what?
I'm not saying to do it for free.
You have money?
I said I've been doing shady jobs.
It pays a lot.
Didn't we find you starving?
My money's hidden.
When this is done, I'll show you where.
I see. We could buy more food
for another stew.
I'm begging you, Tomoro.
Okay. Let's talk strategy.
So you two will do diversion and delay.
-Got it.
-I understand.
I'm counting on you.
You really want to be free
with Commandramon?
Of course I do, Tomoro.
I'm gonna get some air.
What's with him?
You two.
Listen to me...
Tomoro!
S-Stop it! What are you doing?!
Are you worried about Haruomi?
Do you think we can really trust him?
Something doesn't feel right.
But he saved you, ya know?
Huh?
If you'd gone out there...
you could've been really hurt, ya know.
In here.
What's this about making a deal?
He wants to be free with Commandramon.
Will you let him?
You want freedom?
Why do you do stupid things
by acting emotionally?
We should just follow our orders.
Right?
Just follow orders?
Don't you have feelings of your own?!
Are you stupid?
What?
Of course everybody has feelings.
You just control them.
Letting your emotions control you
isn't cool.
It's what stupid people do.
Tomoro Tenma, I mean people like you.
Stop calling people stupid.
After him!
Gekkomon!
Here goes!
Pound the beat!
Gekkomon Evolution!
Armalizamon!
You won't escape.
Nice, Wolvermon!
It's not over yet!
Oh no you don't!
Whoops! Oh no!
Neutron Laser!
Dummy!
They're gone, ya know!
Behind us!
Armalizamon!
What?
That wasn't Sone?
Rhamphomon! Don't let them escape!
Crystal Rain!
It was just a warning shot.
I know it was!
Haruomi...
You...!
You used Commandramon as a shield?!
And now I'm alone.
What?
With Commandramon gone,
I'm no longer an Owner.
I don't have to do any more shady jobs!
I'm free! I've gained my freedom!
You...
What are you thinking?!
Stop it! What are you doing?!
Raito! Let go of me!
What are you doing?!
Our orders are to retrieve him.
Commandramon's gone!
There's no point
in taking just me, is there?!
The job's done, Rhamphomon.
-Roger.
-Are you listening?!
I've had it with you!
Neutron Blade!
I already know that attack!
I'm a genius, you know!
What the heck is that e-Pulse?
Tomoro, I got this!
Death Roll Press!
That was close.
I didn't need your help!
We're leaving.
Honestly...
That was a vintage shirt.
You can come out now.
Commandramon?!
Ya know!
What's going on?!
Back there...
Listen to me...
I'll use Commandramon's
camo ability to trick them.
That's not the plan...
...we discussed, ya know!
You two can't act to save your lives.
Tricking an enemy
starts with tricking an ally.
Huh?
But the plan was to have Tactics give up
and for them both to be free.
Why did they...?
No.
This is what Haruomi intended
from the start.
It was all... so I could...
be free.
Haruomi?
Commandramon.
Use your camo ability to escape.
Leave it to me.
No matter what happens,
don't lift your camo.
Got it?
So he put on that cheesy show
to make you angry.
It was to convince them...
that I'd really been deleted.
He knows what'll happen
if he's taken back to the Tactics.
He knows, and yet he still...
Haruomi?!
That's not fair, Haruomi!
We'll see each other again, right?
Their e-Pulse is...
I see. So they were reduced to a Bommon.
All we can do now...
is respect Haruomi's wishes.
Haruomi...
Sir Klay wanted
to put them up for the auction.
Losing Commandramon was a massive failure.
This is your last chance.
Yes, sir!
Where am I going?
Do you believe in hell?
Like there's a worse hell than here?
With those guys, you can start over.
You won't be hounded
by nightmares anymore.
You are...
free.
Don't let the normal be normal
atarimae wo atarimae ni shinai
Playing to the score is not enough
gakufu doori ja monotarinaindayo
Take in everything, even the noise
And make it our own session!
noizu sura mo torikonde
jibun dake no sesshon wo!
Things won't change in others' hands
Boot! Boot!
hitomakase ja kawaranaishi
Reach out your hand
te nobase
Don't be scared to mess up, go on
Boot! Boot!
machigai mo osorezu susume
With courage
yuukan ni
Go tell the rules NO
Error, error
ruuru ni tatakitsukeru NO
error, error
Scale out? Bring it on
Error, error
sukeeru auto joutou
error, error
An unexpected code
Error, error
yosoku funou no koodo
error, error
Prompts can't control these feelings
puronpto nanka ja seigyoudekinai omoide
Give it a shout
kamase shauto
BRAVE! No more fear
BRAVE! mou kowakunai
Keep my head high
utsumuitari mo shinai
I've got someone who's got my back
senaka azukeaeru kimi ga iru kara
GROOVE! We can't be stopped
GROOVE! mou tomaranai
Our beats are in unison
yunizon suru koudou ga
We're going to update the world
kitto sekaijuu wo appudeeto shiteiku
With a bang
bakuon de
A charity auction?
It seems Klay Arslan, a Five Star,
is the organizer.
-Fine bark?
-No, a "Five Star."
What about that?
There are rumors that it's a front
for illegal Digimon auctions.
Okay! We just gotta infiltrate,
and investigate the auction!
Next time on DIGIMON BEATBREAK
"Black Market Auction"