Can Hijikata Toshizou and
his men survive this attack?
This "deed book" the government
wants so badly to be rid of...
If it's real...
It must be Asirpa who has it.
If I can get my hands on it, I'm sure
everything will turn out the way I want.
Even in this chaos, could someone
find me if I fired a single shot?
Yeah, that Russian soldier could.
Golden Kamuy
Episode Sixty-One
Bushido
We're going in!
Cover us!
The soldiers made it inside!
Our fortifications on the other
side all got wiped out, then.
We expected the enemy to make it inside.
Purple: Enemy
Red: Ally
What we wanted to avoid was having
them all swarm Goryoukaku at once.
Purple: Enemy
Red: Ally
It's better to have them
come in a few at a time,
and fight where we have
a numerical advantage.
We will win this!
We will be the ones to survive!
The soldiers are inside,
and Sugimoto's started to fight.
I know you're worried, but forget
any ideas about helping him.
Let's focus on what we can do.
We need to be ready,
so we can run if we need to.
Right now, your one focus should
be protecting the deed book.
It'll help all the Ainu who
live in Hokkaido, right?
And so we won't dash
Kiro-chan's hopes, too...
Everybody says Russia's invading!
The Japanese warships
all got sunk, they say!
We need to run!
You alive, broke-ass?
Nispa who looks up people's asses...
Looks like your head's okay.
Ow...
Your left leg's broken. You can't stand.
You're doing better than Mansur,
though. He lost his right hand.
Where's Nagakura Nispa?
You guys get out of here, now.
You don't need to come back to Goryoukaku.
You've more than done your jobs.
What will you do?
Go help Hijikata Toshizou.
This time, I want to be
with him until the end.
The soldiers who came in through the
south entrance have caught up with us!
Good!
We'll wipe out more soldiers at the
fortifications on the
north and east sides,
and stick our men inside!
Ushiyama, you and the others
head to the fortifications there
and stop more from coming in.
Toni Anji and I will defeat the
soldiers who made it inside.
Grenade!
Hijikata Toshizou...
Toni!
My nipple!
Damn you!
So loud...
Go! Go!
I don't have time for this!
I need to find Sugimoto!
Toni... I can't believe you saved me.
Yeah? If it weren't for you,
I would've died two or three times.
I shouldn't be alive anyway.
I can give up this life if
it'll keep you alive longer!
Now, go!
I'll protect the bridge!
Good work! Good work! Tsukishima!
Charge! Charge!
We have the east gate!
Charge!
We have 50 soldiers who can still fight,
including those at the
south and east gates!
Good. All of you, secure the north gate.
Nobody escapes.
Deploy soldiers at each gate.
Lieutenant Koito,
Sergeant Tsukishima, follow me.
We'll search the buildings
for the deed book!
My ears hurt so much, damn it!
The noise stopped.
It's so quiet...
I'll never forgive you!
We'll rip Sugimoto apart, and go
back to there being two of us!
Hey, Kouhei, want an orange?
Move, Nikaidou!
Give back Youhei!
Stop talking!
We're killing each other here!
Where's Commander Koito?
He stayed on the ship
instead of evacuating.
The gentle lie told by the
Tsukisappu anpan seller.
You've lied so much,
you can only feel like somebody loves you
after you test them with a lie, right?
Lt. Koito!
From the central government's perspective,
everyone here is a rebel plotting
to overthrow the government.
If we win, we're heroes.
If we lose, we're doomed.
If we come back empty-handed
from this war,
we'll be put on trial by
the military as traitors.
I and my father came here
of our own volition.
So we'll accept whatever happens.
But if something happens,
to protect my men from the
central government, I will...
I'm not going to lose.
I'm going to attain it all.
If all you'd done is ask for my
help, I would've followed you!
Let's go, Tsukishima!
Tsukishima, it seems
you're my only ally now.
You'll pay for what you did to my brother!
Give back Kouhei's body!
You and your brother can
wait for me in hell!
Let's blow up together, Sugimoto!
Oh?
Hey, Kouhei.
Hey, Youhei.
We meet again.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Golden Kamuy
Instead of going through all this trouble,
why don't you just tell me
alone where the gold is?
Can you prove you're
really Hijikata Toshizou?
Even Warden Kadokura... his dad was the
one who met Hijikata of the Shinsengumi.
And what about you?
Are you really an Ainu?
My eyes are blue because my father was
a Polish man who was exiled to Karafuto.
The Polish have been rebelling
on and off for a century now.
I think your real plan was to use the
Ainu gold to fight Imperial Russia.
And even if your father was Polish,
that would only make most
people more suspicious, right.
I've heard that the Ainu think that the
man inherits blood from the father,
and the woman inherits from the mother.
I'm not after revenge for the
oppression my father suffered.
I'm doing this for the future.
Keep your voices down, or I won't be
able to hear the guards' footsteps.
"Hokkaido must become a multicultural,
independent country,
to stop Russia from taking it over."
This is our common understanding, right?
If you can't escape prison,
you have no choice but to entrust
it to me, no matter who I am.
That's not good enough.
Some things only Hijikata Toshizou can do.
What does that mean?
I simply mean that I can't trust you
to act in the Ainu's best interests.
If it was just for me,
I could give up easily.
But I can risk my life to
fight for something else.
That's Bushido.
Do you understand that, blue-eyed Ainu?
After our defeat at Hakodate
I was called a traitor
and jailed at the ends of the earth...
But I still think about the
future of Japan, constantly.
The family I love, the
home where I was raised...
And Japan, the place where both dwell...
How can I protect it?
And of course, that includes the Ainu.
I have a personal debt
to the Ainu, as well.
Which Ainu, specifically?
There was a man named Kimuspu.
A man with a strange tattoo at the
base of his thumb on both hands.
Find a girl named Kochoube Asuko.
She'll know me.
I found Hijikata Toshizou!
Their soldiers are stronger than us!
We're in bad shape!
Find Lieutenant Tsurumi.
If we defeat him, that will
destroy their morale.
How can we find him in the middle of this?
The south and east gates have fallen.
And the soldiers inside are
attacking the north gate.
And when it falls, all their
soldiers will come after us!
Let's run! So we can
protect the deed book!
What's going on at Goryoukaku?!
That's dangerous!
If you're not behind the
tree you might get shot!
The stable on the north side
started to burn brightly,
and for a moment, drew everyone's
attention even in the middle of battle.
That's the signal Shiraishi talked about!
He's decided to leave!
We should fall back!
We can regroup and come back
before they dig up all of
Goryoukaku to find the gold!
This battle wasn't a waste!
We cut down Tsurumi's
army by a lot of men.
If we can regroup, we can win!
Head to the east!
They may try to run!
With the deed book in hand,
they can't try to go through the moat!
Do we check the stable?
What's wrong?
I'm a messenger! I'm coming through!
Stop him!
That's Shiraishi!
Don't hit the bag!
It's got the deed book and the girl!
What?
Why did they show up at the
other side of the bridge now?
Nagakura Shinpachi!
Oh, shit!
Of course, that bag doesn't contain
either Asirpa-chan or the deed book!
It's just some ropes!
Asirpa's waiting by the
side of the moat, though!
The quiver that contains the deed book
was waterproofed with diatomaceous
earth and animal stomach lining!
I'll cross the bridge with the horse.
And toss the rope from the opposite side.
I'll pull it with the horse and
get Asirpa-chan across fast!
That's the plan!
But it failed!
So swim across and run away
on your own, Asirpa-chan!
No sign of Shiraishi.
What's wrong?
Toni Anji...
He found me!
Come at me, country samurai from Satsuma!
Whoa, there...
Have you gotten too old
to fight, Shinsengumi?
More of them!
Your blade is weak!
You're no match for the fighting
spirit of the Satsuma soldiers
I faced 40 years ago!
The deed book!
Asirpa-san!
Sugimoto!
Hurry! Hurry!
They're coming!
The south exit's no good!
There are soldiers there!
The east, then!
That won't work either!
The north exit's our only hope!
How do you know?
I think Sofia's still
blocking the north exit,
so the enemy's coming around
to the east and south.
Which means there shouldn't
be many of them on the
other side of the north bridge!
What's important is what
happens when we get out.
Let's get away from here!
Next time
Daughter of Wilk
Next time: Daughter of Wilk.