You, dear. Listen closely.
What you need to eradicate are the ones
who are trying to plunder from us.
You, dear. That's why you shall fight.
So that you can take your
mother back someday.
You filthy spellcaster!
Oh...
You're missing quite
a lot deep down there.
Let me tell you something interesting.
Those spellcasters that were repeatedly
calling you guys "You, dear"...
They all died, okay?
If you still want to keep living...
come with me.
Oh, and... about your mother.
She's long since died in
a country called Japan.
Let me tell you once again.
This operation is to recreate
a Magecraft ritual...
that was once held in the Far East.
We fished up six Masters and their Servants
using a fake Holy Grail War as the lure.
We will use them as
catalysts to officially
summon seven Servants, and the real...
the True Holy Grail War will commence.
As a Master of the True Holy Grail War...
I will have you summon a Servant.
If the summon succeeds—
You don't have to report
to me what showed up!
You can do whatever you want
after it's summoned, too!
If anything, you can even consider
coming after my life!
Please make sure to report to me.
And this has nothing to
do with the job, but...
The wish granter that can make
any wish come true...
What will you wish upon the Holy Grail?
I don't have any wishes.
I don't have a god to believe in
or a homeland to return to.
All I desire are meals
and good sleep each day.
I didn't expect the favorite...
that you kept talking about
to be a boy like him.
Oh, right. He looks like
a boy because they fiddled
with his body too much when he was young.
He probably can't live that long a life.
Though, he's not the type
to worry about stuff like that.
Is that the reason why you didn't prepare
a catalyst for him?
I had a lightbulb moment.
If I made a fake Holy Grail choose
a Servant for someone who has nothing...
what exactly...
would be drawn to it?
For the elements, silver and iron.
For the foundation, stone
and the Archduke of Contracts.
That's why I want you,
who doesn't have anything!
No desires for the world,
no intention of leaving anything behind!
With someone like you,
the Holy Grail can enter a plain state.
Just what will...
come to you?
Come forth from the circle of binding...
Guardian of the Scales!
So, you're a Master of the Holy Grail War?
Hah!
How this face lacks ambition.
I am indeed the Master who summoned you.
You can call me "Captain."
But that will soon become meaningless.
Who exactly are you?
My boy, you have a misunderstanding.
We were not...
summoned by you.
Who are you?
We are nothing more than shadows
of the Heroic Spirit you summoned.
We are not Heroic Spirits.
You're outta luck, man.
You can't escape now.
You have summoned a hardship
that has no way out.
However...
we have high hopes for you.
That you will become a Lancer
that pierces through all.
What do you mean?
Are you lot not the Lancer?
If Fuyuki's system was used as is,
Lancer would have been the
one rightfully summoned.
Then, what in the world...
Let's see.
A guardian whose job is to always look
down on us from a high place...
I guess you could say... "Watcher."
Hurry up already!
Now, whatcha gonna do?
Mr. Cordelion?
Bazdilot!
What are you doing
to a member of the family?
A fly.
Wait—
If you thought you could infiltrate
with a disguise like that...
that's a great insult to Mr. Scradio.
No way! Spies?
Come to the basement
once you're done cleaning up.
I received a catalyst from the States.
I will summon a Servant.
Bazdilot Cordelion.
His public face is the president
of an industrial waste disposal company.
His hidden side is a high-ranking member
of the Scradio Family,
a huge mafia group...
that is very close
to a portion of the government.
There are over 125 murders
that he is suspected of involvement.
During his first incarceration,
three wardens and 26 inmates
went missing in six months.
He painted the entire penitentiary
into allies of the Scradio Family.
I am still against it.
Taking someone
with so many enemies out of jail...
to weave him into the Holy Grail War.
You say that, but all the Masters I called
are kinda similar, you know!
The Masters can all be controlled
however we wish.
But...
you and Bazdilot Cordelion
are a different story.
Hey, what do you think will happen?
I mean, he's trying to summon
the great virtuous, unyielding hero...
Heracles!
Are you the one...
that will become my master
and present me a labor?
The one who decides that
isn't me. That's you.
And I shall ask you, as well.
O hero of Greece.
Can you take the life of a young child
if it meant winning the war?
Are you...
testing me?
If you speak of such
knowing my background...
I will deem those words
as something you risk your life for.
Of course.
I have already...
thrown my life away long ago.
How facile.
Restraints from Command Spells
are meaningless to me.
I order you with a Command Spell.
Drop your facade.
Bastard!
What did you...
I don't need a hero.
I need human obsession that uses
any means necessary to meet an objective.
Impossible!
This is not a level of Magical Energy
that someone of this era can harbor!
I further order you with
another Command Spell.
Remember all the humans you have observed.
Stay away from me, monster!
Only when you're together with me,
you won't be a monster.
Don't detest your own blood.
Father!
Wh-What's going on?
I further command you.
This Mage is dangerous!
I...
must stop him!
Accept the true nature of humans.
Was it really all right?
I mean, to hand him that thing
you brought here from Fuyuki.
It's fine, it's fine!
I mean...
I didn't want to keep touching...
that uncute and nasty mud!
How does it feel
to get rid of what is unnecessary?
Why do you hide your face?
Admonition.
So that the sins of man
never reach my eyes again.
I ask you.
Are you my Servant?
My name is Alcides.
I will have my vengeance
against the gods...
and using the power of the Holy Grail...
I will rid myself...
of my posthumous name!
Though it was due to an interference...
I didn't think you'd let those
affiliated with the gods escape.
Ridiculous.
I am simply using you for my vengeance.
But tell me. What is the source
of your Magical Energy?
Even after such a fierce battle,
I did not feel it ever flicker.
That is not the Magical Energy level
of an ordinary Mage.
It's quite simple.
I am using batteries.
In the past...
a Mage named Atrum Galliasta created
a system that efficiently
creates Magical Energy.
We pilfered it, improved it...
and built upon it.
A Magical Energy forge...
that runs on human lives, huh?
With this much, I'll
have no issues fighting
at full throttle for about half a day.
Half a day with this much?
Then...
you should be able to continue fighting
with all you've got for several months.
How many humans have you sacrificed
to this contraption until now?
Oh...
just 24,976 people.
Surprising you were able
to keep it a secret.
Of course.
It is all thanks to my lord
Galvarosso Scradio's connections.
The bigger the Scradio Family gets,
the more enemies we have.
If we have to eradicate them anyway...
we should make good use of them.
I appreciate that you
stopped their squabbles...
but we'll be in trouble
if you don't hold your reins properly.
Whaaat? Are the States
threatening me right now?
Am I going to be murdered?
I hear you have been erased by the Agency
twice or so in the past.
Yep! It hurt quite a bit, you know!
I cannot understand it.
Why the government decided
to join forces with you
even if it has been several decades...
or you, who has the nerve
to join forces with a government...
that tried to eradicate
your very existence.
Having my physical body killed
is not something I feel despair over.
Well, there are many people
who have murdered me,
but... I can easily count
the number of those
that brought me to my knees with an "Oof!"
Let's see. The old man Kischur,
the hedonistic Saint Germain
and most of all...
Scar Red!
She'll kill you if you
say that to her face.
She did kill me!
That's how I ended up in my current body.
Is that why you became
interested in eternal youth?
Yep, yep!
"Drag down the Third Magic
to Magecraft levels"...
was your ultimate objective, right?
Is it not for you?
For me, that's only a checkpoint.
It's better if there is no magic
that defines the limitations of humans.
That's what I believe in...
and I believe that the
true nature of humans...
is the foolishness to face that threshold!
Because the world is
more amusing that way!
I have no intention
of putting up with your hedonism.
If necessary, I will forcefully have you
exit the stage.
What are you talking about?
You and I are enemies
in the Holy Grail War.
You shouldn't forget about that, okay?
I know that.
I have never once thought
that you were on our side.
Jeez!
Faldeus should enjoy the war more.
We have so many actors
that shine on the stage after all!
Hey, don't you think so?
Isn't this where you welcome me
with a "Welcome home, master!"?
I did some work immediately
after being summoned, you know.
But...
I'm the master here!
And that was nothing
more than a performance
to make the States feel relieved.
But still, it wasn't all
that bad a show, right?
Yep! I gotta hand it to me!
Oh, but I wanted to see it in person...
the angry face of the King of Heroes!
Now, now, this is just the beginning, me!
Yep!
Let's put our souls on the line
and win this Holy Grail War
fair and square, me!
I, François Prelati...
I, Francesca Prelati...
- in pure, righteous glory...
- ...swear to win and acquire
-  ...swear to win and acquire
-  the great Holy Grail!
- Just kidding!
In other words, you lot can objectively
observe the Holy Grail War?
To be precise, not us,
but the one you summoned.
I don't get it.
Is this what you call an "Extra Class"?
And... what do you mean
I'm going to become Lancer?
I got some sleep and thought
it over once again,
but it's not making sense to me.
I think you're quite something
to be able to sleep
and even eat in this condition.
Sleep and meals are more
important than anything.
We are slightly different
from those Extra Class folks.
Didn't I tell you?
You're the one who will become Lancer.
Watcher is the barrier and watchtower
for that to happen.
Isn't it absurd to say
that a human will become Lancer?
What is absurd is this
Holy Grail War itself.
It has derailed all too far.
Those that normally would not be summoned
are calling for each other...
and more will be drawn over to this land.
Those parents have not shown up
for two days now.
Tsubaki...
It's all right.
I will never abandon you.
Is this a tattoo?
Was this here before?
Did you pull this bird out, as well?
Thank you! I love animals!
Love!
You know, Mr. Black...
nobody will disappear anymore, right?
Nobody will disappear anymore, right?
Oh, yes! I'm sorry!
Yes. Thank you so much.
Goodbye.
Professor wasted two hours of his time
because of me.
I see the reason why you admire
your mentor so much.
He is a magnificent
instructor of Magecraft.
Taking into account the tale that
he survived a Holy Grail War,
he must also be top-notch as a Mage.
Of course! Professor has solved
all sorts of cases for the Clock Tower—
What's wrong, Master?
The fog is rather thick.
What are you talking about?
There isn't any fog anywhere—
Mr. Berserker, we might
be in a bit of trouble.
This fog... has at least
swallowed up the entire city.
What will happen to me now?
From hereon out,
an assortment of difficulties you may
call "trials" will stand in your way.
By overcoming them,
you will slowly become someone.
I am a mere soldier with no name.
I will not amount to "a somebody,"
even to death.
We'll see about that.
That just means that you
can become anything.
Escape the jaws of death, young man.
Rage against God.
Never submit.
Beyond all that
is where the proof of your life will be.
See...
your first trial has already arrived.
Are you a Mage seeking the Holy Grail?
Are you...
a Servant?
Answer my question.
Hold on. I have no hostile intent.
Can you allow me
to negotiate with your Master?
Jump.
You have some hair coming your way.
Zabaniya.
That's not a Master.
That's a poor little girl
who got roped into the Holy Grail War.
Get away!
If you stay here...
EPISODE 5