I should rest while I can.
Hiya!
The kidnapper!
I can't move.
I can't speak, either!
It's no use! I immobilized you.
Beautifully divine handiwork!
I'm Kuusetsu.
She's one of the Eight Thunder Gods!
I got back to my lair
and my lookouts were dead,
and my prey had escaped!
My plan was totally foiled!
I wanted to lose my cool and raise hell,
but Big Sis Shikoku
forbade me from fighting.
Then I saw you and followed you here!
Me?
Yuuki Wakura.
Big Sis Shikoku's favorite.
I've heard a lot about you.
So I might as well bring you back
as a souvenir from Yokohama.
My body just-
And I need you for my test.
You'll do, I guess. Barely.
"Test"?
Before I snatched one of my prey...
she was having sex with a male.
I wanna know if it feels
as good as it looked.
M-my tongue... and my arms...
They're moving on their own!
Mm, this is nice.
I wonder what happens to a human
when they have sex with a god.
Should we test it out?
Test it? Sex with a god?!
Nectar of a god.
Don't waste a single drop.
Area exercises for circles
Oh, I get it!
Thanks for the help, Miss Himari!
Just use the ratio and the formula.
Yokohama
Travel
Chinatown
I wish I could go to Yokohama.
The commanders are there on a mission.
Yeah, but imagine
the city's skyline at night!
Just the thought is so romantic!
It's beautiful.
You're even more beautiful, Shushu.
Huh?!
There's something
different about you, Yukki.
I can't hold back any longer.
Huh?
You won't be getting any sleep tonight.
Oh my god, as if!
Quit messing around.
They're up against a Thunder God.
They could be facing a situation
more dangerous
than anything we've ever imagined.
Aw, look at that scowl.
You're just a little numb right now.
It's harmless.
So relax and let yourself be mesmerized.
This scent...
This sensation...
This taste...
I like all of it.
Now, let's make it feel even better, hm?
You should be able to move a bit now.
So dedicate your tongue
to every last inch of your god.
C'mon, hurry up.
MISS MIRA!
Who are you?
My heart sunk and I no longer feel hope for the future
It felt like time froze and now it's all over
Brooding and silent
The umbrella of my heart began to open
Still, I kept my chin up and went on
I won't ask you to comfort me
I want to grow strong and focus on what's ahead
But weakness crushes me
Meeting you is what filled my world with light
I didn't have an ounce of hope, and yet I could laugh
Ordinary conversations always brought me a smile
I won't say thanks 'cause you'll blush and laugh
But I'm thinking it
Can I move forward from here?
O light, come to me
A Commander's Resolve
Episode 9
This sensation...
This taste...
I like all of it.
Now, let's make it feel even better, hm?
You should be able to move a bit now.
So dedicate your tongue
to every last inch of your god.
MISS MIRA!
Who are you?
Oop.
Are you okay?
I-I'm fine.
But the enemy...
She's a Thunder God!
On it!
Where do ya think yer goin'?
Do not kick...
MY BEAUTIFUL BODY!
A heliport!
Perfect for gettin' the party started!
God's Wrath!
Did she just...
All Killing!
Bring on the wrath!
A cloning ability?
I guess she did that
at the storehouse, too.
Oh well.
I'll defeat all of you
with a beautiful flick of my wrist!
Okay, so I missed one of you.
You really think...
you can beat me in midair?!
Sure do.
If you're my opponent...
then this execution
just turned into a battle.
What are those? Cards?!
I'm forbidden from fighting.
"If you're forced to fight, flee instead."
So I'll set these guys loose in the city.
Wha-
Everyone, go!
Mato Mishap in progress!
An enormous Shuuki has appeared!
Assess the extent of the damage
and evacuate citizens immediately!
How dare you!
How many can you save, I wonder?!
Good luck!
Ta-da!
Kuusetsu, I'm giving you
my handmade Shuuki deck.
Just give the signal and
the Shuuki trapped inside pops out.
I neutralized them
to put them in the cards,
but their powers will return ten seconds
after you let them out.
Ooh, neat!
Aside from the cannon fodder,
there are four strong Shuuki in it.
Ordinary members of the
Demon Defense Force can't beat these guys.
I brought one of 'em back to life
and upgraded it.
It's stronger and it spins a web
that keeps its prey alive.
Here's a giant Shuuki amalgamation.
It's a tough cookie.
It's everything I could ever ask for!
I love you, Big Sis Shikoku!
Call it insurance.
I scattered Shuuki all over Yokohama!
I'll show ya just how many I can save!
When creating clones,
Mira's ability allows her to choose:
Clones with enhanced strength,
or she can focus on splitting into
as many clones as possible.
I won't let a single person die!
All Killing!
Scarlet Regiment
All Killing
Let's aim for numbers!
Push it to the limit!
HQ, please respond!
A large number of Shuuki have appeared
in the Yokohama bay area!
We need officers on the ground ASAP!
HQ, we're unable to contain
the gigantic Shuuki!
Call the Demon Defense Force for backup!
M-Mommy...
This place is dangerous!
Get out of here, now!
O-okay!
Follow the person in front of you
and keep moving!
Help her.
Of course.
It's gonna be okay now, ma'am.
It's no use! We're trapped!
God, you're pathetic. I'll do it!
NO!
It's stronger than the ones
roamin' around Mato!
Make it bow down!
Kyouka!
I'm all healed up.
What's our game plan?
We slay this thing
and regroup with the kid at the hotel.
Then we meet at Rinko Park!
Roger!
Shuuki this massive in size
are extremely resilient.
That just makes it a prime punching bag.
Mira!
Yup!
Wow, you're really protecting them!
Kinmamon
Looked out for my crew
back in my hometown,
but I always wished I could be
in several places at once.
Maybe that's why
I'm so grateful for my cloning ability.
And now...
See ya later!
You'll feel my wrath next time we meet!
A god runnin' away scared?!
Talk about an ugly hag!
HA!
Fine! You get to feel my wrath right now!
She's going down like the rest of 'em!
Used a whole buncha your energy
just now, didn'tcha?
I bet you can can't even
clone yourself anymore.
How do you expect
to fight a god like that?
With my skills.
She doesn't learn.
A feint?!
Feather bullets!
And she can control them remotely?!
I'll shoot you while you're falling!
Use what little ya have left!
All Killing!
What?!
EAT SHIT!
Humans can muster up
a surprising amount of power
depending on their emotional state.
Big Sis Shikoku was right!
Yer gonna learn that
wreaking havoc on Yokohama...
was the wrong decision!
No more Miss Nice God!
With this form...
your judgment is nigh!
A giant Shuuki is approaching the area!
Please evacuate immediately!
I have to catch up with
Miss Kyouka and Miss Mira, quick!
Miss Kyouka!
Yuuki!
You aren't injured, are you?
I can move perfectly fine now!
Then we rendezvous with Mira. Let's go!
Yes, ma'am!
She might've changed forms,
but my goal is the same!
The clones she sent to counter the Shuuki
are coming back.
I created these clones in numbers in mind.
They won't last long, but I can
recall the ones that are close enough!
Now that I'm in this form...
my strength is in a class of its own!
Feinting won't work a second t-
She's fast!
I barely have time
to activate my slime ability!
Not bad.
Her endurance is through the roof, too!
That felt like the real you!
I won't let your clones distract me!
God's Wrath!
That was a clone, too?!
She managed to make another one?!
If you had more clones...
you might've killed a god.
But you wasted all your energy
saving bystanders instead.
Mistakes come with a price!
Surely you were prepared for this outcome?
The god doesn't know
what she's talking about.
I'm gonna save everyone and destroy you!
That's what I'm prepared for!
Kuusetsu.
My name is Kuusetsu.
I'm one of the Eight Thunder Gods.
Commander of the Demon Defense Force
2nd Squadron, Mira Kamiunten.
Y'know, you're very beautiful, Mira!
I'll show ya how the
Demon Defense Force does it, Kuusetsu!
Mira's clones
have defeated all the Shuuki,
and the city-goers are safe.
Miss Mira saved me earlier,
so it's my turn to save her!
Whew, I'm full!
The Demon Defense Force again?
I just consumed Mira,
so I don't have room for seconds.
Love beam!
Wanna know and wanna do, wanna touch
These feelings pouring out of me just won't stop
Sweet, so sweet, let me in with your body darling
I'll domesticate you, time for a reward
With the heat from skin on skin overlapping
It's fully charged
Now ready to launch!
Shoot from my hand now, love love beam
Aim for your heart now, love love beam
Bridging the gap between us
And firing from point blank
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
You won't escape my love love beam
To the ends of the Earth, love love beam
Yeah, love is what changes the world
Dye it all heart-colored, even the darkness
Yokohama Showdown
Episode 10
Next time, Episode 10:
"Yokohama Showdown"!
And this is today's bonus!
Allow me to explain.
Kuusetsu is using her ability
that secretes a mucus to heal wounds.
That's all that's happening.
You hear me?