You were invited, as well?
Well, I'm technically a distant
relative of the royal family,
so I'm often invited to
these kinds of events.
Even though he acts a bit like a playboy,
he's surprisingly well-mannered.
So he's actually of royal blood...
Yet he's being treated
like a mere retainer.
I mean, the chances of me inheriting
the throne are practically zero.
So, please, no need to be formal with me.
Seichiro?
My, I hardly recognized you.
Prime Minister Karvada.
ISEKAI OFFICE WORKER: THE OTHER WORLD'S
BOOKS DEPEND ON THE BEAN COUNTER
EPISODE 5: I WENT ON AN EXPEDITION
We were able to expedite the expedition
considerably because of you. Thank you.
No, Your Excellency and the
other high-ranking officials
are the ones who worked hard
to truly make it happen.
Let's just leave it at that, then.
By the way, you look quite well today.
That outfit also suits you nicely.
Thank you very much.
A colleague of mine prepared
everything for me.
As for my complexion, well, I've learned
some of the struggles women face.
I was forced into attending
this obnoxious gathering,
but I don't intend to waste this time.
Um, Prime Minister Karvada,
there's something I'd like to ask you...
Hmm?
Oh! Prime Minister Karvada!
Purple is the color of the
royal sorcery department.
Director Zoltan, I thank you for your fine
work on the recent summoning spell.
Oh, stop.
Granted, it was indeed a large-scale spell
that wouldn't have been possible
without the royal sorcery department.
We've even been asked to participate
in the purification expedition!
More than the third royal order
that relies solely on brute force,
it's clear the kingdom is in need of my
department for its knowledge and ideas.
Sounds like they see the third
royal order as their rival.
Let me introduce you.
This is Seichiro Kondu, assistant director
of the royal accounting department.
He is a highly capable individual who
worked hard to hasten the expedition.
Oh, the holy maiden's...
This saves me some trouble.
A proud noble like him
should be easy to handle.
P-Please excuse me for a moment!
What are you doing?!
Greet His Excellency!
But I haven't left my research
laboratory in ten days. I'm starving.
This is His Excellency
Prime Minister Karvada
and Assistant Director Kondu
from accounting.
Accounting?!
Please give us money!
No.
What's wrong with you?!
You only just met the man!
Introduce yourself first!
Oh... Okay.
Don't wipe your mouth with your sleeve!
I'm Ist, the assistant director
of the royal sorcery department.
Um... Kondu, you're from the
accounting department, correct?
The royal sorcery department
needs a lot of funding,
but we don't get much,
and we're very poor.
So give us money.
Ouch!
It seems Zoltan is focused
on politics as director,
while Ist is a royal sorcerer
focused on practical matters.
Ow, ow, ow...
We can't increase your
budget for no reason.
However, I could take things into
consideration if you grant my request.
What do you say?
Commander Indolark...
Aresh-sama, that hurts.
Aresh-san!
Oh?
The holy maiden?
Your Holiness. I was informed
you'd be entering with His Highness.
Oh, I-I'm sorry, Camile-san!
I couldn't help chasing after Aresh-san.
He was supposed to enter with us.
Well, no matter.
You should return before
it causes a commotion.
I'm sorry. Aresh-san, let's go back.
This event is about Your Holiness
and the royal family.
You've no need of me.
Huh?
Your Holiness, allow me to attend you.
What's with your face?
I don't understand what you mean.
I mean your face. And those clothes...
Where did you get them?
Someone from my department
lent them to me.
As for my face, his household maids
painted me with all sorts of things.
It's makeup that's low in magicules,
so it shouldn't be a problem.
What's gotten into you?!
Don't do your hair in ways
that make me uneasy!
They put so much effort
into it and everything!
Whatever. I should get
away from this guy...
The king made his entrance,
expressed concern over the miasma
from the demon forest,
and extolled the sacred ritual
that summoned the holy maiden.
Then the holy maiden herself entered,
escorted by the firstborn prince.
Though she sounded a bit hesitant,
she said she wished to do her
best for everyone in the kingdom.
I will now announce the
participants of this expedition.
First, I shall be leading the operation.
So the firstborn prince will be in charge?
I'm sure that'll cause no end of trouble.
Isn't this far more operatives
than we anticipated?
We'll have to revise the budget...
What?!
Why?
Seichiro! I didn't know you
were joining the expedition.
Will you be all right?
I'm joining the purification expedition?
This is unthinkable for you.
I'll speak to His Majesty on your behalf.
Even the frail Yua is going.
Yet a grown man like you
wants to run away?
It has nothing to do with age or gender.
Unlike the holy maiden,
he has no resistance to magicules.
Going somewhere with a high concentration
of miasma is too dangerous!
It's absurd that the one who pushed
for such a perilous expedition
gets to stay in the palace,
comfortable and safe.
He should go himself.
Unlike other people, the risks of the
demon forest are too great for him!
Your Highness, I have to agree.
For him to go to the demon forest
is tantamount to suicide.
The prince refuses to listen.
He must really hate the fact
that I rushed the expedition.
Are you joining the expedition, Kondu?
My participation wasn't part of the plan.
That's why I wanted to connect
with Ist and ask a favor, but...
I can't deny it would be most efficient
for me to see the situation for myself.
Yes, I'll go.
The expedition is set
to depart in three days.
The journey there and back will take six.
In the precious time we
have before we leave...
I told Nor I wanted to visit his home.
To thank everyone for the clothes
and makeup they provided, of course,
but I also had another purpose.
Which is why I wanted to speak with Nor's
adoptive rather than biological father.
Nor happily made all the arrangements,
so I think everything's gone well.
Since the banquet,
I've been busy delegating
my work to the right people
and preparing budget proposals.
All because...
Seiichirou, let's go.
...of the commander, who drags me
to the cafeteria every lunch break
and picks me up right
when my work day ends.
My only saving graces are the facts
that I bring my work home and that
I can secretly drink nutritional tonics,
because I recover each time
he casts the barrier spell on me.
Sei-san, the journey is about an hour
each way, so let's go home tomorrow.
Tomorrow? But my work...
It's my family that has
to arrange for the carriage.
Fine...
All right!
We have tomorrow off
for expedition preparations.
I'll be able to finish the work I brought
home when I get back tomorrow.
Where were you?
I was out on personal business.
Personal business?
Right before the expedition?
I heard you went out with a
man from your department.
So he's asking even though
he knows the answer.
He helped me prepare for
the banquet a few days ago,
so I visited his home to thank his family.
Then what's this?
You're already going somewhere
dangerous in such fragile condition,
and you're still working without rest?!
Oh.
Do you still feel hot?
No. I'm fine now, so may I return to work?
Absolutely not.
I want to make sure everything's
in order for the expedition.
If you want everything in order,
you should put your own health first.
You need to be more conscious
of your own weakness.
I'm well aware.
If it weren't for him,
I'd die just from breathing.
Even a minor scratch would be fatal.
I also know that our present relationship
is strange, even for this world...
Besides, I've already prepared expense
summaries for the second and third orders.
Huh?
What's with that face?
I don't have them on me.
I'll give them to you tomorrow,
so do your work then.
I came here to reinforce the
barrier spell before we sortie.
Oh...
I was waiting for you to bring it up,
but I didn't expect you to go
on a long two-day trip,
then lock yourself in your room
to work the day before.
I... do apologize for the trouble.
You and I will depart from here tomorrow.
What? You aren't going home?
No, I'm not.
He's planning on making
sure I don't work!
Home, huh?
Commander... Aresh-sama,
do you have any siblings?
I have two older brothers
and an older sister.
So the unruly, handsome
commander is the youngest child.
Totally expected.
That hurts.
This hurts? Really?
Do you all still live at home?
No, my older sister has already
married and left the house.
My second-eldest brother
also lives at his own manor.
It makes sense for the eldest
to stay and inherit the estate,
but why's this guy still there, too?
I have a room in the knights' barracks,
but my family home
is closer to the palace.
It's less of a pain,
so I basically live there.
Group living doesn't suit the
young master, does it, huh?
That hurts.
What about you?
I'm an only child.
I expected as much.
Given the situation, maybe it
would be better if I'd had a sibling.
I was so busy with work that I rarely
went home for Obon or New Year's.
Back in my world,
with their only son missing,
what's going through my parents' minds?
How are they spending their days?
If possible, I hope they take it easy,
expecting I'll come back eventually.
It's just me...
I'm the only one.
If I can't return to my own world,
I won't be able to take care
of them in their old age.
If it comes to that,
I hope they'll get all the assets
I left behind without any fuss.
No matter how many times I hear it,
it sounds like singing.
Like a lullaby...
The carriage I'll be riding is...
Seiichirou.
You're over here.
Come again?
Um, Aresh? The tagalong—
I mean, civil official
is riding horseback?
You already know he has
no resistance to magicules.
He'll die if not constantly monitored.
I'll take care of him.
Then what was the point of casting that
barrier so thoroughly on me last night?!
I wanted to chat with the royal
sorcerers while we were traveling...
Aren't those clothes from Aresh's place?!
Commander Indolark,
I've never ridden a horse before.
Due to my frail constitution,
I don't think I could take
a long journey this way.
Stop making that unhappy face just
because I called you by your title.
Not a problem.
I'll continually heal you as we go.
So he'll cast barrier
and healing spells on me
while staying close and familiarizing
me with his magical energy.
Wait, is he serious?
Hold on tight.
Is it okay for two grown men
to ride this horse together?
Not a problem.
Diana can outrun any horse,
even when I'm fully armored
with a sword and shield in hand.
Did a clerk from the royal
order prepare this?
No, I put it together.
Huh?
What's with that reaction?
Is there something wrong with it?
No, it's a very clear and
well-organized document.
What do you mean by "costs of repair
and complete replacement of parts" here?
Oh, that's...
This is my chance to learn about the
accounting methods of the royal order.
Anything to make my work easier
is always a good thing.
I finally have some time to myself.
I have to use it wisely.
Ouch...
First, I need to speak with Ist-san...
Kondou-san!
Nothing ever goes according to plan.
Kondu?
May I have a moment of your time?
The director told me I should
try to avoid talking to you.
Not the kind of thing you
should repeat to my face.
I wanted to discuss a way to increase
funding for the royal sorcery department,
as I mentioned at the banquet.
Come right in!
He's fundamentally the honest type
who stays true to his desires.
This is common among those whose
hobbies become their line of work.
If you know their goals, it's easy to
work with them on a professional level.
Then there's the difficult type...
Um...
Tomorrow, please switch places with me!
Isn't it a bodyguard's job to
discourage this kind of behavior?
Hey!
Is that a no?
Shiraishi-san, do you understand
the purpose of this expedition?
Huh?
Of course I do.
Aren't we going in order
to purify the miasma?
That's right.
And you are the precious holy maiden,
the only one who can purify that miasma.
That's why you're in the same carriage
that the royal family uses,
and why the knights are providing
you with full protection.
Whereas I am the person most susceptible
to the miasma in this world.
Um, is that because you have
no resistance to magicules?
That's right.
To put it in our world's terms,
just breathing the outside air weakens me.
Yet here I'm going
somewhere filled with gas
that would sicken even normal people.
I will most certainly die.
What? No way...
Indeed, I will die. Guaranteed.
I've already nearly died twice
since coming to this world.
I'm sure you meant nothing
by your request,
but you're increasing
the workload of those
tasked to protect you and
asking me to risk my life.
No!
I didn't mean it like that!
Shiraishi-san.
You should start considering
things seriously.
This isn't a world where you
can just blindly do as you're told
and expect to live peacefully ever after.
After all, I plan to ruin her
brilliant future as a holy maiden.
I heard you said something
to the holy maiden.
Where did you get that information?
From the holy maiden's bodyguard.
I shut him up so that
His Highness won't find out.
I'm most grateful for that.
She was visibly down
during the dinner party.
I'm almost certain it was because of me.
But the fact that she came and
didn't stay holed up in her room
means she must have given
some thought to what I said.
If the holy maiden had skipped the lord's
dinner party while staying at his estate,
it would have been a great insult to him.
The firstborn prince, as expected,
covered for her by saying she
was tired from her journey
as he thanked the lord
for his hospitality.
I took him for the first to be blinded
by infatuation with her,
but I need to revise my opinion on him.
I thought you had no interest
in the holy maiden.
How could I have no interest in her?
I see.
Aresh-sama...
Isn't it about time you
return to your quarters?
I'll go back once you stop
working and get into bed.
You're not planning on going back?
You're not planning on sleeping?
Where did you go before dinner?
To hear reports from the civil officials
who went out to survey the area.
Before that.
I went to ask some questions for work.
Who did you visit?
He must have seen me enter Ist-san's room.
If Aresh-sama spreads the word
to the third royal order,
this is going to be a headache.
If you saw me, you should
have said something.
You completely ignore me or postpone
things with me while you're working.
I wouldn't be so rude to someone
who's saved my life...
Except, yeah,
I've totally done that. Sorry.
Oh, please! No way.
Guess he's not planning
on going back to his room.
Well, if that's what it takes to sweep it
under the rug, it's a small price to pay.
On the third day of the expedition,
we finally approached the demon forest.
Yua!
It's all right. Our formation's
just a bit disorganized.
But didn't you hear animal noises?
Everything is fine, Your Holiness.
We're close to the source of the miasma,
so the beasts have probably
grown more ferocious.
In addition to the second
royal order's elite knights,
the third royal order is here
to protect you, too.
We won't be outdone
by any ordinary creatures.
Ferocious beasts?
Is everything all right?
I mean, I can cast healing magic, so...
It's dangerous. Please refrain
from going out, Your Holiness.
Be at ease.
The royal medical bureau is also with us.
You need only to think
about the purification.
I've heard about the miasma,
but everything has been so
tranquil and everyone so kind.
There wasn't a single sign of danger.
Everyone protects me,
so I live peacefully, but...
What about Kondou-san?
I will most certainly die.
I've already nearly died twice
since coming to this world.
This isn't a world where you
can just blindly do as you're told
and expect to live peacefully ever after.
Kondou-san!
Looks like that's the last of them.
They don't normally attack
humans holding weapons.
They've grown weaker, too.
I agree.
This is the entrance to the demon forest.
We will proceed on foot from this point.
The civil officials are to wait here.
You stay here, too.
Hold it.
He's coming with us.
Looks like he wants to drag me
into danger, no matter what.
Your Highness, with all due respect,
civil officials will only be
a hindrance from here on out.
Even if I stay here,
it'll probably be all right since
I already made a personal request...
Ist-san.
Do you remember what I asked you to do?
What was it again?
I'll go, as well.
EPISODE 6
I MADE A PROPOSAL