Cyber out!
Onipien
Demon Sadface
Is that the best you can do...
Soji Enishiro?
Not a scratch?
What just happened?
How does he know my name?
Why did he show up here?
Is it because we have the same ability?
I don't give a shit!
C'mon, body... Move!
You...
You killed Akari.
Do you mean Akari@Hospital?
That was so sad.
After all the work I did to kill her,
you made it so her death was in vain.
Move!
Just move already!
You have to move!
I'm gonna kill you!
That's a tie to this world.
I'm just mouthing off.
It doesn't matter if I can't
muster up the strength.
If you have ties to this world,
you'll be reborn after you die.
Damn it.
Damn it!
A gust of wind? Inside the building?!
Who are you?
Just an exorcist.
Or rather...
a teacher.
His teacher, to be precise.
Azaki-sensei!
I see. A teacher.
Soji Enishiro's teacher.
Kasubata-kun, Urusugawa-kun!
That was fast.
Kasubata! Urusugawa!
Don't worry. They're not dead.
You mean it?!
They just took a dose
of miasma, same as you.
Keep calling to them.
Kasubata! Hey!
Uh, look alive, you piece of shit!
Jackass!
Don't...
Don't?
Don't use... such vulgar language.
Urusugawa!
Don't stare.
Th-Thank goodness.
I'm sorry, you guys!
Those ladies wouldn't let me go!
And you even ran into a mid-level?!
I feel so worthless!
Doing karaoke with those ladies
while my students were in danger...
Hey, Sensei! The enemy's still here!
K is—
That's an EMP pseudo-barrier.
A barrier?
An electromagnetic pulse emitter
created by the laboratory division.
It will block out electronic entities
for three minutes.
But it breaks if a physical
object passes through.
Not following in the slightest.
Dumbass.
Let's just say it's a mini-barrier that
keeps ghost accounts and their powers out.
Stay put, you three.
So sad.
You did a good job, Enishiro-kun.
But I failed miserably.
What matters is that you didn't break.
You kept your head high.
That means you haven't lost yet.
Leave the rest to me.
A carp?
Gallant Carp!
Gallant Carp
Can't have fire in a building,
so let's put that out.
You're his teacher.
So if I kill you...
that might make his ties
to this world even stronger.
Look out!
He's on a different level!
There we go!
He's crazy good!
What kind of cyberkinesis
does Azaki-sensei use?
That's not technically cyberkinesis.
Azaki-sensei doesn't use any.
He's just running his spirit power
through a digital converter.
The fan is a special
mechanism for doing so.
Most older exorcists with well-honed
psychokinesis do the same thing.
Folks from the analog era struggle
against digital ghost accounts.
Indeed. That's why we have the academy.
We need a new generation
of digital native exorcists.
I'm just an old man.
Azaki-sensei!
When an analog exorcist
digitizes their spirit power,
it converts to less than
ten percent of what it was.
No way!
But there's no reason to worry.
Shall we dance?
His original ability was broken,
so it's still broken in a weakened state.
Gallant Carp: Three Color Shimmer!
Gallant Carp
Three Color Shimmer
Yoimaru Azaki, the genius exorcist.
He distinguished himself as a child, and
at eighteen, he vanquished a Guen Kabaki.
Guen Kabaki?
A calamity-level youma.
Apparently it earned him the
super cringe title the Living Legend.
He's a legend? You kidding me?
But he suddenly retired from active duty.
He declined a leadership
position in the Society
and devoted himself
to training the next generation.
As much as it annoys me,
it's hard to imagine Azaki-sensei losing.
It stinks getting old.
Loath as I am to say
"things were better back when,"
my hair's thinning and smartphones
are too complicated.
Nevertheless...
I can't afford to embarrass myself
before the new generation!
He disappeared!
You beat him?
Nah.
He got away.
What are you doing, Garan-san?
Why did you pull me into the internet?
It was just getting fun.
K-sama, you told me
you were just going to say hello!
You nearly ran out of charge out there.
I completely forgot.
No wonder it was so hard to move.
That's what makes you so charming, K-sama!
How inconvenient.
As a ghost account, I can't remain
in the real world for long.
But K-sama, that problem
will be resolved very soon.
Once the land of
dead accounts is complete.
That's right. A mid-level ghost account.
Yes. And then Sad Boy K...
Yes.
Indeed, they were injured,
but they're all fine.
He was on the verge
of running out of battery.
In other words,
he was in power saver mode.
Which means he wasn't fighting
at full strength whatsoever.
You're kidding me. With all of that?!
You're saying we lost our
best chance to exorcise him.
That's frustrating.
Hey, it's no big.
After all...
You're alive!
We're all alive!
We're... alive.
Relief. A new appreciation
of how weak I am.
Self-recrimination. Admiration.
Let's get him next time!
I have a new goal.
I want to be like you.
Hey, don't try to be like me!
I'm an old man! An anachronism!
I wanna be like you, Sensei!
Let's go home.
Back to our classroom.
Sad Boy K
Follow
Crested fifty thousand...
K is gaining more followers again.
Over three thousand in five days.
Almost like a cult leader.
Tell me about your troubles.
Using Tweeter since August 2016
Following
Followers
A 100% follow-back ratio, but 10% are
dead, and 1% become ghost accounts.
Sad Boy K
So, why the rise?
"If you follow this account, you die."
People treat it like a
thrilling urban legend.
It'd be nice if the admins
could ban it, yes...
What's he need all those follows for?
I guess he's sad and lonely,
like his handle says.
People these days struggle with a lot.
Birds of a feather, then, eh?
It's frustrating.
These things wouldn't be happening
if not for the plague of social media!
I feel we've gotten
off topic a bit, yes...
Silence.
Miden Academy
Staff Footbath Conference
Azaki. Why did Sad Boy K appear
on a first-floor student mission?
Kyuko Yabami\h\h(65)
Miden Academy Principal
Er, before that, Madam Principal...
My feet are getting pruny. Can I get out?
Only those who are bathing may speak!
Hey, your wrinkles
come out when you're mad!
It really ruins all that anti-aging
you do in the nurse's office!
Madam!
You look as beautiful as ever, Madam Principal!
H-He's so flippant,
even with the principal.
That's Yoimaru Azaki for you.
My feet are also feeling tingly, so I'd
like to get this conference over with.
Mr. Azaki, why did K appear?
Because of Soji Enishiro-kun, I'm sure.
K knew that they share the same ability.
Furthermore...
If you have ties to this world,
you'll be reborn after you die.
I think he wants to kill Enishiro-kun
and turn him into a ghost account.
To what end?
He wants our student on his side?
What a ridiculous plan.
If he's the prize K is after,
we can't simply leave him for the taking.
We should kill Soji Enishiro after all!
Let us exorcise his spirit
and burn the body.
A full-purge ritual?
We'll want to cover all our bases.
Nanzo-kun...
Haven't we been through this?
Call me "sensei," Azaki-sensei.
It's not like the old days.
We're on even footing now.
Nanzo-sensei!
He's in my class now.
You need to leave him to me.
I'm feeling pretty annoyed right now.
Intelligence division chief.
Yes?
You knew there was a mid-level
in that building, didn't you?
Y-You make it sound like I set them up.
P-Please stop throwing around
such awful accusations!
I-I do apologize for giving you
incorrect information, though, yes...
I've determined Enishiro-kun's flames
to be harmless to humans.
And the fact that he was nearly killed
proves he's not a spy.
If you try to execute him now,
it's murder, plain and simple.
But...
Azaki is right.
Now that we've acknowledged him,
he is a student to be protected.
But Nanzo has a point as well.
We don't know what K is planning.
Should the situation spiral
past the point of no return...
Azaki, what will you do then?
If that comes to pass...
Hey, Kasubata!
Azaki-sensei's pretty cool, isn't he?
I'm already sick of hearing about it.
B-But...
It got my blood racing!
What he did... He's in a different league!
I feel like my whole body's going brr!
The vocabulary of a fool.
But I know what you mean.
The infamous demon flame-user beat
a mid-level account on his first mission.
Piques your interest, eh?
Title: "The Soldiers' Return."
No, not up to my standard.
Kasubata-kun's all beat-up. Poor baby!
I wish I could go make him feel batter.
K-Kusaba-chan!
He's beat-up because he
got his butt kicked!
He also let K get away!
Don't you think that's lame?
What are you talking about, Owada-kun?
He fought a mid-level!
And after running into K, it's just
amazing that he made it back alive!
Owada, I wanna pee.
Then hit the bathroom.
The glint in his eyes kinda ticks me off.
What about you, Minoru?
Needless to say, we could have
beaten it... thoroughly.
Soon, we'll show them all
which is the truly superior class.
Nurse's
Office
Comin' in!
We're here to get patched up!
Hey, you need to knock!
Urusugawa?!
Wh-What the?!
You got the crap kicked out of you,
but your skin looks brand-new!
I figured you'd be in for a hospital stay!
Knock it off!
Quit staring at a lady's skin!
Beg pardon.
We'll come back later.
Hang on.
You are Urusugawa, right?
Don't stare at my lack of makeup either!
What's this? You guys're really
beating down my door, huh?
Kids these days totally
fight way too much!
I'm Mina-chan, the nurse!
Mina Kochi
Peace! Peace!
A gyaru doctor?!
Gyaru
Doctor
G-Good to meet you.
It's actually our second meeting,
Enishiro-kun.
Though you were unconscious last time.
How about a demonstration?
Sweep your hair up and look here.
Um...
Taking now!
Three, two, one!
Awesome selfie face!
This is ticking me off.
All righty! Let's get to work!
Cyber out!
Photo Touch-Up
Photo Touch-Up!
Apply
Th-That's awesome!
Cyberkinesis can do stuff like this, too?!
That must be why I wasn't the worse
for wear when I first got here!
I also touched Urusugawa-chan up,
so I'm almost out of battery.
It uses a lot of spirit power, huh?
I also help the principal with
her anti-aging treatments.
She's been coming all the time lately!
Though I had to cancel her
appointment for today.
We're closed for business.
So your cyberkinesis is touch-ups?
Yeah! So I can't heal
internal stuff like diseases.
But Urusugawa...
Didn't she have a broken arm?
Wanna know how I did it?
D-Do you have another
amazing ability up your sleeve?!
I called an anesthesiologist, cut open
the arm, and exposed the broken bone.
Then after touching up the bone,
I touched up the incision and closed it up.
That's kinda gross!
Mina-chan-sensei, thanks so much!
You're the best!
I'll patch you up as long as it matters.
Since it hurts to do when it doesn't.
That's right.
Then with me...
Did you strip me and take
a picture of my whole body?!
It was for medical purposes!
Strictly for medical purposes!
I'm a professional!
And don't worry! I deleted the photos.
Kochi-sensei, you could act
more like a professional.
Come on, Kasubata-kun!
I'm a total pro, aren't I?!
In what way, exactly?
Okay. Now then...
Hey, you three!
Welcome back!
Sounds like you went through the wringer.
But you beat a mid-level! That's amazing!
Hey! Unless you're sick,
out of the nurse's office!
Darn! I missed Mina-nee and
Kiyomin's sapphic healing session!
Hey, Enishiro.
I heard your flames don't work on humans!
Silly me, being so scared.
Don't get too cocky, now.
I've been doing this longer, so—
Hey, don't get angry! I'm the one
who got cocky! I'm sorry!
I get it. You're crazy, too.
Everyone at this school
is totally abnormal!
I'm the only normal one here, damn it!
Where do you three think you're going?
Training. I don't want to waste a moment.
Not that I feel any obligation
to this exorcism gig...
But it pisses me off
how bad I got beat up!
I'm gonna exorcise that creep.
I'll show him just how clingy I can be!
He was right in front of me.
Right in front of me, yet...
I never want to feel that way again!
Ah, the fire of youth!
You love to see it, but...
Pull out your channeling devices.
When you output your cyberkinesis,
your smartphone's battery
reflects your remaining spirit power.
If you went to train now, you'd run out
right away and KO yourself.
Rest is part of training. Okay?
She's right. I can't be hasty now.
Rest is part of training.
Even if I can't train my cyberkinesis,
I can train my muscles!
Are you kidding me?
They almost died out there!
They did seem a little nuts back there.
Let me in there!
I'm gonna get a picture!
You gotta put your back into this stuff!
If that comes to pass...
I'll kill him myself.
But that won't happen.
This school needs Enishiro-kun.
And so does class 1-B.
See? Told you so.
They're all going to get stronger.