We're back!
Huh? Stude?
Ma'am?
Miss?
Could it be...
What's up?
Sara!
Okay.
Stude?!
Why?
Milkit!
Huh?
Flum's mind was consumed by an unquellable
rage toward the evil before her.
But it was not out of a sense of morality.
What, you came back?
I was told you wouldn't!
Why, you!
CAMARADERIE
CRUELTY
CRUELTY AND CAMARADERIE
Wait, miss!
Stude and his mother are alive!
They'll be fine. I healed 'em with magic.
There're better ways to punish that guy!
Miss!
Heh, gotcha.
Like I said the other day, Sara...
C'mon, you think you have time to chat?
One little flick from me,
and you'll bleed to death.
Some pieces of trash never learn
their lesson and are better off dead.
You're the piece of trash,
you stupid slave.
Let me hear you beg for your life.
Wh... Why ain't that killing you?
D-Don't. Please don't.
Wait, miss!
No, please! Don't do—
Hearing you beg for your life felt good.
Forgive me, Sara.
But I think I did the right thing,
even if nobody else does.
Real bad guys don't learn
even when they're punished.
The right... thing?
Disgusting.
I'm so glad you're okay.
I'm so sorry I ruined the clothes
you bought for me, Master.
You don't have to apologize for that.
But I do.
It was the very first thing
you gave me. It was important.
So I apologize, Master.
Even then, why worry about clothes now?
There's something much,
much more important!
Are you... crying?
I am, because I feel terrible.
Mast—
Why won't you scold me
for not coming to save you sooner?
Come on, snap at me!
She knew it was impossible, but she wanted
to hear something other than an apology.
A slave has no right to expect
her master to come to her aid.
You do have the right!
I want you to expect all that
and more from me!
Lean on me more!
I'll do everything I can
to grant all your desires!
For a moment, I did picture you
coming to save me.
But that's... not acceptable.
That's fine!
We're not slave and master!
We're Milkit and Flum!
That's how we ought to be!
I'm going to pamper you to death and
make you the happiest girl in the world!
What did it mean for someone
to shed tears for her?
What did it mean to want
to make somebody happy?
It was all so new to Milkit that
she struggled to find the answers.
What?
You want a burial?
For those scoundrels?
I'm all for being compassionate, but
I think prayer is wasted on the wicked.
Miss, I spent all night thinkin'
about it, but I still don't get it.
I'm not much of a thinker, see?
So I dunno what makes one truly evil,
or the right way to deal with 'em.
I just don't get it at all.
I don't think there's
anything wrong with that.
But you got hurt because of me!
Introspection is the privilege
of the young!
Pfft.
What's with that?
We're only six years apart!
Six years is a long time at our age.
Be a good girl and listen to me...
or else I'll tickle you good!
Huh? Wait!
That tickles!
Okay. Cyrill, get us back to the capital.
Right.
Only you, with your Hero affinity, can use
magic to return us to our saved location.
Get your act together, Cyrill.
I'm sorry, Jean.
You think an apology's going to cut it?
Stop.
Damn it.
Damn it all!
I got rid of the distraction!
So why is this happening?
Cyrill, please.
Return.
We depart again in two days' time.
Get your supplies in order by then.
Once again, we failed
to reach our destination.
No surprise, given how
Jean and Cyrill were.
I wish Cyrill would act in a manner
more befitting the hero.
We have been tasked with the noble
duty of exterminating the demons.
We must see it to fruition at all costs.
Is something the matter?
Oh, I was just wondering
if we could even pull it off.
We have fewer members now.
There is no point thinking
about those who left us.
No point, eh? The Church
isn't going after them either.
Speaking of, I couldn't believe
my eyes when I first saw Flum's stats.
Made me realize even a god
can make mistakes.
They don't make mistakes.
Not Lord Origin.
If that wasn't a mistake,
it'd mean Flum had some necessary role
to play in our party.
What do you think it was?
I couldn't say. That's something
Lord Origin only knows.
Did your investigation of the lab
yield anything, Neigass?
You were right, Sheitoom.
It was an old facility.
I found papers from thirty years ago.
I also found a beast with one
of those cores embedded in it.
Are those guys trying to start
something again?
It's not a power that can be controlled.
Where in the world is it leaking from?
Maybe the seal's weakening, Demon Lord.
Not one thing has changed
in my time as the medium.
Also, I keep telling you
to stop calling me that, Brother.
Pah!
You guys put this Demon Chief label on me,
so I'm just playing my part here.
But, Tsyon, I get the feeling
you like being called that.
You were all, "Entertain us three
Demon Chiefs" just the other day!
Shut yer trap, Neigass!
Is this true, Brother?
Dinner is served.
NAME: HUGE GOAT SAUTÉ WITH MUSHROOM SAUCE
Tonight, we have a huge
goat sauté with mushroom sauce.
I'm sure the heroes' party
has no idea that we Demon Chiefs...
are just a bunch of childhood friends.
Tsyon.
Neigass.
Dhiza.
I simply put together the most capable
team I knew, and this was the result.
And in fact, you are doing a great job.
"A great job"? I can't say
I'm too fond of destroying towns.
But it has to be done.
We want the humans to realize
that we don't want war.
Humans... I don't want to fight them,
but I always thought we could
never understand each other.
Why'd you suddenly clam up?
It's nothing. Anyway, look at this.
What's with the flower?
Huh? Oh, no, forget about that!
How? Even my heat did nothing to those!
Who cracked it?
Flummy.
No way!
Flum? How'd that useless girl
with all zeroes for stats pull this off?
I don't know. But she seems
to have a rather unusual power.
Reversal.
I would surmise she reversed
the spiral created by Origin.
Dhiza.
NAME: RICH ICE CREAM WITH YAK BUTTER
Here's your dessert.
We got our hands on some good
yak butter, so it's rich and creamy.
Reversal, huh?
Could that be why she was chosen
to join the heroes' party?
But she's just a simple country girl.
I don't think she would ever have realized
what her power was if she wasn't chosen.
Maybe it had a reason to risk
keeping its natural enemy close.
As always, I can never tell what
it's thinking. Any of them, really.
Either way, we mustn't
let the Reversal girl
or the heroes' party near the seal.
Or the world's peace
will come under threat.
That's Shoppe Mancathy's owner for you!
Why don't you sit down
and have some tea too?
The aroma and flavor are both really good.
No, I'll pass.
Oh, okay.
Is she mad about my outburst
the other night?
Sorry to keep you waiting,
Miss Flum and Miss Milkit.
Please be seated.
Oh? Where's Miss Sara?
I bet Mr. Leitch is gonna try
and give me some kinda reward.
But I'm a nun. I can't accept that stuff.
She returned to the church,
saying she had work to do.
Is that so? Too bad.
Anyway, here. Kialahri flowers.
Thank you so much.
I'll have them processed right away.
Flum Apricot?
Hey.
I didn't expect to run into a member
of the heroes' party here.
Welcy!
Sorry about my little sister.
How does she know about me?
She's a newspaper reporter.
I saw you while covering
the heroes' party.
It's an honor to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
So the rumors were true.
Pardon me.
I had a feeling.
So you really are the famous Flum Apricot.
My brother caught me up to speed.
Thank you for going to gather
herbs for my sister-in-law.
Don't mention it.
But everybody says the Church has eyes
on all the places with medicinal plants.
Did you see anything at all?
No.
Nothing in particular.
I'm actually investigating the people
providing herbs to the Church.
But doesn't the Church
prohibit herbal medicine?
On the contrary,
they're trying to monopolize it.
But for what purpose?
Let me know if you ever find any leads.
Why me?
If we can track down the dealers
providing them with herbs,
we can go from there and reveal
the Church's dark side.
Stop it. Don't be a bother.
Mr. Leitch.
Really? Thank you.
What's this?
Burn Projection.
I can leave paper records of
everything I see with my eyes.
I'M WAITING FOR YOUR LEADS <3
-WELCY MANCATHY
The reporter who clips
facts from this world,
Welcy Mancathy, needs you!
Sorry. She's always like that.
Miss Flum.
Yes?
We've confirmed
that it is indeed kialahri.
You've saved my wife's life.
Thank you so, so much!
How would you like me to repay you?
I appreciate the thought, but it's fine.
That won't sit right with me!
Please name one thing you desire.
Anything. I'll make sure you have it.
E-Er... There is one thing.
I'd like a place in the West District
to use as a base.
We're here.
Thank you.
I'll take my leave now, Miss Flum.
This is the right address...
But this is a whole-ass house!
I don't see the problem.
You always put yourself
in danger for others.
You deserve this.
He said it hadn't been used in ages,
so it's probably full of cobwebs.
Huh?
It's actually pretty clean.
No dust, either.
What a huge room.
What? There's a flower bed in the yard.
All the dishware you'd need is present.
It's almost like
somebody's been living here.
The flowers have been watered, too.
Something's fishy.
Let's investigate.
Right.
Nobody here,
here,
or here!
That leaves the second floor.
What was that noise?
A small animal or rodent, maybe?
Wouldn't it be noisier, then?
I'll go take a look.
You stay here, Master.
Hang on.
I'll go.
You wait here.
Okay.
As you wish.
I'll wait for you here, Master.
Right!
That won't do.
Someone really is here.
Ugh, this reeks.
It tastes awful, but no nutrients
have been lost.
Huh? I know that voice.
Hmm? Is somebody there?
Eterna?
It's Flum.
I thought you went back to your village.
Wait, why?!
Who did this to you?!
"Who"?
Jean, obviously.
This is what you deserve.
That vain, bratty, weak, virgin mage!
You didn't know?
We would've all put a stop
to it if we had!
I'm... I'm so glad.
I'm so glad I got to hear that...
We should never have
believed what Jean said.
I'm sorry, Flum.
It brought Milkit into my life,
so it wasn't all bad.
Is that her?
Yeah.
That face... Is it mustardo toxin?
Trust Eterna to know.
You can tell even with the bandages, huh?
It's one of the most obvious
toxins out there.
I have a favor to ask of you, Eterna.
Please make an antidote.
I gave her the antidote ingredients
I found during the kialahri search.
It'll take about three hours.
You can trust Eterna.
It'll take a while for the toxin
to clear up, but you'll get better.
But...
Even if the toxin does go away,
I'll still be an filthy, ugly being.
Your face isn't the only thing
that's ugly about you.
It's oozing out from within—
from every inch of you.
You filthy, ugly creature.
I'm a filthy, ugly creature.
Do you really think my feelings
for you are that shallow?
They're not.
No matter what,
I'll always be here for you.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
AN ORDINARY LIFE