My name before the Great
Cataclysm was Sugita Sumire.
In 20XX, 250 years ago,
I already served the one meant to bring
about the Great Cataclysm, the Evangelist.
At last, it begins.
The Great Cataclysm is imminent.
The rules of the world
will be remade once more.
This planet has experienced the Great
Cataclysm over and over countless times.
As a result, humans are born,
and humanity's collective unconscious
has come to hold one single desire:
the endpoint of the evolution
of life and of this planet.
In other words, a desire for death.
The furthest extremity of the
evolution of life... is extinction.
The planet will transform into a sun.
The driving force behind the final Great
Cataclysm that will destroy everything...
is despair.
There is no such thing as a
human with independent thought.
Sometimes, it's their country that
carries them along, or a religion.
People these days believe things from TV
or the internet as if it was a religion.
They worship the collective
unconsciousnesses on social media.
They do not think. They just get
swept up in rumors and fads.
Their personal identities
have never been established.
Keep Your Distance!
Well, shall we go?
Once glance at social media
and they're swept up
in some fad with no
substance, the whole mob.
The way they swarm toward the latest
craze... They're like insects.
Every time I look at a smartphone
screen, there they are.
There are the insects.
This one is an idiot.
This one is an idiot, too.
So is this one. And this one.
And this one and this one.
If the number of brainless, imbecilic
insects has grown to this extent,
then our preparations are flawless.
For the World-Builders, there is an
abundance of fuel with no self-awareness.
The number of Great Cataclysms left
until the destruction of humanity...
is two.
Now, let's begin.
The great waypoint on
the path to extinction.
With this Great Cataclysm,
the world will surely become one of
flames and spontaneous human combustion.
Give me a situation report!
A disaster of incalculable scale
has the whole empire in chaos.
As for the situation... I can only
say that it is as you see it.
Captain Hague said
that we, as fire soldiers, are powerless.
In this moment, what should the 4th do?
Captain Pan!
There's a transmission from
the 8th to all companies!
Connect us at once!
This is the captain of Special
Fire Force Company 8, Akitaru Obi.
What I am about to relay sounds
nonsensical, but please believe me.
It's how we stop the Great Cataclysm.
The flames that are burning this planet
are using people's despair as fuel.
To extinguish them, our only option is
to negate that despair
and give the people hope.
Now is the moment when we must show
the people that we are fire soldiers.
We have to show them
that there is still hope.
Do not abandon hope!
All companies, keep
fighting and good luck.
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Episode 20
Where Hope Is
Evacuation of civilians to
inside the barricade complete!
Good work, Karin!
We will help the citizens
and give them hope!
We must not let ourselves be disheartened!
We will support the army, too!
We'll be shorthanded with
the Fire Force alone!
Captain Honda!
All companies are continuing relief
efforts with everything they've got.
And we are going to head
into the urban areas
under large-scale attack
for relief and rescue!
Yes, sir!
Arthur, what are you doing? Let's go!
No, I have somewhere to go.
As Knight King, I must
settle things with him.
Dragon.
Where? Can you get there alone?
This holy sword you forged
for me will show the way.
I don't remember adding a feature like
that, but the way you are right now...
All right. I'll tell the captain.
You can win, right?
I swear it on this sword!
The school up ahead is a shelter.
What's your name?
Huh? Um, Tatsuto.
Tatsuto-kun.
As long as we fire soldiers are
here, don't you give up hope!
What a relief.
Now we'll be safe.
For the time being, we've
evacuated this whole area.
Right. I hope this can help just
a little despair turn to hope.
That's the pros for you.
The evacuation of every area has
already progressed pretty far.
In theory, if we lessen people's
despair, the flames should get smaller.
But the force of those flames
doesn't seem to be dropping.
You're right.
In fact, a cruel prediction
is beginning to emerge.
There is no human in this
world who is worthless.
And as a member of the
8th, I believe that.
But in truth, in a mob, the masses
possess no sense of self-identity,
so the power they have to affect
this world—in other words,
their value—is nonexistent.
Humans with no value are simply released
to stir things up and start fires.
Saving a faceless mob of humans
who don't know how the world
works and only make a fuss
may be a pointless act.
In every era, there are those who
have a fully realized self-identity,
and it is that small handful of
World-Builders who construct everything.
World-Builders
Joker?
Seriously, it's just one bad thing
after another happening here.
They're here.
Those who will guide
this world into despair.
The doppelgangers of
powerful World-Builders?
Apparently so. I'll go and look into it.
All right. I'm counting on you, Dark Hero.
Everyone, please don't worry!
Don't lose hope! We'll save you!
Tamaki, we're heading to
the next damaged area!
Right!
Now, into battle.
You're...
The Assassin of the Abyss.
The Bloody Fire Blast.
Assault.
Assault, again, you're—
Eek!
"Activated"
He didn't even twitch an eyebrow.
It can't be. That's impossible.
So you're a fake Assault...
a doppelganger!
When you put it that way, yes.
But nay!
I am not the me who would be
shaken by wanton lewdness!
Absolutely not!
This is the true form
I was meant to be: Assault!
So that's the man who kept
following Tamaki around?
But Assault was that nobody who got taken
out by Tamaki's lecher lure, right?
In the battle in the Nether, if Assault's
powers had activated properly,
he would have annihilated the 8th.
My arrows don't work against him.
If Tamaki's sensuality doesn't affect him,
then there is no one who can stop him!
Everyone, please stand back!
That explosion...
Noto, reporting from the
2nd! I've come to assist!
But why, Juggernaut?
I have permission from Captain Honda!
He said, "The 8th's shorthanded,
so go and help!"
We're grateful for the relief.
An increase of one person
poses no problem.
Come at me. I'll take you all on.
Maki and I will create an opening!
Hinawa, back us up with your sniping!
You three will follow Hinawa's attacks!
Even for Assault, if it's one-on-six
against this fighting capacity...
Let's go!
Into battle!
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Th-This can't be real!
Instantly?
You traitor.
The man over there...
You're not a member of the 8th, are you?
I'll let you go. Leave.
I can't do that!
Abandoning those precious
to me and running?
That's not what a fire soldier does!
Did you not see what just happened?
You have no chance of winning.
I know that!
In this moment, when the Great
Cataclysm is moving to end the world,
this life of mine may end at any moment,
so I don't want to have any regrets!
I will protect the one I love!
Juggernaut...
Kotatsu-san, if the world is saved...
please go on a date with me!
You die now!
Speaking of love on the battlefield?
How soft and weak can you be?
You have no right to stand
on the field of battle!
Tamaki Kotatsu, you're the only one left.
Your lewdness will not work on me.
You have no means of winning.
Shut up!
It's no use.
I commend that resilience of yours.
However...
I do not acknowledge eros!
And now a derrière attack? It won't work.
Tamaki!
What an indecent fire soldier!
What is that girl doing?
Has she no shame?
Shameless.
Could that be the only skill she has?
She's a disgrace to all women.
From this point forward, I will not allow
you to expose your bottom or your chest!
Truly problematic.
What a vulgar woman.
She can't do anything
other than flash her skin?
She's worthless.
She's a fire soldier!
Why is she just lazing around?
Why are they... Tamaki is fighting
for the sake of the people!
Mobs just get swept along. Now that it's
come this far, there's no stopping it.
Tatsuto, you mustn't look at that.
Prepare yourself, Tamaki Kotatsu!
I will kill you, and eros
will vanish with you!
Eros is necessary!
That voice...
You lost to eros. Why are you here?
The real Assault!
Because of your worldly desires,
eros has appeared again!
Assault!
Tatsuto! I told you not to look!
You're a disgrace to women!
Just disappear!
You're a bad influence on the children!
Oh. You're Haijima Senior
Researcher Yoshida-san.
And you're Licht-kun.
Is that female fire soldier a
combatant from your company?
What is all that?
What do you mean? It's just
her involuntary lewdness.
Tamaki is fighting her hardest!
You moron!
There's no such thing as "Lucky Lecher"!
She's tricking you, that's all!
What is the Lucky Lecher Lure?
It must have something to do
with her role in this world.
You're a disgrace to all women!
Up until now, I thought Soldier
Tamaki was just clumsy, but...
You're a disgrace to all women!
What a vulgar woman!
You're disgusting!
Quit your complaining.
If you hate sexy stuff that much,
then let me show you...
VOOM
the weight of eros!
How dare you dress like
that in front of children?!
You despicable whore!
Have you no shame as a woman?!
Shut up, you damned hag!
Hag?!
I have to take down the fake Assault!
Stop talking!
What was that, Licht-kun?!
Can you believe her?!
You're asking me?
Why aren't you saying anything?!
She's a stupid woman with no talent
for anything other than stripping!
Because she's young and cute,
she thinks that if she strips,
everything will work out!
So it's bad because Soldier Tamaki
is cute and has a nice body?
Exactly!
That only people with nice figures get
complimented for their looks isn't fair!
Mama, what you're saying
doesn't make sense.
What?
If that cute soldier with the nice
figure has to be considerate of others,
then doesn't everyone who's exceptional
have to be considerate of others, too?
In sports, we'd have to let people
who suck play as regulars,
and universities would have
to admit stupid people.
You're an elite researcher at Haijima.
You're smarter than other people.
You're exceptional, right?
But if someone wanted to be a researcher
and couldn't because they
weren't smart enough,
this means you'd have to give up your
spot as a researcher to them, right?
Your mama worked very hard to get smart!
That's different from someone
who was just born good-looking!
We aren't the same!
Getting smarter is a talent, too.
There are tons of people in this world
who don't even know how to study.
Since you're not one of them,
you must have been born smart.
And also...
that lady soldier's
toned body is beautiful.
What?
The beauty of that body is the result
of daily training, of diligent work.
Stop that right now, Tatsuto!
That's right. I'm Tatsuto.
Hearing the words of the captain
of the 8th earlier awakened me.
Now that I think about it, Mama...
what's your name again?
What?
Could it be that you're
someone who doesn't think
and just gets swept along
by the info you get on the spot?
[mäb]
Simply a large crowd of local people or horde of rioters.
Just part of the mob?
Licht-kun! Something's wrong with Tatsuto!
It's all that female soldier's fault!
It's because he saw that!
It's true. It's just as Tatsuto-kun says.
You and I are supposed to be colleagues,
but other than the fact that
you're Tatsuto-kun's mother,
I can't recall anything.
She vanished?
Her role was finished, so she disappeared.
Tatsuto-kun, you're...
A part of the mob who was granted a name.
I've become a World-Builder
capable of thought.
The mob is meant to cause a fuss
and burn, and nothing more.
Tamaki-san, do your best to show that
these flames can be extinguished.
Tamaki Kotatsu.
By stripping off the veneer,
you've grown even sexier.
I hate it, but when people reject me that
much, it makes me want to fight back.
Stand proud! Thanks to you,
I've awakened to eros.
Huh?
Eros is not needed!
Sensuality is not something
to be exhibited publicly!
You're saying sexual desire
should hide in the shadows?
You're saying everyone
should become a perv like me?
If there is nothing sexy, what will become
of children who know nothing of eros?
It's always bothered me.
This seemingly supernatural phenomenon
of the Lucky Lecher Lure.
Shinra-kun is a hero.
Commander Sho is an angel.
And just as Captain Obi has a role
as the light that guides everyone,
she is a symbol of life.
It's a hope that ties us to the future.
Eros is not necessary!
Sexual desire is exactly what we need!
You were defeated by eros!
What you say is no more than
an excuse for that defeat!
Assault!
It's true that there was a time when I
thought I had been overpowered by eros.
But I realized that at the same time,
I'd gained tremendous vitality.
Once, all I could do
was kill my opponents.
But through sensuality,
I became able to feel the future!
It did that much for you?
I will defeat you!
And I will protect all the
lewdness in this world!
I will not let you have your way!
I will not fold before anything but eros!
Assault...
Crimson Throbbing Bullet!
A world without eros...
has no future!
Life...
Pulsing...
Vigorous...
Vibrant...
Sexy...
What's the situation?
What?
What is happening here?
Maki! This is no time to be sleeping!
Captain...
That's it, Tamaki! Go!
The lieutenant, too?!
This is...
Tamaki! Go!
What did you two do?!
Sexual desire is hope!
It's beautiful and cool!
Why do you reject it?
Throb! Throb! Throbbing!
Bullet!
Tamaki's Lucky Lecher is destined!
It is no mere accident!
You... perv.
The atmosphere was so gloomy,
and now it's got this happy aura.
Soldier Tamaki changed it.
She's in charge of this
world's sensuality.
She's someone who can bestow hope.
Lewdness is a hope that connects
our lives to the next generation.
There can be no future for
a person who lacks eros.
Tamaki Kotatsu, I doubt
we will meet again.
Thank you...
for coming to help.
Farewell.
You were my first.
Tamaki-san, well done enduring all that.
I don't want to lose to anyone
who thinks that whatever
makes them uncomfortable
makes everyone uncomfortable.
That is the hope that you called forth.
To Be Continued
Fire Force Chapter 3
You will not despair!
Next Time
Fear not. I will defeat you!
This will stave off my boredom
until the world ends.
Give it a try, whelp!
Next time, "Dragon and Knight
Surge Toward the Heavens."
Episode 21
Dragon and Knight Surge Toward the Heavens
Return to the great flame of fire. Látom.