Boys High Jump Finals
1st Attempt
That was the first time I saw
beauty in the way someone jumps.
Mizuki!
That won't be necessary.
We're leaving, and you're coming with me.
Onii-chan!
Sano, you're...
You're still dragging
that baggage around?!
I don't care what you say or think.
You did it...
You could jump!
I could jump.
I could do it.
Hurry up.
Wanna be late for the first day
of the new term?
Hey, wait! Wait!
And as of today, I, Ashiya Mizuki,
am now a second-year student
of Osaka Private High School.
What?!
Dorm 2 is undergoing renovations?
They want us to just
"please go home for summer break"?!
This is rather sudden.
For two whole weeks?
Hey, hey.
No blocking the entrance.
Nanba-senpai!
What is this?
Exactly what it says.
Apparently, the deteriorated
water pipes need to be replaced.
Make sure you make arrangements
to go home this week.
Oh man...
All this after I made a big scene with
my brother about not going home...
Hey. Stop playing with your food.
Do I really have no choice
but to go back to the States?
Idiot, that's not your mouth.
I'm pretty sure he'd make me
stay there for the break...
Stop fooling around and eat
your food properly, dumbass.
That hurt, Sano!
I don't want to hear any complaints
before you look at your plate.
Ew, that's gross! How'd that happen?
Hey, so...
It happened because you
were flinging food around.
Look. You've got some on your mouth.
I was thinking that Sano's like...
You look like a mother cat
diligently grooming her kitten.
Yeah, I totally see it.
Who the hell are you
calling a mother cat? Seriously?
I'm done eating.
I'm going back to my room.
Guess I'll also go on and—
You stay and eat your food.
Total mother cat vibes.
Sano's changed since
you showed up, Ashiya.
Huh?
Yeah. It's like he's gotten
more cheerful or something.
He's definitely less guarded
about his emotions.
He was different before?
It's not like he was ever
hard to get along with.
He just always kept us
at arm's length, I guess?
Like he kept himself closed off.
Yeah, exactly.
It really had him and Nakatsu
butting heads at first.
I'd say that was more Nakatsu
refusing to let it go.
Right, Nakatsu?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
Either way, I feel like Sano's
vibe and aura aren't so bad now.
His aura?!
C'mon, there's nothing to overthink here.
Man up, Shuichi!
This is nothing weird between bros.
You're just inviting him to your place
if he's got nowhere to go.
That's right.
I'm inviting him to come
hang out together, eat together,
bathe together...
Not that!
Shut it.
Can we help you?
"We"?
Yeah, you sure can.
Welcome back.
Nakatsu?
What's up?
Mizuki, if you don't have anywhere to go,
wanna stay at my place?
It's in Osaka, but it's
still closer than the States.
Our house has plenty of spare rooms.
And I'm sure my mom would welcome you.
Really?
I-I couldn't.
On the off chance I get found out...
Actually, I can't put you out like that.
It's too much.
Yeah?
No problem then.
Don't even worry about it.
I just figured I'd offer.
See ya!
Thanks, Nakatsu.
Are you sure about that?
You don't have a place to stay, right?
Yeah, I guess.
In that case...
Want to come to my house?
We'd have to share a room,
but we've been doing that all along,
so you wouldn't have to worry
about being considerate, you know?
Yeah...
I mean, let me give it some thought.
I know I said that,
but I can't think of anywhere I could go.
I'm just going to go to sleep!
Hey. As a woman, shouldn't you be
a little more wary than this?
At the end of the day,
I'm a guy and you're...
Hey, get up!
Your bed is up there.
Why, you...
You want me to jump you or something?
Come on.
Because I'm a Guy!
This feels so nice and cuddly.
So warm... and snuggly...
Oh, you're up.
S-Sano! I, uh...
You sleepwalked into my bed.
I'm so sorry about that!
I wasn't wearing my binder
while I was in bed!
What do I do?
D-D-D-D-Did he figure me out?!
Sorry for invading your bed.
But we're both guys, so whatever, right?
Yeah, we're both guys,
so I don't particularly care.
R-Right?
Today's the end-of-term ceremony,
so hurry up and get ready.
Yeah, okay.
I couldn't sleep a wink...
Seriously, it's insane
how unguarded you are.
Infirmary
Doctor!
Cooking, cleaning, laundry, the works!
Chores and weekend DIY projects!
I'll do it all!
Just please let me stay at
your place for two weeks!
I'm begging you!
Nope.
Don't say that!
Listen, starting tomorrow,
I, Master Hokuto,
will be off on a passionate
vacation to a southern island.
The hot soul of the southern
lands is beckoning me!
Onii-chan!
Rio?
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be in school?
The end-of-term ceremony was today.
I haven't been able to reach you at all!
Don't you remember Io-neechan's orders
to help out at the Hayama Boarding House?
Er...
Oh, Mizuki-kun.
Uncle.
Nanba-senpai?
Huh? Ashiya?
Wait, did you just call him "uncle"?
Hey, Minami-chan.
"Minami-chan"?
Hey. What's going on?
Hang on a sec.
By any chance, are you...
related?
Yeah.
So Nanba-senpai is
your older sister's son?
Which makes me their nephew.
Isn't that right, Auntie Rio?
That hardly matters when
I'm younger than you!
Ah, so that's the story here.
Uncle, my mom was pestering me about
the Hayama Boarding House thing.
Like I'm going there!
What a pain in the ass.
She figured this would happen,
so she's driving here to pick you up.
In ten minutes.
Then I'm getting out of here
on the double!
Give my regards to the demon witch!
Where are you going, Hokuto?
M-M-My dear sister...
Looking beautiful as ever today.
It's because I'm a demon witch.
We don't age.
Th-That's your older sister?
Y-Yeah.
Where were you trying
to sneak off to, Hokuto?
Nowhere. Just a little walk.
Tell me the truth or else...
I'm going on a vacation to a
southern island with a friend.
You're so heartless, Hokuto!
I've been asking you to keep this
summer open for over a year!
How cruel you are when we're
so direly understaffed!
I can hardly believe
we're related right now!
You dirty hag...
Nothing to worry about, Ms. Magistrate.
I've got a pretty face just itching
to work for you right here.
Oh?
You weren't kidding.
Looks like she likes him.
Yeah.
Looking at him reminds me of when
I used to play dress-up with you.
Y'know, Hokuto?
The bastard snuck away!
Hayama Boarding House?
Yeah.
The gig comes with room
and board, so it all works out.
Hey, that actually sounds perfect.
Then I'll sign on too.
What?
I was going to look for
a part-time job anyway.
I-I'll do it too, Mizuki!
Count me in.
What's gotten into you two?
I mean, she did say they
were understaffed,
so I guess it would be okay.
So long as I breathe, I'm not
letting you two be alone!
Ashiya-kun!
Ma'am!
Could you serve this?
Sure.
Having you here has been such a help.
We're so shorthanded this year.
The only people I've been able to hire
are two local college students.
I was in a real bind.
The other two workers you
introduced me to are great too.
We have to thank you.
We were also in a tough situation because
we got kicked out of our dorm.
I'm telling you, it's true.
Come on!
Makita-kun.
Coming!
See you later.
Your romantic life is your own business,
but if you touch a customer, you're fired.
Talk about harsh.
But I know that.
You've only been here
two days, Mizuki-kun,
but you're learning fast.
You're just a really good teacher.
Mealtimes sure are busy.
No, not like that.
You fold it here.
Like this?
You got it. That's great.
Yeah.
The last step is folding it right there.
I did it!
Okay, very good. You pass.
Great!
So that's how it's done.
Ashiya, stop taking it easy
and come help out here.
Oh, sorry.
Be right there.
Hey, Sano. Check this out.
Looks good, right?
Yeah, yeah.
It's great.
Oh yeah.
I have to go feed Yujiro.
I'll come with.
I love dogs.
Oh, really?
What the hell?
That guy is all over Mizuki!
He's just babying him a
little since he's so cute.
But Ashiya-kun's a boy, so he'll be fine.
I'll go keep an eye on them!
He does good work, but you know...
Mayumi-chan, you be careful too.
I see.
So Io-san said to bring
the dog along as well?
Yeah.
When we told her there would be
nobody left to take care of him,
she told us just to bring him too.
Hey, so, can I ask you something?
Sure.
Which of those two guys is your boyfriend?
What? N-Neither one.
Besides, I'm a he—
Oh, that's cute.
You go by male pronouns?
Then I'll call you Mizuki-kun too.
No, you don't understand.
I...
Oh, I get it.
The boss tried to warn me about this.
I guess she doesn't trust me.
I...
Mizuki, what are you doing?
Um, I'm a guy!
That's so cute.
"I'm a guy," huh?
I love that naivety.
Nakatsu, what are you angry about?
Nothin'!
I'm all sweaty, so I'm going to go change.
Sure.
Hey.
Time to peel potatoes.
I'm seriously soaked in sweat.
Damn, this is so tight...
Thank God I could close it.
Have I gained weight?
It's because Io-san's cooking
is too delicious!
Hey, man, doesn't that Makita
dude piss you off?
He's such a creep around Mizuki.
I'm kind of worried about him now.
It's none of your business.
What?!
Okay, yeah, I get it.
I'm not part of the inner circle.
Even though I got a room
here, it's a single.
All while you two get to share!
It's so lonely!
I'm so alone!
Nakatsu?
Okay, fine, I'm sorry.
Come back!
I had no idea he was so
lonely staying by himself.
It's nice you all are such close friends.
Thanks.
Ashiya?
Yeah?
You aren't... in trouble?
Huh? What do you mean?
If not, forget I said anything.
Okay.
That was weird.
So today, we've got Ota, party of two.
And then...
Huh?
Mizuki, how many guests we got today?
Io-san told me to go make the beds.
Mizuki?
You must be Kagurazaka-sama.
W-Welcome.
So I just had to make this guy's bed?
What the hell are you guys doing here?
The food's gonna taste awful
with you around.
Dumbass!
Look who's talking!
Idiot!
How dare you speak to our esteemed
guests in that manner, you lout?!
I-I'm sorry.
I apologize for the rudeness
of my employees.
But please rest assured.
I prepare all the meals here myself.
You have my word they'll be good.
But Kagurazaka-sama, I believe your
reservation was for four people.
Our family's temple had
a sudden change of schedule.
Oh, your family operates a temple?
Yes. I'm here in place of my parents.
H-His parents run a temple?!
Hey, Onii-chan.
Oh my God, it's Sano Izumi!
What?! No way! He's real!
What are you doing here?!
This is such a coincidence! I can't even!
My brother told me you'd made
a comeback, Izumi-sama!
But I never dreamed I'd run into you here!
"Izumi-sama"?
My name is Tamami.
I've been such a fan ever since
my first year of middle school.
Come on, Tamami.
You wanted to hit the beach.
This is so embarrassing.
Izumi-sama!
Let's talk more later!
And let's go swimming
together in the ocean!
Ya know, I'm not surprised he's
got a little sister like that.
The heck?!
Nii-cha—
No.
She must've mixed you up with Kagurazaka.
Damn him.
Who leaves their baby sister behind?
That's a big shock, huh?
What's your name, little lady?
Kyomi.
And how old are you, Kyomi-chan?
Three.
You brat!
Whoa there, Sano,
can you hold Nakatsu back?
Lemme go!
Nakatsu, she's just a little kid.
Okay?
Kyomi-chan, why don't we go to your room?
Come in.
Kagurazaka, I brought Kyomi-chan...
I'm so sorry!
It's fine.
It's a swimsuit.
Come on in.
I can't believe I actually
got to meet Izumi-sama!
I'm so glad I forced my
brother to bring me here.
Our folks wouldn't let me come
with just friends
since I'm only a second-year
middle schooler.
I see.
She's only in the second year
of middle school, and yet...
I'm jealous.
Oh, wait, that would actually be
a detriment for me right now.
Hey!
Mizuki-kun, I wanna ask you something.
Nee-cha. The ocean.
Uh, what?
Does Izumi-sama have a girlfriend?
Who knows?
I d-don't think he does.
In other words, he's available right now!
This is my chance to snag
him with my hot body!
Huh?
What?!
Hey, Sekime.
If Sano is a mother cat,
is Ashiya a kitten?
I'd say he's more like a dog.
A dog, huh?
That tracks.
Always running around and being loud.
So, what am I? What am I?
I guess a marmoset?
Next Time
It's Not Like We Could Become Lovers
What is that?