Causes of death are many and varied.
Old age, suicide, illness...
But the cause of death that scares the
most people in this day and age...
...is death by fire.
There is one pillar left.
The preface to the Great Cataclysm ends here.
Indeed.
The Great Cataclysm consists of this
world and humanity's imaginings.
It is the process of unifying
the collective unconscious.
All humans subconsciously wish
for destruction, don't they?
Which means the destruction of the world.
Which is why we must guide humanity's
collective unconscious in the proper direction.
The final destination of all
humanity's imaginings is death.
We cannot permit the correct image
of death to waver in the slightest.
Haumea, how is the collective unconscious?
No problems. The final ending is death!
The Evangelist will be overjoyed!
Insects leaping into the flames.
Humanity facing death and destruction.
Though the scale of the sequences
is different, they are the same.
This planet—this universe—are thus, as well.
That's the eighth one.
What's happening to this world?
Another Titan's gonna
appear! We've gotta run!
Call the Special Fire Force!
The 2nd has arrived on site!
Soldiers of the 4th, take your positions!
Get the catapult ready!
Secure the line of fire ASAP!
So this is the final pillar.
The 2nd and Haijima are
in charge of the Titan!
We'll evacuate the civilians!
Yes, sir!
Hurry up!
Work together!
Get to your positions!
It's the last one. We should be
able to leave everything to them.
Direct the civilians to evacuate!
It's nearly over.
Stop complaining and just do it.
Back with the first one, it was shocking
just seeing a giant pillar appear,
but now, look at that.
To ensure that the Cataclysm
proceeds smoothly,
we will completely eradicate the savior.
The 8th pillar has finally appeared.
We will commence operations
to stop the Great Cataclysm.
Special Fire Force Company 8, move out!
Yes, sir!
It's a Titan!
Don't panic! Evacuate according
to the soldiers' instructions!
Spontaneous human combustion!
Karin! You all right?
Sorry! I let my guard down!
You say you let your guard down
as if it works as an excuse.
Letting your guard down
in itself is a bad thing!
That's why I apologized!
I'll stop these Infernals!
Scale Barricade!
What do we do?
I've cast a heat resist buff on all of you!
Don't be afraid of the flames!
Please evacuate this way!
Ogun, lay them to rest!
Sir!
Father, the prayer!
The flame is the soul's breath.
The black smoke is the soul's release.
Ashes thou were and art.
May thy soul...
Return to the great flame of fire.
We have to lay that Titan to rest
before further damage is done!
Captain Honda!
The catapult is ready!
Good.
Super Headbutt Cannon!
Honda Shot loaded!
Tomorrow I will wake, open the window,
and bathe in the light of the sun!
I will go to work, perform my duties,
and return home to my waiting family!
And every night, I will think,
"Today was a good day!"
Tomorrow will be another of those days!
And those days must continue!
Honda Shot, Oni-Muso!
Bring it on!
This will defeat the Titan,
and this pillar will turn black, too.
What will happen next?
For the tomorrow of the Empire!
Clank
Captain Honda!
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Episode 16
"Savior"
Honda Shot has been lost!
Retrieval team, hurry up!
Well, isn't that something?
Imagine the captain of the
2nd's attack having no effect.
Well, we have no chance now. Let's withdraw.
If we leave that monster running
loose, what place is there to run to?
I'm not saying that as a joke.
That Honda headbutt
may seem like a joke of an attack,
but its power is the real deal.
If it has no effect, then...
I'm not interested in your opinion.
I'm telling you to figure something out.
Playing with kids at the orphanage
pays the same as killing monsters.
How does that make sense?
That's what it means to be a salaryman.
The truth is, I'm thinking of changing jobs.
If this country still
exists tomorrow, that is.
Now get going.
Here at the Tama Riverfront,
TAMA RIVERFRONT
the Fire Force is attacking the
Titan and laying Infernals to rest.
As the sun sets, this looks
to become a night battle.
The moon's smile looks even more eerie.
The sun is setting.
The Cataclysm is near at hand.
The laws of this world will change.
Despair.
Abandon all hope.
The collective unconscious shall
guide us to the correct conclusion.
Look at that!
Cameraman, zoom in! Zoom in!
I already am!
Th-That's...
Raffles?
The pillar's great
Titan
Raffles I
appears!
Látom.
What's going on with the sky?
The stars... What's happening to the world?
People's imaginings are exploding.
It's Emperor Raffles I.
He has descended to save us from
the abnormalities in this world.
Látom.
Why, Raffles-sama?
Raffles-sama is angry.
We are fools, and this is
our divine punishment.
This is divine punishment!
Please forgive us, Raffles-sama!
This is why I hate the strong.
Mother!
Hey! Are you okay?
You can stand, right?
It's just a scratch. Come on. Get up!
Damn it! How could he turn into an
Infernal at a crucial time like this?
He was useless right up to the end!
Who needs some feckless
newscaster to make a broadcast?
As long as there's a camera, that's enough!
What's that?
A bird?
A plane?
It's I'm-gonna-stop-the-Cataclysm Man!
A superhero?!
Is that it?
The father of the empire...
the Great Father.
That's...
Raffles I!
We will pluck the shoots of humanity's hopes.
Abandon all hope,
and turn to thoughts of despair.
Observe and think!
Which of them is your true savior?
Shinra!
Let us handle laying the Infernals to rest!
Focus your power on dealing with the Titan!
Yes, sir!
The 8th?
What business do you traitors have here?
Is this really the time for that?!
We're in an emergency here!
What are you plotting?
Don't act without orders!
Shinra-kun, I'll back you up!
I can handle this alone!
Huh?
Adolla's closer, so my ignition
powers have gotten stronger!
Right now, I can get to the
speed of light on my own!
That light speed kick from when you
defeated that Demon back on the continent!
Shinra, don't worry about things here! Go!
If we get hit like this,
we'll all get wiped out.
Karin!
Our role is to put up defenses!
We're gonna cover the whole
river's edge with shields!
All of it?
I'll focus all my buffs on you, Karin.
We need to get this done
before the next bombardment!
I'll give it a try!
Scale Shield, full power!
That's our captain!
Karin, you're amazing, too!
Of course I am!
Show 'em the spirit of the 4th!
Barrage from the Titan incoming!
Well done, Karin!
Sir!
What does the 4th do?
We never abandon anyone and
we protect the survivors!
Wouldn't expect it from Karin,
but that's pretty good!
And now, what I have to do...
is lay the Titan Raffles I to rest!
Fire Force
Chapter 3
SHOOM
What the hell? My body suddenly...
got heavier!
SHOOM SHOOM
SHOOOOOM
With you alone, the curtain will not fall.
Well?
How does it feel to be kicked
and fall into the sky?
A White Clad?
Crap! My body won't...
Allow me to disrupt your gravitation.
How does it feel to fall in every
possible sense of the word?
I can't get the right posture in the air!
Oh! Is this it?
What is this, damn it?!
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Brother, against someone like that,
you just need to kick them between moments.
You can't tell which way you're falling.
One mistake at light speed,
and you could fly out of the atmosphere!
Before thinking about taking down an enemy,
you have to think of your own... safety...
Sho!
Why are you here?
Are you okay?
Whoa!
Nothing bad happened to you, did it?
We'll talk later.
The players are all in place.
My role ends here.
Preparations to pluck out every
hope have been completed.
What's his deal?
Brother, the Great Cataclysm is an
explosion of humanity's imaginings.
If your achievements can lead
humanity to hold on to hope,
images of hope will increase, and the
world's destruction can be stopped.
Achievements?
And to do that...
First is that Titan, right?
Just try your hardest.
You are not a devil.
Show them who the real hero is!
Yeah, I don't really understand everything,
but I came here to become a hero!
I'm not a devil.
I have to become a hero!
So the one who inflicts guilt on people
and metes out atonement is the hero, huh?
Látom.
What is that?
That form...
He must still be angry.
Oh, please forgive us!
The tips are showing high energy readings!
There's another barrage on the way!
The lasers were deflected!
That light...
Are we saved?
Did that fire soldier protect us?
The spikes around the edge disappeared!
There are eight new powerful heat sources!
They're Demons!
Demons?
Just laying one to rest is hard,
and there are eight of them?
Shinra-san.
Incredible...
All eight Demons... have been extinguished.
68% of Light Speed
Another attack is coming.
What will you do, brother?
I'll hit light speed and
lay him to rest in one go!
Hey!
Shinra-kun!
Given the data from the light speed kick
that defeated the Demon on the continent,
it will produce a shockwave
that will hit us here!
It could result in serious casualties!
But if that's true...
Everyone, please...
Upon we who are lost,
bestow the Sun's blessings.
What?
Please, I beg you to grant it.
What is this?
Is it Iris?
What is this light?
Captain Pan, is this a buff?
No. I haven't done a thing.
What's that?
Brother!
It's the light of an Adolla Burst!
This is... the miracle she
showed us with Dragon.
The sister has awakened
with the eighth pillar?
Brother, it seems you don't have
to worry about the shockwave.
Having the sister's devotion
and prayers is reassuring!
Citizens of the Tokyo Empire!
I will show you the path to salvation!
Return to the great flame of fire.
The time for death has come!
Raffles-sama.
That's not salvation!
A savior...
is a savior because they save the world!
Shinra-kun's styling has changed!
So he's finally overcome the devil, has he?
My big brother is a real hero!
A hero...
finishes things in one blow.
Go, Shinra!
Shinra-kun, you can do it!
Shinra!
Go get 'em, Shinra!
Go! You can do it!
What? It can't be...
Here I go!
Here comes the shockwave!
Látom.
That was amazing, Shinra!
That was insane.
Yeah.
You really are a hero!
He did it, Lieutenant!
Yes.
Captain, it was over in an instant!
Well done, hero!
Honestly. He's grown far too strong.
Incredible. That fire soldier...
No!
No, it isn't true.
Raffles-sama!
That fire soldier... What has he done?
Hope has been eradicated.
Now humanity will despair.
Shinra Kusakabe must not become a hero.
This is farewell.
He's a devil!
He's a devil who killed Raffles-sama!
Oh, Raffles-sama!
Never forgive that fire soldier!
Kill him!
Devil!
Devil! Devil! Devil! Devil! Devil!
C-Captain!
What's wrong?
It's Shinra.
Shinra... disappeared!
To Be Continued
Fire Force Chapter 3
Next Time
I'm on my way to Amaterasu! You come, too!
Hey! Is the 8th always doing stuff like this?
Next time, "At the Center of the World."
Episode 17
At the Center of the World
Return to the great flame of fire. Látom.