I'm sure you had your own plans,
but it was all for nothing.
Whatever you do, don't fight the Tensen.
If we do, our plan will fail.
Gabimaru.
It's over.
Over?
What should we do
if we actually have to face them?
Simply run away?
The moment that happens, the plan is over.
It's time for plan B.
Prepare yourselves.
Fight with everything you've got.
Once the Tensen are engaged,
it's impossible to flee from them.
We will not run.
We won't give up either.
We will defeat you and leave the island.
Hell's Paradise
A faint flower was blooming
unnoticed by anyone
Not a burning red,
but flickering serenely in red
I've been pausing for a long time
dragging my past at my feet
If I break free from this ambivalence,
will I be able to bloom by its side?
The future is slipping away
between my fingers
What mistake did I make
to pay this price?
Always hurting myself
and hesitant even to a small joy
I want to stop now
The flower just bloomed in dignity
and that was all I needed to be happy
I just wanted to protect this one flower
Wishing to be strong, I
picked up the vulnerability
I had once cast away
Can't break free from the ambivalence
In ambivalence, I become myself
Like rooting strongly into the soil
like swaying ephemerally to the wind
I'm slowly loosening myself to bloom
Hell's Paradise
Hindering and Restoration
To be blunt, any effort
to fight back is pointless.
Plan B? You mean using brute force?
No. I have an idea.
Sister.
You should return to our brother
and the Grandmaster.
After all, our brother
banished you out of love.
It saddens me to see you at odds.
If you still oppose the
Waitanhua Flower, it is pointless.
The perfect tan—the Elixir of Life—
will be completed soon.
Tan that does not turn people into trees.
What...?
We learned how to refine it
with help from a human.
Our research on the
Waitanhua Flower is complete.
We have no reason to fight anymore.
Now we need only acquire enough tan.
We need more higher-quality materials.
To that end, our brother
has begun the ritual.
The Hekiji Fukusho ritual.
You're not yet aware
of our brother's anguish,
but you could surely reach
an understanding now.
But I want to see Rien and
Grandmaster one more time.
Mei-san...
I missed everyone, too.
But I understand now.
I am different from rest of you.
Both dying and not being
able to die are sad.
I came to see all of you.
I came to say goodbye.
I am leaving the island.
Then you leave me no choice.
Let us finish this first.
The ritual has already begun.
The last thing we need are the offerings.
In other words, all of you.
We know of only one way to win.
Destroy their tanden
using hindering tao—
in other words, one with
a favorable attribute matchup.
The situation changes according
to the attribute of your opponent's tao.
For example, Gabimaru, your tao is
strong against Gui Fa's metal attribute.
Wood
Fire
Earth
Metal
Water
But facing Ran, whose attribute is water,
puts you in a difficult position.
Touching your opponent
will weaken your fire tao.
Even if you destroy their tanden,
it won't kill them.
In other words, you cannot defeat them.
And besides, they have
far more tao than us.
What do you intend to do?
I have an idea.
Why did we have to encounter
Gabimaru's worst matchup?
Sagiri.
What?
Take Mei and go to the room
with the Elixir.
Yuzuriha and I will handle this.
What? Why me?
Ran's tao is water.
You're the only one with earth tao,
the hindering attribute.
Gabimaru, not here.
Not rentan palace. No Elixir.
What?!
They're fast.
My sister is correct.
This is not the rentan palace.
It is my doin palace.
How?
But we confirmed the locations
of the rentan palace, tan, and tao.
The tan of inanimate objects is far easier
to manipulate than that of living things.
You simply command it to change shape.
The construction of the buildings
and stone statues on the island.
Renovations based on feng shui
are my responsibility.
Changing the castle layout
to counter your intrusion was simple.
The tao of corpses behaves like
that of inanimate objects.
I created the illusion
that the tan was here.
Mei-san!
See?
Now be still, Sister.
We'll have to settle this here after all.
Gabimaru!
Yuzuriha!
Follow the plan!
Marvelous! Such lively flesh!
It's a shame, though.
With your tao, no matter how many
times you hit me, you cannot kill me.
So this must be what you're really after.
It's possible to imbue weapons
with tao, right?
Yes.
Then aren't ranged
weapons better than melee?
They're safer, and it's easier
to catch someone off-guard.
Maybe it's because they can regenerate,
but the Tensen leave
themselves defenseless.
Yikes!
Why? I should be hindering!
As I thought, simply blocking
their attacks takes a lot of effort.
Is this the effect of hindering, too?
But most of all, this is different
from fighting Zhu Jin.
Why are they so hard?
I stretch my tao thin
and bundle it together.
It makes it tough and supple,
like muscle fibers.
Uh, in other words?
Their entire body is covered
in hard tao armor.
If that coordinated attack
was your plan, then it is pointless.
Unlike a suit of armor,
tao has no gaps or blind spots.
This is harmony between muscles and tao.
True flesh.
Are all the Tensen this crazy?
Don't ask me.
We should remove that
while we have the chance.
Ninpo: Stone Storm.
Gabimaru!
They're not just tough.
They know more actual combat
techniques than Mu Dan.
At this rate...
Don't worry.
I expected this.
I've got the gist of it now.
Let's begin, Yuzuriha.
Yeah, yeah. Finally, huh?
I thought we were going to die.
Begin?
They haven't been executing their plan?
The amount and attributes
of their tao hasn't changed.
They shouldn't even be able
to damage my muscles.
Try all you want. The result
will always be the same.
That seems to have worked.
We've tried the first method.
Now let's try the second.
Hell's Paradise
Yuzuriha
Gabimaru
Yamada Asaemon Sagiri
The names of those who landed.
Rituals and curses require names.
We'll use their names
for the Hekiji Fukusho ritual.
Then should we capture them
and force them to tell us?
Gabimaru.
Gabimaru the Hollow, Tamiya Gantetsusai.
I remember all the names on the roster,
including the criminals.
Not that I know who's survived.
My brother is among them.
We already fought you once.
There's no point in hiding it now.
I have one condition for helping you.
My brother's safety.
I'm willing to side
with you guys to ensure that.
Take me to your whatever ritual.
I'll recruit my own brother.
Stay out of it.
Then tell us all of their names.
Keiun
I'll use talismans to view
their current condition.
Twisted Keiun.
Yamada Asaemon Kisho.
Rokurota.
Yamada Asaemon Eizen.
Akaginu.
Yamada Asaemon Shion.
Yamada Asaemon Shion
Alive. Wood. Male.
Strong mastery of tao.
Yamada Asaemon Shion
Nurugai
They encountered Zhu Jin
in the taisoku palace.
Shion does not hinder
Zhu Jin's water attribute.
Therefore, he has no way to kill them.
He's accompanied by Nurugai,
whose attribute is water.
Their attacks against
Zhu Jin are effective,
but their skill with tao is weak.
They don't stand a chance.
However, I detect a powerful rage.
Emotions dramatically
impact a human's tao.
Yamada Asaemon Toma
Yamada Asaemon Fuchi
Tamiya Gantetsusai
We mustn't underestimate them.
Yamada Asaemon Fuchi
and Tamiya Gantetsusai.
They encountered Tao Fa
and Ju Fa in the bochu palace.
Fuchi's metal attribute hinders Tao Fa,
but their training
with tao is insufficient.
Instead, Ju Fa's fire
attribute hinders Fuchi.
They will kill them both.
And...
Chobe will recruit his younger brother.
It should be easy.
Our focus should be...
Gabimaru
on this man.
Is this the first method
Gabimaru mentioned?
Tao is like a current
surrounding your body.
It's a physical phenomenon.
The speed and size of the current
determines its strength.
Attributes describe
the direction of the flow.
Restoration is a flow that supports yours.
Hindrance is one that halts it.
But the Tensen's currents are too strong,
so the standard principles don't apply.
There are three countermeasures.
Temporarily or locally exert
more tao,
or do the opposite and locally
weaken your tao to deflect attacks.
To prevent both the acceleration from
restoration and rebound from hindering,
join your opponent's current
and turn it back on them.
It's similar to what's known as
hua jin or silk reeling in tai chi.
They're techniques for turning your
opponent's strength back on them.
Is that even possible?
It's not easy, but it's an application
of what we've learned.
I've learned to use another person's
tao through training with Nurugai.
I've learned to dampen my tao
as much as possible from Yuzuriha.
I've learned to control it
locally from Shion.
And...
In order to match my breaths
to my opponent's tao...
I must possess both
stillness and intensity.
By attuning my mind to the middle path,
I deflect my opponent's attacks.
I once learned that from you, Sagiri.
So this is the sum
of everything you've learned.
Yeah. I'll hit them
with everything I have.
Dampening my tao weakens my own defense.
I'm fine if I can keep
deflecting their attacks,
but even a scratch takes a massive toll.
A direct hit would be really bad.
Impressive.
If I look closely,
I can tell you began developing your tao
after you arrived on the island.
And yet, you've achieved such skill.
Many become aware of tao
when they're exposed to the dense tao
that hangs about the island.
In fact, that's one of
the purposes of this island.
But your adaptability can't
be explained by that alone.
You possess true talent.
Enough to impress me.
Talent?
Talent, you say?
This isn't talent.
It's the last resort I desperately
struggled to come up with.
The combined knowledge gleaned from
the many sacrifices that were made.
All to kill you.
But you'd ignore that
and call it talent instead.
That's an awfully carefree way to put it.
You're free.
Gabimaru, we'll go to the
rentan palace and get the Elixir.
Stay where you are!
The Elixir.
This is our chance.
The other sages are engaged in battle.
The ritual.
What's the risk?
Do it!
Got it!
Wait...
Is he planning to use my tao again?
Then I'll weaken mine instead.
The hindering woman.
This is what she was waiting for.
Such impressive physical
abilities and teamwork.
They could surely reach
even greater heights of tao.
They are the ultimate opponents.
However...
Again!
Wait!
Unfortunately, this is a ritual.
I don't have time to play.
Is this...?
Yeah.
It's coming.
The real battle starts now.
It's really such a shame.
So Ran transformed.
Gabimaru
That hasn't happened in centuries.
He's that powerful a man.
That incredible a material.
Grandmaster.
The starter for the Elixir is complete.
We will first grow it using
those who came to the island
and then cross the sea
to gather more materials.
It will finally all end tonight.
Such a shame.
First, we need to identify
the idiosyncrasies of their tao
like we did before.
Will I be able to handle it?
L-L-Lively flesh!
It's too powerful.
We can go this way.
Okay.
G-Gabimaru will be okay.
They're measuring our stamina
and avoiding fatal blows.
Is it so they can turn us into tan?
They're not like Zhu Jin or Mu Dan.
Ran retains their sense of reason
even when transformed.
They're using techniques and strategies.
This is bad.
My consciousness is fading.
There's a problem.
Tao is also life itself.
Using it while badly injured
could shorten your lifespan.
Lively flesh.
Ninpo: Stone Storm...
So depending on the matchup,
it may make sense for me to protect you.
We're both shinobi,
but you and I are nothing alike.
In desperate situations,
I only protect myself.
We should retreat for now.
We'll wait for another opportunity.
As long as we don't die,
we can figure something out.
Nothing's more important
to me than my life.
I'm not risking it for anything.
Enough.
The ingredient for tan is your life,
but you are simply too tough.
Enough is enough.
I agree.
My own life is my top priority.
I don't intend to die.
My goal is to make it back home alive.
To live and see my wife.
On the other side, even today
Someone is unraveling,
yet they still stand
A stab to the chest, this loneliness
Points and lines,
breaking off and vanishing
My shattered mask
It's more than I can bear
But I must keep on living
Tomorrow awaits to greet me
It's endless
And so fragile
Is it better to believe
hearts don't exist at all?
Radiant and soft
Was the hand
I squeezed back on that day