Forgive me, Master.
Sorry. I didn't mean to startle you.
Don't stiffen up so much.
We slept in each other's arms, didn't we?
Aw, you got it all over your hands.
I can just wipe it away.
Master, you mustn't!
Mm, that's sour.
I apologize. It's not done yet.
Nah, it's good.
Hey, there's more.
That should do it.
Um, you've got some on you, too.
Huh? Where, here?
No...
Milkit...
Master...
Milkit!
Master!
Mil...kit...
Mas...ter...
Milkit...
Master...
Okay, no way I can go in there now.
AN ORDINARY LIFE
I'm done.
Thank you.
That was delicious.
Right?
I like your cooking too, Flum.
Oh, it's nothing compared to Milkit's.
I want to eat your cooking again.
But I have Milkit here.
My cooking's happily retired.
What's your plan for the day, Eterna?
Milkit and I were thinking
of going shopping.
There's a lot we need
to settle in around the house.
I'll come and help carry stuff for you.
You don't have to do that anymore!
FLUM APRICOT
TOTAL STATS: 3,396
Look!
Total stats of 3,396?
See how much stronger I am now?
Yep. You've come a long way.
All right!
Let's get shopping!
We'll take these.
We'll take these!
Huh? Are you sure you want
another of the same?
As the first outfit you bought for me,
it has a special place in my heart.
Okay, if you say so.
We'll take this.
We'll take these.
That's a cute outfit,
but I don't think it'd look good on me.
What to do?
Hmm...
All right.
Sorry, we'll come again.
We'll take these.
Huh?
Did you find something you like, Eterna?
PRICE: 100 GOLD
One hundred gold...
Let's save up and buy the set
together someday, okay, Eterna?
I'll buy it myself if I have to.
I don't want to inconvenience you.
But if we're all gonna use it,
we should all chip in.
We're housemates, after all.
Any objections,
Eterna?
I wish Jean had even
a sliver of your geniality.
Heya, Miss Flum and Miss Milkit!
Oh, hey, Sara.
What?
Eterna... Rinebow?!
Ah.
Don't blame ya for leavin',
even if it is the heroes' party.
If ya don't vibe along,
ya don't vibe along.
You mean "get along."
Though I guess you're not too far off.
Why are you headed
to the West District church?
I thought you were at the Central—
If I don't go, those two get lonely.
And who gets lonely, exactly?
Hey. Name's Ed.
And I'm Jonny. Thanks for
nabbing those thieves back then.
Somehow, we got all the credit.
No money to show for it, though.
Thanks for your help.
I'm Flum, by the way.
She's my friend.
Wow, good goin', Sara. You finally
made a friend outside the Church.
That's reason to celebrate!
Hey, stop that!
Cut it out, Ed. You're bothering her.
I just always feel like pettin' her.
She's like a dog or somethin'.
I feel you.
E-Eterna...
...Rinebow?!
Identical reactions.
They must be siblings.
No! We're not siblings!
Pardon me.
We did grow up like siblings, I guess.
Right?
Stop that!
Okay, we should be headin' off.
Oh, I forgot.
Mr. Leitch left me a reward to give you.
How's his wife doin'?
I hear she's recovering
thanks to the medicine.
That's good to hear!
We're living in a house near
the big florist on Suzuran Avenue.
Come by sometime to pick it up.
I can't accept that. Helping people
is part of my duties as a nun.
Sara, we need to get going.
Consider this helping me, then.
I'll be troubled if you don't accept it.
I can't...
If you stop by, you'll get to eat some
of Milkit's super-yummy food...
F-Fine, you win.
Okay, we should get going, too.
Oh, I need to stop by the guild.
You two head back without me.
Gotcha.
What's taking those guys so long?
Bitley and Dolph both.
And yet the slave girl made it back
as though nothing happened.
Okay, that bitch's going down.
We can overpower her anytime.
That's boring.
We should torture her mentally first.
Really take our time with it.
Hello.
Hey! What are you doing here?
Picking up a job. What else?
You won't find those here.
All we have are dummy requests
meant as traps for you.
You drew too much attention, girl.
Are you worried about me?
Pah! You should've just
become a whore like I said.
This is what you get
for not heeding my advice.
Maybe, yeah.
Now you see what kind of place this is.
If you don't like it,
take Dein out and change it
for the better.
So I gotta take down Dein, huh?
I was just kidding.
Run along, now.
O-Okay. Thanks, Y'lla.
Not gonna take a job?
Nah. I'm just gonna leave for today.
You will bow down to me, slave girl!
I'll settle things with you someday.
Thank you for looking out.
Flum's specialty?
Yes. You mentioned
her cooking at breakfast.
So you got curious?
Well, um...
The cheese's aroma is restrained.
It's sweet, but the sour kick of
the apricot jam balances it out.
That's Flum's cheesecake for you.
Yep, this is great.
You get a perfect score.
Looks like it came out well, Flum.
Yay!
How's my shortcake, Maria?
It's lovely!
So much for a nun's abstinence.
P-Please don't misunderstand.
A girl I know back at
the Church loves cakes,
and she's like a little sister to me.
You can enjoy your food.
I'm not gonna stop you.
Whoa, Maria's going to town again.
Those look good.
Heroes' cakes.
Could start a business.
Would the two of you like to join us?
Would the two of you care to join us?
We have some for you as well.
Oh, will you have some too, Jean?
We baked too much cake.
I am far too much of a prodigy
to associate with nobodies,
but I suppose I could humor
you fools once in a while.
Gadhio, Linus. Which cake would you like?
Or will you have both?
A tough choice.
If there's enough to go around,
I'll have both.
A wise choice.
Just a moment, please.
Here you go, Jean.
That sounds good.
I wish I could've tasted it.
In the first two months after we
set out to fight the Demon Lord,
there were times when
everything went well.
Master said she was thrown out
for being a hindrance.
I know now that she was the
glue holding us together.
She has the power to draw people in.
And that made Jean jealous.
Flum's a great gal. You won't
go wrong sticking with her.
And if you ever want to say anything
to her, don't hesitate to speak up.
Okay...
I'm back!
It's so great to have
a home to come back to.
Welcome home, Master.
Milkit has something
to ask of you, it seems.
What?
E-Eterna!
Put the things you care about
into words, or she'll never know!
Um, well...
I want you to expect all that
and more from me!
Lean on me more!
U-Um...
I'm worried about you going to the guild.
And I think the dress you were
looking at would suit you very well.
Also, I want to try your cheesecake!
That's a first.
You never made your wishes
clear like that before.
I'm so, so glad you finally did.
I'm so happy! I'm just so happy!
M-Master...
Oh, Milkit.
Master.
Milkit!
Master!
I missed my chance again.
Thanks for havin' me!
Welcome, Sara.
Somethin' smells yummy!
We have harpusy cream stew,
sautéed genofish,
meat and vegetable stir-fry, and...
Er... What is this?
Pickled herbs. Stude's mother taught me.
Th-This all looks amazing!
Okay, then.
Let's eat!
Uwwy!
"Yummy."
Did you catch that, Flum?
Nope. No idea.
Master.
Thanks.
Meah, is ood.
"Yeah, it's good."
Miwit's ookin izo gway.
What was that?
Thank you, Master.
Milkit understood that, huh?
More, please!
To enjoy tea at its finest,
you need to heat your cup first.
Put the leaves in the teapot,
put the lid on, and let it steep.
Why steep it?
Steeping brings out the tea leaves'
aroma and components.
It's done, girls.
Ta-da!
Cheesecake!
Master baked it.
You did, Miss Flum?!
Milkit requested it.
Let's eat it together.
Hooray!
It's so yummy!
I love the sour jam! Gimme more!
Huh? Already?
I love cake, ya see.
Ah...
So she was talking about you.
Who was?
Don't worry about it.
Say "aah."
I can eat by myself.
You don't have to feed me.
No can do.
I wanna feed you to celebrate
your first ever request.
Now say "aah."
U-Um...
GIVE
UP
AND
DO
IT
Come on.
Say "aah."
H-How is it?
It's great.
Thank goodness.
They're so close.
I can't bear to watch.
I'm kinda envious.
I told Eterna about the lab and that
weird experiment gone nuts.
Sara, did you learn anything
about the lab?
I looked into it after we got back to
the capital, but I didn't find nothin'.
What about the records
you found the kialahri's location in?
They were gone.
They'd been out for a while, but they
musta figured I saw and put 'em away.
Anyway, the church had documents about it,
so there might be another
research facility somewhere nearby.
There's only so many places
a nun like me's got access to.
What about the West
and East District churches?
I can enter them, but...
The West District's church
also has an orphanage attached.
They wouldn't be able to keep a secret
research facility under wraps there.
What about the East's, then?
Well, that's where the rich
and powerful live.
They wouldn't want to get on the bad
side of the influential people there.
The roots of the kingdom's research
run deeper than you'd think.
We should assume they're still continuing
somewhere in the capital.
Wait, the kingdom?
The suppression of every religion
but the Church of Origin,
the ban on herbal medicine, and the
monopolization of healing through magic...
None of those would've been possible
without the kingdom's backing.
The kingdom and the Church
had a deep, twisted relationship.
On the surface, the royal army and
the holy church knights worked together
to maintain peace and order, but they were
actually participants in a power struggle.
Even if there are no active research
facilities, there might still be ruins.
I believe it's well worth it
to investigate the capital.
I'll look into the West District church.
I'll check out non-church places, then.
Master...
Please don't do anything reckless.
Sorry to ask this of you, Sara.
No worries.
As a member of the church, it's my duty
to bring its shadows to light.
Thanks, Sara.
Oh, right. I nearly forgot.
Here, from Mr. Leitch to you.
What's that?
I can't accept this!
I think it'll make him sad if you don't.
It's pretty rude to send back
a gift. Even for a nun.
Right you are. I'll go ahead
and take it, then.
It's all sparkly and pretty.
Okay, I'll be going now!
After you drink that, remove the bandages.
I want to examine the affected area.
Very well.
Good. It's healing right.
That's not the issue.
What is, then?
I heard about how she got poisoned.
It made me sick to my stomach.
Who did it to her?
She doesn't know.
The effects came out of nowhere.
It's likely her previous mistress
mixed it into her food.
How awful.
Who feeds a girl poison
to make her face fester?
What a wicked thing to do.
She must've been jealous
of Milkit's beauty!
I think you're probably right.
She'll have hell to pay
if I ever run into her.
I'll help too.
It was the same when we traveled together.
You always try to do too much by yourself.
Eterna...
I know I can be of help.
Thank you.
But don't force yourself.
We're housemates, remember?
Right!
I'll be counting on you, Eterna.
Morning, Milkit.
Good morning, Master.
I'm heading out now.
Have a nice day, Master.
Now... research facility ruins, huh?
Where do I even start looking?
SCREW YOU, YOU UGLY BITCH!
WANTED
FLUM THE MURDERER!!
GET LOST! MURDERER!
What is this?
Dein!
SCREW YOU, YOU UGLY BITCH!
WANTED
FLUM THE MURDERER!!
What's Dein trying to pull?
You there, the slave.
What?
You're coming with us.
Don't cause a scene.
Why? What do you want with me?
Don't tell me the royal army's
in cahoots with Dein as well!
If I go with them,
they'll frame me for sure.
But hurting the guard
is a serious crime, too.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
MEETINGS AND PARTINGS