Let's give them everything we've got.
Here we go.
Evilly!
Bloody!
Fantastic!
Neuntöte!
I wonder if those boys are really
doing their best to protect Lynn.
Miss Lynn. Protect.
Thank you very much, guys!
Little Red!
Please wake up, Little Red!
Lady Lynn?
What in the world happened to me?
You were fighting somebody
and got knocked out, Leah.
Protect.
Protecting.
Oh, that's right! The painting!
Huh?
It's gone?
What was it a painting of?
Alas, I was uncharacteristically taken
by surprise, so I didn't get a good look.
Watch out, Lynn!
Th-Thank you very much!
Not at all. I was simply returning
the marvelous favor.
They just keep coming, huh?
Assemble.
Take that.
There was a gentleman standing
in front of the painting.
It was almost as if the painting
thirsted for his blood.
The raw, ominous odor of blood filled
the room in a very, very un-marvelous way.
The painting wanted blood?
Lady Lynn, what next?
We go find Lord Arne, of course.
Then, a marvelous operation
to rescue Lord Vampire it is.
Right.
Lord Arne!
I'm impressed you've made it this far.
My compliments.
Of course I did.
I'm Lord Arne's assistant, after all.
And now, it is time for you to die.
I will not allow that.
You briefly managed to gain the upper hand
thanks to an underhanded ambush,
but I, Little Red Phantom Thief,
will marvelously finish you off
once and for all!
Lynn, let me handle this.
I'm on my way, Lord Arne.
Watch out!
Miss Lynn!
Protect!
Zombie guys!
Miss Lynn...
Protected.
Oh, zombie guys.
Thank you for your sacrifice.
Return Lord Arne to me now.
Looks like you've run out
of friends to protect you.
And you still think
you're going to rescue Neuntöte?
Now, you are no more than my plaything.
I can't control my body.
Pray tell, why do you go to
such extreme lengths to save him?
Because Lord Arne is Neuntöte,
the ultimate vampire,
and a magnificent detective who has
earned the trust and respect of many.
Trust and respect?
Additionally, Lord Arne puts
his faith in me as his assistant.
So I feel obliged to live up to that faith.
Preposterous.
Vampires are sublime beings
that rule over the entire world.
To us, humans are mere livestock.
Nothing but food.
It is inconceivable that one of us
would have faith in you as such.
You are mistaken.
While Lord Arne has not spoken
of it directly, I understand him.
Lord Arne is far too intelligent to
discriminate between humans and vampires
in such a vulgar way.
Lord Arne respects me
for the person I am.
He accepts me as Lynn Reinweiß.
And that, Mister Vlad, is what
makes you and him very different.
Spare me your delusions.
Neuntöte only made you his assistant
because he assumed
you would be a valuable tool.
If that is indeed the case...
If he did see some value in me,
I could not possibly be more honored.
Then, feel honored now...
to witness the spectacle
of Neuntöte's death.
You know...
If you enjoy dancing so much,
allow me to cut in.
For I make a marvelous partner.
Now, Lady Lynn. Hurry.
A-All right!
Lord Arne. I've finally made it.
Lord Arne!
Wh-What the...
Where the hell am I? Who the hell am I?!
I-I'm so sorry! I slipped.
Give it here.
What?
This.
I'm back, baby!
So we meet again, Vlad.
Is that you, Nachzehrer?
Oh, so now you remember me?
That supremely pisses me off!
Yup, this body seriously rocks.
Very nicely timed transformation there,
Lord Plushie.
Who are you calling a plushie?!
Obviously you, plushie.
What the hell is so funny?
I'm gonna eat you alive!
A red moon.
It's just like the moon on that night.
When you allowed me to see beyond
the boundaries of the tiny world I lived in.
It's just like that moon.
L-Lord Arne?
There.
Take that!
Did you get him?
He's simply far too resilient.
He ain't got a heart.
Huh?
This is becoming tedious.
Damn it.
I'm out of blood.
Are you guys okay?
Leah?
Nach? Amy?
Evilly!
Bloody!
Fantastic!
Neuntöte!
He's supreme! He can't be beat!
We think he's really, really neat!
And so vampire-y!
Would you quit fidgeting?
O-Oh, come on! I-I'm obviously acting out
'cause I'm so embarrassed!
Lynn! Arne!
Stand aside, Lynn Reinweiß.
Okay.
Are you that eager to
get captured again, Neuntöte?
What do you mean "captured"?
That was pretty much
the best nap I've ever had.
Lord Arne.
Search for it.
Well played.
But it seems you've reached your limit.
Not a chance.
And my assistant has found
something interesting.
So you found it?
Yes.
A portrait of Vlad himself.
I'm impressed you knew it was here.
I have the floor plan
of this entire castle memorized,
and while I was looking
at the place from outside,
I noticed a slight inconsistency.
I realized there must be
a hidden chamber,
which wouldn't have been
included on the map.
You'd be mistaken if you thought
you can fool the trained eye
of the vampire otaku
known as Lynn Reinweiß!
Do it.
Right!
Lynn!
Please stop, Lynn.
Stop right there.
Please stop.
Stop, honey.
It's time to stop.
Stop right meow.
Stop.
Just stop, okay?
May I ask you to stop what
you are doing, Mistress Lynn?
Lynn.
Lynn. My dear, beloved Lynn.
Come to me.
Father.
You are not my father.
Lynn?
This amulet protects against evil.
I already tested it on Nach
so I know it works.
It looks like it's effective
against you as well!
Wh-What do you intend to do with that?
I intend to do...
this!
Th-That was no mere amulet.
It was full of holy water mixed
with silver-infused paint.
Silver and holy water?
Vampires are susceptible
to both silver and holy water.
It's common knowledge.
Lord Arne.
He is Vlad the Third.
Vlad Țepeș.
Vlad the Impaler.
And one of the nine vampire kings.
He's Count Dracula—and this is his heart!
It's just as we suspected.
Evilly.
Bloody.
Fantastic.
Neuntöte.
When did you acquire
such a horrid weapon?
Right before I came to this castle.
Thank you kindly, kiddo.
Did you really think
I wouldn't know the weaknesses
of a super-major vampire
like Count Dracula?
Now...
Let's see you...
dance joyfully!
I warned you not to underestimate
Lynn Reinweiß.
We did it, Lord Arne.
Up you go.
That really is terrible.
How can you say that?
This is my ultimate masterpiece!
"Ultimate masterpiece," my fangs.
Nothing about this is artistic.
It's insulting.
Neuntöte. This was your idea, wasn't it?
You'd better not have put the heart
inside this painting, Zwei.
Not to worry, Lady Amy.
Lord Dracula's heart is safe and sound
inside Lord Vampire's body.
Well, well, Vlad. Looks like
you've seen better days, huh?
I could say the same about you.
The same?
But hey, look, I can move and stuff.
I never imagined a stuffed animal
would get the better of me.
Might as well sharpen my claws a bit.
Scratch, scratch.
Hmm? Hey. Cut that out, damn it.
Scratch, scratch, scratch.
Scratch, scratch, scratch, scratch,
scratch, scratch, scratch, scratch!
Stop clawing at me.
I said stop with the clawing.
Would you keep it down?
Hey.
So, Lord Arne, I guess nobody will ever
be hypnotized by Vlad's paintings again.
Most likely.
Hey, Arne.
Huh?
I went out and fetched
a new client for you, kiddo.
Already jumping into our next case!
I'd expect nothing less from Lord Arne.
Huh? It's already late, man.
Looks like it's nighty-night
for Lord Plushie.
I told you to quit calling me that!
Zwei, why not wait and hear
about the case tomorrow?
She's right, Arne. There are all sorts of
rumors in Lugenberg about the agency
being a really toxic workplace.
We must not delay!
This world is still packed
full of cases and mysteries
that can only be solved
by the Arne Detective Agency.
Isn't that right, Lord Arne?
What are you waiting for?
Let's get going, Lynn Reinweiß.
All right!
THE CASEBOOK OF ARNE
DRACULA'S FINAL CASE
PART 12: ALL'S WELL THAT ENDS WELL
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
TIMING: HENRY LIN
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: ELISABETH CRIST
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS