You coming by today?
Got work
When you're a Brave,
you can die at any moment.
Guys you saw alive yesterday
might be dead the next morning.
I'll admit that thinking about how the
same could happen to me gets me down.
The reason we started frequenting
Ed Cyrus's bar might've been
to distract ourselves from that reality...
Just 8,000 yen?
What a joke.
Scum of the Brave
A Brave's Special Training
Hey, it's been a while, Yashiro.
Malta the Mole
Unlicensed Brave
Pretty nippy today.
Barkeep, can you turn up the heat some?
Surprised to see you alive, Malta!
I thought for sure you were dead!
It's been six months, right?
Where are Joe and that bastard Ishino?
Joe's working, and I have
no clue about Ishino.
Haven't heard from him in a while,
so maybe he actually bought it for real.
Hey, Ed, gimme a glass, would you?
Hey, that's my beer.
Yeah? Cheers!
So, where've you been
for the last six months?
I'll have you know...
I got a job.
A job?!
I didn't even know you had an address!
This company is willing to make
contract employees out of guys like me.
They send us out to stand in line and
buy rare toys and tickets for events.
So, you're finally getting
out of the Brave biz!
That's the thing, though. I got fired.
My boss told me to sell some piece of crap
game hardware to honest old ladies.
Kinda messed up, right?
So I gouged the bastard's eyes out,
robbed the joint, and took off.
Well, that definitely
sounds like you, Malta.
Real wrath of god stuff.
Right?
So, today, I was hoping to see if I could
find any buyers for this thing I took.
A ticket to see King Rob in Japan!
The Seven Medallions: Grand
Winter Season Championships!
Are you serious?!
You want it that bad?
Damn right I do!
His Majesty King Rob
is a hero to guys like us!
He's a superhuman who's on a three
win streak with the world title!
I'll take it right now! How much?
Thirty grand.
If you don't want the tix,
I can see if Joe or Ishino do.
Hold up, hold up!
Can I pay you next month?
Sure can't. Right now, I don't even
have money for tomorrow's beer.
It's just, I've got a big
gig coming next month!
Yashiro, I would say...
That what you need is a gig right now.
We've been waiting for you, Master!
I heard you're tutoring now?
I'm impressed.
Practical exercises, Master!
Next week, the academy
will be testing us on swordplay.
It's a major event.
It will determine if we advance
to the next grade or get expelled!
Fight!
You win!
Which is why I was
hoping to receive
swordplay instruction
directly from you, Master!
Nope! Go home!
I was wanting to ask you too.
I can pay...
Is the chairman gonna be
after my head if I say no?
I'm not gonna snitch,
even if you say no.
My old man would probably be
relieved if I got expelled.
One less thing for him to worry about.
He sure sounds like a Brave.
Even if he's a real scumbag of a father.
That's right. He's scum.
Which is why I want to learn from you.
You're a strong Brave.
Plus, we can trust you.
Aki said as much.
Jogamine said that?
She must be crazy.
The thing is, a first-rate Brave like me
costs more than what some kids can—
Look, I'm a Brave, not a teacher.
Yes, we know.
I think I might even be bad at teaching.
Yes, I'm fairly certain of that!
The fee's 100,000 for all three of you!
I get paid, or no deal!
LOL EZ!!
How about 50 grand in advance, and
then the rest after the lessons?
Ten, twenty, thirty grand!
All right, let's get this over with.
We need a big space and
weapons to practice with.
Your school oughta do it.
Right! First thing
tomorrow morning, then—
No, right now.
But the schoolgrounds
are off-limits at night!
You think I care?
We'll sneak in.
You think someone who
can't bust into a school
will be able to get into
a Dark Lord's fortress?
Yeah, I think it's a good idea.
It sounds like real training!
Scum of the Brave
Tatami for the whole floor, huh?
They're rolling in it.
Thank you for your guidance!
I'm hoping to quickly learn
some kind of super move!
No such thing.
Super move? That's...
What?
It doesn't exist, damn it.
Anyway, put on your gear.
We'll start with sparring.
You can all come at me at once.
Right!
We just need to try
and hit you, Instructor?
What about you?
Not gonna wear any gear?
You guys do know I'm a pro, right?
Bring it already.
Right! Then I will take the honor
of being the first to strike!
Looks like Indo's got the initiative.
Nice spirit, but...
Coming straight in
is a little too obvious.
And now, the real star,
Jogamine, will go forth!
Again with the direct approach? Idiot.
Jogamine is up second...
Her style is about deflecting with that
shield and then going for a counter.
In her case...
Being obvious with the intent to counter
is a bad choice when dealing with
someone who can overpower you.
It makes you easy to throw off balance
and vulnerable in close quarters.
Granted, on E3, you'd probably
have more arm strength than me...
But, more importantly, could
you take this seriously?
No fair! You can't throw
your sword in a match!
That's the most naive, stupid
thing I've ever heard.
If it bothers you,
maybe try landing a hit.
Well, that was a good workout.
What the hell have you been doing, man?
You keep fighting dirty.
We can't use stuff like that in a match.
Yeah, it won't be much use.
But now I understand why
you three are failing.
How's that?
I'm impressed, Master!
As your first apprentice, I'll go first!
Please, offer your honest criticism!
Sure.
First up, Sara, you're too easily spooked.
Who are you calling chicken?!
Way to prove me right.
That brash attitude of yours tells me
you'd rather avoid fights outright.
During sparring, you're always
the third to make an attempt, right?
And it was always a
full-strength downward swing.
Because I wanted to take you down!
In other words, you want to end
the fight with one strike.
You don't want to be on the receiving
side, so you wanna end things early.
And if you think your chances
are bad, you give up easily.
Something tells me you were
trained this way, though.
A "don't pick a fight unless you
know you can win it" kind of thing.
Point being, you need to fix that.
The goal is winning, even if it means
taking the other guy down with you.
Next, Indo.
Your issue is...
Well, you don't have one.
Hell, I get the feeling you get
good marks in practice, too.
Yeah.
Yukine's trouble is academic stuff.
Doesn't even have her times tables down.
I do too.
Don't lie. When I was tutoring you,
you kept using some weird
code to figure things out.
That was a coincidence.
There's no such thing as "coincidences"
when it comes to multiplication, girl.
Not to mention—
Okay, that's enough chitchat!
From now on, you raise your
hand if you wanna talk!
Point is, Indo doesn't have
any major issues.
But, Instructor,
I want to get stronger.
And you're stronger than me right
now, so I want your advice.
Did you just say "right now"?
Cocky brat.
We'll get around to it later.
When is "later"?
Later is later.
Then there's Jogamine.
Yes, sir!
You're a total mess.
I don't even know where to begin.
Surely it's not that bad!
No, seriously...
It's like, first of all...
You fight like you're reluctant
to hurt or injure your opponent.
I noticed this when we ran into
the Count of Amber Thorns...
Do you really think you can do
this without killing anyone?
Because if that's true,
you shouldn't even be a Brave.
An issue like that goes beyond
something like ability.
But Master, I was taught that
Braves are meant to bring hope!
If you can maintain peace
without hurting anyone,
wouldn't that be the best option?
Being a Brave is already
a difficult path...
In that case, should we not always
strive for the ideal outcome?
Oh, she's got it bad.
Should I be harder on her?
What is this?
Her face...
Something about it...
H-Hey!
Yeah, we don't wanna get caught.
This works out, though.
Sara, Jogamine, I want the two of you
to beat these guys to keep them quiet.
The idea is overcoming your
issues in real combat.
If you screw up and get
caught, you're expelled.
Damn, maybe I'm better at
teaching than I thought?
But Master, even if it's for training,
the idea of harming innocent
security guards...
They let us sneak in on their watch,
so they're not that innocent.
Just think of them as
helping with your training.
I suppose it makes a kind of sense...
Damn it, Aki, don't buy into his nonsense!
Instructor, what about me?
You're good for now.
I can't accept not doing anything.
Will you train me more?
If you do as I say.
Go sit over there.
Fine.
I'm impressed, Yukine!
Even I'd be a little disturbed by—
You're sure it was in here?
This is it.
I know I saw some light.
You're so serious.
This is outside our contract, you realize?
But I guess it's fine.
How about we grab something
to eat after this?
It could be related to
the guy from yesterday.
And they were pretty skilled.
I guess.
I'm still aching, actually.
How about you help me recuperate?
See, they already ran off.
We didn't need to bother...
Not another word, Ido.
That woman's voice...
It's ether fried.
Happens to addicts who become
Dark Lords through shady surgeries
or do an illegal amount of E3.
From what they're saying,
I doubt they're teachers
or security guards.
They might be close still.
I'll find them.
Now, go!
That hurt, damn it!
She actually went on the offensive.
I really am a good teacher.
Eh, maybe not.
That woman's pretty good, though.
What the—ouch!
Trespasser! Are you an
enemy of the academy?!
State your name!
Just hit him, dummy.
Students? What the hell
are you doing here?
Indo, heads up.
These guys know what they're doing.
We're getting out of here!
Go ahead and use E3!
Do I kill them?
Dummy. Just cover Jogamine
and get out of here.
Got it.
Come on, don't chicken
out on me! On your feet!
You...
It hurts...
Damn it!
Again with this?!
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Next Time
Master! There's been no response
to the message I sent Ishino-san!
Actually, it looks unread!
You really shouldn't contact him
anymore. Guy's whole thing is—
Next time, Episode 7: "Death of a Brave"!
Death of a Brave
Listen to me, damn it!