Plant the seedlings, let them take root
Weak roots and weak hearts
Sink your legs into the mud
and bend your back
Thin sprouts and thin bodies
With empty stomachs we wish
for golden fields
Plant the seedlings, let them take root
The weeds are disappearing into the earth.
Wheels for striking rice paddies...
It's a tilling machine.
This will save us
a lot of time and effort.
You've created another great invention.
I'm glad to be useful.
Now let's get weeding again.
Of course.
I will publish a new book for
Sakuna by the end of the year.
KOKOROWA'S RICE-FARMING DIARY
PART TWO
Kokorowa!
I made treats.
They're beautiful.
What is that?
Those blades won't last long,
so I made new ones.
You did? You have my thanks.
I can't write.
I should be able to finish writing
about growing rice.
Oh, no. The rain
is making the water rise.
Are you okay, Kokorowa?
Sakuna, the rice.
Don't worry. I'll handle it.
They were so small at first.
They've grown so much.
I'm not struggling to grow rice
thanks to Sakuna and her friends.
Tauemon, does this
look adequately drained?
Yes.
It's about time to add
the water back in.
Wouldn't more stems produce more rice?
The offshoots divide
their ability to grow,
making the grains smaller.
I see.
Minimizing the number of stems
produces good, large grains.
It also keeps the soil firm,
making the rice easier to harvest.
The harvest...
Now that they've grown this much,
we need only maintain course
until the harvest.
I hope you're right.
What?
When the temperature rises,
the rice will grow rapidly.
But the rice isn't
the only thing that will grow.
What is that?
Straight swift larva.
Large numbers of insects will appear,
including plant hoppers and stink bugs.
Insects?
It's beautiful.
I'm exhausted.
Lady Kokorowa.
Good evening.
Your clothes... Where did you go today?
To Rockslide Passage,
to look for Flaming Cores.
The foot of the volcano?
But it's so dangerous.
Why would you do that?
Mixing them into fertilizer
helps control pests.
I didn't find any this time, though.
Surely pests aren't a concern
if the plants look this nice.
Weeds can be removed by hand,
but not bugs.
There's no such thing
as being too careful.
It happened before I was born.
There was an unprecedented
famine that affected thousands.
It was caused by pests.
Straight swift larva.
Straight swift larva?
Those small insects I see sometimes?
Indeed.
But in large numbers, they cause
wilting and ruin rice plants.
We've been fine until now,
but who knows what would happen to us
if that happened on Hinoe Island?
We've got the goddesses of harvest
and invention on the island.
We can overcome any problem.
We have nothing to fear.
You're right.
At very least, I'm sure we'll be fine
with Sakuna helping us.
What could be more dependable
than two goddesses on our side?
Right?
The rice...
It's sprouting.
I must tell Sakuna.
Sakuna.
I have news.
The field...
Yours, too?
What's the damage?
Damage?
I came to tell you my rice is sprouting.
I see. So your field is fine.
What happened?
They wilted.
Those are the wilted plants?
This is just the beginning.
The plants affected by straight
swift larva are wilting instantly.
What will happen to the plants?
Not only will they not produce rice,
but the whole field could be affected.
No...
Oh, no.
Here, too?
I'm worried that this happened so soon.
What do you mean?
Straight swift larva
mostly show up in the fall.
But this time, they appeared
right after the rice sprouted.
If it's this bad now,
they could multiply
to even greater numbers.
And then...
What happens then?
This year's Amahoho crop
could fail completely.
Sakuna, I'm going to take
another look at my field.
Okay.
Let's cut the wilted plants.
As you wish.
I'm sorry, Kokorowa.
Not at all.
I'm glad the damage
didn't spread further.
Anyway, what are we going to do?
It's only summer.
What's going to happen in the fall?
We'll have a drastically reduced harvest.
Lady Sakuna...
Sakuna?
Kokorowa?
What are you doing here at night?
You're going to look for
Flaming Cores, aren't you?
I didn't find any in Rockslide Passage.
I'm going further up the volcano.
Please take me with you.
I appreciate the sentiment, but no.
But...
This is all I can do.
You should do what only you can do, too.
I'd prefer that.
What only I can do?
Lady Toyohana's scrolls on agriculture...
Perhaps there's something in here.
Sakuna.
I'm back, Kokorowa.
No, wait. Good morning.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Here.
Incredible. You actually found one.
I searched all night,
and this is all I found.
It's only enough for one row of rice.
I'm thinking about
searching elsewhere, too.
Sakuna, I have a suggestion.
When was the last time we performed
the Mushiokuri ceremony?
The fields have already suffered
damage. Isn't it too late?
This method was described
in my mother's scrolls.
It's a bit different from
the ceremony we performed.
Is that oil?
Yeah.
We're going to scatter this
toad oil all over the fields.
We pound the rice with mighty blows
And say farewell to pests
Send off the pests and dance
Let the golden flowers bloom
Why can't I come up with any ideas?
I've experienced so
many aspects of growing rice.
Again.
So I didn't just imagine it.
Is that a dragon?
What is that?
That's not a dragon.
It's a swarm of plant hoppers.
Why are they swarming around the boat?
Did I bring the swarm with me?
But why are there so many?
I'll burn them away.
A demon insect?
Is it absorbing the plant hoppers?
Then I shall defeat it.
Automatons!
I...
Um, that's...
This is fantastic!
What?
It's really interesting!
R-Really?
Did you write this?
N-No, it wasn't me.
I see.
I wonder who wrote this.
I'd love to read what happens next.
Why am I recalling the past now?
Kokorowa!
We made it in time.
Sakuna and Tama.
Are you all right?
That must've turned it into a demon.
I thought I destroyed all
the barrier stones.
Kokorowa, you did well on your own.
No, I caused all of this.
The plant hoppers I brought on
my ship made that demon insect.
You did nothing wrong. He did.
Pests come with growing rice.
It's not your fault.
Now, let's beat that thing and go home.
Okay.
I-Incredible...
You're mine!
What is this?
Sakuna!
Sakuna needs help if we're to defeat it.
Your Highness!
Sakuna!
The Mushiokuri ceremony!
That's it.
Kokorowa!
Got it!
Sakuna?
Sakuna!
Sakuna...
Good grief.
Now let's go home.
I can barely stay awake.
Kokorowa? What's wrong?
I can't breathe.
Sakuna, you're always
coming to my rescue.
Of course. I'm your best friend.
I understand now why I couldn't write.
K-Kokorowa, I can't breathe.
It's time to harvest the rice.
They look fine. They're ready to harvest.
Your rice looks great.
Th-Thank you.
Don't be so stiff.
You can do it, Lady Kokorowa.
Do it!
Like this, Kokorowa.
Crouch down and grab
the rice plants with your hand.
Let's see...
Sakuna, I...
You're doing good.
Thank you.
Ta-da!
We're having new rice tonight?
Yes, but not just any new rice.
It's Kokorowa's new rice.
This is the white rice I grew?
That's right.
Kokorowa, you grew this
rice from start to finish.
Okay, everyone. Let's eat.
Let's eat!
What do you think, Kokorowa?
It's so good!
Glad to hear it.
RICE CULTIVATION STORY
KOUSHI OBOROZUKI
You needn't thank me, Koushi Oborozuki.
I shall keep waiting until the
day I get to meet the real you.
RICE CULTIVATION STORY
KOUSHI OBOROZUKI
What I really wanted to write
wasn't something for Sakuna.
I wanted to write about you,
my dear friend.
I hope this year's rice is good, too.
Yes.