Whew, I'm full!
The Demon Defense Force again?
I just consumed Mira,
so I don't have room for seconds.
Mune ga shizunde mirai kanjirenaku nattari
Toki ga tomatte mou owatta tte kanjitari
Fusagikonde hanasenakute
Jiwari kokoro no kasa ga hiraita
Soredemo tsuyogatte ikiteta
Nagusamete nante iwanai
Tsuyoku natte mae o mitetainda
Dakedo yowasa ga oshitsubusu
Kimi ni atte sekai afurete hikari ataetekuretari
Sukoshi datte kibou nakatta boku ga waraetetanda
Nanigenai kaiwa de zutto egao ataetekuretari
Arigatou tte terete warau kara iwanai yo
Dakedo omotteru yo
Kono saki mae muite ikeru kana?
Hikari yo, boku ni
Yokohama Showdown
Episode 10
Whew, I'm full!
The Demon Defense Force again?
I just consumed Mira,
so I don't have room for seconds.
Gorgeous power.
Mira's skills certainly are
fitting of a commander!
How dare you!
Now then...
Let me hear it!
Praise the glorious Kuusetsu!
Wild Mountain Cherry Blossoms!
I'm telling you...
that won't work!
She managed to stop
my lightning-fast slash attack?!
You thought that was enough
to fight a god?
Just so you know,
at their full power, the rest of the
Eight Thunder Gods are stronger than I am.
Well, I'm going to
surpass them eventually.
The only reason you're still alive
is 'cause Big Sis Shikoku thought ahead.
You. You're Yuuki Wakura, yes?
Turning down my lovely invitation earlier?
You've got some nerve.
Let's pick up where we left off
in our current forms.
Are you kidding me?!
I'm going to make you mine.
Any woman who gets near my brother...
won't live to tell the tale!
Big Sis!
A new challenger?
I can feel Coco and Naon's energies.
They're inside of her!
The people she assimilated
are still alive?
Then that means-
We'll force her to purge Mira
and the others!
Right!
This is where we put Kuusetsu down!
Can you still say that once you see this?
I consumed Mira.
So I can use her ability now.
Shall I destroy the city
and put a new god on the map?
Time for the ace up my sleeve!
Follow the person in front of you
and keep moving!
Sector Three to HQ.
We're nearly finished
evacuating the residents.
What is that thing?!
Is that a... Shuuki?!
Holy... It's enormous!
I didn't know they could get that big!
Don't let it intimidate you, Yuuki!
Looks like Mira made a miscalculation
keeping me here!
Mira made the right decision.
If we let you escape,
it'll be too risky to deal with you later.
So instead,
she gets consumed and
we throw a clone party?
We are the Demon Defense Force!
The real battle begins now!
Lady Ren!
We're ready to send reinforcements
to Yokohama!
Our finest combat specialists!
Now allow me to reiterate!
Kuusetsu! This is where you die!
I'm going to trample you
with my godly army!
I am the Supreme Commander
of the Demon Defense Force!
Give it your best shot, I dare ya!
Supreme Commander...
Supreme Commander?
So she's the top dog?
That makes her worth beating!
Hey, wait!
They took the bait.
We'll draw them over to the bridge.
Keep us ahead of them.
Aw, jeez. What a bunch of sheep.
There are less of them now!
We owe Miss Tovera big time!
Should we get in there, too?
Good. All the cars are cleared out, too.
Take us down.
Okay.
There's a lot of 'em.
Buy me some time.
You got it.
Here goes!
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam!
The Great One!
Feather bullets...
They're no joke.
Battering my hands to pieces in seconds...
Fine, then!
I'll just keep summoning new hands!
They'll serve as our tank!
How long will you last?
Can't wait to find out!
That's enough divine punishment, I think.
Wow, you're a stubborn one!
But you're already exhausted.
Let's finish it off with ten more seconds!
How about a visit
from a hail of godly gunfire?!
All in favor?
Aye!
Stand down, Maia.
I'm ready to soak it up.
Ephemeral!
What did... you do?
I stole your life force.
Azuma Years
Ephemeral
Direct Contact
Ephemeral: Direct Contact!
Excellent work, Lady Tovera.
Nice job standin' your ground, Maia.
Feels like my senses
are in their prime again!
Lady Ren!
According to the report we received,
they succeeded
at dividing the enemy's forces.
However, Yokohama's still in trouble...
Yes, I'm aware.
I'll use my ability to join the fight
from Washington.
Ren's ability:
All-Encompassing Lord of the Cosmos.
She boosts her power by reflecting
the same ability in both of her eyes.
What you did just now...
Did you aim it at Japan?
It won't hit any aircraft,
so there's no need to worry.
Using an ability that powerful,
and she didn't even break a sweat.
My subordinates will handle the rest.
Let's continue our meeting.
Ren Yamashiro...
She truly is Earth's answer.
The emergency exit is this way!
Protecting the injured
should be prioritized above all else!
Oh, look!
Shouldn't you be a little more concerned
about that thing?
It's got a pretty brutal ability.
Y'see-
Huh?
The Supreme Commander.
She sent cover fire from America.
It was too big.
An easy target.
That was my ace in the hole...
That was the ace in the hole
that Big Sis Shikoku gave me!
Yuuki!
On it!
Ame-no-Mitori.
It's got range!
Nice work!
Miss Tenka!
During battle, the briefest words
can hold the most meaning.
And Yuuki's feelings hit the mark!
My clones are slow and clumsy.
Perhaps it takes practice to master.
That said, my real body...
isn't so harmless!
What are you doing... to my sister?!
Where did that power come from?!
This one was a clone, too!
I'm right over here!
Looks like phasing works better in combat
than my slime ability.
What are you doing...
TO MY BROTHER?!
Now you get...
all my power...
in one shot!
I got her?!
You're as strong as a commander, too.
She's started setting traps
by hiding her clones in the ground.
I'll take care of your backup
after I finish you off.
'Cause I can keep on fighting forever.
Yuuki...
Activate your Heavenward form.
I think that's our only option!
Be sure and make the most of it!
Yes, ma'am!
I get to see your trump card now?
Yuuki?
Yuuki...
HEAVENWARD
Heavenward!
Miss Mira... I'm on my way to save you!
Love beam!
Shiritai teka shitai furetai
Afuredasu kono omoi wa tomannai janai
Amai amai sono karada de uketomete ne darling
Kainarashite ageru gohoubi no jikan
Kasaneawasu hada to hada kara umareru netsu de
Juuden max
Ima hassha OK!
Kono te kara ima love love beam
Sono heart megake ima love love beam
Kokoro no kyori mo tobikoeteku
Zero kyori de hanate
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
Nigasanai wa mou love love beam
Sekai no hate mademo love love beam
Sou ai koso ga sekai o kaeru
Kurayami mo somero heart iro ni
A tremendous torrent of power.
Seems Yuuki Wakura
also has a lot of potential.
I like that.
If Himari drags her feet,
then perhaps I'll send in the others
to help lock him down.
Hmm...
First, I can take the lead
and teach 'em the basics...
More enemies on the way!
Oh good!
Let's do this!
We're in the homestretch!
Slave: Heaven
Episode 11
Next time!
Episode 11, "Slave: Heaven"
For today's bonus...
Your present. Is. Me!
I've always wanted to try this!
I hope you'll accept
the chocolates... and me!