Who are you supposed to be?
His name is Namu-san.
He's a great psychic whose powers are
so strong, he can't settle in one place.
Your powers don't work
on normal human beings.
This is exactly why monsters
can't live among humans.
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 9: People Who Can See Them Aren't Scary?
My parents abandoned me
for being different.
This is Namu-kun.
He'll be joining us from today.
Let's all help him feel welcome.
Nice to meet you, Namu-kun.
My name is—
Momoko.
That's what the person hanging
behind you is calling you.
Momoko. Momoko.
They're hanging onto your shoulders.
You must feel the weight.
I'll get rid of it for you.
He's super weird.
He's a freak.
Maybe he's got a screw loose?
This is why his parents left him.
Punishment Room
Being around everyone was exhausting,
so the punishment room was perfect
for me, since I could be alone there.
I won't say mean things
\h\h\h\hto my friends anymore.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
I truly regret what I did, and hope I can
make up with my friends. I understand this
is home to others who each have their own...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
I feel profound remorse when looking back on who I was until yesterday.
I understand that my actions and words caused distress and harm to others
at the facility, and I deeply regret that. Moving forward, I am determined
to make a fresh start and become a better person.
First, I would like to sincerely apologize for repeatedly making careless
remarks towards my friends who live at the same care facility, and for
causing them harm as a result. I regret allowing my own anxiety and painful
experience turn into anger in my words. Moving forward, I want to focus on
respecting others' feelings and building relationships where we understand
one another.
I further express my deep remorse for repeatedly behaving and speaking
in ways that caused fear among the staff and fellow residents. They are here
to support us and deserve our respect. Going forward, I will remember this,
work cooperatively, and make an effort to build a safe and mutually
supportive environment.
I fully acknowledge that my past actions resulted in my isolation from those
around me. From now on, I will actively engage in communication, cooperate
with others, and strive to create a community filled with mutual support
and smiles. I sincerely pledge to become someone who brings positive
influence to others through my words and actions, and who treats everyone
with respect. I am truly sorry for
truly
sorry
for
People are unforgiving of things
they don't understand.
Don't mess with me! The heck is your problem?
They ran every evaluation on me
and had me on all kinds of medications.
Oh, you mean that rumor?
Room 313, was it? The room upstairs?
Yes, precisely. Do you happen
to know anything about it?
They say patients who get
put in there attempt suicide.
Word is, they smash their heads
against the wall.
I see. I'd love to hear the details—
Behind you! Look behind you!
Huh?
Huh? I'm still alive?
Oh, you're awake, huh?
You're lucky those bushes broke your fall.
Who are you?
My apologies.
This should answer your question.
A "psychic"?
Yup. I've been investigating the rumor
that an evil spirit haunts this room.
That's when I encountered you, just as you
were about to become its next victim.
You got lucky this time, but it will
happen again if you stay in this room.
But never fear! I, the psychic
Mob Osamu, will protect you, Namu-san.
Eek!
Excuse me! Don't go entering places
without permission!
Get him out of here.
On it.
W-W-W-Wait! Hold up! Wait a minute!
Let's go, pal.
He's the victim of an unknown threat!
What was that man's problem?
He's just loopy, that one.
That's right.
People would just call me crazy
if I talked about what I see.
And he thought I tried to kill myself
because I was possessed?
Not even close.
Still, calling it a fall
is pretty pathetic, too.
But I guess no one would care
either way if I lived or died.
I don't even care myself.
I, the psychic Mob Osamu,
will protect you, Namu-san.
Nobody asked you to.
Listen carefully.
This is a protective talisman.
Execute
at once
Put this and some salt
at each corner of the bed. Plop!
Execute
at once
At the very least,
this area will be protected.
However! If the salt loses its shape,
discolors, or gathers dust,
it'll have the opposite effect.
If that happens, replace it with fresh—
Hey, mister.
Yes?
Everyone's making fun of you.
Doesn't that bother you?
Good grief. Listen to yourself.
We all perceive the world
in slightly different ways.
When that gap becomes too vast,
it's natural for people to feel uneasy
or want to deny what's being said.
It's no one's fault, and it's not
something I need to feel ashamed about.
That's a pretty self-serving way
to look at it.
And yet, Namu-san, you're not
rejecting my presence. Why is that?
No reason.
I'm just killing time.
You again? How do you keep getting in?
H-How? Well, um, that is to say, uh...
Get out! I'm seriously
gonna call the cops!
Stay strong!
I promise I'll protect you—
Come on now. You've babbled long enough.
You're pretty strong, aren't you?
"We all perceive the world
in slightly different ways."
Up until he said that, I thought I was
the only one who saw a different world.
Execute
\hat once
What are these? They're totally fake.
Still, we should avoid this
turning into a long battle.
Let's do a stakeout and wrap it up fast.
The plan is simple and straightforward.
I'll be on standby in the room next door.
If anything happens, he'll knock
to signal me, and I'll charge in.
Then, with my homemade
exorcism spray...
Time to put my skills to work!
Purify
Sh-Shame on me!
What are you doing, mister?
Namu-san!
Th-Thank goodness you're all right!
This isn't what we agreed on.
I'm terribly sorry!
I promised I'd come immediately when
I heard a knock on the wall. So I'm very—
Yeah, so...
Why were you banging on the wall?
Huh? Uh, no.
I-I didn't...
N-Namu-san, what room is this?
Huh?
Room 313.
Oh, you mean that rumor?
Room 313, was it?
They say patients who get
put in there attempt suicide.
Word is, they smash their heads
against the wall.
Mister, what do you see?
E-Everything's going to be okay.
I-I'm a p-p-psy...
I'm a psychic here to protect you.
Namu-san, run—
Mister?
What made me think I could
take on something like this?
H-Help me!
No, Namu-san! This room is dangerous!
You have to leave at once!
Thanks for looking after me.
Oh, no, don't mention it!
But for a so-called psychic,
you suck at dealing with ghosts, mister.
So...
Starting today, I'm your master
and you'll be my student.
Got it, Osamu-kun?
Chie-sensei Isn't Scary
I can't just sit back while my student
gets involved in something so dangerous.
Kaya-chan!
Kaya!
I'm sorry. It's because
I took my eyes off her.
No, it's my fault for
stopping you to chat.
I'll look over there.
I'll check that side.
H-He's...
Stop!
You're N-Namu-san, right?
Where are you taking Kaya-chan?
I'm pretty strong, you know.
That's awfully rich.
You're the one who left this in the crowd.
What were you gonna do
if someone saw her like this?
I guess she's never run into a problem
she couldn't fix with brute force.
She doesn't even know
how to retract her claws.
Figures. She's a monster
that's barely hatched.
Kaya-chan!
It's okay. I'm right here with you.
You don't have to be afraid.
Let's go back to your daddy, okay?
It's okay. You're safe.
What's with that "I'll protect you,
no matter what" attitude of yours?
Are you obsessed with it?
Or is that how you tame it?
Quite impressive, Sensei.
Cut it out already!
"Barely hatched"? "Tame"?
She's not an animal.
Besides, aren't you also
a psychic yourself?
Well, I don't know about that.
Huh?
Sensei, did you honestly believe
everything that child said from the start?
If you hadn't seen "them" yourself,
how would you have treated her?
There you go saying "No" again.
You can't just say "No" to everything.
When someone deviates
too far from the norm,
they're marked as defective
and cast aside.
They then get slapped with
a plausible label like "psychic."
But even deviation has degrees.
It exists on a spectrum.
And when it tips too far,
you're practically dealing with a beast.
Even I find it hard to
recognize her as a fellow human.
Osamu-kun worships her like she's divine,
but nothing born into that family
could ever be so benevolent.
It's something far more
malevolent instead.
What do you mean?
And how would you know that?
Because...
I'm Ebisumori Namu, I guess.
Ebisumori?
Tell me, Sensei.
That thing you're holding so dearly...
Are you sure it's what
you believe it to be?
What are you doing?!
Watch closely, Sensei.
This is what a woman from
the Ebisumori family really is.
This is what's inside Sato Kaya.
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan, stay with me.
Kaya-chan!
What did you do to her?
What are you talking to?
This is Sato Kaya.
Huh?
The thing you call "Kaya-chan"
is a specter from the Ebisumori family
wrapped in human skin.
For generations, Ebisumori's eldest
daughter, the shrine maiden,
has carried a power beyond the ordinary.
While its intensity varies,
the power manifests
when the shrine maiden's
inner self is replaced by a specter.
And I can see the change.
That's why I know.
The "inner self" of that thing
has been completely replaced.
There's not a trace of
the human element left.
For generations, the family has claimed
this aberrant power as its own,
discarding whatever doesn't suit them.
And in the end, they have become
specters themselves, it seems.
Hasumi Chie
I couldn't care less if they self-destructed,
dragging the entire family down.
The problem is Osamu-kun is totally
enthralled with this thing, just like you.
She's so amazing
I can't contain myself
Kaya-sama is supreme
And to protect his life,
I will exorcise this specter.
Do you get it now? The "Sato Kaya"
you're trying to protect...
never existed in the first place.
You're a victim of this, too, Sensei.
You've been through a lot
of scary things, haven't you?
I'll take care of it. If you need the
body, go ahead and take it.
Although having her listed as "missing"
is probably the easiest option—
Are you out of your mind?
Take it back.
Huh?
Take it back!
Kaya-chan's not human?
You don't know anything about her!
Kaya-chan is...
She's...
I don't want to change.
But you can't eat lunch
in those dirty clothes.
Fine, I won't.
Oh, come on. Please?
She's in total stickler mode.
She's not gonna bend.
She's been doing so well lately.
What a mess.
Shush.
At least tell me why
you don't want to change.
Wouldn't understand.
What?
It's not like you'd understand anyway!
Huh?
Kaya-chan.
Chie-sensei?
I did some thinking.
Could it be you don't want to change
because you really like that outfit?
Huh? Wrong.
Then, are you shy about getting changed?
Nope.
You're just in the mood
to stay muddy all day?
That's not it at all.
It's not?
Why are you asking me?
Because I want to get
to understand you, Kaya-chan.
But I wasn't even close, huh?
Sensei...
You don't hate me?
Why would I? I love you
so much, Kaya-chan.
Long sleeves.
I wanna wear long sleeves. Because...
I turn black.
But the other teacher
said I was being selfish.
I didn't know what she meant.
But as long as I could feel
her inner struggle,
the meaning of her words didn't matter.
You probably don't understand because
you only pay attention to the surface.
So what if she's a specter inside?
No matter what you say,
it doesn't change the fact
that Kaya-chan gets angry, struggles,
feels joy, and laughs, like anyone else.
She has a human heart.
And if you're still going to treat her
like a monster, I'll make you pay.
I'll protect Kaya-chan, no matter what!
I'll be the one who
protects you, Kaya-chan.
Huh? What's happening?
Tch. It got too close to the body.
After I finally managed to separate it...
Can I pull it off again?
This is...
Chie-sensei.
Kaya-chan! It's you, right, Kaya-chan?
I...
I got lost!
You must've been scared
all by yourself. You're safe now.
Let's go find your daddy together, okay?
Daddy!
Kaya!
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Thank you for finding her.
Not at all. I'm glad she's all right.
Bye-bye, Chie-sensei.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Don't tell me you're still trying
to do something to Kaya-chan.
I'm not. Or more like, I can't.
I can only deal
with spiritual things.
I can intervene if the specter's
out of control and fully manifested.
But I can't do anything
if it's contained within a vessel.
How did you put it back inside?
Are you in that line of work?
Of course not.
Something must have made her
genuinely want to return to this world.
I'll protect Kaya-chan, no matter what!
I, the psychic Mob Osamu,
will protect you, Namu-san.
That sounds just like
a normal human being.
It looks like I need to do
a little more research.
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
The reason Kaya-chan's skin turns black
when she defeats a specter
is because what's inside her pierces
through her skin and becomes visible.
She doesn't understand why it happens,
but she's aware that her skin darkens.
That's why she wears long-sleeve shirts
and pants all year round,
and even her swimsuits
give her extra coverage.