Sato
Again! Again!
Aw, but Daddy's tired.
Um, just one more time.
Okay, one more time.
Up you go!
Okay, that's enough now.
We have something important
to tell you, Kaya.
What is it?
Kaya, you're going
to be a big sister soon.
Big sister?
There's a little baby
inside Mommy's tummy.
The baby's still very small, so let's
take good care of it together. Okay?
Will it make you happy
if we're nice to the baby, Mommy?
Yup. Very happy.
Kaya.
Mean? Selfish? Or just different?
There are children who are
seen that way by others.
But what if that child could
see something you couldn't?
This is the story of Kaya-chan,
a girl who could see ghosts.
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 7: Hospitals Aren't Scary
There's a possibility of
threatened preterm labor.
Given your previous delivery
was an emergency C-section,
I think it'd be best if you stayed
in the hospital for today,
so we can closely monitor
your condition and the baby's.
I have to stay in?
Let's do what the doctor recommends.
Don't worry about things
at home. Right, Kaya?
Huh?
Yeah.
I was too anxious to sleep
when I was pregnant with Kaya.
Doctor, please do everything you can
to make sure this baby is born healthy.
Of course. We'll get
through this together.
Kids'
Room
Wow. Very good, Kaya-chan.
Thank you for looking after her.
Daddy's going to get Mommy's
clothes and some other things she needs,
so you stay here
and be a good girl. Okay, Kaya?
Okay.
She's in good hands.
Bye, Daddy.
What's the matter, Kaya-chan?
Bathroom.
Want me to go with you?
I can go by myself.
No!
My baby! My baby! My baby!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Where's my baby?! My baby!
Where did my baby go?!
Not this one! Not this one!
Help!
Please, someone!
My baby!
Bring me my baby!
Man, not again. What should we do?
Should we check up on her?
There's nothing we can do.
Things would've been different
if only her baby had been born healthy.
I really do feel sorry for her.
No! No! No! None of these are mine!
My baby doesn't look like this!
Go away! My baby... My baby is...
Where'd my baby go? My baby...
The ghosts are all gone now.
Th-Thank you.
Is there a baby inside your tummy, too?
Y-Yes, there is.
Of course there is.
I'm certain I have a baby!
In Surgery
She's hemorrhaging!
Ready the transfusion!
Heart rate dropping!
Run it wide open and start vasopressors!
Where's my baby? Where'd my baby go?
My baby!
Where are you?
There...
There you are.
I'll take the baby.
That's right. My baby
was too small to even cry.
Oh god. There's no pulse.
Start ventilation.
Begin chest compressions.
Before I could really see
my baby's face, I...
Thank goodness. I finally found you.
Thank goodness.
Oh? What are you doing here?
You shouldn't go into rooms by yourself.
I'm sorry.
You're from the daycare, aren't you?
Let's go back there.
Okay.
Bye-bye... Huh?
What's the matter?
Where's the baby with its mommy?
What?
Don't try to scare me like that.
Postmortem
Examination
Report
Hemorrhagic Shock
Placental
Abruption
weeks pregnant
There's no one...
Hemorrhagic Shock
Placental Abruption
...staying in this room.
Thanks for looking after her.
Have a good evening.
Yes. She had to be hospitalized.
Right.
Yup.
Regarding my daughter, I was thinking
of talking to her teacher tomorrow.
Okay. Thanks for your help.
We don't know how long
it'll be before she's stabilized.
So yeah, Mom, could I ask you to...
I know it's really out of the blue.
What about tomorrow?
She's not even in elementary school yet.
I can't leave her home alone.
Okay.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Sato Shizuo-sama
I sincerely apologize for showing up
so suddenly that day. I hope Kaya-chan
and Mirai are both doing well.
Please feel free to contact me if there's
anything you need.
Ebisumori Nana
Never mind. I'll handle it.
Ebisumori
Nana
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Playground Equipment
Isn't Scary
Mori-no-Oka Park
Everyone, don't hurt yourselves.
Follow all the rules when playing
on the playground equipment.
Listen to your teachers!
Kaya-chan, let's go on the jungle gym!
The spinning one!
Yeah.
Wha?!
The spinning jungle gym is gone!
Why isn't it here, Sensei?!
Oh, you're right.
They remove stuff as soon as
anything happens these days.
It's sad how things keep getting removed
and nothing new gets added.
Oh well. Let's play somewhere else.
The slide at the park is my favorite!
Let's go on it together, Kaya-chan.
Okay.
Vroom, vroom! Move over!
Hey, Ken-ken! No cutting!
Hey! It says you can't do that!
Let's follow the rules and play nicely
Let's wait our turn
Sit down before sliding
Don't climb from
the opposite side
Do not
jump off
Let's follow the rules and play nicely
See? It says, "Let's follow
the rules and play nicely."
Hmph. I'm telling Teach—
Saku-chan?
What's wrong?
Saku-chan, are you okay?
Huh? Why do you ask?
I'm just looking at the sign.
Oh, hey, Kaya-chan.
Huh?
I have a great idea!
That slide's way more fun
if you go down headfirst!
No!
Look. It says it right here.
Sit down before sliding
See? "Sit down before sliding."
Seeing that just makes me
wanna do it even more.
Ah, Saku-chan!
This looks fun!
Watch me do it, Kaya-chan!
Saku-chan!
Let's do it our way.
Sliding the normal way is boring.
I know, right?
Wouldn't climbing up
from down here be awesome?
That'd be so cool.
That sounds super fun!
I'm gonna do it!
Do it! Do it!
Saku-chan, no!
Huh? What's up, Kaya-chan?
Stop!
You'll crash into him!
I can't hear you!
We're gonna crash!
Gross! There's sand in my mouth!
Have you learned your lesson, Saku-chan?
It said on the sign, didn't it? What'd
it say about sliding down headfirst?
It said not to.
And going the wrong way up!
You can get seriously hurt
crashing into someone!
We're sorry.
Don't ever do it again!
Okay.
So strong.
Whew. What happened at the park
scared me for a second.
Kids really do some
dangerous things on impulse.
Makes sense why the
equipment gets removed.
Does it though?
Huh?
Does getting rid of playground
equipment prevent accidents?
At this rate, all the equipment will
be gone before there are any accidents.
Agreed.
No matter what you do,
kids will have impulsive moments.
Look, Daddy! Aren't I so cool?
Yeah. You're very cool.
Really?
Look, I can even stand up
without holding on to anything—
That's why adults need
to keep a close eye on them.
Staying Home Alone Isn't Scary?
Hanamugi Kindergarten
Bye, Sensei.
See you tomorrow.
I'm here to pick up Sato Kaya.
Oh, hello... Uh...
You really came.
Hi, Auntie Nana.
Just call me Nana. Hello.
I'm here on behalf of her father.
I'm Kaya's aunt, Nana.
Guardian ID
For: Sato Kaya
Hanamugi Kindergarten
Did nobody tell you about me?
Oh, sorry about that.
I'm Hasumi Chie, and
I'm in charge of the middle-year class.
Let me check.
"Chie"?
Her aunt? Well, she does look
exactly like Kaya-chan.
Your name was in the visitor log
at my mother's nursing home.
Huh?
How much do you know about Kaya?
No!
Huh?
I see now!
How terrible!
Ebisumori-san?
Why?
G-Grandmother? She's...
Sato
Kaya
Nana... What happened to Nana?
Sh-She... She didn't do anything wrong!
It's all my fault!
S-So if you're going
to kill anyone, kill me!
Only take me!
Sato
Kaya
Nana is...
How could you say something
like that to a child?!
H-How much? Uh...
I don't know what she's asking,
but I shouldn't say what I saw.
Oh, you mean how she's doing at school?
I can tell you what I know.
A kindergarten teacher doesn't visit
a student's grandmother for no reason.
You had some motive for approaching
her relatives, didn't you?
I'm sorry, but I don't know what you mean.
You're probably mistaking
me for somebody else.
Well, no matter.
Still, you'd be wise not to snoop around.
In this world, there are things
ordinary folk can do nothing about.
Meddling will only bring you misfortune.
Do not look at it.
You'll attract it.
She's so small and doesn't even
know the rules of specters.
I'm surprised she's been
all right until now.
I'm home.
It followed us.
Demon
Strong
Execute
at once
Kaya, where is your mother's room?
Huh? It's upstairs.
Thank you.
I'm looking for something,
so I'm going to try her room.
Okay.
Don't mind me. Just do
what you normally do. Also—
We cannot answer the door
at the moment.
Incoming
Playback
Monitor
Indoor Call
Menu
Talk
End
Please leave your name and message.
Talk
Yes?
Nana-san, thanks for
picking up Kaya today.
Shizuo-san?
Thank you very much
for picking her up.
I forgot my keys at the hospital.
Could you open the door for me?
I'm on my way to see Mirai, so I probably
won't be able to get home until around 6.
There's food I bought in the fridge,
so please have dinner with Kaya.
Didn't you just message me to say
you're going to the hospital now?
Uh, th-that's...
Kaya, people you know might come
to the door like just now.
But please ignore all of them.
Can you do that?
Yup.
♫ Long Cat ♫
Long Cat
Long Cat.
♫ Long, long, meow ♫
♫ Cat, cat, meow ♫
♫ Long Cat, meow, meow ♫
We cannot answer the door
at the moment.
Please leave your name and message.
♫ Let's play, let's play together! ♫
Kaya-san!
♫ Long, long cat. Let's play together ♫
Mobuo?
Oh, Kaya-san! It's an emergency!
Can you open the—
You're not him.
Huh?
Mobuo calls me "Kaya-sama."
Wh-What kind of weird adult would—
♫ Long, long, meow ♫
♫ Cat, cat, meow ♫
♫ Long Cat, Long Cat! Meow, meow ♫
Again?
We cannot answer the door
at the moment.
Please leave your name and message.
Kaya, you must get out of there.
Inside the house with you right now
is a specter that copied how I look.
Note-
book
That house is dangerous.
You need to leave at once.
I'll handle it.
So please open the door for me.
Thanks for letting me in.
This is the last one.
It should be enough to drive it off.
Kaya, stay back.
Auntie Nana.
I accidentally opened the door.
I'm sorry.
I said to call me Nana.
I'm glad you're not hurt.
What was that?
Her power is beyond anything
my mother or I have.
I knew it, Kaya.
You're...
Incoming Call
Hasumi Chie
M-Mob-san? We're in trouble.
Kaya-chan's aunt knew
we'd visited her grandmother.
She said some creepy things
about misfortune or stuff.
There's something wrong at
Kaya-chan's mom's house, for sure.
We shouldn't get too involved.
This is why I warned him.
Hasumi Chie
Uh, Mob-san? Can you hear me? Mob-san—
Call Ended
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Mori-no-Oka Park
In this episode, Saku-chan
and the other kids playing at the park
were possessed by a specter.
They did dangerous things and ignored
the rules of the playground equipment.
Children will sometimes act impulsively.
That's why it's important for adults
to keep a close eye on them.
Be mindful so that
nothing irreversible happens
while you're distracted by your phone.