Syugo, wait!
That's dangerous!
To-ou Medical University Hospital
We haven't seen each other
in three years...
And this is how we reunite?
This may sting a little.
That looks hella painful!
No fractures.
Nothing abnormal in their
brain CT scans as well.
No, it's abnormal.
Starting a fight on a pedestrian bridge?
Falling down the stairs?
Are you two stupid?
Kizuki!
Are you sure nothing's broken?
Are you really okay?
I told you. It's no big deal.
Such a drama queen.
Shut up!
You'd react the same way if you
got a call from Mizuho saying:
"They're going to die! Help us!"
My soul left my body!
Then I saw Kizuki
for the first time in forever!
Two grown adults all banged up
grabbing and thrashing
at each other on the ground!
Of course I'd think
something's messed up!
I was going to go home
once I blew off some steam.
How dare you take my car and drive us
to the hospital without my permission?
Like I'd let you go home after that!
You stubborn four-eyes!
Oh my god, you're so loud.
You two also caused trouble
for Mizuho, too.
Kashiwagi.
Hm?
Your childhood friends are a riot.
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Okay...
Why were you even in Omotesando, Syugo?
I check out restaurants
I'm interested in on my days off.
Diligent about your work research, I see.
It was my fault.
Syugo has a right to be angry.
"I'm useless to Mizuho if I can't swim."
I drowned in those thoughts and I...
Mizuho's not like that.
Yeah. You're right.
I'm sure she'd accept any version of me.
But I...
The past me didn't realize that.
Childhood friends are so nice.
Would you like some coffee?
I'll have one, too.
You've known Kashiwagi since
you were little, right, Nishino-san?
Yes. I've heard from Shin that
you've been friends with him
since college, Kuroda-sensei.
What?
Um, well..
That's not really true.
I was only sticking around
Kashiwagi by my own will.
So it wasn't like that.
Is that so?
Shin has it really good.
I should have just been friends
with Kizuki, too.
Syugo?
I'm going home.
What?
I'll go with you.
Let me catch a ride.
It's too far for you.
I don't need a buddy to keep an eye on me.
I'll spend the night at my dad's.
I'm worried about you, Syugo.
Do what you want.
Wait for me!
Thanks, Shin.
Yeah.
I'll be chewing you out
the next time I see you.
It's been a while since we've heard
Shin-chan's lectures from the heart!
Kizuki.
I don't know what you want to do.
But I'm never letting you
have Mizuho ever again.
To-ou Medical University Hospital
Kashiwagi?
Nishino-san...
left with the guy wearing glasses.
Oh.
Thanks for before, Kuroda.
You were a big help.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll treat you to something next time.
Okay. I want a super expensive meal.
You always ask for that.
Kashiwagi makes me smile.
But also hurts me a bit.
Let's see...
Building C...
Room 3002?
Where is that?
Excuse me.
Building C is over there.
If you're in anatomy,
that's where I'm headed.
So we could go there together...
Oh. That would be great.
Thank you so much.
Oh, it's nothing!
This way, then.
You okay, Kashiwagi?
I'm just super sleepy.
I see.
Who would have known the welcome party
was all night karaoke?
I wonder if college
is like this all the time.
Hey. Can I ask you something?
Hm?
What inspired you to become a doctor?
Oh. My family
owns a hospital in Fukuoka.
It's been passed down
for three generations,
and I have to take over
the family business.
Something basic like that.
That's really impressive.
Nah...
I'm telling you this
because it's you, Kuroda.
Back in elementary school,
the mom of a childhood friend of mine
passed away from an illness.
My friend, who used to
always smile without a care in the world,
made the saddest expression
I've ever seen.
And I couldn't forget that face.
I wanted to be a doctor
who could cure any illness...
So I can ensure my friend will
never feel that kind of sadness again.
I took those feelings seriously.
That said...
My resolve sounds more basic.
It's kind of a selfish reason
for me, right?
That will be all for today.
Be sure to submit your report
before the next class.
Kashiwagi.
Hm?
Did you pull an all-nighter again?
You need to take it easy.
Even doctors need to rely
on their own health.
Yeah.
Oh! Shin!
Mizuho. Kizuki.
Why are you two here?
When I visited home the other day,
your mom gave this to me.
We were about to go to your place.
I see. Thanks.
How've you been, Shin?
Bye, Shin!
Oh. I see.
She must be...
The childhood friend
Kashiwagi was talking about.
Is Kashiwagi absent today, too?
Are his credits gonna be okay like this?
Oh.
Bye, Shin-kun.
Let me spend the night again, okay?
Is that a new girl you're dating?
No, it's not like that.
Here.
Notes from two biology lectures.
If you keep this up, you won't make it
to your third year, Kashiwagi.
Leave me alone.
While you're at it, take the notes
you brought last time, too.
What?
I don't know what
I'm studying for anymore.
Even if I don't do my best...
Everything will be fine.
You need to show up to class.
How long are you going to keep this up?
Weren't you going to be a doctor
for your childhood friend?
Could you show her how
you look right now?!
What would you know?
Sometimes caring so much about someone
can make a relationship painful.
Kuroda.
Wanna...
spend the night here, too?
Who do you take me for?!
Don't underestimate medical science!
Regarding the study of DNA analysis,
please refer to Document 2...
You're late.
Sorry.
I'm sorry about the other day.
Thanks for your notes.
I opened my eyes after what you said.
Let me treat you to something
to make up for it.
Y-Yeah. Sure.
Oh! Kashiwagi!
It's been a while.
Yeah.
I was talking to Kuroda about
going out to eat somewhere.
You guys wanna join?
Sounds good.
Where at?
Of course...
Why did I expect that he meant
just the two of us?
What do you want to eat, Kuroda?
Something expensive!
What's with that?
All right.
Kashiwagi makes me smile.
But also hurts me a bit.
I should have just been friends
with Kizuki, too.
My only choice was to
stay with him as a friend.
To-ou Medical University Hospital
Did you eat dinner?
If you're hungry, you can have that.
Wow! Looks yummy!
You sure?
It's from my market research today.
Take whichever one you want.
What?
I was just thinking about how you always
do something like this to cheer me up.
Thanks for the meal!
I'm fine as long as I can
see that expression forever.
That's what I thought.
Let's go to the same high school...
Okay!
Greetings!
Late night pizza delivery!
Are you a god?!
I was just getting hungry!
You...
You aren't studying at all!
W-Well...
Shin's notes are too advanced.
That guy's too smart.
Look at this!
Exam Prep Notes for Clowns
Oh, hmm...
Best of luck on your studies, Mizuho.
Let's go to the same high school.
W-With everyone!
Y-Yeah! Everyone!
You're right!
Otherwise it'd be boring!
Yeah.
What kind of pizza is it?
Ham? Teriyaki chicken? Scallops?
Cheese! Oh wait, of course it is.
He's so hot!
You can do it!
Quite the crowd here.
Syugo!
Aren't you bored seeing this every day?
But Saito-senpai is so cool!
He's handsome and super fast...
Oh!
Kizuki! Don't lose!
You don't know yourself the most.
What?
Nothing.
But because he's scared,
he's hiding his true feelings...
He'll definitely regret
it when he's older.
This is a nice song, Shiraishi-chan.
What's it called?
And she's ignoring me.
Shiraishi-chan.
You need to call me "Shiraishi-sensei."
If I gather up some courage...
and get rejected...
Would you cheer me up?
Probably not.
But I could play you this song.
Hoshikawa-kun.
The name of this song is...
I decided that I'd be by her side
no matter what happens.
Manga Seminar
Let's Draw Manga
Greetings. Pizza delivery.
Syugo!
I heard from your dad
that you're not doing well?
What are you going to do with those?
Oh, well...
I'm thinking of giving up on making manga.
You serious?
Yeah.
Everyone else is busy
job searching...
But I haven't even debuted.
I tried to do my best like Kizuki.
He's giving it his all to represent Japan.
But it feels like I'm
still clinging to a dream
that will never come true.
I must look so childish to you, Syugo.
But that's what you've
been wanting to do, right?
Right now...
No matter what I write,
it doesn't feel right.
I don't know if this is what
I really want to do anymore.
I can't draw anything.
Which is why...
I'm going to start job searching!
You're forcing that smile.
Syugo?
Here. For your new resolve!
What?
It's nice.
If that's what you decided on,
go on and do that!
Yeah!
Why did he leave me?
I'm borrowing your kitchen.
Eat whatever you'd like.
And take a break from work, too.
Don't even think about Kizuki today.
C'mon, you have to eat something, Mizuho.
Please. Just one bite.
Syugo...
It's so good.
Mizuho...
Thank you, Syugo.
For always cheering me up.
Stop grinning at me
like that while eating.
I can't help it. It's good.
Syugo?
Nothing.
You always make a scary face, Syugo.
I was so shocked
when you jumped at Kizuki.
I haven't seen you make
a face like that before.
As a chef, what would you do
if you hurt your hand?
Are you out of your mind?
You and Kizuki!
Throwing hands at each other like that—
No more talking about Kizuki.
Syugo?
Right now...
The person in front of you...
is me.
Out of anyone else,
the one by your side...
is me.
Syugo?
Huh?
Time to go.
I'll drop you off.
You don't need to chaperon me.
The name of this song is...
"My Regretful Heart."
# 19 I Don't Want to Have Any Regrets