Demon Defense Force Headquarters
(10th Squadron Stronghold)
Hello and welcome, 7th Squadron!
Lady Kyou and Mr. Yuuki, right this way.
Just the two of us?
Totally!
It's an order
from the resplendent Lady Ren!
Aren't you afraid of the
Supreme Commander, Ginna?
Her scariness is a part of her charm!
I take pride in being
Lady Ren's direct report!
So she's feared and respected...
Please proceed through these doors here.
A Japanese garden in the middle of Mato?
It was installed after Ren
became the Supreme Commander.
Miss Yamashiro has that much power?
Her connections
to those at the top run deep.
Sometimes even the prime minister requests
her presence for security purposes.
So that's her job in the real world.
Mune ga shizunde mirai kanjirenaku nattari
Toki ga tomatte mou owatta tte kanjitari
Fusagikonde hanasenakute
Jiwari kokoro no kasa ga hiraita
Soredemo tsuyogatte ikiteta
Nagusamete nante iwanai
Tsuyoku natte mae o mitetainda
Dakedo yowasa ga oshitsubusu
Kimi ni atte sekai afurete hikari ataetekuretari
Sukoshi datte kibou nakatta boku ga waraetetanda
Nanigenai kaiwa de zutto egao ataetekuretari
Arigatou tte terete warau kara iwanai yo
Dakedo omotteru yo
Kono saki mae muite ikeru kana?
Hikari yo, boku ni
Rampage
Episode 4
She looks happy...
Supreme Commander!
How cute!
Doggies in a Japanese garden.
Isn't it lovely?
Looks like Kaname and Miyabi
are fond of you.
They're big sisters,
so they'll take good care of you.
As their subordinate, that is.
Subordinate...
Is there a reason
you called the two of us out here?
Head on inside.
I want to borrow your slave.
While you still have the energy.
But that's...
For all we know,
he might display a new trait.
We ought to at least test it.
Right?
If you're ordering it,
then I have no choice.
Oh, it's quite comfortable up here.
Eternal Chains: Slave
Killer Fang
Yuuki...
Supreme Commander!
That form is dangerous!
No deactivating it!
There are Shuuki nearby.
Yuuki!
Go on, show me your strength.
Insta-kills? Impressive!
Oh, a whole horde.
Sacrificial
Goat
What a beautiful view!
Hey!
Trying to bite me?
Bad dog.
I'll teach you some manners.
He's never taken
such a violent form before.
Yuuki!
You aren't afraid.
Unlike when you're in human form.
I get along well with people
who respect my authority.
As for those who don't...
I make sure...
to put them in their place!
Pulling that move?
I'll crush you first.
You tried to bite me again.
His wounds heal in the blink of an eye.
Guess I'll have to really discipline you.
Ren Yamashiro's ability:
All-Encompassing Lord of the Cosmos.
She deploys a mandala
and can use one of the
Eight Buddhas' abilities at will
by reflecting it in her eye.
What makes it dangerous is the fact that
she can combine two abilities at a time.
No one outside of Ren herself
knows what all eight abilities are.
This is your master's power.
Get it now, doggie?
Well, the first half
of your little rampage was splendid.
Shall I give you some head pats
as a reward?
Huh?
Ren Yamashiro: The Pinnacle of Life.
Ren Yamashiro: Earth's Answer.
I always ranked first on practice exams.
Was always the victor in sports.
And I always served
as the student council president.
She decimated an entire task force
of elite soldiers with abilities.
Prime Minister
That Country's President
This was her going easy on them,
Madam President.
With our eyes on the heavens...
us mortals strived to achieve greatness.
And at the end of our journey,
we found you.
Ren Yamashiro, the pinnacle of life.
Ren Yamashiro, the Earth's answer!
The president made a fuss over me,
sang my praises.
And yet here I am...
This is his reward? Not head pats?
I thought you were a cute dog...
but you're a beast.
I can't override this absurd farce
with my ability.
When I observed Kyouka using her ability
against the Shuuki before,
she was able to call off his Slave form.
But she couldn't avoid the outcome
of the slave contract.
It must be the same principle.
Slave...
It's a more unique ability
than everyone thinks.
How much more is there going to be?!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Nudge
Rub
Why am I acting like I want to be pet?!
P-pet?
Am I supposed to pet her?
The Supreme Commander?!
Like this?
Sh-she's terrifying!
You're the dog, not me!
You know that, right?!
Petting me like it's nothing...
You beast!
I can move! Is it over?!
Yuuki!
You're all right.
My form is too much of a challenge
for your slave.
He needs more training.
And the way he lost control like that...
It's dangerous!
That part doesn't worry me.
I'll be sure to keep him in line.
Yuuki!
Yuuki Wakura!
Ouch!
My whole body's sore.
Oh, that's right.
I passed out afterwards.
I completely lost control of myself.
I have to train harder!
Why can't I... focus?!
Why does lending Yuuki
to the others bother me so badly?
Miss Kyouka!
Ah, you're awake.
I'm ready for some training!
Yuuki...
You must still be tired.
I slept it off! I'm fine!
The repercussions of the
Supreme Commander's form are too severe.
You've got spirit, but I told you
to stay in bed until you recover.
I'm sorry.
Things have been hectic lately...
I wanted to get back to training with you
as soon as possible.
Just get some rest.
But...
It won't do any good if you're worn out.
That's an order.
Yes, ma'am.
It seems the joint practice sessions
are effective.
We'll hold more of them
when we have the opportunity.
She's in a really, really bad mood!
Blend in.
Fade into the background.
Don't attract her attention.
Speaking of which, Kyouka...
Where's Yuuki Wakura?
Didn't I instruct you
to bring him with you?
Sounds like she's taken a liking to Yuuki.
That's going to cause problems.
He's exhausted from training
with the 10th Squadron.
He can't do anything in his condition.
How sad for the little slave!
I see.
In that case...
See me afterwards, Bell.
Huh?
You figured out how to lend Yuuki
to other people, didn't you?
It's like I said during the meeting:
Yuuki's exhausted!
I know, he's ready to drop.
Poor thing...
If anything happens,
the 6th Squadron will back you up.
So give him a break.
I was certain you were
going to ask to borrow him, too.
Of course I'm interested.
I did suggest it that one time.
But... there's no need to rush.
Things are different between us nowadays.
Commander Uzen.
I'd like to discuss something with you.
I appreciate everyone
taking turns like this.
I'm feeling a lot better.
It's 'cause we need you back
on chore duty soon.
You and I have some training to do, too.
Yeah.
Which reminds me...
The last time, his reward was...
Makes me wonder how lewd
it's going to get the next time.
I'm back.
Commander! Welcome home-
So the time has finally come.
Move aside, Himari.
You aren't working his body properly.
Huh?!
It's no ability, but...
The Illustrious Azuma Family
Massage Technique
I feel like a brand new person!
I'll keep going.
Relax for me.
So that's the correct hand motion.
This technique relieves the fatigue
from a busy schedule.
Himari.
It's almost time for the Azuma Banquet.
The Azuma Banquet...
A battle to decide
the next head of the family!
Mother made the announcement
after seeing the 1st Squadron
select their new commander.
Ordinarily, as her daughter,
I would receive the position...
but not in our household.
It's based on potential.
The Azuma Banquet is in five days.
Take time off and
gather at the Azuma estate.
I've already cleared it
with all the commanders.
Wait a minute!
I won't be there.
I don't even want to look at that place.
Count me out of it!
I don't care who
the next head of the family is!
Himari.
Shall we take a bath together?
No way!
Nice and muscular.
You've grown in more ways than one.
And yet, you were severely injured.
Cracking under pressure
is a fatal mistake.
Letting others cover for your weaknesses
is only going to get more people hurt.
Just like Yachiho.
Don't jump to conclusions!
If you intend to keep fighting,
then before you can disgrace
the Azuma name...
I, as your mother,
will finish you off myself.
And I should participate in the banquet
if I don't want that to happen, right?
Prove my strength.
All right, fine!
I'll blow the entire Azuma Family
out of the water!
I haven't talked to the members
of the 9th Squadron very much.
There's no reason to outside of work.
The Azuma Family...
A distinguished family closely connected
to the history of the Demon Defense Force.
Especially Miss Tovera,
the former Supreme Commander.
She's barely even human...
You get along well
with the Azuma Family, don't you?
I look after
one of their precious daughters.
That's why I manage
to stay so cordial and neighborly.
You sure are amazing, Miss Tenka!
You look like
you're feeling better, Yuuki.
I am.
But the Supreme Commander's form
really took it out of me...
Then we should be picky
about letting people borrow you.
That's absolutely right!
No more of this willy-nilly stuff!
We need to make my form stronger!
It's the best course of action!
Not to worry!
I'll be back to normal in a few days!
I have Miss Fubuki's massage
to thank for that!
I studied her hand movements.
I think I can do it now, too.
As a commander, I should also learn it.
Nei wants to master it, too!
Me, too! Me, too!
All right, c'mere!
I promise you can trust me
with this, Yukki!
When she said she'd finish me off,
she wasn't joking.
An Azuma would do it.
Cipher, cipher
Watashi o nozoku hitorikiri
Kaitentaishou loop shiten ne
Saiten bakari de tsukareta wa
Seikoutaiken doko ittanda?
Doko? Nee
Hattentojou panic sunzen
Ontei bakari o awaseru wa
Rinsen taisei jirettai ne
Glass no kutsu wa mou
Saitei sa
Konna no wa mou yameyou yo
Meishoubu no yokan
Kimi ni wakaru ka?
Cipher, cipher
Watashi o nozoku hitorikiri
Only you no taikendan
Inu ni nacchimae yo
Cipher, cipher
Mero sugiru kamo sono kusari
Sensenkyoukyou nonfiction
Hikiwakerannai ne
Daioujou
Watashi o nozoku no dare?
CHECK OUT
What happened
after Ren Yamashiro
used Slave...
I'm home, Kaname, Miyabi!
The Azuma Banquet
Episode 5
Next time, Episode 5: "The Azuma Banquet"
And here's today's bonus!
Lady Ren punishing dumbasses in Mato!
She's totally godlike!
If it were me on the other end...
I'd pee my pants!