Name: Tsav.
That's me!
No surname. Codename: Man-Eating Ghoul.
Yeah, that's pretty much how us
Gwen Mohsa assassins roll.
Eight people in a month, huh?
That's quite disturbing.
Nah, ya got it all wrong.
I'm an honest guy,
so I'll lay it out straight for ya.
I killed twelve people. That's 50% more.
See how honest I am? I'm such a pushover.
I'm always the guy drawin' the short straw.
You killed all those people,
yet you feel no remorse at all?
Aw, shit. Sorry. Were we talkin'
about what's "right and wrong"?
I was never great at
that whole "morality" stuff.
I do kinda feel like crap
if I hafta kill someone I like,
but everythin' beyond that
don't make no sense to me.
The Gwen Mohsa brainwashing
never took hold, either,
'cause that stuff seemed so silly and dumb.
We're aware of how the Gwen Mohsa operate.
They use pain, drugs, pleasure...
all kinds of methods to make children—
Hey, are ya thinkin'
I'm some kinda chosen one?
Gosh, that's such a big responsibility.
You aren't afraid?
At best, you'll get a life sentence.
At worst, death awaits.
Aren't you afraid?
I'm hella scared, man.
But bein' scared won't change much,
so I'm just gonna enjoy it while I'm here.
That isn't a normal human reaction.
Do you lack imagination?
That's mean, dude! I'm imaginin'
the hell out of it all right now.
It's just...
I can't wrap my head around that stuff.
I mean, outside of what's good for me
and the people I like...
Is there anythin' else that matters?
How interesting.
Tsav, was it?
How did you choose who to kill?
Dunno.
Guess those guys were just easy to kill.
"Easy to kill"?
What about this man, Taldy?
He vanished from the government office
where he worked
in a mere seventy seconds
in broad daylight.
You're saying he was easy to kill?
I don't mean the method.
It's more about, uh, the feeling?
I mean, I can kill anyone
if I set my mind to it.
So when I'm pickin' who to kill...
I pick the ones I won't feel bad about.
What's your standard for that?
Um, I guess it's just kinda like instinct, yeah?
They just seem... y'know. Easy to kill?
I see. Yes, yes.
Magnificent.
Tsav, my boy.
I think death is too good for you.
A sentence worse than death?
Yes. I am sentencing you to be a hero.
N-No!
Wait a minute! The hero penalty—
Yes, that's right.
You won't even be allowed to die.
Sentenced to Be a Hero
See? I was a total pushover
when you got right down to it.
The more I'd look into a target, the more
I'd think, "Whoa, I can't kill this guy!"
"He's got a wife and kids at home!" y'know?
So I'd never kill the guy.
That man is also a hero?
Death has repeatedly failed to change him.
But the organization'd get mad at me
if I didn't have proof of the kill,
We've heard this story
a few dozen times, too.
so I'd mess up some other dude's face
and bring him back with me instead.
Total sweetheart stuff—
Tsav.
Shut up.
Ah, sorry 'bout that, bro.
Am I talkin' your ear off again?
Can we put a muzzle on this guy already?
He'll be talking all night
if we have to share a room.
I just can't stand it when it's quiet, y'know?
You know my tragic past, right?
I was basically tortured as part of my training.
At times, they put me in this dungeon—
Shut up.
Don't make me say it again.
See? Now Xylo's mad.
Aw, shit! Sorry, bro!
C'mon, Dotta. Say you're sorry, too.
Why should I apologize? This is why
I hate you. Get some perspective already.
Aw, seriously, Dotta.
Ya gotta learn to take a joke.
They've advanced quite far.
They'll likely arrive tonight at this rate.
Y-Yes.
So? How many knights
of the Order are staying?
About fifty. All trustworthy knights.
Still not enough.
Even with the prisoners Venetim
rounded up from Milnid Jail...
Prisoners? Was a bribe involved?
Yup. "They're all on death row, so do what
you like with 'em," was the response.
Same treatment prisoners get everywhere.
Hey, look. Those are faerie scouts, I think.
For real? Let's have a look-see.
Looks kinda doglike.
Must be a cir sith.
He can see it from this distance?
The man's vision is inhuman.
Tsav, can you handle it?
Guess we'll find out.
Just...
don't kill me if I screw it up, 'kay?
A Daisy made by Verkle Corp?
Yeah. His Majesty retuned it
for long-range sniping.
Say, you sure about this?
If he's in a pack, I'd hate to rile his buddies—
Can't you shoot without talking?
Copy that.
See that? Bullseye, right?
Yeah. But there's more coming.
Yep, on it.
Can we trust them with this?
More coming. Hurry.
They're an obnoxious pair,
but they'll get the job done.
Ah, it's hard to fire fast
at this power and speed.
Particularly Tsav.
I've never seen him miss a shot.
Just hurry!
It's a hit.
Now, let's go set the trap.
Some days, I think I'm a genius.
Okay, there's another.
Mr. Dotta never listens to me.
What?
You're not giving up?
Even in this situation?
Some people want us dead.
I'd rather not give them the satisfaction.
Besides...
All that stuff about her usefulness...
There! There! Beside it, see?
I'd heard you were a man who imperiled
his unit in his eagerness to climb the ranks.
Copy.
There's some left.
Man, give a guy a break.
That's funny. What noble family
are you from, anyway?
Okay, we got most of them.
I'm not a noble.
Time for a break?
That seems unlikely.
Galtuile let a commoner
become an Order captain?
No, there's another.
Gotcha.
Huh? Is that a faerie?
My uncle is a high priest.
Behind that boulder? Yeah, that's a faerie.
So a bigwig at the Temple, more or less.
That explains why I didn't know.
Bro, we're all done here.
Every shot a hit.
Dotta, Tsav, stay here and keep watch.
Kivia, let's go.
Carry it all inside!
We need more materials here!
The captain's heading out
already. Get it done!
You're staying, Captain Kivia?
Staying to watch the heroes die seems in
poor taste to me, but I'll pray for your safety.
I shall also pray for your well-being, Kivia.
Pelmerry, stay close.
That's the goddess killer.
You bastard.
Yes, Hord. I'll stay close.
Hord, was I useful in my role?
You were perfect.
There can be no room for doubt.
In that case...
Won't you say, "Well done, Pelmerry"?
Very well.
Well done, Pelmerry.
Excuse us, then.
That's the ninth goddess?
Yes. The Goddess Pelmerry.
She's pacted with the captain of the Ninth Order
of the Holy Knights, Hord Clivios. Know him?
His family holds a lot of land in the south.
Clivios-made wine is considered
quite a delicacy.
But...
What he's left in there
is nothing at all like wine.
Boy, looks dangerous.
So we're luring the Demon Lord in here
and detonating the barrels, huh?
Yeah. To continuously kill
Iblis with poison.
And that'll kill all of us as well, huh?
Man, that sucks.
Kinda ticks me off, even.
Might even drive me to kill someone!
Huh? What'd you just say?
You looking for a fight?!
You disgusting heroes
had better watch what you—
Stop, Zofflec.
Fine.
Why do you have to kill anyone?
Gotta vent my frustration.
Don't tell me you've never kicked a rock
when you're ticked off, bro.
Humans aren't rocks.
Hey, that's human exceptionalism!
Humans are just one part
of our big wide world.
It's not good to give 'em special treatment.
I have found you, Xylo!
Ah, Goddess!
How'd you like holdin' down the fort?
Spare me your pleasantries.
You left without telling me.
That is conduct unbecoming of my knight.
Goddess Teoritta.
We were simply carrying out our duties.
Please show us mercy.
Xylo.
You seem to have enjoyed
scouting with Kivia.
There's no such thing as enjoyable scouting.
G-Goddess Teoritta.
I picked these berries in the forest.
They're quite sweet.
You were picking berries...
in the forest...
together?!
It must have indeed been enjoyable.
N-No, I was merely carrying out my duties—
Do you have a map?
Yup.
Xylo! My knight!
I observed the Ninth Order
of the Holy Knights at work.
Here, bro.
Thanks.
Oh, yeah?
Do not be so dismissive!
Do you hear me? Their goddess
got her head patted seven times!
Seven times in a single day!
What's your point?
I have not had my head patted even once!
I am not asking for a generous
seven pats, but even half that...
I have not had my head patted even once!
Oh, yeah?
Why do you not understand?!
Point is, we're short on people.
My... My knight!
Please, please pat my head!
The faeries are gonna
trample us at this rate.
Captain Kivia.
An unknown group of men
is at the back gate.
They say they're here to see this man.
To see me?
You guys...
We heard you'd been given
an impossible task at the fortress.
Surely even insignificant miners like us
can offer some assistance?
You realize what we're up against, right?
We want to help the king and the champions
who saved our lives, as any man would.
Sorry, but we're not royalty
or champions of any kind.
Go back to your families.
We're doing this for ourselves as well.
We all hail from the villages in this area.
If this fortress suffers
the same fate as the mines,
we'll have lost both
our livelihoods and our homes.
I get how you feel,
but after getting your lives ba—
Welcome, my people!
His Majesty!
You are the warriors of my realm.
It's really him!
He's so brave and strong.
You are the true heroes of this day.
Your Majesty, don't encourage them.
Why not, Commander Xylo?
Our forces are sorely depleted at the moment.
I realize that.
But these men are—
Of course, I would never ask my people
to throw their lives away.
But I will accept their aid.
Under my instruction, they'll be able to handle
even the most intricate sacred seal tuning.
With these loyal servants
of the crown by our side,
this fortress will become truly impregnable.
And we shall seize victory together!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Follow me!
Let us get to work!
His Majesty! His Majesty!
Well, it's all gone according to plan so far.
Now then, Xylo...
Please outline the plan.
Tatsuya will seal off
the underground passage.
I want twenty of the Order's knights with him.
Tsav will be at the back gate.
Shoot anyone who comes close.
Ah, that's my time to shine.
Say, where's Mr. Dotta?
He's got another job to do.
Next, the miners will be
by the front gate at the rear.
I want them providing support
to the Knights.
We've been ordered not to raise the drawbridge,
so it'll be a dangerous location.
Don't push yourselves.
Just try to hold out for half the day.
We'll work on tuning the sacred seals.
What will you be doing, Xylo?
Going on the attack.
That's my bro.
Now, listen.
Hold firm against the faeries' advance for
as long as you can to draw out Iblis itself.
Before it can reach the fortress,
I'll use a trap we set in advance...
to finish it off.
This is the only way we all survive.
Gimme a damn break!
I'll kill you!
Don't order us around!
Why should we do what some hero tells us?
Huh? You people are subhuman.
You goddess-killing bastard!
Don't make bro mad, okay?
I don't wanna deal with the blowback.
Wh-Why didn't you shoot me?
Why? Because you're bigger
and stronger than that guy.
You'll be a bigger help to the cause.
Bro—
Tsav. I do think that was quite effective...
but don't do it again.
Oh, that's right. I shoulda killed him right—
Ow!
Wrong. Get him inside and use
a sacred seal to stem the bleeding.
Yeah? What did you want?
A sealed message arrived for you, Xylo.
It's from—
I don't want it. Burn it.
Um, but it's from Frenci Mastibolt.
The Mastibolts are a family
of night-gaunts from the south, yes?
They want to lend us some soldiers.
Personally, I think it'd be good
to have their help.
Don't you think—
This conversation is over.
O-Of course.
Although we could really use
those two thousand soldiers.
More importantly, we still haven't
gotten Jayce and Rhyno here?
Jayce said, "I refuse to push
Neely like that. Go die."
Rhyno simply ignored me.
He volunteered to be a hero,
yet that aspect of him never changes.
What about the mercenaries?
I tried contacting them,
but since we can't pay...
Dotta's out raising money.
I just hope we're in time.
Good morning. Haul it on in.
We need to get those miners
off the front line.
It'd have to be the end of days
to force men like that into combat.
The end of days, huh?
Your Majesty, what do you want us to do next?
Xylo.
Hold it there. I'll adjust the placement.
Imagine, just as a thought experiment...
Yes, sir.
If there were people out there who really did
want to put an end to humanity...
What would you think?
What?
Do you enjoy conspiracy theories, Xylo?
This is pointless. I know all about
those bullshit articles you wrote.
About Demon Lord worshipers
and coexistence advocates and that.
It's clear you made it all up.
Well, I understand why you'd think that.
But if there were a faction out there
worshiping Demon Lords
or seeking coexistence with them,
and taking action to make sure
humanity lose this fight...
Wouldn't it explain this nonsensical plan?
If people like that really existed,
they'd have to be the shittiest scumbags alive.
The Demon Lord's still far away.
They have arrived, my knight.
Coiste bodhars.
The vanguard of the horde.
All right.
It's starting.
The future of humanity rides on this battle.
We must protect our homeland.
All men, ready yourselves.
Your Majesty, I told you
to stay on support, damn it.
Now...
Fire!
Activate barricades!
Well done, men.
Your gallant offensive
has them on the back foot!
Yeah!
Now, prepare the next volley!
His Majesty's awfully close
to the front line.
Mr. Venetim, if somethin' happens to His Majesty,
we're pretty much doomed, right?
They're here! Fire!
I tried very hard to talk him out of it,
Damn it! Missed!
but he wouldn't listen.
Mr. Venetim, if you can't talk people outta stuff,
what are you even bringing to the table?
That's a very rude thing to say, Tsav.
Clear the way for the cavalry!
Support Captain Kivia!
Fire!
Let's go!
Knights of the Thirteenth Order...
Charge!
Zofflec!
Ma'am!
Cavalry, turn back!
Keep harrying them!
Don't let them near the fortress!
They really are quite impressive.
Bro, what's that over there?
Is that...
Yeah. I see it.
I just didn't want to believe it.
They're humans?!
Humans?
Humans.
Flaming arrows?
Look out!
The barricade's on fire!
Th-This is bad!
The sacred seals are ruined!
Cover the barrels!
Don't let them catch fire!
Second wave incoming!
There's too many of them!
We won't be able to take them all out!
Damn it.
The portcullis on the front gate won't hold!
They're gonna break through!
Damn it all.
At this rate, before the
Demon Lord even shows itself...
They made it inside!
Put out the fire!
...we're all gonna be dead.