Moegi-san?
You, join the other team.
But...
But?
But what?
It's nothing. Right?
S-Sorry.
There's no one here.
Yeah.
Seriously?
Kozue, look at this...
Kozue?
Nishida-san?
Hey.
You're there, aren't you?
Come on. This isn't funny.
Why are they screwing around?
They're interrogating her.
What?
Where are you hiding the weapons?
We were ordered not to use violence.
I really don't know.
Breaking fingers would be faster.
Really? Tickle, tickle!
Apparently, that's not a good
idea with this many players.
Oh?
The breakdown of morals
makes groups fall apart.
My job is to chaperone the new players.
Huh.
Her name is Kushieda.
There are about thirty people on her team.
Most of them are new, and someone
named Moegi is ruling by fear.
Then we might be the better group.
Yeah.
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
It just looks like kids playing to me.
It's surprisingly effective.
Have you ever been tickled
by that many people?
Well, no.
Tickle, tickle!
Hey!
Sumiyaka-san, what are you doing?
I see. This does seem effective.
Nice try.
Don't... You jerk...
Sheesh.
Sumiyaka-san.
My next game is my thirtieth.
You believe in that curse?
I didn't realize you were cute like that.
Let me hold you for a while.
Hey, wait!
Damn!
Thanks for that.
We're teammates, after all.
I know, but thanks anyway.
The tutorial has concluded.
Please figure the rest out yourselves.
Hey, could you cut that out?
The tutorial has concluded.
Can't you hear me? Enough already!
Please figure the rest out yourselves.
It's not what you think!
All of our teammates were killed, so I...
I didn't have a choice.
I didn't run away! I didn't—
The tutorial has concluded.
Please figure the rest out yourselves.
It's fine. I just ran away, too.
Huh?
You ran? What do you mean by that?
Are you okay?
The tutorial has concluded.
Are you hurt?
Please figure the rest out yourselves.
It's okay. Are you cold?
The tutorial has concluded.
How many are still alive?
Please figure the rest out yourselves.
I don't know.
The tutorial has concluded.
Please figure the rest out yourselves.
What's going to happen to us?
I don't know.
The tutorial has concluded.
Please figure the rest out yourselves.
The grey nightjar is a truly hideous bird.
Its face is spotted like it has
flecks of miso all over it.
Thanks for waiting.
I thought you were amazing.
You killed so many so freely.
Please make me your student!
Do you like animals?
Like dogs and cats.
I don't dislike them.
What do you think of
people who keep pets?
I don't like their sense of superiority.
What if a child were
being loud on the bus?
I'd think they were annoying.
Are your parents alive?
Yes.
Do you love them?
I'd like to kill them.
Oh, really?
Ask Shion if you have any questions.
O-Okay.
Shion-san.
Um, I'm Moegi. Nice to meet you.
Do you know what's making that sound?
Shut up!
Your clothes are cute, Kyara-san.
Are they?
You have a lot of loose clothes.
That's right.
I think you'd look good in
form-fitting clothes, too.
Unlike me, you're pretty.
I don't like constricting clothing.
Um, I'm sorry.
Hey.
I'm going to kill someone
after this. Care to join me?
Well?
Um...
We'll drive there.
I'll teach you how to kill.
"'The king decreed that we're allowed
to stop playing on cloudy days,
but we were playing the flute
because it's just so fun.'"
"Pose briefly stopped playing to speak."
"'But he'd never let us travel.
The clouds could clear at any time.'"
"The comet said,
'Don't worry. The king told me so
himself the other day.
He said to let those twins
travel one cloudy night.
Let's go. Let's go.
I'm lots of fun.
My nickname is the whale of the sky.
Did you know that?
All those frail stars like sardines
and black rocks like killifish...
I gobble them all up.'"
Did you kill your parents?
Not yet.
I see.
These are good, aren't they?
"The fern frond drank the morning mist
and swayed green and cold.
The grey nightjar squeaked high and loud.
Then it tidied up its nest,
fixed its feathers and down,
and flew out of the nest again."
"The mist cleared,
and the sun was rising in the east.
The grey nightjar endured
the dizzyingly bright light
and flew toward it like an arrow."
"'Sun. Oh, sun.
Please take me to your place.
I don't care if I burn to death.
Even my ugly body
will produce a small light
when it's burned.'"
"The fern frond drank the morning mist
and swayed green and cold.
The grey nightjar...
The grey nightjar..."
Sun. Oh, sun.
Please take me with you.
Please turn a weakling like me
into someone as strong as you.
Moegi-san.
One of the girls said
she saw something strange.
There was a naked and dead stump.
The body was really badly damaged.
Yuki.
Did you see the girl with
long caramel-colored hair?
Is there a problem?
We can't find her anywhere.
She's apparently—
Everyone!
Everyone stand up!
No... But then there
won't be enough for us...
Moegi-san?
I'm sorry. I don't know what to do.
Run! The plan's on hold!
Her killing is like drinking seawater.
Once she starts, she doesn't stop.
At this rate, there won't be anyone left!
There's a homicidal maniac among us!
The girl with agarwood-colored hair!