Seems like there's
poison flowers around here.
Wait. Forget poison.
I should decorate the outside of my cave
with some pretty flowers to help take the
edge off the pains of everyday life.
What's that?
I've never seen
that kind of monster before.
Venom Princess Lacerta
Status: Normal
Attack:
Defense:
Magic:
Agility:
Normal Skills
Venom Fang
Venom Claws
Roll
Clay Gun
Species: Venom Princess Lacerta.
Skills: Venom Fang. Venom Claws.
Venom Fa-
Venom Cla-
Double Poison. Poison Master.
Venom Fa-
Double Poison
Venom Cla-
Venom Fa-
Double Poison
Venom Cla-
Poiso-
What the heck is this?!
It only has poison-related skills!
Did it run away?
How'd it get there?!
Oh crud!
Is that the Clay Gun skill?!
Ouch!
It left?
Huh? Did it give up the fight?
Huh? This pain feels off...
Poison Resistance
has gone from level three to level four.
This poison is something else!
I can't even move my shoulder!
Is this part of its plan?
Status: Special Venom (Major)
What is special poison?!
Is it really different
from the normal kind?
The View Stats skill cannot provide
such specific information at level three.
I knew you'd say that.
This is getting pretty bad!
Come to think of it, I haven't seen
any plants that can counter poison...
What can I do?
How should I fix this?
Oh wait,
maybe I'll learn something
by getting the info on that black lizard!
Venom Princess Lacerta.
Rank: D-.
Princess
Lacerta
A crafty monster
that poisons its prey and flees,
then feasts upon the remains
after the poison takes effect.
Venom Princess...
Seriously?
That's even worse than Dastardly King!
By ingesting highly poisonous substances,
it creates a potent poison internally.
Its bodily fluids can serve as an antidote
to the poison it creates,
and it uses that to bargain for its life
whenever it gets captured.
So I need to capture it
to get the antidote, huh?
I can still move a little
thanks to my poison resistance.
She must be waiting nearby
for the poison to kill me.
I'm gonna have to gamble here!
Losing sight of me
would make it all a waste.
So it's gotta be chasing me!
Where are you watching from?!
Found you!
Think you can hide?!
It uses the Roll skill too, huh?!
However...
Up ahead...
is that cliff that I jumped over when
I was running away from the spider jerk!
I'll draw it over there and capture it!
The skill Roll
has gone from level four to level five.
All right, awesome!
This'll make things so much easi-
That's... Clay Gun!
No way,
it can shoot even when it's rolling?!
I've gotta hand it to her.
As if!
You damn witch!
Ouch!
You're really good at rolling,
Black Lizard.
One day you'll get even better than me
at using that attack.
Unfortunately...
Now is not that time!
Gotcha!
I did it!
Now I just have to catch i-
Wait! My antidote!
I'm screwed if you die!
The worst possible time
for the poison to damage me...
I promise...
I'll save you!
Baby Breath!
Gah!
This really hurts! I'm gonna die!
But...
I'm glad you're okay.
I can't go on...
No luck today either.
Where could Mr. Doz be?
Myria! Myria!
Miss Marielle?!
Good grief,
where did that girl get off to?
Miss Marielle!
So you were around here, eh?
You should've answered me!
I-I'm sorry.
Um, were you looking for me?
I was.
I hadn't seen you lately,
so I was concerned and paid a visit
to your house, but you weren't there.
So, what in the world were you doing?
Well, you see,
I was stuck in bed with a slight cold,
but I went for a walk
after I started feeling better.
Oh, really? Well, that's fine, but...
You aren't going into the forest, are you?
No, I'm not.
Is that the truth?
It is!
Please believe me.
Okay, then.
I've gotten word from the guild
that adventurers are headed our way,
so don't worry.
R-right. Thank you.
I'm about to go shopping now,
will you give me a hand?
Sure, I'll help.
Where am I?
Oh, yeah!
I got poisoned by the
Black Lizard, then I was chasing it...
Wha?! You're still here?!
You're just waiting
for the poison to kill me, huh?!
Crap!
Huh? My arms don't feel heavy anymore.
Wait, is the poison gone now?!
So, hey...
did you give me the antidote?
Really?
You did!
Thanks!
You and I had a really fierce battle going
through blood, sweat, and tears.
It made you realize
we were kindred spirits, huh?
Oh, you!
Now that I'm getting a good look,
you're actually pretty cute!
Do you want some of this too?
Okay.
Here, have some.
Are you telling me it tastes good?
It's nice to have
someone else to eat with.
Uhh...
Come to think of it,
neither you nor I have a name, huh?
Young Plague Dragon
and Venom whatever are just species names.
Well, whatever.
We don't really need names.
I don't mind just calling you "You."
Seems like you've gotten
pretty attached to me.
I guess you're my first friend, huh?
You can stay here as long as you'd like!
Yeah, that's the special poison I made.
Hey, what are doing? That'll kill you!
Oh, right.
When you eat something
that's highly poisonous,
it strengthens your own venom, right?
Is this delicious to you?
Seriously? Let me see...
The skill Poison Resistance
has gone from level four to level five.
How can you eat that like it's nothing?
Come on, bring it!
That was a cinch with the two of us!
We've got this whole teamwork thing down!
Whoa, so close!
It's easy to forget,
but this thing is packing a deadly poison.
I'm begging you, please don't bite me
when you're half-asleep.
But it feels normal
for you to be here now.
Yeah.
This life isn't bad at all.
The Toxic Woman Turned Out to Be Wife Material
Spicy, just like I thought.
Makes me wanna eat meat.
Oh, not something you like, huh?
Well, spice isn't meant
to be eaten straight, anyway.
What's up? Something yummy over here?
I see, where's it at?
Wh-what's that?
It stinks like rotting flesh!
Candidi Cadaverous. Value B-.
A giant mushroom
that emits the odor of a corpse.
It has a potent poison, but practically no
animals would attempt to eat it, anyways.
Don't tell me you're drawn to its poison?
And you're gonna eat it?!
You'll reek if you eat that!
Sorry, I'm sorry!
I'll make it up to you
with a different poisonous plant.
Clay Gun?!
Are you really that angry?!
Oh no...
What...
is this pressure I'm feeling?
Twinheads
Gravity
Status: Enraged, Fear
Gravidon
Tenacious
Not only does it have OP stats,
but it has creepy-sounding skills like
"Gravity" and "Gravidon."
I honestly don't know if I can win.
But skills like "Tenacious" and "Marking"
sound like they are used for tracking,
so escaping seems difficult too.
In that case...
Seems we're thinking the same thing,
partner!
I'll attack and draw its attention!
Use that opening
to hit it with your poison!
The rest...
is just a waiting game!
Figures it wouldn't be that easy.
What?!
My body feels... heavy?!
I can't move!
Is this "Gravity"?!
I might be screwed. This thing is strong.
Like...
serious double trouble!
The Gravity skill wore off!
Take this!
All right, it's working!
Does everything in this forest
have recovery skills or what?!
But I learned something!
The Angry Face does physical attacks,
and the Weeping Face uses magic!
That looks more dangerous
than the previous one.
This must be Gravidon!
I definitely can't let it use that!
Bring on the Bite!
Ouch!
But...
Dragon Punch!
Do it now, Black Lizard!
We did it!
It's poisoned!
Of course you'd use recovery magic.
However...
Whaddaya think?
The poison's pretty potent, right?!
I've experienced it once,
so I know good and well!
Serves you right!
This fight is ours!
Seriously?!
He took his partner out to prevent
the poison from spreading any further!
Dude.
I am NEVER evolving into
a two-headed dragon or anything like that!
But I don't think
it can use magic anymore.
View stats!
Twinheads
Status: Enraged
SACRIFICE
"Sacrifice"?
Oh crap! It's trying to...
drag us down with it!
Run, Black Lizard!
Wait!
Dammit.
I have to hurry after them
or Black Lizard is in trouble!
Get outta my way!
You're finished!
Nutcracker!
The skill Nutcracker
has gone from level one to level two.
This guy's taken care of but...
Black Lizard!
Please be okay!
It's only been a few days since we met,
but we've done so much together...
She's the only friend
I have in this world!
So please, God...
I don't need Human Transformation!
In exchange for that, let her be okay!
That's blood...
It can't be!
Black Lizard!
It didn't get you, right?
Please, answer me!
Black Lizard!
Don't you DARE!
It's okay now.
I'm so happy you're still alive.
Like, honestly...
What a relief.
You have received 234 experience points.
Shut up, don't say a damn word!
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
You're my one
you have earned an additional
and only precious friend that I trust!
234 experience points.
Young Plague Dragon has gone
As long as I have you,
from level 33 to level 37.
I don't care if I can become a human
or not anymore!
You have received the skill
"Human Transformation."
For real?
I've finished cleaning the entrance
and the hallway.
Okay, thanks for that.
But we hardly ever get guests
from out of town like this.
I wonder what they're like.
We'll find out soon enough.
This book looks pretty old.
It's about monsters.
I thought you might like it,
so I took it from the library.
Thank you.
May I take a look?
Of course you can.
A Darkwyrm...
See the large script
along with the pictures?
Yes.
I can't read it, though.
That is ancient text.
It describes the monster's rank.
The Darkwyrm is F-rank.
Even you could beat it.
However,
D-rank monsters are another story.
You have to be a trained adventurer
to have any hope of defeating those.
Moreover, monsters higher than B-rank
are extremely dangerous,
and only Heroes
and Saints can defeat them.
Is this it?
Yes.
They said we should just
go straight inside.
A Rock Dragon...
What's its rank?
The book says C-rank, but I hear
they can get stronger with evolution.
It is no doubt a monster
that would easily kill any normal human.
Which is why I always tell you
and the village people to never, ever
wander into the forest.
Yes. I understand.
It seems they've arrived.
Huh?
Pardon us.
I Became Human and Got Caught
"I Became Human and Got Caught"!
Get stronger.