-I can't wait!
-The snow stopped, too.
-I'll carry it!
-Oh?
We'll be late for the birthday party!
If you run, it'll get ruined! Anna!
I know!
Hey! What's wrong?
Is she lost?
I'll find it for you!
I never lie.
Watch the cake!
Found it!
I'm impressed you figured out
that her ribbon blew off in the wind!
I got it when I saw
she only had one ribbon!
ANNA
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Looks gold-star delicious!
Okay, time for me to get ready!
You're so excited!
Of course I am!
I'm going to make today a special day!
I'll put my coat away!
Mom! Thank you!
Huh? For what?
For my birthday present!
What is she saying? I promised to buy
a smartphone for her present.
Wow!
Now that I'm 14, I really look mature!
Pochi...
Pochi!
What?!
What's this? A dog? A cat?
I'm Pochitan!
-I-It spoke...
-Be quiet!
Wha--
-You need to come with me!
-What?
With this pendant!
W-Whoa!
I haven't finished explaining yet!
Anna?
What's all the... huh?
She's not here?
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
A brilliant inspiration
I'm sure we'll find it
We're Precure, after all
It's calling to us
Where's the truth?
What will we discover?
One mystery after another
Gather the pieces
From now to the past and future
Like evidence
Something shining across time
How? How? Is it a trick?
Why? Why? We'll face it
Look and feel
Figure out the secret
One brave step will lead to a miracle
The answer?!
Found when you notice the unnoticed
It's destiny, it's love
Whispered in a tiny voice
Let's walk that road together!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
A brilliant inspiration
The jewel key connects us
Opening the link moving forward
Hey, us being born and having met
Is a wonderful mystery
Go on! Star Detective Precure!
Debut! Star Detective Precure!
CUREtto Detective Agency.
This day is finally here!
I'm totally going to pass this test!
Excuse-- whoa!
W-What's happening?
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
Was it this pendant?
Come on, what is going on?
-I don't get it!
-A fairy!
You're with a fairy!
So you're a star detective
from the CUREtto Detective Agency?
What?
I'm Mikuru Kobayashi!
I'm Anna Akechi.
That's not important!
What do you mean, fairy?
I was in my room. How did I get here?
Has the detective test already begun?
Ugh!
Allow me to answer!
The famous detective, Sherlock Holmes,
could tell where someone had been
from the marks and stains on their shoes!
So in your case!
You're... not wearing any!
Packed with new features!
The newest in communication!
Alright! Next up is weather!
Okay...
They're perfect!
Which ones should I get?
Those!
Forget that!
I can't believe you
fell here from your room!
It's true!
Pochi-pochi!
Pochi-pochi doesn't mean anything to me.
This little one...
She's got a pacifier. So she's a baby!
-I think that's why she can't talk.
-Huh? But before...
For some reason,
she's a baby now and can't talk.
How do you like my reasoning?
Did I pass the detective test?
What is this detective test
you keep talking about?
That's an easy question to answer!
Star detectives investigate cases,
and help people by solving them!
They're everyone's hopes and dreams!
In order to become a star detective,
I've come to take the detective test!
Star detectives really are amazing!
Alright!
Huh?!
Hang on!
I haven't paid!
I paid for your shoes.
Thank you!
-This place...
-It's a wedding hall?
It's not here!
Where did it go?
Ms. Kono.
Thank you very much.
A bride!
I'll give up on it.
What?
But...!
There's no time before the ceremony.
Help her!
Excuse me!
If you're having trouble, we can help!
Once again, I am Kono,
I work for this wedding hall.
I'm Mari Sohda.
I lost the tiara I was planning
to wear for my wedding.
What?
Then, what's that?
The venue supplied this so I would
have something to wear instead at 1 p.m.
It's similar in size and shape to Mari's,
so we offered it as a replacement.
This is Mari's tiara.
My mother wore the same tiara
at her own wedding.
I wanted to wear it at mine as well.
But it disappeared from this room.
How could it suddenly disappear?
No way!
Is this the real detective test?
I promise I'll find it for you!
Why have you called us here?
You three were the only people to enter
this room after Mari last saw the tiara.
One of you is the culprit
who stole the tiara!
No! That's impossible!
What?
O-Of course it is...
We just have some questions...
I came to photograph the bride.
I came to ask Mari a favor.
A favor?
She wanted me to throw the bouquet to her.
Oh! The bouquet toss!
Yes! If you catch the bouquet thrown
by the bride, you'll share her happiness!
I've always dreamed of catching one!
Requests are allowed?
Mari, you agreed to do it, didn't you?
Tomoka's always late but she came on time,
so I couldn't help myself.
I see.
I was in and out,
preparing for the ceremony.
Are they wearing
the same clothes as earlier?
Yes, there's no way
they could hide a tiara...
Is that so...
The hat!
Maybe he put it in his hat?
Huh?
This tiara is roughly
the same size as Mari's.
-May I see your hat?
-Sure.
It doesn't fit.
He couldn't have put it in here.
What about Tomoka's bag?
It doesn't fit in there either.
Ms. Kono's pouch is too small, too.
Thank you.
But it's really okay.
I'll just have to...
give up on the tiara.
If we can figure out how they took out
the tiara, we'll know the culprit.
I just don't know how.
I always...
Mikuru-chan.
Mikuru-chan!
Are you okay?
I don't know.
We won't make Mari smile at this rate.
I won't be a star detective.
Why do you want to be a star detective?
They helped me before.
Now, I want to become
a star detective and help others!
You're amazing!
If you're a star detective, you can find
the tiara and make Mari smile, right?
Yeah, for sure.
Then become one! A star detective!
But...
Worrying about it won't make it happen!
Take a single step,
and the answer will follow!
A single step of courage
becomes the answer!
Mikuru-chan! Let's go!
Let's go over it all again!
Okay!
That's the second time today!
Earlier today, a girl's ribbon
flew into the hedge...
Inside... the hedge...
Flowers?
I see!
This is the answer!
-The culprit is...
-...that person!
We know who the culprit is!
Who could it be?
The culprit...
is you!
What?
But you saw how the tiara
wouldn't fit in my pouch!
I could never take it out of this room.
Yes.
The tiara is still in this room.
What?
You asked Mari to throw
the bouquet to you.
Then, you hid the tiara in the bouquet.
Then, when you got the bouquet from Mari,
you planned to remove the tiara.
You're good.
But you've made one big mistake.
I'm not Tomoka!
I'm Nijee! A thief from
the Phantom Thieves' Guild!
Phantom Thieves' Guild?
Wasn't that an amazing disguise?
I'll take that!
The tiara!
Huh?
Oh no!
Stop!
He's fast!
Oh snap, baby!
Give back the tiara!
No can do!
This tiara has
a Makoto Jewel in it, after all.
A Makoto Jewel?
The bride's deep care for
the tiara drew a Makoto Jewel to it.
Our goal is to collect these jewels.
In exchange for the tiara,
I'll put on a special show for you!
Lies, envelop!
Come forth, Hanninda!
Hanninda!
It's a Hanninda,
newly developed by Phantom!
It's showtime, baby!
Hanninda!
We have to do something!
Something?
The time to play detective is over!
Your fearful eyes say it all.
You're no detective.
You're just a fake,
who pretends to be one!
She's the real thing!
Mikuru-chan is going to be
a star detective!
Star detective?
Never going to happen.
She will!
Now I want to become
a star detective and help everyone!
She wants to help people!
You're playing tough,
but I know you're scared.
It's true... I'm scared.
I'm scared, but I want
to get the tiara back.
Mari needs help,
and I want to help her too!
Together with Mikuru-chan!
Mikuru-chan!
A single step of courage!
Becomes the answer!
Show me this answer of yours!
Hanninda!
We'll get it back!
-Huh?
-Whoa!
-Another pendant!
-It's the same?!
Precure!
Open!
Jewel Cure Watch!
Precure! Wake-up Time!
3! Discover!
6! And face one another!
9! We are the miraculous duo!
Spin around!
And finish off cutely!
Gold-star closing the case on any mystery!
Star Detective, Cure Answer!
Jumping towards smiles
with layered reasoning!
Star Detective, Cure Mystique!
Star Detective Precure!
I'll show you my answer!
Hanninda!
Han! Nin! Da!
Did I say Precure?
Star detective! I wanted to be
a Star Detective Precure!
Huh? Is this it?
Pochi!
Precure?
They're not like her... Newcomers?
Hanninda!
Da!
You'll never defeat it like that!
Hanninda!
-A single step of courage!
-Becomes the answer!
This is our answer!
CUREtto Case Closed!
Hanninda!
I'll bring down the curtain for today!
He disappeared?
Congratulations!
I'm glad we made it
on time for the ceremony!
Thank you so much!
It wasn't just me!
-The thief?
-It's the real Tomoka!
Sorry I'm late!
Here goes!
Yay!
I have to go home! It's my birthday party!
Um! If I became a Precure,
that means I passed the test, right?
April 1999!
I finally became a star detective
at the CUREtto Detective Agency!
1999?
You're not making sense!
No, it's 1999! April 2nd! Spring!
See?
Huh? Cherry blossoms?
I was in 2027, January, winter.
Then, did I travel back in time?
(NaNaNaNa why? Why? WHY?
NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER?!)
Connect the dots, oh? Oh my!
Could it be a "gold-star case closed!"?
Could it?
Reasoning turns around riddles
Twists and turns, reverse
Even words and behavior are traps? Traps!
Don't just believe them! No!
Pay attention, think and then
Take the first step!
When I see someone in trouble
I immediately want to help
Cause I wanna, wanna do something
So I go running off
Na Na Na mystery! Mystery!
Solving mysteries
Is what a Star Detective does
See through lies and find truth
Find the answer for a smile
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 100
Working together, we can figure it out
Friends are a true miracle
Let's go! Star Detective
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 1,000
Hand in hand with my friends
Until everything's solved!
We're Precure, after all
(NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER!)
What's a Precure? Time travel?
Maybe we'll find the answer
if we go there!
-Go where?
-To the CUREtto Detective Agency!
STAR DETECTIVE PRECURE!
"INTRODUCING THE GENIUS, JETT-SENPAI!"
That mystery! CUREtto Case Closed!