That isn't Fushi!
Fushi and Yuki attempt to save Mizuha.
Alas...
Fushi loses the vessel of the boy.
This way, guys!
We defeat it!
A Willingness to Believe
The hell is your problem?!
Let's lock the door!
Right!
Hey, what are we doing in the science room?
What are you looking for?
Anything we can use.
I found salt!
What good is that going to do?
I thought maybe it'd melt it, like a slug.
Stupid. It's just going to get
washed away by the sprinklers.
We just avoid using fire.
We're making use of it.
Tonari-san?
Found it!
What are you doing with that?
I want to mix it with panko.
Hey, what should we do?
Make a barricade.
Draw its attention.
Draw its attention?!
But how?
Let's get this over there.
Is this going to be enough?
I wish we had a little more.
We'll need time.
So heavy.
Seriously?
It's coming!
Hold it back!
Dumbass! It's a pull door!
What did you just do?
This way, guys!
Are you sure you want to do this?
Yes. I'll give it a try.
See you on the rooftop in ten minutes.
Try what?
Everyone, please come with me.
Now, very quietly...
I'll tell you what we need to defeat it.
Let's split into two groups to gather it all.
Defeat it? How?
No, no, no! There's no way!
Hey, that Tonari girl isn't with us.
It's okay.
Tonari-san is buying us time.
What do we need to defeat it?
Nagisa!
Tell us, quick!
That's it! Follow me!
Fire. Fire.
How's that?!
The water makes it burn even more!
You're a tough one!
I still have more!
No! Why?!
Shoot!
Shit! Sorry, let me go!
Fushi!
Do something! Please!
It's the metal sphere we used in Renril!
I have to let everyone know we're safe!
Fire. Fire.
Don't worry, Fushi.
I can keep going!
Fushi-sama!
R-Reverend...
Chami, ammo.
Ammo!
W-We're all out!
Fushi-sama... I'm sorry.
It's fine.
I guess not all Nokkers are the same.
Now, let's go.
I'll get you out of here.
Reverend!
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to fight back?
I'd like to defeat you and
give Mizuha back her father,
but I don't feel like doing it by force.
Is something wrong?
Well, no matter.
I'll play with you until you run out of ammo.
Come on, now.
Lost your will to fight already?
It's no fun if you aren't
at least trying to dodge!
I did.
It isn't that I lost my will to fight
so much as that I'm just interested now.
What do you want to know?
This Paradise that you were in...
What is it like there?
Are there plants?
Homes to shelter from the wind?
A favorite chair?
A window that gives you a
free view of the outside?
Warm meals?
I hope Fushi-san can hold his own.
I'm sure he can. He can do it.
Okay, we're almost out.
Hang in there.
What shall we do when we're home?
First things first. A bath.
I'm so hungry.
You should come over.
Extraterrestrials welcome!
You might get invaded.
Fushi can make us as much bedding as we need.
That's not what I mean.
We have a common language.
We can become friends.
I believe it.
A common language?
That's cold!
What?! I'm drenched!
I'm sorry, Mizuha.
I dropped some water.
Oh, Dad.
Welcome home.
Look.
I got some new flowers delivered.
Don't you love the colors?
What's the occasion?
We're having Dad's favorite again.
Oh, but you love beef stew, too, Mizuha.
This is the kind of shit
that makes you miserable.
It's delicious.
Here, Yuki, we brought you some gifts.
Well, we'll be off now.
Be well, Yuki.
Okay!
Leaving so soon?
Stay safe.
Look at this, Yuki.
Hi, Yuki!
Have you been a good boy?
We may be far apart in body,
but we're right there in spirit!
Vice President!
Aoki-kun!
Jeez! You could have told
us you were struggling!
Now's not the time to be whining.
We gotta get back before sundown.
You're right.
Or I won't make it home for dinner.
That's what you meant?
We're being tested right now.
Tested?
What do we believe?
What do we do?
I have hope.
We can understand each other's
pain because we have bodies.
And our hearts can grow closer.
Almost ten minutes.
Over here!
Look, the exit!
Jump over!
We did it!
It worked!
We got it!
No way...
Are we still in danger?
Shit...
It isn't dead!
Run!
The hell is that shit?
Uh-huh.
The hell indeed.
Messar-san! Hairo-san! Kai-san!
You're here to help!
You know them?
They're Fushi-san's friends!
Tonari-san's Ligard came to let us know.
Does Fushi know about this?
Bon says he's headed
where he should find him.
Can he make it on his own?
It seems he isn't on his own.
Lay a finger on the kids! I dare you!
My sword of justice will taste your blood!
Hirotoshi!
Who?
Okay, let's go home, guys.
Everyone, get on the bear!
I can't!
It doesn't know when to quit.
Everyone, go!
Let's go!
Can we really take it on without Fushi-san?
We're taking it on.
What's that supposed to do?
My sword didn't seem to be very useful.
Stop it!
The water reservoir!
Oh, shit! Run!
Hurry!
Touch the water and you're dead!
Avoid it, mister bear!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
What about the enemy?
N-No way!
It revived?
Apologies. We took it too far.
Tonari!
What the hell?!
Fushi-san?
Tonari-san!
You're joking. Was that her?
What's gotten into her?
The Nokkers.
Impossible!
Fushi-san already defeated all of them.
Think about how he's been acting
lately, and it'll make sense.
Something's been happening
when we weren't watching.
It's been 500 years.
Who knows how they might have evolved?
We don't have time to talk.
Wanna go?
Absolutely not! She's one of ours!
Stop it!
Why?!
It's kill or be killed!
What is it, Fushi-sama?
No...
What just happened?
We were too late...
What the hell is this?
It's that steel ball we used in Renril!
Fushi?
We aren't Nokkers!
Messar-san's locked in!
Fu-chan did it.
Well? What do we do now?
Look over there!
It's looking at us!
Is it coming?
Stay away! Stay away! Stay away!
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm sorry. What happened?
It's as if time has stopped.
They're stuck.
I made it.
Who's that?
Dunno.
Oh, no!
Don't step in the water!
I remember him! Satoru!
You know him?
Yeah!
He was hanging out with Fushi-kun and, uh...
Aoki-kun, from a year below us.
With Fushi?!
With Onii-chan?
Could you bring that here?
Huh? Bring what?
Oh, she moves.
Now, then...
What to do with you?
Kill you? Or...
Wait.
Please rest.
Take it easy.
It's okay.
It's all okay now.
What's okay?
Don't worry about me.
I'll stay here.
I'll stay and complete my duties
as the head of the Guardians.
I want to live up to my
ancestors' expectations.
Are you saying goodbye?
Are you trying to get us to hate you?
Mizuha, I don't care where you stay,
but if you want to finish your duties as the
head of the Guardians, you'd better act quick.
Make the Nokkers stop messing
with Fushi and getting bystanders
involved in your invasion,
including by what they're doing at school.
Yes.
I'll do what I can.
I-Is there any kind of food you don't like?
Any allergies?
What's gotten into you?
Let's talk about the future!
For us and the Guardians!
At my place!
Over some hot pot or something!
"Us"?
You trust us?
No matter what the past was like,
we need to give the future a chance.
Let's go to that crêpe shop again.
Come to the Occult Club, too.
We can go dowsing together.
I can trust you, right?
All of you?
Preview
In a moment of relief,
the Guardians offer Yuki and the
others a token of friendship.
In the underground hollows,
Fushi fights against the final resistance.
His last remaining vessel
becomes the key to his awakening.
Clean Water