He did it...
Well, I managed somehow.
You okay, man?! Yer arm's gone!
We should get back, and fast!
You need treatment on the double.
Jeez, would you pipe down?
Enough with the shouting!
It's not helping me heal, y'know?
Sorry, but most people would f-freak
out over something like this!
Are you seriously okay?!
Not good. Bled too much.
I've got a whole lot to say,
but for now, let's head back.
Hajime, your arm...
Are you all right?! Let's get
that looked at quickly!
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
EPISODE 9: AFTER THE BATTLE
Where am I?
My left arm got eaten, huh?
Wish I had something to eat.
Am I hearing this correctly?
Pure silver adventurers are
a valuable resource for our guild.
Especially when it comes
to covering rural areas,
where they shoulder
even more responsibility.
Which is why we take great care
in doling out work to them
to ensure they will be available
for as long as possible.
Please see to restoring your combat
assets as quickly as viable.
I'm ending the transmission.
R-Right. Ending transmission.
Hey, Olive.
Was this grub yours?
I was starving, so I couldn't help myself.
I'm so sorry!
I had no idea there were two
quasi-calamity creatures...
I failed in evaluating the situation!
Mr. Shinonome, I don't know
how to make it up to you!
Look at me, Olive.
See? Right hand works
just fine, so it's all good.
You know I'm injured, right?
I-If that'll satisfy you,
th-then go ahead.
Go ahead and what?
Yours aren't really big enough to—
I bid you to continue resting
on the second floor today!
Man, the whole town's turned up.
And where the hell's Rirui?
I haven't seen her at all today.
You up, Pops?
Huh? Yeah.
Whoa, your arm really is gone!
Does it hurt? You okay?
The wound was taken care
of with healing magic.
But I'm supposed to rest today,
since I'm short on blood.
We haven't spoken since
you first came to town.
I hear you helped some
of our youngsters out.
I wanted to thank you.
You're the chief of the dwarves, right?
We all live here,
so I figured I should help out.
Right you are. Mind if I have a seat?
Go on.
Now, as for why I'm here today...
He's just gonna act
like nothing happened!
I wanted to discuss making a prosthesis
for your missing left arm.
I make my living working with machines.
I've done a few artificial
limbs before too.
I thought I'd offer my services.
Sounds good to me!
The chief's gizmos are awesome!
They go whir and clank!
He even handles the upkeep on 'em!
You oughta take the offer!
And, uh, how much would this cost?
I reckon the village
and guild would cover—
Pleasure doing business!
All righty, then I'll be on my way.
A projectile punch? Maybe a drill?
The stuff of dreams!
A drill? What?
Well, Pops, you need anything?
Don't be shy!
Nothing I can think of.
Rirui! What's she doing out there
instead of coming to see me?
Oh, is Rirui around?
Yeah, there she is!
Hey, Rirui!
And there she goes!
What?!
After I lost my arm protecting her!
What's she thinking?!
For real?! Then it's no wonder she ran!
Why? I saved her life, y'know.
It's gotta be awkward!
She probably thinks you can't adventure
anymore and that it's her fault!
Is that it?
Is this another girl thing?
More like a compassion thing.
She thinks I'm out to pasture, huh?
Guess we're doing this. Come on, Anyango.
Hey!
Hajime! Stop it!
We can't do this!
What are you thinking, Hajime?!
You're supposed to be resting!
She's right, Pops!
The guild lady was in tears!
You can't! Please, stay in bed!
She's just doing her job.
Go back, Hajime!
What're you gonna do if a slime shows up?!
Nothing special!
You're hurt real bad! You could die!
Not freaking likely.
I swear...
Here we are.
Today's job is collecting yogul fruits.
But Hajime, you can't climb trees anymore.
Unbelievable...
Watch real closely, you little dummy.
I'm gonna lower the rope from up above,
so you two use it to climb up.
K-Kinda slippery...
Damn it! Enough! Get out of my face!
Hajime!
Pops!
Well, it wasn't exactly flawless, but I
still got it done without much trouble.
This is all Rirui's fault...
Now you can't even climb a tree right!
Yeah, I'll admit I had
a lot to say to you.
But I'm not one for big lectures,
so I'll keep it simple.
I'm glad you're okay.
Hajime.
Rirui... is gonna get strong.
I'll get strong enough
to replace your left arm!
No, strong enough to take care of you!
Hey, if we're doing this,
I'll get real strong and give
you an allowance, Pops!
What, so I'm gonna be mooching
off a pair of kids?
Well...
I'll be waiting,
but I won't get my hopes up.
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
Man, something doesn't sit right
about being told to take it easy.
I hope my arm's ready soon.
Work is piling up too.
The sooner I'm back in action, the better.
Fool. You should be patient enough
to wait for a proper prosthesis.
Bosslady Veronica!
You're back in town?
I heard my childhood friend went
and got seriously injured.
We'll cover the guild jobs
until you're able to work again.
What are you plotting?
You are so rude!
Chair.
Yes, ma'am!
You've seen how poorly
things go for adventurers
who rush back to work after
being injured, right?
You need to take it slow
and make sure you're ready.
Yeah, but can you two
really handle things?
Well, I don't plan on overexerting myself.
And despite everything about him,
this one here's a top-ranked silver.
Wait, so he's not just some degenerate?
So, that being the case, don't worry
about us. Just take care of yourself.
Being able to take my time like
this on a job is wonderful.
The better the arm, the better
it'll be for both you and the village.
Okay.
I included some synthetic nerve
circuits. What do you think?
It moves perfectly!
This is a hell of an arm!
Still can't feel anything, though.
Even dwarven technology
isn't that advanced.
However, why not improve on
things your old arm couldn't do?!
So that no matter where
an adventure takes you,
whether you fall into a volcano
or get trampled by a dragon,
it will remain unscratched!
What about the rest of me?!
Dwarves are really like that, huh?
Yo.
Whacha doing?
Making a chair!
Remember how the chief smooshed
that one from the other day?
Oh, yeah.
A real dragon could park its butt
on this bad boy, and it'd be fine!
Getting your dwarf on, huh?
You're amazing, Anya!
I'm impressed you can put
something like this together.
Aw, don't go buttering me up!
Besides, the chief's my mentor,
so I know a thing or two!
Wait, do you even know what a mentor is?
Of course I do! Tastes great, right?
Ow, ow, ow...
Old Dai!
You okay, Old Dai?
Oh, it's Anyango.
Did you throw out your back
pulling radishes again?
Yes, but we need to do
a bit more today...
Ow, ow, ow!
Don't force yourself to move!
Leave this to us, Gramps!
Just need to yank this out, right?
Yeah, that oughta do it.
Ready and...
What is this thing?!
That's so creepy!
You're not getting away!
That was really something!
That was great, Anya!
Teach Rirui how you did it!
Gosh, she's really gotten better at this.
Did you teach her how to harvest them?
I am, in fact, Anyango's
radish harvesting mentor.
A mentor, huh?
Slap a leather glove on it, and you
can't even tell it's prosthetic!
I'm glad you like it.
This really is amazing tech, though.
Say, Chief, did you have
a mentor of your own?
Well, of course.
When I was younger,
he helped me polish my skills.
That makes sense.
I use a blunt weapon,
and she uses a sword.
I'm bad with spirit magic,
but she's got a knack for it.
She might be better off
learning from someone else.
By the way, what's this button do?
What was that?!
We have returned!
Welcome back.
Hajime, your arm's done!
Yeah. Turned out pretty good.
What a relief!
She's back too, huh?
From a job well done, no less!
People are abuzz about the show
of swordplay and spirit magic...
from the chair person!
Stare...
Can I help you with something?
Strip.
Say what now?
It's not gonna cost you
anything! Just do it!
He's manhandling me!
Knock it off!
Is this what you're into now?!
Well, you still need
to confess to me first!
I just wanted to check out his physique...
Hajime's getting clobbered!
Hajime, Hajime! Rirui is a girl!
And Hajime, Hajime, Hajime
loves girls! He sure does!
And Rirui is a girl!
And Rirui will always be beside Hajime!
Always will!
What kinda dream is this?
Who said you could waltz into my dream?
Don't use your succubus
powers for this nonsense.
But Hajime, you...
Unbelievable.
Come on, get dressed.
Today, I'm gonna see if he's good
enough with a sword and spirit magic
to be Rirui's mentor.
MOUNTAIN WOLVES
We're tagging along for your job today.
What are you doing, you klutz?
Thank you so much!
Let's work hard!
Yeah!
I don't mind you coming with,
but is your arm okay?
Yeah, just think of this as some rehab.
Stare...
I-I feel eyes upon me!
I can't believe this fool is ignoring
me to make eyes at some guy!
Oh, thank you! Thank you so much!
Stare...
Come on, Rirui, don't stare
like that! It's rude.
I-I'm sorry, but I'm just
worried about your arm...
How many times do I gotta tell
you! It's just fine! Seriously.
I swear. Just take a good look!
Not only that...
How'd you like that?!
I'm gonna be even stronger with this arm!
So quit your sulking already!
You got that, Rirui?!
Really? You're not weaker now, Hajime?
Enough already!
Where's a squirt get off worrying
about a big tough guy, anyway?!
Understood! And awesome!
You really are awesome, Hajime!
Sounds like you finally get it.
Gonna work hard today!
Hajime, I got a mountain wolf!
That's a rabbit. Let it go.
Oh, okay.
Lucky little guy.
Damn it, I'm trying to scope
this guy out today.
His gaze is so intense!
This is so irritating for some reason.
This is my chance to see what he's got!
That was nothing.
What did you think of my
graceful attack, Hajime?
Dumb broad got in the way.
Hajime...
Watch it! That's dangerous!
Shut up!
I demand your life to satisfy my pride!
Man, I seriously don't understand
what makes women upset.
Quit dodging!
I just wanna see how he handles a blade.
Let's go, let's go!
Rirui! There's a mountain wolf!
That's a damn bow!
Er, yes?
No! I mean, I thought you used
a sword and spirit magic!
That's what the rumors say!
Well, I used wind spirit magic
to slice up some enemies
while protecting Lady Veronica,
so maybe it just appeared that way?
Wh-What the hell?
Then what was the point of even
coming out here today?
How should I know?!
What's wrong, Hajime?
Huh? Oh.
Are you okay?
It looks like I'm gonna be the one
to show you the ropes after all.
I wouldn't want anyone else.
Is that right?
Welp, looks like it's you and me
again going forward, partner.
Yeah!
NEXT TIME: A HAIRCUT AND A DECISION