According to witnesses, the victims were
attacked by a large flock of eyeballs.
Sara's not coming today either?
Flum?
Flum.
Are you okay, Flum?
Your face!
Hmm? Is there something on my face?
Don't you remember?
You were popping out eyeballs!
Huh? What the heck?
Did you have some kind of bad dream?
You weirdo. Anyway, where's Milkit?
I didn't dream or hallucinate it!
I clearly remember the smell and sounds!
You'd turned into a monster, Ink!
A monster? That's such
a mean thing to say.
But I know what I saw!
You weren't human!
I'm a human being!
The Church's tinkering must've
turned you into something inhuman.
That's why...
That's why you don't have a heart.
Huh?
I see. Now I know what
that medicine you took was.
It was meant to suppress your powers.
But you stopped taking it and
your powers went out of control,
so those eyeballs appeared...
and went after all those people—
after Sara.
No!
No, no...
No, no, no!
I wouldn't do that!
I love Sara and all of you!
But Ed, Jonny, and even
Ottilie disappeared!
And now Eterna and Milkit are gone, too.
I wouldn't hurt my friends.
You did, though!
That's not what a friend does!
So I'm not a friend?
I guess...
I'm not allowed to be
anywhere else but there.
Why... Why is this happening?
Get out here, Flum Apricot.
FLUM
DEIN
DEIN AND FLUM
Dein!
What are you doing here?
What else? A little guinea pig ran away,
so I came to take it back.
Wait, did you abduct Milkit too?
The mummy girl's probably
being tortured by the lady.
She'll be dead by now, I'd wager.
"The lady"?
Can't you figure it out?
I mean the mummy girl's former master,
Satils Francois.
Huh?
Is that why she reacted like that?
Whoa.
Come at me, Flum!
You want to save your friend, don't you?
If you can even call this freak a friend!
I like that murderous rage
of yours. Bring it, Flum.
Dein! Where'd you go?
I'm impressed you could
keep up. Attagirl, Flum!
Dein!
I'm sorry to say this after
you chased me so far,
but it's my job to get her
where she needs to be.
If you want her,
you'll have to fight your way out.
Dein!
What's with them?
They're working together
and moving in sync.
How?
Scan.
GODIN TORRES
TOTAL STATS: 2,482
Godin Torres, total stats of 2,482.
C-Rank? Is this one the leader, then?
GODIN TORRES
TOTAL STATS: 2,482
Huh? Godin again?
I know that one.
He's Grimmy, Dein's lackey.
GODIN TORRES
TOTAL STATS: 2,482
Why does it say Godin?
GODIN TORRES
TOTAL STATS: 2,482
They all have the same name and stats?
GODIN TORRES
TOTAL STATS: 2,482
What's going on here?
GODIN TORRES
TOTAL STATS: 2,482
Something's up with their eyes.
The Church must've meddled with them.
Here he comes.
Reversal!
One down!
Am I supposed to take all of them on...
all by myself?
I...
I'm not going down.
I refuse to die here!
Flum, use your prana!
Strike the ground with your prana!
A technique that cuts up the enemy
with a barrage of sword slashes:
Cavalier Arts: Prana Storm.
Stay alert, Flum. There's more coming.
Right!
Gadhio.
You came to help.
Yeah.
This girl named Sara asked me to.
Huh?
Sara's... alive?
Yeah.
Having thought she'd lost everything,
Flum had been shrouded in despair,
but with those words, a ray of hope
began to shine within her once again.
I have to go.
Link up.
Connection.
Flum!
Get going!
I'll handle this.
What the heck? You're a freak.
One of the Children?
Ink blabbed about that too?
That useless nitwit.
You spiral monster.
Prepare to die!
Right back at you, mister.
Connection.
Just wait! I'll be right there...
Milkit!
Ink!
I see.
The stable outside the yard has
a hidden passage to the inside, huh?
A Church lapdog?
Welcome, Flum Apricot,
to Satils Francois's mansion!
Where are Milkit and Ink?
Beats me. You should worry
more about your own life.
Ha! You're the one who's gonna die!
I'm sending your ass to the grave!
That's one bothersome body
you've got there.
I could say the same to you.
Did you get that in return
for joining the Church of Origin?
Yes, that's right.
Isn't it great?
And just for that,
you sold out your buddies?
I had no other choice!
You're no different!
If you were faced with absolute power
that no amount of money
or influence could ever equal,
a power that could even
change the laws of the world,
even you...
would make the same choice.
That's Satils Francois for you.
The mummy girl's former master
has some nasty taste.
Those tentacles will bat
any regular attacks away.
In that case...
Prana Shaker.
Too bad!
Come on! What's wrong?
Do what you always do,
and show you've got the guts
to take from me!
Gotcha,
Flum Apricot!
With my buddies dead
and my humanity gone...
I was forced to think about
what I even had left!
But it looks like I can cross
one last regret off that list!
Your life is mine, Flum!
The lady told me not to kill you,
but like I care about her orders!
This will be the first step
of my comeback.
I'll rule the West District again.
Actually, no.
I'll take over the whole
kingdom this time,
with this power of mine!
Create a clear vision in your mind
and say the words that come naturally.
Rev...
Begging for your life? Not gonna help.
Reversal...
What did you do, Flum?!
Huh? The tentacles are rotting away?
Flum had only pictured them
loosening their grip on her.
Reversal!
What the hell?
My power's supposed to be divine!
Isn't it supposed to be
the great Origin's power?!
That's what you get for relying
on Origin's shady power!
I'm not letting some
damn slave girl stop me!
Prana Shaker:
Reversal!
I see. So even Origin's power
can be reversed.
It's a voice of corruption...
Flum Apricot.
You mustn't listen
to the voice of corruption.
Flum Apricot.
You mustn't look its way.
Damn, those voices again.
That lady and Origin...
Flum Apricot.
Why are they so scared of this slave girl?
What are you mumbling about?
Making excuses for losing?
You think you've already won?
You don't have a clue.
You have no idea what my true ability is.
This is my very own power,
granted to me by Origin.
One that I can use thanks to the
dark crystal embedded in me!
Huh?
Ink's heart isn't beating.
There must be something
acting as its replacement.
Has Ink had a dark crystal
embedded in her, too?
The power of the core will
slaughter all that defy me!
The core?
The core broke?
More! Take over her body!
Turn into an ugly lump of flesh
and die, Flum!
Okay, next.
Ink didn't know she was
popping out eyeballs
or attacking people.
This power must be...
What's wrong? Why'd you all stop?
Defend me like you always do!
Make me...
Not happening.
Huh?
That's Ink's power.
A power she uses to protect her friends,
family, and those dear to her.
Bah! This power is mine!
That's what they told me, too!
You were tricked.
Because that made you
easier to manipulate.
You seem to be in a spot of bother.
I'm with the Church.
I'm willing to lend you aid.
"I wouldn't put it past
that bitch," he thought.
And the moment he followed up with,
"And I'd fall for it as I am now, too..."
We want to be linked. Let's connect.
It can't be! This is my power!
Defend me!
I said all those awful things to Ink,
and she's still protecting me.
I have to apologize to her.
Tell me. Where is Ink?
It makes no sense!
How could I lose to a slave like you?
I'm a natural-born ruler!
After we lost our nobility,
I was forced to struggle in the slums...
But I clawed my way up with my own hands!
I'm a champion of the people!
I spent years building my empire,
and some heartless monsters show up
outta nowhere to destroy it all?
This isn't right! It can't be right!
Screw the Church. Screw the Children.
Screw Origin!
Fuck it all!
Fuck you!
What the hell? How could I lose?
I don't give a shit!
All my buddies who I used to
goof off with are dead too.
Hey, what do you think I'm supposed to do?
You're the one who abandoned them.
They believed in you and followed you.
But you took away their wills
and turned them into pawns.
You have no right to whine
and moan after what you did.
Why are you getting mad at me?
Oh, are you playing hero again,
Miss Goody Two-Shoes?
They were able to be of use to me.
They should be happy about that.
Yeah, keep telling yourself that.
Keep trying to run away from the fact
that you betrayed your friends.
I didn't ask for any of this
either, you know.
If that punk Kahnis hadn't turned on me...
What's with that look?
If you were forced to choose between
your life and your friendships...
If you had to choose one or the other,
you'd make the same choice!
I'm not like you.
I'd never sacrifice the people
near and dear to me.
Enough of your idealistic nonsense!
You were sold out by your friends, too!
Into slavery, even!
You were this close to ending up like me!
Did you think that'd make me
take pity on you?
Don't expect to be coddled.
It's disgusting.
Me, coddled? You're kidding me.
Dein had lost everything—
his power, his fame, his friends,
and his place in the world.
All he had left was his pointless ego and
his obsession with the girl before him.
And now, even his ego was in tatters.
No... No!
What drove me was...
We want to be linked. Let's connect.
Go away! Stay out of my head!
I...
We want to be linked. Let's connect.
I decide what I do!
What's going on here?
I'll kill...
I will kill you.
Flum.
If only you hadn't shown up,
my dream would...
Dein did say he had
a core embedded in him.
In that case...
I can put him down for good!
Reversal!
Who knows how many people
you've sacrificed for your dream?
Regret the choices that
led you here as you die.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
THE END AND THE BEGINNING