I told you no!
You are absolutely not
going into the forest!
But Mr. Doz might still be alive!
Then why hasn't he
come back to the village?
I-I'm not sure why, but...
If you're worried about me going alone,
then let's get the villagers
to form a search party!
Will you give it a rest already?!
We cannot afford to risk your life
or that of anyone else in the village!
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'll ask the guild to investigate.
Adventurers should
come to help in due time.
All right.
I'm sorry for being so unreasonable.
I ate well and slept so good yesterday.
Now I'm gonna level up like crazy
and aim for that Human Transformation!
What's that?
Can't be just a puddle, right?
Maybe it's a monster.
Doesn't look very strong.
I can use this to farm experience points.
Wonder what its stats-
Ow!
My head hurts! What is this?!
The View Stats skill cannot provide
such specific information at level three.
Even my eyes are burning!
The "View Stats" skill has gone from
level three to level four.
Whoa!
Wh-what the hell is that?!
What was that stuff?
Oh no!
What in the world was that?
Definitely something
I shouldn't get close to!
But its stats weren't anything special...
Oh well, I should just leave it be.
I'll search
in a different direction today.
What's that?
A pot?
It'd probably be handy
to put fruits and stuff in.
That's a monster?!
Rank
Potortoise
Status: Normal
So is a Potortoise a tortoise or a pot?
Dragon Punch!
That did nothing!
I'll have to give it all I've got, then!
Yah!
How'd you like that one?!
That jerk used Rest!
It's too hard!
Okay, then!
A tortoise, eh?
The non-aquatic type, perhaps?
Let's see if you can swim!
Go!
You have gained 36 experience points.
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
you have earned
additional experience points.
You have gone from level 14 to level 15.
Feels good to sweat after a good fight!
Dastardly King
Wrongdoer
You have received
the title "Dastardly King."
"Wrongdoer" has gone
from level two to level three.
Whoa! Why are there so many?!
Oh, I know!
Normal Skill
Call Allies
You were calling your buddies, huh!
Eh?
Don't tell me they're...
c-combining?
Nah, couldn't be.
Well...
Here I go!
Take...
this!
You have gained the skill "Meteorite."
Oh, so that counts as a skill then.
You have gained 594 experience points.
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
you have earned
additional experience points.
You have gone from level 15 to level 30.
Fly
View Stats
The skill Fly has gone
from level one to level two.
View Stats has gone
from level four to level five.
Ooh, beating a group of them
is pretty efficient.
Well, darn.
Their shells are always
gonna break when I beat them.
So much for having a useable pot.
But I leveled up, and I got some meat,
so it's not all bad.
I want vegetables too, not just meat.
Veggies are important.
But I still haven't learned
Human Transformation, even at this level.
I've got 10 levels
until my next evolution,
but will it really take that long
for me to learn it?
What's that sound?
Sounds like footsteps.
Haven't heard any like that before.
A bear?
But something's off...
What are its stats?
You are too far away,
and the stats can not be read.
Details on the species can be viewed.
Let's do that.
Claybear
Monster made
from clod.
Powerful,
with high recovery ability.
"Claybear": a D+ rank monster.
A monster made from clod.
It is powerful,
with high recovery ability.
So it's the same rank as me.
Can I stand a chance at beating it
if I fight hard enough?
Also...
a Claybear?
Does that mean it's bear-shaped clay?
In which case, maybe after I win,
I can freely mold it and fire it up...
to make stuff like pots and jars, right?
All right, I'm gonna make it
into some furnishings for my pad!
Looks like it hasn't noticed me at all.
Then this calls for a sneak attack!
Eat this...
Dastardly...
King Fist!
It's too late!
Wha-
That's no bear! Definitely NOT a bear!
That thing has no right
to call itself a bear!
Hey, here's round two!
How'd that do?!
That took out a good amount of HP!
Regenerate
Crud! It can heal itself!
I'll never beat him at this rate!
What do I do?
I can't beat him in one shot
at my current level.
The most powerful thing I have
is that Meteorite skill I just learned,
but there's no way it could pick up
that behemoth and fly.
For now, I'll just have to use
hit-and-run tactics!
I'll go around to the back...
and attack!
Then immediately run!
Come on! Bring it!
I can win if I keep running down its MP!
This fight is mine!
Is that a Sandstorm skill?!
You're kidding me...
Hey, that's cheating, man!
I can't hit you with my Roll attack now!
My plan of going around the back
won't work anymore.
It's lost a whole lot of MP.
Maybe because it used
Regenerate, Sandstorm,
and Transform?
What happened to its body?
Maybe I could...
Now!
The clay softens
when it's away from the body!
If I use this to hit it with Meteorite...
No, that probably won't
take away all its HP.
It can still use Regenerate
even with just a little left.
Well then!
Oh, just shut up already!
Did I do it?
You have gained 150 experience points.
Walking Egg
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
you have earned an additional
150 experience points.
Young Plague Dragon
has gone from level 30 to level 33.
Thank goodness.
You have gained the skill "Nutcracker."
Nutcracker?
Oh, that attack I just did
became a skill, huh?
It wasn't very cool, though.
But...
it sure did look like a Nutcracker.
In any case, I got the clay.
The Pot Turned Out to Be a Tortoise
That should do it.
I'll go gather some food
while I wait for it to finish firing.
What's up with this one?
Lightning Shroom, Value E-.
Because it leaches all nutrition
from the trees it grows on,
they are unable to bear any fruit.
The nutrients taken in
make it rich and delicious.
However,
it has a slightly paralyzing poison.
Paralysis, huh?
I don't have resistance to that,
so forget it.
I get so many more details now that my
View Stats skill is leveled up.
It's a huge help.
Let's appraise this one, too.
What's the-
Carnivorous Flower, Value C-.
A rare plant that eats animals.
However, it cannot digest salt,
so the salt is accumulated
in the white part of the root.
A meat-eating plant...
That's disturbing,
but the salt is stocked up in here, huh?
Salt is crucial for cooking.
I'll take some, then!
I told you no!
You are absolutely not
going into the forest!
I'm sorry, Miss Marielle.
Don't worry.
I'll ask the guild to investigate.
Adventurers should
come to help in due time.
But, if there's a chance
that Mr. Doz is still alive...
Was out there fishin',
and I saw Doz in a thicket o' trees.
But he didn't notice me.
Just kept walkin' deeper in the forest
until he disappeared.
He was mutterin' something along the way.
I'm not sure if it's true, but...
Myria, we're goin' for the Rock Dragon
even if you don't come with.
But if you don't help us out,
there's a chance
me and Grantz are gonna die.
Oh no...
Fine.
But if things get dangerous,
we're going back home.
None of this would have happened
if I had just stopped them.
So if Mr. Doz is still alive,
then I have to find him.
Fireball!
I'll be fine if I keep calm.
Monster Shroom, Value D.
It can walk after reaching maturity
and becomes a monster that attacks people.
It tastes similar to meat
and is considered a delicacy.
Another good one.
Seems like it'd make a flavorful broth
when simmered.
Oh, found another weird mushroom!
Moro Trogia, Value A.
Value A?
A mushroom so valuable
it can revive a nation with a failing
economy if successfully cultivated.
Whoa!
It is hallucinogenic
and causes an intense euphoria.
500 years ago,
it was discovered that it could be
crushed and mixed with stimulant drugs,
which created a
substantial number of addicts, and-
Nope! Never touching that one!
The title Itty-Bitty Hero
has gone from level one to level two.
Good.
Piperis, Value B+.
Has a unique aroma
that works up an appetite,
and was at one time considered
the most popular spice.
Demand for the spice
was high among the nobility,
to the point where it had the
same value of its weight in gold.
Wow.
This fruit was that valuable?
I'll gather some to try.
I'm pretty deep in the forest now.
It might be too dangerous
to go any further.
What a huge haul!
I'll take another look around the
outskirts near the village then go home.
This Light Shroom is amazing!
It really lives up to its name!
Should be about done now.
Whoa! It worked!
Now I can cook!
It's almost ready!
Tasty!
Salt really is a game-changer!
The saltiness and the umami of the meat
mix perfectly with the broth!
I feel like I've reclaimed
a life I'd forgotten.
Title Skill
Mr. Cook
The title Mr. Cook
has gone from level one to level two.
Hm.
This bowl is a bit hard to drink from.
There was some spillage, too.
Guess I'll make a new one.
I know. I'll make a spoon next!
After that,
I'll cover the wall with bricks.
You have gained the title
"Ceramic Artisan."
Ma'am, we've come to the forest.
Miss Meltia, wake up! We're here!
There's no doubt about it.
This is the place the guild
wants us to investigate.
This is Noah's Forest, then?
I'm home!
Oh, right. No one's gonna answer me.
Well, better butcher the meat
and strip the pelts from these wolves.
I'll put the pelts out to dry later.
I'm getting pretty used to this world.
Hey!
Dang it! Those stupid monkeys!
I've gotta do something or they're gonna
eat my entire stock of jerky!
I need to fend them off somehow.
Just you wait, stupid monkeys!
I'm gonna steep some jerky
in this poisonous concoction
that I just cooked up.
Then let you eat it!
You know,
I've pretty much learned
how to tell from sight
whether wild plants are poisonous or not.
Seems like there's
poison flowers around here.
Wait. Forget poison.
I should decorate the outside of my cave
with some pretty flowers to help take the
edge off the pains of everyday life.
What's that?
I've never seen
that kind of monster before.
Venom Princess Lecerta
Status: Normal
Attack:
Defense:
Magic:
Agility:
Normal Skills
Venom Fang
Venom Claws
Roll
Clay Gun
Species: Venom Princess Lacerta.
Skills: Venom Fang. Venom Claws.
Venom Fa-
Venom Cla-
Double Poison. Poison Master.
Venom Fa-
Double Poison-
Venom Cla-
Venom Fa-
Double Poison-
Venom Cla-
Poiso-
What the heck is this?!
It only has poison-related skills!
Did it run away?
How'd it get there?!
Oh crud!
Is that the Clay Gun skill?!
Ouch!
It left?
Huh? Did it give up the fight?
Huh? This pain feels off...
Poison Resistance
has gone from level three to level four.
This poison is something else!
I can't even move my shoulder!
Is this part of its plan?
The Toxic Woman Turned Out to Be Wife Material
"The Toxic Woman
Turned Out to Be Wife Material"!
Get stronger.