Might Tower
Now, we continue with an overview of All
Might's direction in the next season...
Planning All Might's Direction for the Next Season
If you'd all open up the
document in the shared folder.
Currently...
Mr. Yagi?
Please put your phone on
silent during meetings.
E-Excuse me.
I-I need to run to the bathroom.
Mr. Yagi?
What's wrong, Tsukauchi? You
normally just message—
All Might! There's an emergency
at the Tokyo Sky Egg!
Tsukauchi?
The Sky Egg...
is falling!
There we go. The catastrophe
is already a done deal.
Can't fight fate, y'know?
Not unless you're a god or something.
deus ex machina
A type of storytelling device codified in Ancient Greek theater. "The god from the machine."  Typically
identified by a forced conclusion to a series
of events; a narrative contrivance.
This Is a Hero!!
Makoto!
Tsukauchi, what was that noise?
You mentioned the Sky Egg?
Nao!
Welcome home!
Did you come straight home?
Yeah.
You're telling the truth!
I went to the hospital with Mom.
Are you worried about me?
No, not really.
You're lying!
Mom, what did the tests show?
It's something like a mind-reading Quirk.
I figured...
I always knew she was
a sharp girl, but...
I love you, Nao! Do you love me?
Mako, you shouldn't ask
people questions like that.
Oh, it's fine. Adorable, even.
I don't want her making a habit of it!
Constantly probing people's
emotions isn't good for anyone!
You're so serious, Nao.
Answer me this time!
Do you love me, Nao?
Like I said...
If you're going to keep forcing
the issue... then no.
Mr. Yagi
As a police officer, it's inappropriate
to make this kind of request.
But I'm doing it anyway!
Do you hate me?
You're lying!
P-Please save her...
Please, save my little sister, All Might!
All right.
I understand, and I'll be right there.
Yet I don't dare say it.
The reason being...
There's only one thing I should
say at a time like this.
As to what those words are—
Is that...
All Might!
"I am here!"
Smash!
All Might!
All Might did it all on his own!
The dude just set the Sky Egg down!
Wow!
Holy crap!
All Might! All Might! All Might!
All Might! All Might!
Are we saved?
All Might!
That chanting...
All Might?
That must be it! All Might saved us!
Th-Thank goodness...
The number one hero always
makes the impossible possible.
And that's All Might?
Japan's number one hero...
All Might! Quick, over here!
Hey there. It's a pleasure,
Captain Celebrity.
Nice to meet you.
Congratulations on a job well done.
And you are?
I'm a fan!
Can I get an autograph?
It'd be a pleasure.
All Might, can we get a comment?
I'm mostly glad this wrapped
up with no fatalities.
That said, we have plenty of
injured and anxious people here.
All Might Resolves Sky Egg Attack In An Instant!!
To that end, public
services and pro heroes
will be working together to wrap things up
in the best way possible.
It's my hope that you'll all
support all of these heroes!
What the hell?
It's safe now! Please
evacuate without rushing!
Good grief. I guess I don't get
to be the hero this time.
Don't be ridiculous, Captain!
And check it out! All Might
autographed this for me!
I can't help but notice a difference
So awesome! Oh, man, I can't
ever wash this now!
in your reaction to when
I gave you my autograph.
If anyone is thirsty,
we have tea to drink!
We have C.C. dumplings, too!
Here's your tea.
And that's your sister?
There you go.
I'm glad she's all right.
About that... I'm sorry
for losing my composure.
Oh, none of that, please!
If anything, you being so upset
is part of how I made it in time.
Is that how it works?
You'd be surprised what a big difference
your state of mind makes in terms
of what you can accomplish.
You made a point of separating
public and private before,
but I think that personally listening to
cries for help is part of a hero's job.
And the whole reason I received this
power is to give hope to people.
The hope that their voices can
reach the number one hero.
Received... your power?
It's nothing.
All right, Tsukauchi, shall
we help with the recovery?
R-Right.
NaruFest!
One day, I'll tell you everything.
All of All Might's secrets.
What is this? What the hell?
Why is everybody acting
like that's a wrap?
Do they even realize I've been
holding back this whole time?!
They better not think
they've won, dammit.
I'll make sure they all die
out of spite if I have to.
Regenerate and fuse together all the
pieces of the suicide bomber villain...
Have them increase in size, and then...
What the heck?!
No way!
It's monster-sized!
A colossal bomb villain?!
It's not just big, either.
Something of that size would be
easy for Eraser Head to shut down,
or All Might to send flying.
But this bad boy's custom made.
I call it the cluster bomber.
It can release 200 of the bombs it's
generated in its guts all at once!
All Might can't handle that number alone,
and even if every hero here teamed up,
they'd maybe be able to stop half of them!
The other half... the
remaining hundred...
The audience that thought they were safe,
the emergency responders who showed
up to help, and while they're at it,
all of the folks in the area who
are just living their lives...
are gonna be blown sky high!
A swarm of those exploding villains?!
That's way too many!
Oh, no!
Nebraska Smash!
One punch?!
He caught all of the bombs in
the vortex created by a single punch
and they're detonating
safely inside of it?
That's awesome! And insane!
I can't believe there's anyone in the
world who can pull off an OP move like that!
Indeed there is, Number 6.
As hard as it might be to believe,
what you're seeing is reality.
He does in fact exist.
This man who defies the standards
that all other heroes live by...
A genuine superhuman.
A veritable deus ex machina, capable of
bending physics and fate to his will.
That's who All Might is.
The symbol of the heights
you seek to reach.
That I seek to reach, huh?
I never said anything about
wanting to be All Might, y'know.
I suppose that's true.
And I prefer that you're free
to act as you see fit.
Thanks—
The Factory's objective was creating
composite Quirks via human experimentation
and application of drugs.
It was easy to predict he'd use an event
featuring all-star heroes
to run an experiment.
I had already confirmed which building
was best for monitoring the Sky Egg.
A distance of 250 meters,
with a wind speed of eight meters
per second from the southwest.
Aiming for the head.
Something flew by my
line of fire. A bird?
I missed my mark.
But he shouldn't be able to move.
Why, hello there.
You're a fast one.
I guess you've tinkered with your body,
on top of that acceleration Quirk.
A fair bit, yeah.
Lately I've been trying
to boost my muscle mass
and tuning down my pain receptors,
trying to get the right touches.
As far as the acceleration... or to
be more specific, my Overclocking.
I got that one from a certain
high-speed hero—O'Clock.
You don't know how long I've
waited to meet you, Master.
I've been looking all over for you, too.
Who the hell are you, anyway?
The scarred man behind
the modified villains.
No ID, no record,
and not so much as a name.
All anyone knows about you is that you
have my stolen Quirk—Overclock.
Which means I've got a ton of questions,
but let's start with a name.
A name? You want my name?
And, like, you're actually interested
in me? Aw, it's an honor.
The sad truth is, I'm literally nobody.
Early on, I was literally just a tiny,
little, poorly-defined critter.
Experiment Subject 6. Most people
referred to me as Number 6.
But that's just a number, not a name.
If I'm going to become somebody...
somebody important...
O'Clock.
That's the only name I wanna go by!
Funny. Most kids with big dreams
about becoming somebody...
tend to want to be All Might.
All Might, huh?
I mean, he is impressive. But being
him seems like such a drag...
I mean, whether it's fighting
villains or disaster recovery,
he's constantly cleaning
up other people's messes.
That's what makes him
the number one hero.
All of humanity is lucky
that he's so selfless.
If someone with that kind of power
used it for selfish purposes...
it'd mean the end of the world.
That's just what I'm talking about!
All Might is too strong for his own good!
Save the world, or destroy it.
He's got two options.
Can't use his power freely.
And that doesn't work for me.
I'm trying to go my own
way, and live free.
And you're not interested
in helping others?
I wouldn't rule it out completely,
but I can't deny it doesn't suit me.
Which is why I wanna be you, Master!
I don't need the kinda power
to send a building flying.
A Quirk that gives me the initiative,
no matter who I'm facing...
I can force the first move and win before
the other guy knows what happened!
That's O'Clock! My hero!
It gives me the chills!
There's nothing heroic
about someone like that.
Don't be so modest, big man.
I'm already a mega fan of yours.
I know everything there is to know about
you, and will do anything to become you.
When I saw your last
act, it gave me chills!
Because I knew that I was next.
It was gonna be my turn, now.
So I've got a bit of a request to make.
I'd like you to publicly
accept me as your heir.
If I'm gonna do this, I'd like to be the
official second generation O'Clock.
Sorry, kid, but I've already
got an apprentice.
Oh, right, you mean Koichi?
Gotta say, it's pretty clear
I respect you more than him.
I mean, he's a fan of
All Might's, not you.
That's exactly it.
I already told you—O'Clock
wasn't a hero.
And if someone who wants to be him
has managed to obtain his Quirk...
They'd be a terrible villain.
The kind of threat to society
that needs to be taken down.
So that's how it's gonna be?
Labeling me a villain?
Well, I can work with that.
So, what are you gonna do then?
Shoot me with that rifle?
You already botched your sniping attempt.
Or are you thinking you
can't miss at this range?
Just try it!
See? Missed again.
I really did respect you, Mr.
Formerly-Known-As-O'Clock.
But you're just some
guy without your Quirk.
And once I'm sped up, you can't stop me.
Goodbye, Master. Once you're
gone, I'll be O'Clock!
Can you hear this message, Overclock?
What is that?
A recorded message...
Even if you have have obtained
O'Clock's high-speed Quirk,
Played back at high speed?
I doubt that means you fully
comprehend its nature just yet.
The true nature of the Quirk, Overclock,
is a catalyzation of the brain's functions.
Your perception and cognition go
faster, creating a slow-motion sensation.
That acceleration rate isn't uniform.
It varies depending on mental state.
When aiming to deliver a physical attack,
it tends to reach anywhere from two,
three times, to ten times acceleration.
When responding to a sudden threat, you
get several dozen times a reaction speed.
With enough focus, it can be increased
to the point that the world around
you literally seems frozen.
But that kind of high level acceleration
comes with time limits.
Think of it as your brain running out
of breath during intense exercise.
The faster the brain has accelerated,
the faster it wears the brain out.
For example, when dodging
a bullet from a rifle...
Or maybe when trying to perceive a
message played back at 300x speed.
My Quirk!
Looks like you're out of breath!
Sorry, but I'm not giving
you a chance to recover!
Explosions!
I can't maneuver how I want in the air!
I just blew up the top three floors!
This kind of free fall will
keep you from speeding up.
A shotgun!
I'd protect your head. It's
one of your most vital parts.
Although you'd need your
legs to land safely.
You said you'd tweaked your
pain sensitivity, right?
In that case, I need to physically
stop your limbs from working.
Okay, this is weird.
You were aiming for a headshot before,
and now wanna take me alive?
Do you even know what you wanna do?
It's a matter of efficacy.
A lethal approach was ideal when
targeting you from a distance.
But if your target's trapped in a
cage? Then you can take them alive.
Incidentally, the next detonation
will drop the entire building.
Even if you accelerate, you
won't be able to escape.
The cage will become a
coffin at that point.
This is checkmate for you.
So you want me to accept defeat?
'Cuz you don't wanna kill
me if you don't have to?
While you've been explaining
what a big softy you are,
I've managed to recover enough to—
Eliminating a dangerous
villain is my top priority,
but the chance to learn more about
the mastermind is tempting.
Incidentally! Another way!
To shut down Overclock!
Is a concussion! Via blunt force trauma!
In other words! As long as I'm
hitting you! You can't speed up!
Once I've beaten you, I'll restrain you,
and we'll have a little interview.
Do you regenerate faster, too?
The bleeding from where I
sniped you has stopped.
Pretty dangerous, but not much
he can do once he's tied up.
Bad call, Master.
You should've gone blown my head
off when you had the chance.
By parasitizing my body with
the bomber villain's cells,
I can turn my arms into explosives!
The string of events drew to a close,
and the Captain returned to America.
Two years have passed. And
I've made a certain decision.
Storage Room
Interview Room
Next time: Graduation and Career Path.
Koichi Haimawari is graduating
from being the Crawler!
Limited Time Only!!