Work Study Student
Mister Blaster
Yeah, goggles are the ticket.
Having this elastic band
secure the anti-glare glass
that can hold up to harsh winds is giving
my eyes all the protection they need!
Damn, man, you're biting my style again?
Work Study Student
Present Mic
And after the hard time you gave Aizawa.
Aizawa? Like I care what that dweeb does.
Guy's so weak, but goes around acting
like the king of the gloomy geeks.
You think Aizawa's weak?
Oh, well, you're in Class B,
so you wouldn't know.
My man might be wishy-washy
and a slow starter.
But he's a nightmare when
he gets his act together.
What? Then he needs to get his
act together all the time!
You're not wrong, but...
Man, I envy how simple you are.
Hey, rookies!
Am I interrupting your chitchat?
Because it's time for combat!
We suppress the target the
second we hit the scene!
We're Buster Union, the
high-firepower hero team!
Buster Union
Let's go! Our target's the
giant villain directly ahead!
All right! Let's turn up the volume!
All members, unleash your
Quirks at maximum output!
Fire!
What?!
It ate our attacks?!
And grew more warts!
flashback
Recollections of the past.
During a story, they will sometimes act as an
interlude to show what happened prior to current events, as in a "flashback scene."
A Sky with No Rain Left
Nice weather, huh, Shota?
Perfect for a walk!
We're on patrol.
Plus, it's supposed to
rain in the afternoon.
It's Loud Cloud!
Hey, if it isn't the preschool gang!
You guys out for a walk, too?
Let me ride with you!
Me too, me too!
Careful! You're falling!
Nice one, Shota!
All right, let's fly!
Hang on. Let's make sure the
streets are clear first.
You're real detail-oriented, huh, Shota?
You're just careless.
I bet you'd be great fit for a job
where you look after kids, Shota.
Like in childcare or a school teacher.
That sounds more like you.
Kids don't really like me, anyway.
Bye-bye, Cloud!
Bye-bye!
Yeah! See you around!
See you later too, Eraser Head!
See what I mean?
Shota, you're so observant that
you end up overthinking things.
You let it get to you, convinced
about what can't be done.
But I think that you could do anything
if you were motivated!
Like working in childcare
or being a teacher?
Exactly!
You're just making stuff up.
It's how I really feel, though! I mean it!
Looks like the forecast was right.
We should head back to
the office early and...
I wonder what's up? It's from Kayama.
Aizawa, you need to evacuate the
people in your area right away.
A violent villain just
hit our part of town!
Boss, I've got a profile
from the Hero Network.
His villain name is Garvey.
Fifteen previous counts of murder
and destruction of property.
His Quirk is Stock, which lets him absorb
and store attacks directed at him,
before re-directing them outward.
How is he so powerful?
That wasn't in the data!
I'd say he must've absorbed
focused fire from Buster Union,
the first group to move against him.
Right now, he's packing the full power
of a first-rate offensive hero team.
Midnight, call for reinforcements
and lead the evacuation.
What about you, boss?
I'm gonna buy us some time!
There's a villain headed this way!
You need to evacuate!
Get the kids on my cloud!
R-Right!
The weather's starting to turn.
All right, let's get you guys to safety!
The villain's here already?!
And he's huge...
I'll hold the line!
Boss?
You two get the children out of here!
Right!
We need to get clear!
That was Yamada's Voice!
Sensoji's Blast, too?
Does this guy store other people's
Quirks in those warts on his back?
Oh, no! Boss...
Boss!
Boss—
Cloud!
Shirakumo!
Hey, Shirakumo!
Don't do this to me...
Boss...
Shirakumo...
I'm the only one who can still move.
What do I do? Think. Gotta think!
Make the call!
The extreme output of his attacks...
Taking a hit is out of the question, but
it's dangerous to be in the vicinity, too.
Is he amplifying those Quirks,
on top of storing them?
He might use an unexpected Quirk, too.
If nothing else, I've gotta
get the kids out of here.
But how?!
Shota!
It's up to you, Shota!
That's right.
No time to hesitate.
My Quirk is Erasure!
And no matter what Quirk I'm facing,
I can force a fight into a melee!
I can't just offset the timing
of those wart Quirks.
He'll do too much damage
to the surroundings!
Don't fight without a plan.
Make the best call possible.
For the most efficiency...
Take the rational countermeasures!
Get above his head so he'll fire
those blasts into the air!
Countermeasure 2:
kick the stalled warts so they
detonate somewhere safe!
Good!
That just leaves the size difference.
The best way to deal with that...
The countermeasure is...
There is...
No countermeasure.
You can do it, Shota!
You're the only one who
can protect everyone!
It's okay! You've got this!
You can take him!
That's right, I know the
truth! You're strong!
You can't lose!
You've got this, Shota!
Keep fighting, Shota!
You can do it, Shota!
Don't give up, Shota!
He's trying to finish me off.
Come on, Shota!
Don't give up, Shota!
Keep fighting, Shota! Keep fighting!
Chew on this!
I did it.
I actually did it, Shirakumo!
I can't believe a single
rookie took down that giant.
No. It was a team effort.
My partner kept encouraging me.
Shirakumo...
Kayama, how badly hurt is Shirakumo?
He was cheering me on before,
so it can't be that bad...
Or can it? Should we get
to the hospital, then?
Yamada! That speaker is Shirakumo's.
We've gotta take it to him.
Man, this thing's busted.
That can't be. Shirakumo
was just on it...
That'd mean he was cheering you on
through this speaker until his last breath.
But I don't think that's it.
I think you were pushing yourself,
and doing it through this speaker.
In the heat of combat, that
kind of thing can happen.
That can't be it. He
told me I could do it.
"You can do it, Shota."
That's what kept me fighting...
We need a stretcher, now!
Aizawa.
You stood your ground against
a villain that took down
a first-rate team of pros, and won.
All on your own.
You should be proud, Aizawa.
If you can't be proud of this,
then what else is there?
Sensoji, man... I really do
envy how simple you are.
I heard Shirakumo's voice.
Yeah.
I know it was him.
He was cheering me on.
Yeah.
He's always had my back, from
the day we first met.
Just like today. The entire time!
Yeah. I know.
It's starting to rain harder.
Aizawa, Yamada,
come on inside already.
We don't need you getting sick.
Thanks, Kayama, but it...
It matches our state of mind.
Shota! It's when you screw up that you
need to keep it light like you always do.
The three of us start our own agency
and go independent. That's my plan.
I bet you'd be great fit for a
job where you look after kids.
I think that you could do anything
if you were motivated!
It's, like, when there's three
of us, if anybody messes up,
the other two can cover for them.
And I get the feeling the three
of us can handle anything!
How about I lend you my goggles?
You can do it, Shota.
Keep fighting, Shota!
The next year
Faculty Room
How's Aizawa been doing, lately?
Well, his grades are
above average, as usual.
You can tell he developed senioritis
as soon as he knew he was passing.
I've noticed that with a lot
of his classroom work, too.
He puts a lot of effort into his
practical combat training, but...
I think after what happened last year...
he's made up his mind about something,
and not necessarily in a good way.
Yeah. It's a bit worrying.
Guidance Office
So, you're going to establish
your own agency.
Going independent right from the start?
Most people get a few years of experience
at a veteran agency first.
I'm going to focus exclusively
on dealing with villains.
Combat ability will be enough
to keep me afloat, that way.
The simple, rational approach.
Aizawa, are you really going to graduate
UA just to become a bounty hunter?
I know you've been through a lot, but
we're talking about your future!
You could stand to be—
Working solo and operating
in the underworld.
That's the kind of hero I wanna be.
I am so proud!
Quit crying, Ma.
Hey! Aizawa!
Come take a pic with everyb—
My voice?
Eraser!
The rain's finally over.
Make sure to take care of that cat.
Okay. Where are you headed?
Gonna check on the Hotta Bros.
I think I'll tag along, then!
They might have a customer
who'd want a cat, right?
I guess we'll see.
Pawn Shop
Hoppers
Welcome!
Oh, I guess this is your first
time talking to him, Cruller.
Ikajiro Takobe Age 25
Hey there. I'm Takobe.
Mr. Cruller, I apparently chased
you around and threw rocks at you?
Sorry about that!
Wh-What's he doing here?
Well, after what happened,
he's got nowhere to go.
So he and Kamayan have been
living out of a tent.
It's kinda like camping! So much fun.
Man, nobody likes camping
out for this long.
We gotta hurry up and
put together our shop.
Shop?
They got the idea to open a café
where our warehouse used to be.
A big one, where guys their
size can actually come and go.
A café, huh?
By the way, Mr. Cruller...
Who is this cutie?
Is it okay if I pick him up?
Uh, well...
So fluffy! Just like the kitty I
had back home when I was little.
Is he yours, Mr. Cruller?
Oh, no, he was abandoned.
Oh, then I'll take him!
Come on, Tako, we're about
to build a café here.
He can live in the café!
Serving food and drinks with
a pet around? I dunno.
Nah. I like it.
We make it one of them
fancypants cat cafés,
and people will be lining up to get in!
Schoolgirls, for example.
Do you really think schoolgirls are gonna
wanna hit up a place filled with monsters?
Won't know unless we try!
I think it's a great idea!
Let's make it our dream café!
See? He gets it!
I'm telling you, we need roof access!
Where else are we gonna eat lunch?
That's a really weird assumption.
I figure we get a soundproof studio.
I wanna really cut loose with
my voice, every now and then!
Hup! Is there anything you
need for our agency, Shota?
A cat tower.
We're gonna have an agency cat, huh?
I get it! You wanna take Sushi in, huh?
It feels irresponsible to
leave him with Kayama.
And I figure the three of us
can probably look after him...
What do you think?
I g-g-g-guess it sounds good!
Probably for the best...
What any one of us can't
handle, two of us can.
And together, the three
of us can do anything.
We can save anyone.
And we'll start with a single cat.
That was my plan back then...
Hey, Eraser.
Eraser?
Quit acting like a stranger
and tell us what you think.
We've got a spot reserved
for you—right here.
Next to the can.
When you come to mooch coffee off
us, come through the back, okay?
Having a spooky-looking
guy like you around
is bound to be bad for
business otherwise.
Even if it's this dude, having a hero
around is bound to be good for security.
He'll give us an air of
respectability, y'know?
Come and visit this little guy, okay?
I'm just glad we found
a place for the kitten.
I guess no matter how hard it seems at
first, things have a way of working out!
It's cleared up.
I didn't even notice the sun was out.
What're you talking about, man?
A cat café, huh?
It's a good plan.
I'll drop by to check
on the cat sometimes.
Today's Sushi
With Captain Celebrity's issues
back home taken care of,
he's getting ready to return to America.
And we're going to be a part of
the final event planned for him!
Next Time: Farewell Party.
Thank you, Captain!