Boobies...
Is it an earthquake?
Quite a few of these lately, indeed.
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
EPISODE 8: A RESIDENT OF THE VILLAGE
And thanks to Rirui, we took down
a bunch of slimes again today!
Sure did.
Granny!
Oh, if it isn't little Hajime!
On your way home from work?
Yup.
You two taking your jobs so seriously
helps keep our village safe.
I appreciate that.
Here.
Yay! Candy!
I'm counting on you to keep
an eye out for the village.
Sure.
Thank you!
Hey! You the resident
adventurer 'round here?
Strike first to win!
Ow...
What the hell was that for?
Wh-Whoa! H-Hang on a sec!
That was a little too
aggressive, y'know?!
W-We're not your enemies!
We're with the village watch!
The village watch?
You may have proven a tiny bit
stronger today, maybe, but...
We came to remind you n-not to act
like yer such a big deal 'round here.
W-Well, we're saying, it's our job to
protect this place as the village watch!
THE VILLAGE WATCH'S PEONS
Hajime, Rirui! Welcome back.
Hey, Natalie.
We have returned!
Jan! It's been so long.
H-Hey...
How have you been?
G-Good...
Oh, so you're in love with Natalie!
Wh-What the hell, man?!
Yeah, y'know, I was wrestling with
the same kinda stuff just the other day.
So that's why you're picking a fight with
me. Since I'm staying at her inn and all.
Man, I get it. Love's a
tough nut to crack, right?
So, what do you think of him, Natalie?
What? I mean, J-Jan's...
just a good friend.
Dude, she shot you down!
I'm gonna kill you!
Watch it! That's dangerous!
I'm never gonna accept...
you as part of our village!
Stupid Jan.
Give it a rest.
Let's head back.
You don't stand a chance.
Drop dead, you jerk!
Um, did something happen
between you and Jan?
Just a bunch of smack talk
about him protecting the village.
I see. He is part of
the village watch, after all.
And he loves this place to boot.
Hell of a smile to flash
after shooting the guy down.
Say, Hajime, what did he mean
about you not being part of the village?
Don't you live here?
Yeah, I'd say I do my part.
I'm the resident adventurer, y'know?
But that jerkwad said
he wasn't gonna accept you.
Well, I haven't been here very long.
Only since a little before I found you.
Really?
Yeah.
But Natalie and the innkeep
and Miss Olive are all so nice!
They are.
But their jobs involve interacting
with outsiders on the regular,
so they were pretty accepting.
It'll still be a while before I'm truly
recognized as part of the village.
Then maybe don't go starting
fights like you did earlier?
Welp, how about some dinner, Rirui?!
He changed the subject.
Again with this? Damn.
We're dealing with a magic beast
boasting a quasi-calamity threat level.
A spikesaurus has been spotted
on Mount Kunimi.
A spikesaurus?!
And Kunimi is only two mountains over!
What's something like that
doing so close to the village?
It likely stumbled onto
a resting wandering whale
and was carried here on its back.
Spikesauruses are usually
found in the Koxi region.
They are very aggressive magic beasts
covered in hard spikes.
It's likely fighting the creatures
of Mount Kunimi for territory.
That's probably also the cause of the
earthquakes we've been experiencing.
Who would we need to take on
a magic beast of the quasi-calamity level?
This kind of threat would require an
entire team of silver-rank adventurers.
Silver-rank?
And a whole team of them?
Little Hajime.
You're a pure silver rank,
which is stronger than silver, yes?
How would you handle this thing?
I've never fought one before,
and if it usually takes
a whole silver team...
Sounds scary.
Aw, come on! Talk about pathetic!
I guess that pure silver rank
don't amount to much!
Keep your mouth shut when the
adults are talking, boy!
But Dad, I'm part of the village watch!
You're the dregs!
You got a long way to go before
you can start talking down to others!
Get out!
Damn it. What the hell?
I'm just as good as him!
Pardon my stupid son. Please, continue.
Yes, well, given how dangerous
spikesauruses are,
it would be wise to assemble
a team, as Olive suggested.
Thankfully, there's a party of silver
adventurers working out of central Rana
who've taken down a spikesaurus before.
How much will it cost?
Seven villages will be pooling their
funds, so it should be manageable.
All right!
One more thing...
If Mr. Shinonome joins them,
we shouldn't have to pay as much!
You got it.
Since I'm gonna be going after
a spikesaurus soon,
today's a good day to take
it easy with some slimes.
Thank you so much.
Um, excuse me!
You're the resident adventurer, right?
It's Jan, my son. Have you seen him?
Jan, Donato, and Alisa...
All three of them are missing.
I spoke with an adventurer who saw
them on the path to Mount Kunimi!
Those little idiots!
We'll drag 'em back
and teach 'em a lesson!
Hang on.
It's dangerous to go now.
Let me go, damn it!
I'll go after them.
Get me all the material you've
got on the spikesaurus.
Right!
I'll assist you.
No! You don't need to go!
The resident adventurer's supposed to do
whatever's best for the whole village!
Can't risk you getting hurt
over those dumb little—
Sorry, but can you take care of this?
Please!
Sure.
Let's do our best, Dragon!
P-Pardon!
I heard Alisa and the
others were in trouble.
Gosh, what were they thinking?
Don't sweat it. Your friend
will be back soon enough.
I'm pure silver rank, remember?
Right! I'll leave this in your hands!
Yeah!
And now...
You're sitting this one out, Rirui.
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
All right, I'm off.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Resident Adventurer!
My boy's made a real mess of things!
You bring him back safe
and I'll kill him for you!
The little twerp!
We're counting on you.
Yeah, sure.
Not like I'm going to fight that thing.
Bringing three kids back oughta be...
Is it really a good idea
to take Rirui with you?
IS IT REALLY A GOOD IDEA
TO TAKE RIRUI WITH YOU?
To be perfectly honest,
if we run into the spikesaurus,
no, not at all.
Rirui!
I am not your guardian!
You're gonna need to keep yourself safe!
I told you to stay behind,
but you're forcing the issue!
If you die, it's on you!
Leave it to me!
Okay, as long as you understand!
Now let's go!
Yeah!
We're gonna be rocking a lot!
Keep your trap shut
so you don't bite your tongue!
Yeah!
I said keep your trap shut!
And tell me if you get queasy!
Or if you need to use the bathroom!
You had better not go on me!
Did you hear him, Dragon?
I just told you to shut up!
Mr. Shinonome...
You sure as hell look
like her guardian to me!
Are they gonna be okay?
Our resident adventurer was shakin'
in his booties over a little magic beast.
What a loser!
A useless coward!
You kill this thing, and Natalie might
have something nice to say about you.
Th-That's not why I'm doing this!
What's the point in trying to hide it now?
Can it!
I just hate that jerk! That's all!
That's...
I-It's huge.
Maybe we better head back after all...
Wh-What? You two chicken or something?
'Cause I'm not scared at all!
I can protect my own damn village!
What was that?
Something's there!
Is that...
The s-spikesaurus!
It really is huge!
What now, Jan?!
What do you mean? We gotta fight it!
Jan!
You good?
That hurt.
We sure as hell can't let this thing
anywhere near the village!
Man, and here I had no intention
of fighting.
The resident adventurer?
What're you doing here?
Working.
Leave this to me.
You three head back to town.
Your parents are waiting.
Come on, we're in the way!
Taste Rirui's blade!
What're you doing, squirt?!
It's dangerous! Stay back!
Do not interfere! Release me!
C'mere. Yer comin' with us.
And that guy...
Is he gonna fight that thing on his own?
I don't care how tough he is!
That's crazy!
A spikesaurus's weakness...
Hajime said the best thing to do
is to knock all those spikes off!
The spikes are its weakness?!
Its body is supposed to get
softer once they're all gone.
But just how many spikes are there?
He can't possibly get them all.
Ow...
Are you okay, Hajime?!
Do you need my help?
You're all bloody...
This thing dies.
That's some real brute strength!
He's chargin' that thing head-on?!
Hot damn. So that's...
a pure silver adventurer?
He beat it...
And all on his own.
Good grief. Well, I managed somehow.
Got a bit bloodied up, but maybe
that was the only way to win.
Hajime!
Our resident adventurer... is awesome.
You did it, Hajime!
Job's not done yet. We gotta get back
and report that this thing's dead.
Understood!
I guess having him around...
is good for the village.
An earthquake?
They're still happening?
But the creature is dead...
Get clear, Rirui!
That's my left arm gone.
And what the hell is this thing?
I've never seen a monster like it before.
Stay calm. Don't lose it.
Analyze the situation.
Do we run? Or fight?
No, I don't think I can get away.
I've lost too much blood.
So fight it is.
Except in this condition,
I won't last long.
Gonna have to make it fast and decisive!
Lucky for me, I've already
spilled a ton of blood!
HAJIME'S ABILITY:
THE WAR GOD'S FLOWING CRIMSON
Get your ass back here!
Now go to hell!
He did it...
Well, I managed somehow.
You okay, man?! Yer arm's gone!
We should get back, and fast!
You need treatment on the double.
Jeez, would you pipe down?
Enough with the shouting!
It's not helping me heal, y'know?
Sorry, but most people would f-freak
out over something like this!
Because he protected Rirui...
Hajime's arm...
NEXT TIME: AFTER THE BATTLE