Girls...
I don't get them at all.
I love you.
I know she definitely said that...
Gross, what are you talking about?
Well, I'm going home!
What the heck was that all about?
I totally thought I was about to start
a rom-com with a childhood friend...
Hey, hey, Onii-chan!
You already studied so much.
Let's go somewhere fun!
Hey, come on, let's go!
We went to the beach, remember?
I wanna have more fun!
Since I'll be going back home for Obon,
I won't be able to go to the
summer festival with you.
SUMMER FESTIVAL!
You'll be back right after that, though.
Go.
Ask Shio to hang out or something.
Gosh.
Can't you see that I want to
hang out with you, Onii-chan?
Seriously, you don't understand
a girl's heart at all.
GIRL'S HEART
A girl's heart...?
Huh?
What's up? Do you wanna
go somewhere with me now?
Oh, no...
About that "girl's heart" thing...
Can you explain it?
A girl's heart?
I told him I love him.
Eiyu...
I need to erase it...
I need to erase his memory!
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
Why did I say that?!
Why did I say "I love you"
to that idiot?
How am I supposed to
go on living after this?
He's not here yet...
He's here!
Why are we going into your room?
Shush, I don't want
anyone else listening!
Why is he with her?
Why is he being so secretive?
So what is it? What do you
want me to explain?
Yeah, well...
I'm asking for a friend.
He and his friends went on a trip.
But then he and this girl got left behind
because they missed the last bus back.
They ended up spending
the night together at a hotel...
snug
But the girl acted...
really weird.
He's talking about us!
Why is he asking Runako about it?!
Oh, this is what happened
to my friend, okay? I swear!
He just made it so obvious
that it's about him!
Is this relationship talk? Seriously?!
What?! She believes him?!
So, what happened next?!
Well...
When they turned off
the lights to go to sleep,
the girl suddenly slipped
into my friend's bed.
And... since it seemed like she
had trouble getting to sleep...
He hugged her.
Then she told my friend,
"I love you"... or something.
I need to hurry and put an end to him...
But here's the thing.
The next morning, she acted so cold
and went home by herself.
Do you have any idea what this means?
Onii-chan.
I'm sorry to tell you...
But there's no chance with this girl.
No chance?!
I suspect that your friend made a mistake.
Maybe he embarrassed her that morning?
He could've misheard her, too.
I'm sorry, but he should let
this one go and move on.
No...
That's not how I feel at all...
I see. Yeah, you're right.
Well, the thing is, I always thought
that girl hated him, too.
She's always glaring at him
and acting cold only to him...
Supposedly.
Only to him?
Onii-chan.
This isn't over yet.
What?!
There's a high chance that this
is an instance of suki-sake!
Suki-sake?!
Um... And that is...?
It's when you end up avoiding someone
because you like them.
That girl's totally tsundere.
She acts cold to your friend
because she likes him.
She probably left by herself that
morning because she felt embarrassed.
If your friend comes on strong,
that girl will fall for him in seconds!
What?!
I-In seconds?
Wh-Wh-What are you saying, Runako?
Yup, yup.
Aw, so pure!
But that's great!
Your friend is probably not
against that idea, right?
So? Come on, spill it.
He must've told you, right?
U-Um...
Well, um...
Y-You're right.
He's not against it...
Huh?
S-Seriously?
A-Akari?!
Wh-What the heck are you
doing here of all places?!
You're so annoying.
Leave me alone!
But you almost got hurt...
N-No! Was she listening the whole time?
Akari-chan!
Your panties are showing!
Nice one, Onii-chan!
You okay, Akari?
Th-Than—
You're just so annoying!
That's why I came to beat you up!
With a metal bat?!
Forget it!
I'm worn out, so I'm going home.
What?
Cold
Hotel
In bed
Morning After
Missed bus
Not Against It
Friend
Spent the Night
Geez. She makes no sense.
Right, Runako?
I dunno. You should think for yourself.
Huh?
Why's Runako acting like that?
Yeah... I really don't get girls.
INARI FIREWORKS
Do you know the legend of love
at the Inari Fireworks?
They say that when the final,
massive fireworks light up the sky...
INARI
FIREWORKS
the two who share a kiss
will be destined to be together...
Why not make the most
unforgettable memories this year
with the one you love?
A k-kiss?!
INARI FIREWORKS
Steal that kiss with summer lips.
SUMMER KISS
The festival... fireworks...
and... a kiss...
With Eiyu...
Wh-Wh-What?! Those who share a kiss
will be destined to be together?!
That's ridiculous!
Introducing a brand-new way for
those who can't make the first move.
Make his heart explode!
Lips that shine like fireworks...
Mirage.
Please give it a try.
With Eiyu...
Akarin!
What are you doing?
We're supposed to be shopping
for yukata today!
Akari-chan, what are you looking at?
Oh... N-Nothing!
Um...
Do you know the legend of love
at the Inari Fireworks?
Legend of love?!
I had no idea!
I never heard about such a legend
tied to the yearly fireworks festival.
S-Sounds like a superstition to me.
It sounds so romantic.
If I were going to the festival,
I would've totally invited Onii-chan!
Y-Yeah, that's too bad.
Whatever! Let's go
choose our yukata already!
Okay!
Is this one too loud?
Wow, it's beautiful, Shio-chan!
That yukata is cute too, Runako!
Really?
Yeah! Suits you perfectly!
That color especially, it's so you!
Seems like Shio has
feelings for Eiyu, too...
Wow, it's so cute!
Sorry, I didn't mean
to choose the same thing.
No, it's fine.
It'll look better on you anyway.
See? It looks great on you too, Akarin!
Wanna get matching ones?
Yeah, let's do it.
We've always hung out together
ever since we were young...
But we rarely ever fight.
And then, Eiyu brought over meatballs!
Whenever I'm slow to act...
Eiyu's mom's meatballs are so good!
Got the last one!
Sorry, did you want it, too?
Oh, um... It's fine.
Here you go!
Let's split it!
Shio has always been so generous.
Why do we both...
like the same person?
INARI
FIREWORKS
Akarin.
Runako went to the bathroom.
Huh? Wh-What?!
What's wrong?
U-Um...
Oh, the fireworks?
Yeah, it's nothing.
I was thinking about how, year after year,
we all went together
without ever getting tired of it...
Well, in the end, I'm looking
forward to it this year, too.
By the way...
I heard that the legend about
the fireworks actually comes true.
What?
They said that more couples get together
and marriage proposals work out
and things like that.
A-At least, that's what they said on TV!
I-I see...
Well, it doesn't concern us either way
since it's just our usual group again.
Sorry, Akarin...
Huh?
INARI
FIREWORKS
I want to watch the fireworks
with Eiyu this year, just the two of us.
So, I'm planning on inviting him.
R-Really?
I-I didn't realize!
I didn't know you had
feelings for him, Shio.
And don't apologize!
I totally support you.
I'll be mindful of it when we
hang out at the festival, too.
I see... I had a hunch.
So it's true.
I'm seriously rooting for you!
Akarin, are you really okay with this?
I want to be open
and honest with you, Akarin.
And I don't want to ignore your feelings.
Akarin, don't you want to watch
the fireworks alone with Eiyu, too?
Yeah...
So do I. I want to watch
the fireworks alone...
with Eiyu.
I knew you had feelings
for him too, Akarin.
What a relief!
Huh?
I finally got it off my chest!
What?
Gosh!
It was terrifying and embarrassing
at the same time, you know?
Akarin, you always deny your feelings...
What do you mean? I'm not following.
Yeah, I'm saying that...
I'm glad I got to tell you the truth...
Or hear the truth?
No...
I'm glad the person who likes
the same childhood friend as me
is also a childhood friend of mine.
No hard feelings
to each other, okay?
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
Thanks, Shio...
From here on out,
we won't split things anymore.
I won't lose to you.
Okay!
My Childhood Friend
Is Just Too Cute
All childhood friend lovers rejoice!!
"You maggots! Do you wanna go out
with your childhood friend?!"
Yoko's so sweet...
She's so cute!
Rom-coms are seriously the best!
Later this evening...
At the eight o'clock fireworks show...
Two hours from now,
it's the moment of truth.
It will decide the fate of the love
that Akarin and I have for Eiyu.
I want to watch the fireworks
with Eiyu this year, just the two of us.
So, I'm planning on asking him...
I said that, but...
What am I doing?!
I haven't even asked him yet!
How'd this happen?!
There were plenty of chances
leading up to today!
M-Morning, Eiyu!
What do you want so early in the morning?
Well, I wanted to ask you...
about something...
So, lid...
Huh? Lid?
Lid
I mean, did...
What?
Um... Did you...
Did you want to do the morning
radio exercise together?
Again?
Why?
Why can't I muster up the courage to ask?!
Hey, Shio!
Don't get lost.
Th-Thanks...
Eiyu!
Huh?
U-Um...
Um.. Um...
The f-fire...
The fireworks... Can we watch them...
Shio...
Be careful. You're not used to
walking around in that thing.
What?!
Darn it, that was such a cold response!
COLD
How am I supposed to break through
such a cold, impenetrable heart?
Eiyu!
Huh?
Um...
About the fireworks show after this...
Do you think... the two of us...
Huh?
You and...
Akari...
Are you seriously gonna go like that?!
You're so lame!
What?!
Idiot!
Gosh!
Akarin!
It's so hard to ask him out!
Huh?
Oh... Yeah. I'm struggling, too.
But I'm glad we're feeling the same.
Yeah.
No! We're running out of time!
I have to ask Eiyu out ASAP!
G-Go!
Now's your chance, Akarin!
What? I'm going first?
You're closer to him.
Oh, come on.
This was your idea!
No, no.
Your birthday comes before mine, Akarin!
That has nothing to do with this!
Hey, you two.
What the heck are you doing?
N-Nothing.
It's none of your business.
There's definitely something afoot.
Don't look so unamused.
This is a festival, you know?
Come on, come on, come on!
Huh?
What's up with you two?
Let's have some fun!
Let's go!
Come on, what do you wanna do?
Pinball?
Goldfish scooping?
Let's let loose and enjoy the festival!
What's with you all of a sudden, Eiyu?
You're all hyped up now.
Huh? What do you mean?
This is a festival!
Huh?
Still don't get it.
Um... Eiyu?
It's a festival! Woohoo!
What's going on, what's going on?!
There's something off about them today.
What's with this tension?
What's with their gaze?
I don't know... I don't understand...
I don't get anything at all!
Festivals are the best!
Hey!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Gosh!
Wh-Why are you laughing?
It's just... I don't know...
Yeah... But it feels nostalgic.
The eight o'clock fireworks show
will start in an hour.
Now, what should we do next?
We hope you are enjoying the festival.
No! This isn't the time to be sentimental!
Eiyu.
Huh?
Hey...
So... c-can we...
You hungry?
Here you go! Have this pork skewer!
Wow! Thanks!
That's not what I said! Gosh!
What?
Just listen, okay?!
Th-The both of us...
Um...
Just the two of us...
Akarin...
Just the two...?
Got it, you two want to
let loose without me.
No!
See ya.
Huh?
I want to watch the fireworks
with just you, Eiyu!
Me too!
I want to watch the
fireworks with just you, Eiyu!
What?
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
You have to choose one of us.
Meet me at the torii gate at eight.
M-Meet me at the shrine grounds
at the south entrance...
I'll be waiting for you!
Episode 7
Relationship Talk? Sharing Half?
Festival Vibes? Still Won't Start a Rom-Com