m 0 0 l 0 102 32 102 b 3 75 3 32 32 0
OSHI NO KO
If a film creator like me wants to show
a movie on cinema screens nationwide,
there are several steps
one needs to go through.
Step 1: Get a movie producer to help.
Okay, time to go scrounge up some money.
Pitch
The 15-Year Lie
I polished the pitch myself.
All you need to do is express
your passion for the project.
Step 2: Gather investors.
A movie takes around two to three
hundred million yen to make.
You get a bunch of companies
to front these production costs,
promising them rights
and profits in return.
It's what you call
production by committee.
Step 3: Make your pitch to distributors.
Your distributor's reach will determine
how many screens your movie can secure.
If you want your film to go big,
you get the most powerful
distributor you can, but...
Damn it. All the big names said no.
Well, it is based on a delicate subject.
Major players tend to avoid that.
But some distributors
do like risky projects like this one,
so let's be patient.
Don't worry. We should get a bite soon.
Kaburagi's a freelance producer.
Pitch
The 15-Year Lie
He doesn't work for any one distributor,
so he has to go around pitching projects.
Distributor A
On the plus side, that means
he can try every distributor out there.
Distributor B
Distributor C
Distributor D
When you're hellbent on releasing a film,
a man like him becomes real dependable.
Eikyo Headquarters Building II
Members of the Board
Planning Department
Sales Department
Production Department III
Conference Rooms II
Production Department II
The next one's our main target.
Ugh. Everything takes money, money, money.
Would you have preferred
to make an independent film?
I'm not saying that, but man.
Say...
Nowadays, anyone with a smartphone
can make films and release them online.
What reason do any of us
have to stick to theatrical releases?
That's an easy one.
Because that's the only way you can
become the center of a movement.
You can only kick off a movement
big enough to be a social phenomenon
with content fueled
by massive amounts of money.
A social phenomenon, eh?
I never expected the humble Director
Gotanda to have such lofty ambitions.
Please. Every creator wants their work
appreciated by more people for longer—
to be something that is
celebrated a century from now.
You're such an artist.
What can people even say
a century from now?
Backhanded compliments like,
"Wow, it actually holds up"? Spare me.
In my eyes, as long as it
makes money, anything goes.
You greedy money-grubber.
Anyway, our work's not done yet.
Villain
Aqua Hoshino
Confirmed
Agency President Candidates
Melt Narushima
Masato Murakami
Yuu Miyashita
Opening in Schedule
Negotiating w/ Agency
Theater Actor Candidates
Takashi Ichikawa
Opening in Schedule
Step 4: Casting.
The main lead can make a difference of
hundreds of millions in the box office.
Lots of projects live or die
by who they're able to cast.
But popular actors don't often
have much room in their schedules,
and they can be picky, too.
I had an actress earmarked
for the lead role, but she's out.
Something go wrong?
She got pulled at the last second.
I've heard rumors that she's MIA.
I wonder what happened.
Either way, among all the talent
I took under my wing and sent jobs to,
I picked out the biggest names right now
to fill out our prospective cast.
Times like these are
why I did them all those favors.
It's the culmination of all my work.
Now, how many of them
will repay those favors?
He constantly networks
with actors and investors,
knows all the ins and outs of filmmaking,
and oversees and runs entire productions.
He does it all without breaking
a sweat, but it's really not easy.
He might only ever talk about money,
but nothing he does
could be done without passion.
Director Gotanda.
I'm genuinely expecting a movie
capable of sparking a social phenomenon.
If it does that,
I'll make out like a bandit.
Damn greedy money-grubber.
Pitch
The 15-Year Lie
The ultimate choice!
Option one:
Get dropped into a pit full of tarantulas!
Option two: Get shot up by a machine gun!
Option three: Get flattened
by a falling meteorite!
Which would you pick out of those?
Where did this even come from?
Just answer me.
Okay, option three. The meteorite.
At least I'd die before I felt any pain.
Bzzt! You're a moron if you choose
anything other than option one!
Tarantula bites can hurt,
but they're not venomous!
You've got shit for brains, Aqua!
Yeah, I get it.
Well, you've got a shit personality.
I know, right?
Aqua?
As in, Aqua Hoshino?
Yikes! Let's scram!
Is that really him?
Somebody's famous now.
I'll have to think twice before even
saying your name in public.
Yeah, especially after that story broke.
Just goes to show that Ai's murder
left a lasting impression on people.
This is a problem, though.
What am I supposed to call you
when we're out?
Ah-kun.
That should be safe
to say out in public, right?
What? I'm suggesting it
for your peace of mind.
We're only here because you protected me,
so I'll help you out however I can.
But don't get the wrong idea! I'm not
trying to act like your girlfriend here.
I see you as a dear friend, nothing more.
Huh...
I'd never look at you romantically!
Besides, you have a girlfriend and all.
I broke up with Akane, but okay.
Hmm? Wha?
Oh, okay...
You and Akane Kurokawa split...
Me and my big mouth!
I just had to go and ruin my big chance!
So call me whatever you like.
Huh?
Okay, I've got a recording to get to.
Bye, Ah-kun.
Just get going.
Ah-kun, Ah-kun!
Heh, heh, heh.
Now, isn't that something?
"Ah-kun," she said.
You two have grown awfully close.
Kinda.
Kana-chan's been in good spirits lately.
I love to see it, personally speaking.
But, well, you know...
I heard from Akane that you two broke up,
but this is leaving me very conflicted.
It'd help your dear MEMcho out
a bunch if you handled this tactfully.
You've got nothing to worry about.
I'm done with all that.
I no longer have any wide-eyed illusions
about leading a happy life.
Uh, it's pretty common
to feel that way after a breakup,
but everybody has the right to be happy...
That's not what I meant.
It's just more convenient for me
if I'm on friendly terms with Arima.
I'll use everything I can.
Be it Arima or anyone else.
Aqua Hoshino, Son of Former B-Komachi Idol Ai
The play is already in motion.
Everything's going according to plan.
Ai...
Hoshino Family Grave
I will be the one to make
your real wish come true.
Hoshino Family Grave
Look at you,
acting like a star-crossed hero,
Aqua Hoshino.
Youtou Private High School
Graduation Ceremony
Senpai!
Congratulations on graduating high school!
Ruby.
Now you can say that's your
highest level of education!
You keep telling me to go to college,
but you didn't even apply to any.
My life, my choice. I won't need
any academic qualifications.
I've made up my mind to live
and die as an actress in showbiz.
I'll also graduate as an idol after our
summer concerts and focus on my acting,
using my experience
with B-Komachi to drive me.
I know.
Graduates are supposed
to be seen off with a smile.
I think we'll be able to get
Frill Shiranui to play Ai.
Didn't she only have room in her
schedule for a supporting role?
Yeah, but apparently
one of her projects fell through.
A film's main lead is its public face.
Frill-chan has the fame to pull it off,
and an investor asked for her, too.
I think we should lock her in.
You speak cat?
Whoa, who?!
It's me, Gotanda. Don't you remember me?
Oh, right, the director! It's been ages!
I think the last time we met
was your fifteenth birthday.
And you gave me
that video letter from Mom!
Takes me back!
Genetics truly can be cruel.
She's grown up to be so beautiful.
What's up?
Visiting the agency for something?
Yep. What are you doing out here, though?
Uh, there's someone
I don't want to see in the office.
You mean Aqua?
I heard you had some kind of falling-out.
You two still haven't made up?
"Still"?
After how he exposed Mom's secret,
how could I ever forgive him?
Wait, didn't Aqua tell you about the DVD?
What DVD?
Never mind.
Is that obsessive brother planning
to shoulder it all himself?
How overprotective can he be?
Listen, Aqua had his reasons
for doing what he did.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
At this point, I don't really
care why he did it.
It just helped me realize
you can't trust anyone.
Because everybody's a big liar.
My bad.
Come to think of it, Ai was around
that age when she had kids.
What set this movie project in motion...
was two DVDs.
To Onii-chan *
Do not open
till you're 15!
To Ruby
Open this
when you're 15
Director!
To Onii-chan *
To Ruby
Hold on to these for me!
What are they?
Video letters to the future.
I've been wanting to try this kinda thing!
Give 'em to Aqua and Ruby
when they turn fifteen.
Of all the silly ideas...
Just give them the letters yourself.
You know I'd just lose them, right?
Good point.
You're not allowed to peek, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
I'll hand 'em over if I remember.
It's a promise, okay?
I should have given more thought to it.
Why did she address them
to Aqua and Ruby at fifteen?
Why send them separate DVDs?
Why did Ai leave them with me
just before she died?
When I figured out the answers,
Pitch
Title
The 15-Year Lie
Details
I made up my mind to start this project.
So, who's going to play Ai?
Producer Kaburagi
wants to go with Frill Shiranui.
Shiranui, huh? She is popular.
But I have another pick...
for Ai's role.
Ruby Hoshino is the one
I want to play her.
Um, is that what you were looking for?
Have you received formal acting training?
My agency had me take lessons,
for what it's worth.
I also spend a lot of time around actors,
so I guess I kinda copied them?
I see. Thank you.
Excuse me.
What did I just get screened for?
This would've been so much easier
if she couldn't act at all.
Why did you have to go and
complicate things, Gotanda-kun?
As you saw, Ruby can act.
And we can coach her
through the finer points as we go.
Casting her as Ai will be truer to life
and give the film more signif—
That's not the point!
The quality and significance of
the film are secondary concerns!
Get it through your skull!
Sure, make faces all you want!
But you're a grown man.
I know you understand this.
What matters most is that we repay
the companies that invested in us.
Frill Shiranui
Ruby
Casting Frill Shiranui is far likelier
to put us in the black!
As producer, it's my job to ensure
a commercial success.
Frill Shiranui is my top pick,
and I'm not backing down on that!
Producer Kaburagi is totally in the right.
You can't talk about the quality of a
work until it's a commercial success.
I need this film to be a big hit myself.
This guy once told me, "This isn't
a place for art. It's a business,"
but I guess that doesn't apply to him?
Well, he is just a big child who
happens to be able to make movies.
Grow up already, man.
Besides, Ruby's not going to be up for it.
She can't be ready to tell the truth
about her mother yet.
The 15-Year Lie
I hear they're arguing over the cast
for Director Gotanda's movie lmao
But if they want it to be a hit, they gotta
cast you. Blockbuster name ftw lol
Industry insiders know an awful lot about
what happens behind closed doors,
and many try to use that information
to network with talent.
When I hear talk from people like that,
I sometimes start to question how
I should be playing the game myself.
The 15-Year Lie
Hey.
Hmm?
Want to grab some crêpes on the way home?
Sounds good! Let's ask Minami—
Ruby.
This has to stay between us.
I wead the scwipt for
Diwector Gotanda's new film.
I was originally offered a different role,
but my schedule opened up,
and now there's talk of me
playing the lead instead.
I hear they're still arguing
about who to pick, though.
Huh...
Huh? Oh, so that's why they
called me in the other day!
They didn't tell you?
Wait, so you and me
are gonna audition for the role?
That's not going to happen.
In Japanese showbiz, big stars
never have to go through auditions.
Star Actors
They only hold them for supporting roles.
Please join the cast!
Hmm, I dunno...
Supporting Actors
The showrunners can't compare
people on my level.
Please cast me!
Who should I pick...
Offers for starring roles and theme songs
are generally made one at a time.
Offer
Actor A
Actor B
Making multiple simultaneous
offers is seen as unethical.
Actor
Only when the first choice refuses
do they start negotiating with the second.
Actor
Actor B
Actor C
Actors who get lots of lead role offers
get to pick and choose.
In other words, I'm interviewing them.
Making big stars audition
is utterly disrespectful!
At least, that's the view
of the producers and agents.
It's not like we ourselves
really see it that way, though.
We'd prefer to be chosen on merit,
not because of fame or connections.
Top stars have their own stuff
to worry about, huh?
Yep. I agonize over it, sometimes
to the point of depression.
It's our job to make quality films,
and yet there are times when
the quality drops because of us.
Actors should be chosen on merit.
Don't you agree?
I do.
Right?
Let's do just that, then.
Huh?
But didn't you say the showrunners
can't compare us—
The showrunners can't.
But what if we did it ourselves?
Let's have a showdown, Ruby.
Whoever loses has to turn down the offer.
That way, the winner
will get the role by default.
We can call it...
a private audition.
North Exit Shopping Arcade
Hula Dance Club
Private Audition
Sunflower R&R
Yasuoka
Wow.
I didn't know you could
rent out a place like this.
Broke theater groups and underground
idols often use them for lessons.
Community centers like this
have nonsensically cheap rental fees.
Oh? How much?
Two hundred yen for two hours.
Huh?
Two hundred yen for two hours!
That's nonsensically cheap!
It's a government facility built using
the citizens' blood, sweat, and taxes.
Let's be grateful for the chance
to squeeze it for all it's worth.
The silent wrath of the highest
tax bracket! Ooh, scary!
So, what are we doing for this audition?
Could it be...
Huff-puff, huff-puff!
Eep!
Tremble-tremble, panic-panic!
Eek!
Something like that?
Relax. We won't be putting
our lives on the line.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Akane-chan.
Good. Now we have all of
the lead role candidates here.
Long time no see, Ruby-chan.
U-Uh...
Yeah...
Awkward!
Hooked Up On Love for Real
Popular Couple Splits
Aqua Hoshino
Akane Kurokawa
They just announced
their breakup and everything!
But I did call her my big sis once.
I gotta play it cool!
How's Aqua-kun? Is he doing okay?
Y-Yeah...
Eek!
Shiranui-san,
what are you playing at here?
What do you mean?
We're the top choices for the lead role
in Director Gotanda's new film, right?
If you'd let things play out,
you would've gotten the offer first.
But here you are, making a mess of things.
So what are you playing at?
Nothing at all.
Liar.
Not very trusting, are you, Kurokawa-san?
Fine. I do have a goal of sorts.
What is it?
That's a secret.
That said, the reason
I proposed this private audition
is ninety percent because I want
to feel good about doing my job.
I want to go into it thinking,
"I really was the best fit for this role."
Not my problem. This is the
first day off I've had in ages.
If that's all this is, I'm out of here.
We'll be acting opposite Aqua-san.
Aqua?
You say this is an audition.
Who's judging it?
It's between us. We'll decide the winner.
What's the litmus test?
Why don't we just play the part?
The 15-Year Lie
I haven't gotten the script.
I don't know what the part even is.
Me neither.
Oh, right.
I can't really show the script to people
who haven't gotten an offer yet...
Hmm... In that case,
how about I pick a theme,
and we each improvise a scene on that?
Fine by me.
Yep.
Okay, let's go with that.
The theme is...
Lie
"Liar."
I'll go first. Use the time
to think about what you'll do.
First up, here is Frill Shiranui,
with "Liar."
Awoo!
Wolf!
Tch, not a damn soul believes me anymore.
I wish they'd give me attention.
I'm so lonely...
What the hell should I do?
I know! Maybe they'll give me
attention if I tell the truth?
No wolf!
And then men from all over the village
showed up with their hunting rifles
and raked the boy
who cried wolf over the coals.
Fin.
Huh?
A skit?
Oops, my comedian side shone through.
You two don't need punchlines, okay?
Do whatever you like.
So yeah, I can act a bit.
Not as much as Kurokawa-san, of course.
But I do have a sort of appeal
that only I can bring to a role,
so I'd like you to take that into account.
Being good at acting isn't the only
thing that makes a good actor.
She has an air about her that draws
the eyes of one and all to herself.
That's a powerful asset for any actor.
Okay, your turn next, Ruby.
If this were any other audition,
Ruby-chan wouldn't stand a chance.
So there must be a reason
she's a part of this,
and I'm betting it has to do
with this role—this movie.
Say, Ruby.
What does lying mean to you?
Episode 33
Greed and Passion
Translation
Sriram Gurunathan
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check
Gabriella Alabanza
Translation Check
Michelle Tymon