Let's see...
That's my home!
Huh?
MAKOTO MIRAI TOWN
BUILDING SITE
The whole town is missing!
So you really did come from the future?
You weren't a Star Detective
from the agency?
I told you, I never lie!
It's my birthday party! I have to go home!
You're a Star Detective aren't you?
Help me!
If I'm a Star Detective, then so are you!
Oh yeah! I know where we can go!
Huh?
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
A brilliant inspiration
I'm sure we'll find it
We're Precure, after all
It's calling to us
Where's the truth?
What will we discover?
One mystery after another
Gather the pieces
From now to the past and future
Like evidence
Something shining across time
How? How? Is it a trick?
Why? Why? We'll face it
Look and feel
Figure out the secret
One brave step will lead to a miracle
The answer?!
Found when you notice the unnoticed
It's destiny, it's love
Whispered in a tiny voice
Let's walk that road together!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
A brilliant inspiration
The jewel key connects us
Opening the link moving forward
Hey, us being born and having met
Is a wonderful mystery
Go on! Star Detective Precure!
Introducing the Genius, Jett-Senpai!
The CUREtto Detective Agency?
There's a Star Detective Precure here!
Huh? There are other Star Detective Pre--
Shh! It's a secret
that there's a Precure here.
It's a secret and yet you know?
Don't worry about that.
I'm sure she'll help us.
Excuse us?
Nobody's here.
It's not how I imagined...
Pochi!
Is anybody there?
I'm not taking commissions!
Um, we need your help.
I traveled back in time...
I have no time to play along
with jokes. Go away.
It's not a joke. It's true.
We're Star Detective Precures.
You're a child?
You two are Precures?
I don't see it.
It's true! I never lie.
That thing! W-Whoa!
Ow!
A fairy?
You used this to transform into Precures?
A fairy that becomes a human...
Are you a Precure fairy friend?
No, I'm the genius inventor Jett!
My job is to invent detective tools.
Wow, and you're so young.
That's amazing!
Young? How old are you?
I'm fourteen.
Huh? I'm almost fourteen too!
Oh yeah? Gold-star shocker!
-I'm older than you! I'm 222!
-You speak formally, so I just assumed.
We're the same age,
so we can be casual! Call me Anna!
Okay, you call me Mikuru.
Got it!
Typical children...
How did you two get these pendants?
I got mine from my grandmother, ages ago.
I don't know the details.
Mine was on my desk.
And then Pochitan appeared.
Pochitan?
Where is Pochitan anyway?
Intruder! Intruder!
The laboratory!
My snacks!
So many!
I use my brain to invent,
so I need energy!
Pochitan!
A Fairy of Time and Space?
They warp time and space.
A very rare fairy.
So you're the reason for the time travel!
Maybe you can use this fairy
to return to your own time!
Yeah? Hooray!
Oh good!
Hang on.
She wasn't always a baby, was she?
No. Pochitan was speaking normally.
She used all her power in the time travel.
She won't be able to do it again
until she returns to her old form.
-Oh, no...
-Now what?
Makoto Jewels.
Jewels with the power of truth in them.
If you have one of those...
But they're very hard to find.
You mean this?
You have one?!
- This'll change her back!
-Yay!
Pochitan!
-Whoa!
-I got it!
It disappeared?
Will she go back?
Pochi!
Huh?
She's not back!
You may need more Makoto Jewels.
Let's look for them!
I'm sure we'll find some!
If we can get help
from our veteran Precure!
There's no longer
a Star Detective Precure in this world.
Huh?
She was here up until a few months ago.
But she suddenly disappeared.
-Why?
-I don't know.
I came from the London CUREtto
Detective Agency to close this office.
This office will close?
Yup.
It was my dream to investigate
with the veteran Precure.
We're here!
We're here! Let's do it!
We'll be Star Detectives!
Right, Mikuru?
Yeah! But Anna, what about going back to--
It's not up to you to decide.
I don't accept you two as Precures.
I only believe what I see
with my own eyes.
In that case, I'll prove we're Precur--!
But right now I have to go home!
- It's curfew for my school dorm.
- Huh?
I'll show you proof tomorrow!
Mikuru!
Let Anna and Pochitan sleep here!
What?
Even for a Fairy of Time and Space,
28 years is a long time!
Did the power of the pendant
bring her to this time?
We'll find out when Pochitan
goes back to her old form.
Mikuru...
We did it...
She's thinking about her
even in her dreams.
Mom...
Despite wanting to go home... tsk.
Good morning! I'll prove I'm a Precure!
Mikuru!
-What?
-It's just like yesterday!
Stop!
PATISSERIE CHUCHU
A cake shop?
Hewp her!
Okay!
What's wrong?
I lost my pen.
The owner is helping me look.
Eriza is a writer.
She won an award for her mystery novel.
MYSTERY NOVEL NEWCOMERS' CONTEST
"THE VANISHED GEM" ERIZA KURUSU
It's my precious pen
that I got at the competition.
We'll help you look!
Tell us what was happening
when you lost it.
Just now, an old woman
started talking to me.
Then suddenly she was gone,
and my pen was gone, too!
Pochitan came here,
so this could be another case.
The old woman could be the culprit.
Huh? The old woman?
She heard us!
Amateurs!
Police...
It's still just a possibility...
I can't get through.
Looks like the network is down.
Miss Howa, what do you mean?
There's no signal,
and mobile phones aren't working.
I saw on the news.
Huh?
You can use our landline.
Anyway, I'll go look for the woman!
Wait! Take my invention, the Pre-Kit!
-Pre-Kit?
-It's a detective tool.
You can use the Pre-Kit Voice Memo
to contact us.
Thank you, Mr. Jett!
She can't be far!
-Hello? Can you hear me?
-Mikuru?
I'll get more details on
when the pen went missing.
Okay!
I was writing here,
when the old woman came.
She said she was my fan,
and asked to shake my hand.
And you shook her hand?
Yeah!
That was the first time
anyone had told me that.
I was so happy.
But when I wanted to sign...
My pen was gone,
and so was the woman.
What did she look like?
She was wearing a green kimono.
Her hair was in a bun.
Excuse me!
How could she disappear here,
where the view is so clear?
Anna! It's that person!
Huh?
Bye-bye, baby!
That woman's
with the Phantom Thieves' Guild!
Phantom Thieves' Guild?
You know about them?
I guess.
Anna! Where are you?
The woman is entering the park!
Stop!
She's not here.
Anna!
Mikuru! Did you see the woman?
I didn't.
That's strange.
We came from over there.
I came from there.
The park only has two exits,
and we didn't see the woman.
Did she jump over the fence?
Is she hiding in the bushes?
Or maybe she is disguised as someone else.
Huh?
BUSINESSMAN
TAIZO YAMADA
I love you, honey!
Me too, darling!
Huh? Seriously?
That's, like, so tragic!
HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT
HARUE TANIMOTO
What a funny smartphone!
Smartphone? That's a mobile phone.
I went with my friend,
and it was totally bogus.
I see!
This is the answer!
-The Phantom thief is...
-That person!
Excuse me?
As if! I'm on the phone.
That's exactly why.
Huh?
The one who stole the pen,
the Phantom thief is...
You!
Huh?
Pretending to use your phone?
You can't use your phone now!
The network is down!
Why can't I get through?
There's no phone connection.
But we're already connected!
Right!
You were running away,
so you didn't notice.
Your high school girl on the phone
disguise was perfect.
That's why you failed.
Well done!
I am indeed Nijee, baby!
You saw through my disguise twice.
I'll give you a prize.
That's...
Lies, envelop!
Come forth, Hanninda!
Hanninda!
What's that?
It's my precious pen...
We'll get that pen back!
Open!
Jewel Cure Watch!
Precure! Wake-up Time!
3! Discover!
6! And face one another!
9! We are the miraculous duo!
Spin around!
And finish off cutely!
Gold-star closing the case on any mystery!
Star Detective, Cure Answer!
Jumping towards smiles
with layered reasoning!
Star Detective, Cure Mystique!
Star Detective Precure!
I'll show you my answer!
They're Star Detective Precures!
I heard people can become Precures using
the Makoto Jewels in their own hearts.
It was true!
Go! Hanninda!
Hanninda!
Han! Nin! Da!
Envelop a strong Makoto Jewel in a lie...
It'll be so strong nobody can stop it!
What are you doing...
...with Eriza's pen?!
Wrong. It's my pen now.
I pretended to be a fan to get close,
and gotcha!
It's so easy if you lie.
She said she was my fan,
and asked to shake my hand.
I was so happy.
I can use lies to get anything I want.
Hanninda!
We Phantom thieves...
will create a wonderful world
entirely covered in lies!
And we need Makoto Jewels to do that!
A world of lies...
That's not wonderful at all!
No? Even though we have the power
to defeat Star Detectives like you?
Talk is cheap!
But I'll tell you something, too.
The CUREtto Detective Agency's mission
is to expose and stop lies.
Phantom thief! We'll protect
the Makoto Jewels from you!
My, you're an energetic baby.
CUREtto Detective Agency.
Of course we're aware of your mission.
Hanninda!
But under these conditions,
how will you stop the lies, the Hanninda?
We've got Precures!
Historically, there have only been
a few Star Detective Precures.
But now, there are two!
Hanninda!
Hannin!
To think you would be on my stage again.
Eriza was lied to, and her pen was stolen.
She's sad!
Lies hurt people!
We Precures will end those lies!
This is our answer!
CUREtto Case Closed!
Hanninda!
Pochi Pochi Cure Cure!
See you at the next show!
The tree is back to normal?
They disappear without leaving a trace.
Here you go!
My pen!
The culprit got away.
But you got it back! Thank you!
Good luck writing your next work!
Thanks!
You can have these.
Pre-Kit Books.
Proof you're Star Detectives.
You're too clueless.
It means I've accepted you.
You can use the office.
Thank you!
-Yay, Mikuru!
-Yeah!
We'll help people in trouble!
We'll protect the Makoto Jewels,
and change Pochitan back!
Then Anna can go back to her own time!
Yeah! But I decided something!
I want to save everyone!
I can't stand a world covered in lies!
I'll be a Star Detective Precure
together with you, Mikuru!
I can go back later!
Anna!
Okay, as proof you're Star Detective
Precures, write in your Pre-Kit Books.
Huh?
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
Okay!
Okay, once again.
Welcome to the CUREtto Detective Agency,
Star Detective Precures.
Thanks, Mr. Jett!
Mr. Jett?
Isn't there a better way
to call your elder?
Senpai!
Jett-senpai! Thanks for having us!
Same here.
(NaNaNaNa why? Why? WHY?
NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER?!)
Connect the dots, oh? Oh my!
Could it be a "gold-star case closed!"?
Could it?
Reasoning turns around riddles
Twists and turns, reverse
Even words and behavior are traps? Traps!
Don't just believe them! No!
Pay attention, think and then
Take the first step!
When I see someone in trouble
I immediately want to help
Cause I wanna, wanna do something
So I go running off
Na Na Na mystery! Mystery!
Solving mysteries
Is what a Star Detective does
See through lies and find truth
Find the answer for a smile
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 100
Working together, we can figure it out
Friends are a true miracle
Let's go! Star Detective
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 1,000
Hand in hand with my friends
Until everything's solved!
We're Precure, after all
(NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER!)
Let's make it a gold-star lovely
detective agency!
Pochi!
Then we need a good interior.
That sofa is cute!
These curtains are, too!
Star Detective Precure!
"Everyone Come
to the CUREtto Detective Agency!"
That mystery! CUREtto Case Closed!