We're canceling the operation!
Retreat!
I repeat!
We're canceling the operation! Retreat!
You're kidding me, John!
Retreat!
All hands, retreat!
Slaughterer of chaos...
I did not think I could exert
this much power against a human.
You are willing to call me a human...
even though I am in this guise?
Appearance is trivial.
I know not your name...
but I promise I will engrave
this past battle into my heart.
I'm sorry, Master.
I shall make the Little Red Riding Hood
burned within you fade.
Participate in the Holy Grail War...
Ayaka Sajyou.
If you don't want to be devoured
by Little Red Riding Hood.
Saber...
We should hide. It's dangerous.
No.
As Master of the King of Heroes,
I have a duty to continue
watching him to the very end.
I do not have many elements
that allow me to reach you.
However...
When it comes to speed, I can win!
Ex...
calibur!
How naive!
Excalibur!
Ex...
calibur!
Why you little...
Ex...
calibur!
Miss, is your body feeling all right?
Huh?
Oh, come to think of it,
I might be feeling a little sluggish.
"A little"?
Miss...
What...
are you?
Tsubaki Kuruoka's room is the rightmost
one from our viewpoint on the top floor.
Much appreciated.
Leave the rest to me.
No, wait a minute.
I'll go with you.
You've made a wise choice, boy.
Say earlier...
if you had left this lovely lady behind
and retreated by yourself...
I would have carved your heart out,
crushed it, kneaded it with sand...
and scattered it into the slop
for pigs to feed on!
But you really made the worst choice.
I will never allow
a diminutive human...
to even attempt walking
alongside my beloved!
Envelop in the black blades...
Zabani—
Jester Karture.
How many bullets...
are left within you?
Damn you.
How'd you get intel on me?
Are you all right, Mr. Jack?
Master...
You transported a half-dead Heroic Spirit?
You are likely the only fool
who would use a Command Spell for this.
If we defeat that person, will Mr. Ja...
Berserker's Spirit Origin revive?
Jack is fine now.
You see it, don't you?
Yes.
The Spirit Origins have fused within him.
It's as if they melted together...
inside something that looks like mud.
I'm afraid that even if you defeat him...
my power will not return to me.
Not unless I truly disappear
and then get resummoned from the Throne.
But if we do so, will that Mr. Jack
be a different person than you are now?
Wait.
Stop right there, whoever it is!
Oh brother.
You shouldn't make an
author do physical labor.
My name is Dumas.
Alexandre Dumas.
Ever heard of me?
What? Why would a Heroic Spirit
disclose his True Name—
M-Mr. Dumas? Which one?
The general under Napoleon?
Or the author of The Three Musketeers?
No, perhaps The Lady of the Camellias?
The second one. You sure know your stuff.
Of course I would know!
I watched the movie, the anime and
the puppet play of The Three Musketeers!
Well, I thank you for that.
But you're pretty difficult
to figure out, kid.
You jumped into the conversation
while setting up a spell in my shadow.
That's definitely a Mage. However...
even when the spell was completed,
you got worked up and kept talking
about The Three Musketeers.
That's not like a Mage.
Huh? I mean, I set it up because I'd be
in danger if you were an enemy.
But if I executed it and you weren't
an enemy, I'd be wasting Magical Energy,
and it would be bad for you.
You know, kid,
you don't act like a Mage...
but are you prepared to throw your life
into a pot for your objective?
This is not mere recklessness, either.
W-Wait, that's...
So, you can still move.
Ridiculous. Hmm?
Mage, you have come out of the cellar.
P-P-Play Ball!
Master!
I'll leave it up to the boy
whether he does it or not.
Jack the Ripper.
Being able to become anyone
is the best ingredient ever.
By mixing that and the boy's presence,
I can fortify your powers temporarily.
But I can't even imagine what kind
of side effects the Master will have...
after being stewed with a street slasher.
Oh? Is that it?
Huh?
Musketeers' Masquerade!
What?
Game Select!
Running through a part of
Mr. Jack's Noble Phantasm power
you stole is a spell I injected...
that confuses the flow of Magical Energy.
There's no way you can do that—
It would have been impossible
unless I got this close.
Y-You could have transformed
into your Master and casted the spell.
That would have been the same.
Why did your Master take the risk
to stand on the battlefield?
Because he holds something that I cannot.
Archer's Master has already used up
all the Command Spells, right?
If there was even one stroke left,
the power of that connection
would have repelled it.
You have eyes
that can see through that deeply!
However...
I'm not done yet!
At this rate—
The actor showed some courage.
That makes me want to
fix up the logic a bit.
Guys like you are the ones...
that should become heroes.
You are...
John!
Game Over.
You used the Hydra's venom.
But...
the power given to you
is not a god's blessing.
It is a power created
by humans and the earth.
I praise you, my brother...
and...
I pity you, brave hero!
This tainted blood of mine...
The flames of revenge
harboring within my soul...
cannot be stained by a mere deadly poison!
What is he about to do?
What exactly are you?
What do you mean?
It's unusual to be able to supply that
much Magical Energy to a Heroic Spirit.
At the very least, you'd have to be
a top-tier Mage to do so.
You say that, but I
really don't understand
this Magical Energy stuff to begin with.
Miss...
What are you?
I was planning on eradicating you,
church and all.
I have become curious
about this thing's fate.
Gilgamesh...
You did the same for me once upon a time.
You thought of protecting this location?
I ought to sneer at your arrogance
and slay you here...
but by nullifying that attack,
you've earned my acknowledgement.
That is...
an honor.
Saber?
We can win. We can win...
Lord Gilgamesh!
Mongrel...
What are you hiding within you?
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking about your entourage.
I'm talking about the source
of your own Spirit Origin.
In any case, it appears
you still lack a true reason to fight.
To dare challenge me
while in such an emotional state...
Now that is flagrant conceit, mongrel.
I shall execute judgment.
Have you any final words before I do?
I'd like to say I don't, but...
let's see...
The girl that has provided
my Magical Energy is not a Master.
It was one-sided exploitation on my part.
She bares you no hostility,
so please make allowances for her.
All right.
However, if I find her existence trivial,
I shall blast her away without hesitation.
No different from the rest of the rabble.
Mongrel, the judgment on you—
What a tactless act!
You came to settle the
score before you died off?
However, you thought I could not purify...
that tiny portion of tainted mud?
Strong king...
and weak warrior!
What will slaughter you is not that taint!
Oh?
It is what drowns in that mud!
The corpses!
My distinguished enemy
and pitiful fellow...
you shall dance within my mad rush!
Nine Lives!
I shall personally appraise you...
and see how much that hide of yours
recognizes the crafts of humans!
Hydra venom, huh?
I already have plenty
of such poison in my stores.
Nothing less from you, my king!
So...
the Holy Grail can even summon
something of this caliber?
Huh?
We have an interruption.
I did not expect you to stray here.
So...
you have fallen that far...
Ishtar, goddess of fertility!
"Fallen"? That's quite a
terrible way to say it!
The higher ground I've obtained
hasn't changed from the beginning.
You simply thought
you climbed higher than all of us.
You got carried away
and left your Master behind, too!
A Holy Grail War isn't
something so easy...
that you could make it through and win
without a united front.
You know that, right?
More like, you don't feel
the intense pain of the poison yet?
Hurry up and roll around the ground
to make me laugh!
That arrogance plastered onto your soul
does not dissipate...
even after millennia have passed.
To make me walk through
such a clammy cave alone...
is worth certain death.
A cave...
Well, thanks to that, I found
something useful in order to kill you.
The key to the vault!
Why you...
It's something that is of no use
to an ordinary human.
But I can lock it up again, at the least.
Closing the door before my treasures
dazzles your eyes...
I said you had fallen,
but I stand corrected.
You have become quite laudable!
Or...
did that vessel affect you?
That didn't happen.
This body is a doll that was created
only to become a vessel.
Just like this little one.
To think I made a misjudgment...
You are not the actual being,
but an inferior reverberation.
I wanted to play around a bit more...
but going further
would make things a bit troublesome.
What?
Perhaps it is the curse itself?
I think it'd be best to flee.
I made an effort
to avoid your vital spots...
so you should agonize as long as you can!
Or so I'd like to say.
Even if I let it slide...
I don't think this little
guy is so forgiving.
- Lord Gilgamesh!
- Lady Tiné!
It's dangerous!
No!
Nooooo!
Oh brother.
At this rate, the audience, the stage...
everything will burn down to cinders.
If so...
I should lower the curtains
with my own hands.
This might be really bad!
Saber!
Oh, sorry, Ayaka.
I was planning on protecting
the church to the end...
but I kind of screwed up.
It's fine! Just hurry up
and get your wounds treated!
I'm sure the church has
bandages or something!
You really aren't a Mage
through and through.
Your feelings serve
as a better medicinal herb than bandages.
Stop joking!
We have to hurry out of here!
Hold it! Wait!
If I made a citizen who I must protect
do such a thing...
it would be a disgrace to me
both as a knight and as a king.
At the point you're hanging out
with someone like me,
it's already been a disgrace
the whole time!
Just hurry up!
And having you
depreciating yourself like that...
is a disgrace to me as a Heroic Spirit.
EPISODE 10