What's up?
I thought I heard a bell.
Episode 12
"A Country Without Lizel"
Could you appraise these, please?
Magic stones, huh?
Huh? What is this?
There's something crazy in here.
Is it fire? No, flame...
Is this from a boss?
Indeed. That apparently came from
the boss of the Spirit Garden.
They found quite a lot,
so after setting some aside,
he said he'd "offer the
rest to the market."
Mr. Lizel...
Was he hurt?
If the two powerful men with him
somehow allowed him to become injured,
they wouldn't deserve to live.
Good, so he's not hurt.
This one's worth three gold,
and this one's five silver.
You recognize Eleven's skill, too?
I'm kind of surprised.
How could I not, when he
welcomed him into his party?
Also...
I believe I said "if," dullard.
Why are you insulting me?
What's next?
This one's two silver,
that one's three silver.
Those back-to-back award
ceremonies were unbearable.
Don't say that. It's your duty as a noble.
I heard mention of a promotion to count.
Apparently, but the idea was abandoned
out of consideration for the knights.
That said, I'd intended to turn it down.
The police who accept all backgrounds
and knights who value strength
and lineage don't get along.
It's hardly a terrible relationship,
but nothing can be done about
differences in principles.
A certain marquis demanded to know
why I didn't immediately report
that I'd found the bandit bases.
The one who controls the knights?
Yes. He's not wrong, though.
My source was shady.
I couldn't put that on the knights
when they're this nation's light.
Now then.
Has the boss of the Forky Gang confessed?
Yes. Finally, just a moment ago.
I see. He was tenacious.
Now everything has been
wrapped up nicely.
Good work, sir.
And he directed it impressively.
Anyway, I wish people would stop
recommending marriage to me
as soon as they see my face.
I'm sure many ladies would
gladly be your second wife.
I keep telling them I already have
an heir, but they won't stop.
But you aren't determined
not to remarry, are you?
I suppose not.
If I somehow met a greater
woman, I might consider it.
Your wife was strong,
beautiful, and wise.
Women greater than her are rare.
Indeed.
It seems my life will end
with me serving you.
Yes, but if Mr. Lizel were a woman,
I would've relentlessly
attempted to seduce him.
I believe you're already doing that.
Marcade
I picked a fight with
the merchant's guild.
Absolutely not. You know
I reject all their meddling.
Yeah.
And that I'm careful not
to antagonize them.
But they really screwed my grandson.
What? You mean that scandal?
Yeah. You know who told me?
An adventurer with a face
that puts nobles to shame.
What does it say?
You wanna know? Huh?
It's primarily about Judge's preferences.
What?
He wants to cheer him up.
That's all?
Of course not.
It lists every stolen item the staff
member in question sold in the past
and every guild employee who knew
about it, among other things.
It's packed with information that
could bring down the entire guild.
What kind of information
network does that man have?
Hold on. Have you mentioned
this to the guild?
Nah, not outright.
I see.
But I did hint at it.
Absolutely not.
This could upset the balance
of power with the guild.
How much did you tell them?
I just told them off for
screwing my grandson.
And to get rid of those
embarrassments to the guild.
You should've stopped
after the first part.
They tried to hide things from me, too.
They think they can screw me over.
And if he told me, that means he
wants me to do something, right?
You'd let an adventurer
tell you what to do?
Didn't he make you buy dinner for him?
If you've concluded your
business, then leave.
Sorry to have bothered you.
The Forky Gang was brought
down at the same time.
No...
It couldn't be.
What was that, a sneeze?
Do you have a cold, leader?
No. Perhaps someone's talking about me.
If it worked that way,
you'd never stop sneezing.
What should we do today?
Whatever you want.
"Think you're strong? Help wanted
producing healing potions."
You'd like this, leader.
I've been wanting to see how
healing potions are made here.
Am I that strong, though?
No.
Just have the Blade do it.
I'm not sure about having the great
Blade take on an F-rank job.
We did one before.
You were just looking after me then.
You're the leader.
I'll go with you.
But only one of us is strong.
You don't seem much stronger than me.
You underestimate me.
And you underestimate me.
I may not be as strong as
him, but I do wield blades.
Then let's arm wrestle.
Seriously? You think you can beat me?
I think I can put up a good fight.
Begin.
I win.
I'm a bit shocked.
I thought you fought
primarily with technique.
You're not wrong.
No matter how skilled you are,
you need strength to cut a golem.
Then the two of you
will complete the job.
I thought you didn't
want to make him do it.
This is just how he is.
I'm off to make a delivery.
Make sure you stop by the police station.
Yeah, I know.
Hello. We're here for the job.
I'm Medi. I'm an apothecary.
I like quiet and intelligent people.
Even better if they're handsome.
You're exactly my type.
Marry me now so we can
get married someday!
We're leaving.
Don't make eye contact.
I'll make you happy! I promise!
What are you doing, girl?
We're not looking for S-rank adventurers.
Actually, I'm E-rank. Is that a problem?
You've got a mouth on you.
I'm not paying more than I said I would.
Sorry for losing my composure
because you're exactly my type.
That's all right. Don't worry about it.
So polite!
We want you to grind magic stones.
You'll use this.
You put the stones in here.
Turn this, and powder will
come out the bottom.
Huh.
It won't budge.
Of course not.
Three grown men can barely
turn it together.
If you can't do it,
you can call in help to...
Look at it go.
How is it, Gil?
Fine.
I guess you won't need any.
Impressive. No wonder people
think you can't be human.
You're the only one who thinks that.
Well, actually...
Hey.
You could probably crush
them with your bare hands.
They probably can't be used to
make healing potions unless
they're a fine powder.
Stop assuming I can do that.
This is an insane conversation.
Keep pouring in the stones.
We need all of these crushed.
Sure.
Since Gil can do it by himself,
we're hardly needed.
There's plenty more to do here.
If you don't mind, we'll assist you.
Really? How are you at math?
I'm not terrible.
Well, I am.
This is it.
Ugh, that goes right over my head.
Can you solve this?
I don't know what I'm doing, but barely.
Of course.
I should be able to do this.
Is this what you want me to do?
He's as smart as he looks!
May I borrow a desk?
Yes, of course!
You'd look great writing with a pen!
Marry me!
Do you wear glasses?
My vision is good.
I can't do this.
Then why don't you help with deliveries?
If the apothecary doesn't mind, that is.
That would be a huge help.
I'm glad to hear that.
Don't worry. He can handle most things.
You know about that?
No, but I heard you mention the police
earlier, so I thought maybe...
Lately, I've been hearing a lot about
potion deliveries being stolen.
We were attacked once,
but the old fart was making the
delivery, so it worked out.
Yeah, he'd be just fine.
We can't mass produce these,
so any thefts are a huge loss.
Who's even stealing our product?
It's not me.
That's not what I meant.
You can fend thieves off
if you're attacked, right?
Of course. Can I kill them?
No.
Got it.
Well, I'm off.
Is he okay?
He's fine. He's quite skilled.
Anyway, should we leave
the ground stones there?
That's a ton of powder. That was quick.
Mr. Brains, give me the calculations
as soon as you complete them.
I need them for the magic stones.
Understood.
I'm back.
Welcome back. You weren't gone long.
Glasses?! Are they fake?
Why are you wearing those?
I was told wearing them would be
motivating and increase efficiency.
But I just can't get used to them.
Take them off if they're bothering you.
I was going to...
but strangely, they seem to be working.
Hey, quit staring.
Looks like you successfully
completed the delivery.
Here's the money.
And you weren't attacked
by thieves either.
Actually, I was.
What?!
How did it go?
I fought them off, no problem.
They weren't bandits, just arrogant
brats looking to fill their pockets.
Perhaps a merchant hoping to
resell put them up to it.
What did you do with the children?
I ditched 'em.
I see.
Oh, but I ran into a cop I've seen
before, so I let him handle it.
Is there anything else to do? I'm bored.
Hey, you.
Mr. Brains is solving those complex
problems like it's nothing.
What's his deal?
Our great leader is amazing.
He's fetching in glasses,
has beautiful skin,
and he's stoic, but he's sexy, too?
He's a walking contradiction.
But that's what I like.
You sound like an old guy.
What's his type?
I don't know. Girly girls, probably.
Like me?
What did I just say?
What's his type, huh?
The things I'd do to that chaste face...
Could you not talk about him like that?
Maybe I could...
I told you to stop! I'll kill you, bitch!
Language, Eleven.
No fair!
I'm tired.
You just rested after
completing the delivery.
Gil was grinding the whole time.
My arms are pretty tired.
I mean I'm mentally exhausted.
What's wrong with that
man-eater—no, man-needer?
Hey, that was pretty clever.
What's wrong?
I thought I heard a bell.
I must've imagined it.
By the way, what's your type?
My type?
As in who tends to catch your eye.
I wouldn't call them my type,
but they're exactly around your age.
You know someone my age?
Yes, the most important
person in the world to me.
What? Who? A woman? Is it?
Who's to say?
There it is again.
A bell failing to ring properly.
Did you hear that?
No.
Same.
Am I hearing things? No...
Are you okay?
Did you sleep last night?
Yes, soundly.
Not these.
Sorry.
I'm not mad.
If only you can hear it, it could
have something to do with those.
Are those related to
your important person?
That's a secret.
What's going on?
Leader!
He's breathing. Is he poisoned?
I don't smell anything.
Lea—
How long was I out?
A little over ten seconds.
Oh, that long?
Are you okay?
I feel great.
I feel as though a ton of
mana was poured into me.
Is this...?
This mana...
I'd never forget it.
Your Majesty.
Hey, did you get through to him already?
Hey, who do you think you're
standing in front of?
What is this?
How should I know?
Your Majesty, Father,
I'm glad you both seem well.
So do you. Oh, I'm so glad.
If you weren't his father,
I'd have you put to death.
Are you even listening?
Step aside, damn it!
Do you have any idea what it
took to open this window?
He's just like him.
May I assume I'm in another world?
Yes.
Unfortunately, it'll be a while
longer before we can come get you.
Then I'll wait patiently.
What are you doing now?
I'm enjoying being an adventurer.
An adventurer? That sounds fun.
Just try not to get hurt.
He has his father's approval?
Are those two behind you your friends?
Yes. We adventure together.
You don't look very nice,
but you seem like a knight.
I'm sure you'll do a good
job protecting Lizel.
And you look like the
boss of a bandit gang.
Oh, that's not an insult.
Thanks.
I'm relieved you both seem dependable.
I told you to move!
Do I need to command you?
Have fun, Lizel.
Liz.
A country without you is worthless.
Wait for me.
I promise I'll bring you back.
Yes, sir.
Next.
A noble?
You're confusing people again.
This always happens.
It's not my fault.
Uh, what is your reason for entry?
Sightseeing.
Sightseeing? Forgive me,
but aren't you a noble?
No.
I'm an adventurer.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
Sho Stifler
Edgar Cruz
Ashley Barboza
Gabriella Alabanza
Michelle Tymon
Illustration by: Momoji