Episode 10
Agree to my three conditions,
and you can leave.
Do you believe me?
It really wasn't me!
Believe you?
How can I believe you?
Even those who have awakened the
Bright Soul Skill can't handle you.
But I've watched you kids grow up.
I know exactly what kind
of person you are.
I didn't do it!
Then prove it to me!
It's not like I didn't give you a chance.
When you were first caught by the clan,
if some people hadn't turned a blind eye,
do you think you could've escaped
the village on your own?
But after you fled,
did you go looking
for Huan's actual killer?
No, you didn't.
You ran off and had fun hanging out
with those Quan Xing brats!
I... I really had nowhere
else to go at the time.
Bullshit!
You mean righteous clans feared
our Lyu Clan and wouldn't take you in.
Let me name three people!
Zhang Zhiwei of the Tenshifu.
I can't compare to him in terms of
character, strength, or influence.
Mu You of Xiaozhan.
The most upstanding of
the younger generation!
And Lu Jin, head of the Lu Clan.
I don't get along with him.
But I won't deny he's a good man!
I just hate that he's too clean!
We've never seen eye to eye,
even since childhood.
If you were truly wronged,
you could've gone to any one of them!
All three know I'm ruthless,
but none of them fear me!
They wouldn't just listen to the
village's story and hand you back!
And they all have the ability to
help you track down the real killer!
If you really were innocent,
those three were your best options!
But you...
You chose the lowest of the
low, the Quan Xing Sect!
You can't even explain
why yourself, can you?
Let me tell you...
Birds of a feather flock together!
Compared to staying in the
village and following my rules,
it's much more fun to mess around
with those freaks, right?
Even setting aside Huan's matter,
the beatings you've taken these days...
Were they unfair?
Not unfair.
All right, three conditions!
First, from now on, cut all
ties with the Quan Xing Sect!
No more contact!
Second, from now on, you will
follow me and learn Ruyi Jin.
Me?
How could I possibly learn it?
Grandfather tried to teach me.
Mastering innate and acquired abilities
simultaneously is extremely difficult,
but not impossible!
And didn't you hear what I just said?
From now on, you'll follow me!
I'll train you personally!
One last condition.
After you recover, prepare
to marry Qi from Dongcun.
Qi? You mean Lyu Qi?
How can that be...
Not satisfied? You don't like
her looks or personality?
Oh yeah, her Ruyi Jin is really advanced.
Afraid of getting beaten up later?
No, she's a relative from
within five generations!
So what?
Back then, your Great-Uncle,
Grandfather, and Third Great-Aunt
all married within their own clan.
B-But...
Do you refuse?
No, I... Great-Grandfather...
Huan's matter hasn't been...
Why... Why are you doing this for me?
Why am I treating you so well?
Of course Huan's matter isn't over.
If I ever find out it really was you,
I'll kill you with my own hands.
If it wasn't you,
then you go and investigate!
You think just because I'm letting you go,
you can escape my grasp?
Lyu Liang,
deep down, I hope it wasn't you.
You all think I'm ruthless,
that I'm heartless.
Well, I do think I'm pretty harsh myself.
But you also need to understand,
the only thing that truly
matters to me is bloodline.
Even a ridiculous guy like you,
I cherish you in my own way.
Great-Grandfather...
Oh, right, Great-Grandfather...
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Do you know what "Perfect Hands" is?
Where did you hear that name?
Wait...
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
You'll be fine.
That technique you used on
me just now... that was...
This is your memory.
A technique passed down in our
Lyu Clan, the Bright Soul Skill.
It's specifically designed
to deal with this place.
Bright Soul Skill...
You have no idea what you're doing.
Child, let me give you
one more piece of advice.
Leave the Quan Xing Sect
as soon as possible.
Huh?
If they'll make things difficult
for Zhang Chulan over Qi Genesis,
then you're not safe with them either.
What... do you mean?
I've seen your technique before,
a long time ago.
It was exactly the same.
But back then, it wasn't
called "Bright Soul Skill,"
but "Perfect Hands."
It's... one of the Eight Secret
Arts from the Jiashen year.
Why would Tian Jinzhong say that?
Great-Grandfather!
You wait here.
Great-Grandfather.
Father!
Father... how did it go?
Lyu Liang, he...
Lyu Zhong, go and take
what's in Lyu Liang's head.
Father?
Go get the village doctor.
Great-Grandfather! Great-
Come in!
I want him alive.
Every drop of our clan's blood
is precious.
President Qu, this way please.
Yaoxing Society, Qu Tong?
I've heard a lot about you.
Mr. Mu You of Xiaozhan.
Chairman Zhao, what's this about?
Not much.
I just need both your teams
to help out with something.
This shows the location of one
of the Company's secret bunkers.
How did it come to this?
Why didn't you tell me beforehand...?
I just got the news myself!
Zhao Fangxu didn't discuss this
with the Board before taking action.
He planned to act first and report
later from the very start.
As things stand, even if he
notified the Board afterwards,
they wouldn't refuse him.
He's already starting to
suspect the Board.
So what?
No one will fall for such a stupid plan!
Not necessarily.
This time it might
actually be troublesome.
I can't refuse Zhao Fangxu.
If I do, they'll suspect me.
The Company really got lucky this time.
Zhang Lingyu
If it's convenient, I'll come over now...
Bao'er.
You wouldn't mind an
extra roommate, right?
The number you dialed is
temporarily unavailable.
Big Wang
This guy...
I haven't been able to reach him ever
since we parted ways at Biyou Village.
Welcome!
A very warm welcome!
On behalf of the Company, I offer
Master Lingyu a very warm welcome!
I... have one more condition.
Name it.
Can I not cut my hair?
I understand there are regulations, but...
Is that okay?
Master Lingyu, you're overthinking it!
Come, let's get you settled first.
There's an empty room downstairs.
You can tidy it up yourself.
Living in the same building as a girl?
That's inconvenient.
What's inconvenient about it?
I never expected Master Lingyu to take
gender distinctions so seriously.
Brother Si!
Yeah?
Come now, Master Lingyu, this way...
Now that Zhang Lingyu's sorted,
what about Lu Linglong and Lu Lin?
They're in Tianjin.
Lately, when you go out,
have you noticed you're being watched?
Huh?
They're from Xiaozhan.
Those two rookies hired them.
Xiaozhan's one of the largest intelligence
organizations in the Outcast world.
How could they not maintain a good
relationship with the Company?
Those two didn't even figure that out.
The moment Xiaozhan received the request,
they notified me immediately.
What should we do?
Should we drag them out and confront them?
No need.
If they really got involved in this,
they deserve whatever happens.
Master!
The thought of you being in danger
while I remained on the
mountain doing nothing...
I simply couldn't bear it!
Master!
Please forgive me this once.
Huanjin, did you hear what he said?
So he came down the mountain for my sake.
Master, Lingyu has suffered
enough humiliation.
I'm not laughing at Zhang Lingyu.
I'm happy for Zhang Huaiyi.
This Master Uncle of yours,
he seemed so calm and
detached from the world.
But it wasn't until he teamed
up with Master to fool me
that I realized just how strong he was.
Throughout my life as a cultivator,
I always believed I surpassed
him in every way.
But today I've realized that
in terms of successors, I've lost.
Look at Zhang Chulan,
the one he left behind.
All right, Zhang Lingyu.
From now on, you are no longer
a disciple of the Tenshifu.
I am no longer your master.
They say the girls of
Youzhou are so fine...
Miss Bao, what are you...
San's car.
It needs maintenance.
The suspension's a bit loose.
You can fix cars?
That's amazing...
Yeah, it's not hard.
Fuel lines, circuits, pneumatics,
moving parts. That's all.
Impressive. Really impressive.
Really? Lots of people can do it.
All done.
Eat?
Thank you.
Miss Bao, how long have
you been with the Company?
Many years.
Many years...
That makes you sound so old.
What do you do at the Company?
Whatever San, Si, or
Zhang Chulan tell me to do.
Chulan, what do you think?
Chulan?
It's good!
I'll follow your arrangements,
Chairman Zhao.
Um... what about that person?
Master Uncle, how are you
getting along with Bao'er?
Zhang Chulan, come here.
From Miss Bao's description,
the Company seems a bit...
Even if I, Zhang Lingyu,
fall on hard times,
I would never do anything
against my conscience!
She's special! Her job is special.
How could the Company act recklessly?
If you don't trust the Company,
you should at least trust me!
I disagree on that point.
Then you should at least
trust your own conscience.
From now on, you'll have to
experience everything for yourself.
No one can tell you what to do.
All I can say is, in order to survive,
I don't mind ambiguous situations
and doing things I'd rather not.
But if it crosses my boundaries,
then screw it all.
Master Uncle, I believe
you also have boundaries.
Oh right, you've got a job.
Your first job is to protect me.
How about that?
Doesn't violate your conscience, right?
Excellent, Mr. Xiaoxiao.
Your breathing technique is excellent.
You've been very helpful. Thanks.
It's nothing. President
Qu did me a big favor.
Whatever the request is,
as long as she asks,
I'll do it.
That's right.
Almost everyone here has been
helped by Sister at some point.
This is probably why no
one can refuse her.
That's the source of her magic.
This furnace was forged by Sister
using my Divine Craftsmanship,
combined with her own methods,
to restore my missing memories.
But I want to use it to help more people.
I want to become someone like Sister.
You are you.
Why would you want to become me?
Sister, you're back!
Xiaoxiao, please step out for a moment.
Again, Sister?
I haven't needed to take this for ages.
Take it. Be good.
Sister, back then you said it was because
my mental state was unstable...
Take it!
But now I don't feel like my mind is...
Hello, Chairman Zhao?
Let me know when you're ready.
The draft can be sent out at any time.
Why not finish the job?
Just remove all his
memories of Biyou Village!
If you think his trust in
you is starting to waver,
then embed it deeper!
A sound mind can repair itself,
as you very well know.
After repeated repairs,
his mind has already become
extremely unstable.
If we continue, I'm worried about
unpredictable consequences.
So what?
If he becomes useless, get rid of him!
Oh? Since when have you been
able to speak to me like this?
Ah! No!
I-I was just too concerned about you!
I've already given him the drugs.
Unless someone wakes him up,
he'll sleep for at least a week.
As long as you have a plan.
Let me make this clear to you.
It's those few guys making a move again.
You must be careful.
Hang up.
Guys, do you really think this will work?
I gave up a cushy job
to come here, you know!