Armor of Wildfire!
Ow...
Who knew the sky was so blue?
This pain is a step toward
changing tomorrow.
In your dreams, maybe.
If you still have strength to talk,
I guess you can go another round.
Seriously?!
Ryo!
Do you have a moment?
The barrier around the Demon World
is about to break.
A new Demon Emperor may have
emerged to replace Arago.
All right. We'll go see.
Twin Fire Slash!
A tolerable vessel.
Who's there?!
Demon Emperor Ramaga.
I have come to claim your body!
Ryo...
What's Mr. Sanada doing there?
You know him?
He's one of the original Samurai Troopers.
Yama! Isn't that guy...
Yeah, no doubt about it.
He's our hero!
Ryo! It's me!
Nasti!
Save your breath.
His personality is no more.
Ryo Sanada... He made for a fine vessel,
but the years have taken their toll.
And I'm gonna be your next Puppet?
Gimme a break!
Don't give yourself airs, whelp.
I need better than
you can offer right now!
Gai, you turn fifteen today.
To celebrate, I will give you a chance.
Is that...
Henceforth, we will make our
headquarters in this Demon Castle!
EPISODE VI
RESTART
A Demon Castle?!
I grant you seven days' reprieve.
Use that time to make yourself
a Puppet worthy of me
or to find me another Puppet
to take your place.
Fail me, and I will raze
this country to the ground.
I shall lend you the Sword of Domination.
This should prove amusing!
Still, it would be a shame
to retreat without doing anything.
Yeah! Yeah!
What're you blabbing about?!
You want another piece of me?!
You mean you didn't even
realize we went easy on you?
You can't hold a candle to us!
Yamato! Musashi!
I've seen all I need to of your moves.
You pieces of—
You don't stand a chance
without your demon powers.
Enjoy your last seven days alive
as best you can.
Confirmed survivors alone
have reached 110,570 people.
We need to move them to evac sites
and government shel—
First, explain the castle!
And what's this about destroying
the country a week from now?
We have a way to avert it.
It's another reason we need the Samurai
Troopers ready for action once more.
This again?
We have a plan,
and a secret strategy
to make them stronger than ever.
Mirei.
Oh, Commander.
Look at these. They all came out awful.
I would've taken at least one good one
if I'd known he was going to die.
Okay, enough's enough!
Time to shift gears!
Ryusei would laugh at me!
You don't need to force yourself.
Same to you, Commander.
Mr. Sanada being Ramaga's Puppet
must really be weighing on you.
I'm fine.
Speaking of, this is really bugging me.
Why would Ramaga go to all this trouble
and then decide to wait a week?
Good question.
But it does give us an opportunity.
I'd like to ask a favor of you.
I feel totally defeated.
Ryu wound up dead, our hero is Ramaga,
the Ten Warriors are wicked tough...
We don't have a chance in hell, do we?
People do... just die, don't they?
Seeing Ryu pass with my own eyes
finally brought that home for me.
I haven't been able to stop shaking since.
Me neither.
My fear won out over
my hatred and my anger.
Yeah, but it's not like
we can just run away either.
What'd be so bad about running?
Seriously?
I mean, we're still kids, right?!
So why should we have
to deal with this crap?!
Quitting and getting badmouthed
for it is better than dying!
Musashi...
Then let's all quit together.
What'd you just say?!
I don't want to lose any more comrades.
What the hell is wrong with me?
If you ever hesitate to kill a Puppet,
try out this program.
It'll put you face-to-face
with your problems.
GAI'S PERSONAL SIMULATION VER 1.32
START
Isn't this place...
How dare you kill us?!
It's you guys!
We'll make you suffer like we did!
The Samurai Troopers are... in your hands.
No way, no way, no way!
The heroine's not supposed
to die like this!
I don't see any heroines.
Shion!
This is great!
Anything's "great" compared
to the DST's terrible coffee.
Ryusei liked the way it tasted.
I assume you didn't come here
to sample the coffee.
We need your help.
Sorry, but I won't take Ryusei's place.
Of course not. No one's asking you to.
You're you and nobody else.
The commander asked me to give you this.
A final present from Ryusei to you.
What will Gai do if we all quit?
He'll fight on his own.
His life's on the line.
I wonder.
Huh?
What's he groaning about?
He's having a nightmare.
What's this?
You'll pay!
There you are!
You killed us like we
were just mannequins!
I had a family that meant the world to me!
Why me?
I just happened to be there.
You're...
The hell're you doing?
Guys!
This simulation makes virtual
enemies from your memories.
Why do this to yourself?
Ryusei told me I should.
That jackass left me
one hell of a farewell gift.
It's made me realize something crazy.
Humans do nothing but destroy the world.
That's what my dad taught me,
and I never doubted him.
But when I watched Ryusei die...
It hurt like somebody
was squeezing my heart.
I've never felt that way before.
It made me think... maybe every life I
took made someone else feel like that.
Gai...
So this is your way
of taking responsibility?
It's not like I think it'll change
what I've done!
But you still had to
put yourself through it.
What the—?!
Emergency! Emergency!
Intruder on board!
Initiating emergency stop!
Locating intruder with all due—
What just happened?!
They said we have an intruder.
Let's go back to the real world and see.
That won't be happening.
It's that jerk!
Is that any way to talk
to a senior coworker?
Your parents did a bad job raising you.
Why do you have Ryu's Weapon-Gear?
He won't need it now that he's dead.
You bastard!
I'm a bastard now?
Your parents really—
Oh, wait, you don't have any.
How do you know that?
Courtesy of the classified intel
Ryusei gave me.
Of course, he didn't include
how to take over this train.
Mirei!
I didn't want to get rough
with her, but oh well.
What are you after?
I'm going to make a new team
of Samurai Troopers.
Start making sense,
you skirt-wearing jackass!
Find some taste before
you come for my fashion sense.
Surely you realize that you can't beat
the Demon Emperor as you are now.
And so I decided to lay
the best runway you could ask for.
You're going to fight me.
If you lose, you're all fired.
You can get off this train
with a clear conscience.
Great plan, right?
Don't just assume we want out.
It sounds like everyone
but you does, though.
And what if we win?
In that event, I'll join you.
What? Gimme a break!
This is what Ryusei wanted,
so deal with it.
But don't worry too much.
You've got zero hope of beating me.
You sure like to talk a big game!
Armor of Wilderness!
No Armor-Gear for you.
Under-Gear only. I've changed
the virtual space's settings.
But the same goes for me.
All of you come at me, four against one.
It'll save time.
I'll show you!
Yamato Hojo.
You have the most passion
for being a Samurai Trooper
and the most brute strength.
Yamato can be intense,
but he brings life to the team,
and the strength he taps into when
his emotions take over will shock you.
Meaning you leave more openings
when you lose your cool.
Yama!
Damn it...
I'll make you pay for that!
Musashi Hojo.
You're agile and specialize
in quick strikes.
Musashi is a pessimist
and grumbles a lot,
but he has a strong sense of justice,
and most importantly, he's caring.
Which means you have trouble
striking hard enough to kill.
Kaito Uesugi, you have a sharp mind
and always assess the situation calmly.
Kaito seems detached, but he's really
the most sensitive to others' pain.
He thinks of his teammates
and relies on them.
But you're only fifteen.
You struggle to adapt to the unexpected.
Is that all you've got?
Not bad.
But there's a lot more
where that came from!
Maybe there's just something wrong
with my eyes, but...
He looks like Ryusei.
You think so too?
Why...?
Why did you leave us?
What are we supposed to do now?!
That's what I want to know.
That just leaves Gai.
Gai.
What are you fighting for?
Gai is on the verge of really soaring.
As long as he stays obsessed with Ramaga,
he won't break out of his shell.
You don't want to become
your father's next body?
In that case—
I'm not fighting for that anymore!
My dad'll wreck this world
whether he makes me his Puppet or not.
So I'm gonna stop him!
I'm gonna end this stupid war quick
so no more blood gets spilled for nothing!
That's what I'm fighting for!
Awfully idealistic talk for a demon!
I'm not a demon anymore.
Ryusei told me.
You're already a worthy emissary of Fire.
I'm...
a Samurai Trooper!
Excellent.
Now we're heating up.
He's right. If we run away now,
even more people are going to get hurt.
Go...
Go for it!
Get him, Gai!
Hey! Don't let him beat you!
You know...
I like them all.
Being with them reminds me
of the time I spent with you.
He won.
All right!
Way to go!
I call this "Operation
Gotta Do It for Ryusei"!
You can't call that an operation.
Ow...
Who knew the sky was so blue?
This pain is a step
toward changing tomorrow.
In your dreams, maybe.
We win.
Keep your promise.
What promise?
You're gonna join us.
Weren't you going to quit?
No one said anything about quitting.
Heroes don't just turn tail and run.
You can start by cleaning up.
Why should I?
Why? Because you're
the new kid on the block.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm older than all of you.
Stop whining and get to work.
When you finish wiping
the place down, start sweeping.
We're counting on you, new guy.
Do you want to make me cry?
We've gotta go rescue Mirei!
Oh, that was a farce.
See how I convey "Eek! Save me!"
with just a look?!
Am I an actress or what?
Man! You nearly gave me a heart attack!
I can't believe you were in
on it too, Commander.
All to get our new Samurai Troopers going.
We need you all to reach
the next stage as soon as possible.
What next stage?
The Armor of the Supreme Emperor.
The what?
A legendary set of armor
that can defeat Ramaga.
This boy holds the key to it.
Jun Yamano, an ally from our fight
against Demon Emperor Arago.
And where is Mr. Yamano now?
He's on this train.
Mr. Yamano! Open the door!
Is he really in there?
Probably, yeah.
He moved in while the train
was in storage and refused to leave.
What a pain.
If you're in there, come on out!
What do you want?
I've had enough of fighting!
This guy is this kid?
Translation\h\h\h\h\h\hWilliam Varteresian
Timing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Editing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRiley Dalton
Quality Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSMR
Translation Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMichelle Tymon
EPISODE VII
MEMORY
Armor races through your heart.