Hey, where are you going?
For a piss.
Three litters?
Who for? Serizawa-sensei
and his buddies?
Nio!
They're heading for Mibu.
It really must be them.
Hey.
Hajime, what are you...
Get out of my way.
I can't let you through.
You want me to save Taro?
That's right.
He's still a child.
I don't want him to die.
You want me to talk him round?
That's not happening.
His loyalty to Serizawa
is the real thing.
I figured. So keep him away by force.
He ought to know
he can't hold a candle to you.
He'll flinch when he sees
you mean business.
If you want to get by me,
make me move.
But don't blame me if you end up dead.
Figures. Hijikata, you dumbass.
He's no child.
And he didn't come this far
just to chicken out.
Blue Miburo
It's time.
They must be asleep in bed by now.
We'll go check.
Come on, Soji.
Right.
You ought to take your mask off
before going inside.
It'll cause a fuss if anyone
sees you wearing them.
I know.
Should we? While we have the chance?
Wait, Harada-san.
What's that noise?
Is someone there?
Ma, what's wrong?
What is it?
It's nothing. Go to sleep.
Outhouse...
Make a noise, and you're dead.
Itosato of the Wachigaiya, I presume?
The master of the house is
at a meeting elsewhere, yes?
Is Serizawa in the inner room?
I'll start from the farthest seat.
Serizawa.
Oume.
Hirayama.
Kichiei.
Hirama.
That's all?
I see. Thank you.
Take this.
It isn't much, but it should
cover travel expenses.
Leave here immediately.
Forget all that has happened,
is happening, and is about to happen.
Spend a night in Fushimi, then go through
Osaka and get as far away as you can.
Is that clear?
You sure you wanna let her go?
After that, we have nothing
to fear from her.
So Serizawa's in the inner room?
Yes, it seems so.
Good.
Soji and I will take the back.
Yamanami and Sanosuke, the front.
Let the women go. Kill all three men.
Close your eyes.
Get them used to the dark.
Open them.
You can all see?
Yes.
Count to 100, then go in.
Scatter.
81, 82...
That's odd.
What's a light doing so high up?
87, 88...
89, 90...
Hijikata-san...
It doesn't matter. We're doing this.
100!
Welcome.
"Use a woman to lure them in."
Everything's gone according
to Niimi's scenario so far.
So our plan leaked?
Then everything Itosato said was...
Damn it. This couldn't get any worse.
"They'll accustom their eyes to the dark,
so use a bright light..."
"...to blind them."
What the... I can barely see.
No... We played right into his hands.
I can see.
The light's no problem
when you know it's going out.
Ready to die, Okita?
I can see.
What happened? Who just did what?
If I slit my belly,
Hijikata will take action.
Okita will join him.
And two more, meaning four in all.
Five at the most.
Harada, Todo, Inoue, Yamanami,
and Nagakura are all possibilities.
Will Sir Kondo act?
I wonder.
He'll want to, but it will depend
on his sense of gallantry.
Oh, I can hardly wait.
You never change.
But be glad.
We made the Miburo ourselves.
They'll be our last, greatest enemy.
Why not have them add flare
to our last bow?
Come to me, my masterpieces.
Serizawa!
What's wrong, Okita?! Come on in!
Okay!
I can see again.
A woman?
Oh, right. There was another one here.
Harada, I know we've been through a lot,
but siding with Kondo's
the last mistake you'll ever make.
Hirayama!
It's over!
Why, you...
Hirayama-san, I'm afraid
I must take your life.
You're sure you won't budge?
What's wrong? That all you got?
Move.
Move!
Damn it. Damn it all!
Serizawa-sensei gave me this sword.
Now's its time to shine!
Your left-hand grip is wrong.
You'll never get any force
in your swings like that.
What have they been teaching you?
Y-Yamanami, you rotten...
I got careless.
I never dreamed you'd be
the one to finish me off.
Wait. I've got my death poem ready—
I'll listen to it in the next world.
Yamanami.
Damn it, Hirama!
Get back here!
Stand up. You're leaving.
No, I can't!
You will! Now, come with me.
What's the matter, Okita?
Your swordplay's awfully tame.
We can't afford to take our time,
Hijikata-san.
I was worried that woman
would be a problem.
Move, woman! You're in the way!
Make me, if you can!
Why side with Serizawa?
If he threatened you into coming here,
you're safe now.
No one threatened me.
I don't care who I'm up against.
You don't...
The stronger, the better.
The Miburo who have the whole city
scared stiff will do nicely.
Who is this woman?
I know about Itosato of the Wachigaiya
and Kichiei of the Kikyoya,
but what kind of woman is Oume?
Well, I just couldn't work up the energy
to look into her too closely.
What do you mean?
Oume was born in Nishijin.
Of course, all the women
who work in Shimabara say that.
After she left Shimabara,
she saved up a fortune
and married the master
of the Hishiya on Yonjo Street.
She's 25 years old, charming, pretty,
and they say she saved the business.
She was born beautiful,
married a wealthy widower,
and now she's Serizawa's favorite, too,
so she's gotten full of herself.
Basically, she got lucky
and had an easy life.
Anyway, she's nothing special.
Really?
L-Let go.
Let go!
Give me that!
Really?
Is she really a woman
we can afford to ignore?
No. Whatever she is,
she's anything but ordinary.
You got sold. You've got nowhere to run.
Come on. Where's the harm?
You can't even bear children.
The nerve of her.
She's only a second wife.
So what if she's a little pretty?
You go collect the debt.
Even the Miburo will go easy on a woman.
Oume, listen. They'll come
to kill me sooner or later.
What will you do?
It seemed like a golden opportunity.
I'd get my revenge on all of you.
Don't assume a woman
will take your abuse lying down.
Don't assume you can keep
taking from me forever.
I've always wanted to strike back.
To show you that I don't accept this world.
You made it by brute force, didn't you?
Just the way you like it!
Their weakness is women and children.
Women? I know just the one.
And this is how it turned out.
You don't know a thing!
You don't scare me.
What's the difference...
between me turning my sword on her
and Serizawa endangering the city?
How are we different?
A legacy of suffering
leads up to this moment.
A world will come when all women
avenge themselves on all men.
Remember that!
Crap. This woman wasn't part of my plan.
What's the matter? Come on!
Kill me if you can!
She doesn't care who she fights as long
as it's a man? What sense does that make?
I'll kill you!
Damn it!
She's so weak.
Your heart's not in it, Oume.
You'll never kill anyone like that.
Quiet, you!
Once I kill them, you're next!
Oh, right. I'm on your hit list, too.
But you're still one of the better ones.
You didn't flinch when
you heard how I felt.
You offered me this chance.
You treated me as an equal.
That makes you better than most.
You don't sympathize,
but you don't flatter me, either.
Thanks.
Hijikata-san, you're slipping.
She isn't who I should be
turning my sword on.
Hijikata-san.
Hijikata-san!
You hypocritical bastard!
You look down on people
more than anyone!
What? What does she mean?
I'm fed up with men like you
who make a show of being just and kind!
You leave the worst messes of the lot!
Soji!
Don't say another word.
Not so fast.
Now you get it.
What? Am I the only one
who doesn't understand?
Move! I'll do it myself!
Die!
Hijikata-san, you're wrong.
If someone asked me what moment
in my life I'd like to relive,
I know what I'd tell them.
Cherry blossoms.
How pretty those weeping cherries were.
Oh, yes. They were as red as blood.
Where did I see them?
I did it. I had the last fight of my life
with the most feared men
in the city of Kyoto.
Oh, what a thrill.
I fought.
Are you a demon?
Have you no heart, Okita?
But well done.
To think you'd cut through Oume
to strike at my blind spot...
You let your guard down, Serizawa-san.
Hijikata-san, she'd entered the arena.
Man or woman, weak or strong,
it makes no difference.
That's why she was angry.
The only person here who hesitated
when push came to shove...
was you.
Ma, I'm scared.
It's all right.
We'll be all right, so keep still.
What technique. What spirit.
Truly magnificent.
Serizawa-san.
I'd be lucky to beat you three times
out of ten in a fair fight.
I doubt I can land a blow
except by surprise.
And we can't afford to draw this out
anymore or to lose anyone.
I'll just have to risk it.
Two swords, is it?
The Arena
Next time
Yamanami Keisuke, at your service.
They certainly outwitted us.
I can see Niimi-san didn't give his life
to this plot for nothing.
Do all those prepared to die
make such fearsome opponents?
You've brought that lesson home to me.
But we, too, bear the Miburo's future
on our shoulders.
We must succeed at all costs.
Next time: "A Clumsy Strike."
A Clumsy
Strike