Stand up, Kizuki.
If you still love Mizuho, you need
to take a stand once more.
That's right.
Back then, I fell for the Kizuki
that only looked forward.
Welcome in!
One peperoncino pasta, one carbonara,
one grapefruit juice,
and one order of iced tea please—
Oh, uh.
Per... Per favore?
Si, grazie.
What kind of iced tea, Mizuho?
Milk? Lemon? Straight?
Shoot!
I forgot to ask!
I'll go ask right now!
Your apron's loose.
What am I going to do with you?
Thanks.
Ah, youth.
Hey, Mizuho-chan?
Yes?
You know you can work part-time here
in the off-seasons too, right?
Dad!
Honey! Stop grinning like a fool
and start cooking!
Oh, right.
I'll cook your free meal
in a bit, Mizuho-chan.
You can head home
after you eat that with Syugo.
Yay! I love your Margherita!
You need to work your worth for that.
You can count on it!
I didn't realize the Mitsushima Beach
fireworks festival was today.
Yeah.
By the way, you're
working too many shifts.
Don't push yourself, okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Kizuki's giving it his all
for his competitions.
I need to save up enough to cheer
for him outside the prefecture!
I can't believe it's the last year.
I hope he makes it to the inter-highs.
Yeah!
Maybe I'll pay Kizuki a visit
to see him sobbing
when he doesn't beat the standard scores.
I'm sure he'll make it this year!
Whoa! Amazing!
You can see them so clearly!
How did you know about this place?
Toya.
Hey. Why did you invite me out today?
Because I told you that
I was rejected by Kizuki?
It's like you said, Toya.
Kizuki accepted everything about me.
He's a great guy after all.
I really like myself right now.
Thanks, Toya.
I don't deserve your gratitude.
Sorry.
I know I said I wouldn't
lay my hands on you.
But I take it back.
Forget about that guy.
I like you.
I don't know if I could
ever forget about Kizuki.
That doesn't matter.
Kizuki. Hold on.
Huh?
This won't take long.
The others should be here soon, too.
Kizuki? You here?
We brought something good for ya.
Here you go.
A little something from all of us.
We were talking about how we wanted
to root for you for working so hard.
Thank you! I'm so happy.
What's inside?
Something you'll like.
It's a surprise.
What could it be?
You doing all right? You've been
cramming a lot of practice lately.
Yup.
It's a lot, but I've been able to
shorten my time thanks to that.
I'm even doing an interview
for a swimming magazine soon.
Seriously? Cool!
You've been working so hard, Kizuki.
Yeah. I really want to
make it to the inter-highs.
And you will.
Thanks!
Okay, I'm heading out now!
Yup.
The next time we can all meet would have
to be after the inter-highs are decided.
You're right.
Wanna grab a bite somewhere
before we go home?
Sounds like a plan!
Shin, you're coming too, right?
I'll tag along for a bit.
What about you, Airu?
Sorry. I'm gonna pass!
Huh? Do you have a photoshoot today?
Nope.
But I need to stop by
somewhere after this.
There! Done!
Well?
It took some time,
but I think I did a great job!
Come on! Eat up!
Is it good?
C'mon. What's your rating?
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Yay!
I'm gonna eat, too.
Bon appétit!
And then Kizuki told us he's
gonna be featured in a magazine!
Isn't that cool?
All eyes are on him as an athlete.
Here!
Happy Birthday, Toya.
Thanks.
Are you able to spend time
with me this weekend, too?
Yeah. I don't have anything
planned on the weekend, so—
Sorry, I need to take this.
Hello?
A "thank you" for the gift?
You don't have to do that.
What? This weekend?
You're free for a whole day, Kizuki?
We should totally hang!
Is there anywhere you wanna go?
Okay. We can plan more at school.
Later.
Do you not even realize that
since the moment you hung out with me,
all you do is talk about him?
Sorry, I just subconsciously...
Subconsciously, huh?
I'm such an idiot.
There's no way I could
forget about Kizuki.
What a pathetic face.
Even though I'm the one who hurt him.
I was so awkward back then.
Airu.
It's done. Come help.
Yeah!
Now then!
To celebrate the long awaited reunion
of the Koigahama Highlands crew...
Cheers!
Hold on! Why is it just you guys?!
Shin's at work.
I don't know about Kizuki.
Are you still fighting with Kizuki?
Such a stubborn four-eyes!
I'm going back to England
starting next week, too.
What? Stay longer!
Hurry up and leave.
I wanted to say something
to everyone before I flew off.
What is it?
I'm getting married.
M... Married?
Yup.
Well, since my boyfriend and I
have Japanese nationalities,
we can't get "married" for real.
I wanted you all to approve of him
as my partner now that we live together.
That's amazing! Congratulations, Airu!
Thanks. I knew you'd approve, Mizuho.
What's he like?
Introduce us next time.
Yeah.
He's super on top of things.
He knows pretty much
everything about the five of us
since I talk about us a lot.
But one day I hope we can get married
just like everyone else in Japan.
We ended up drinking until morning.
It's a celebration.
But who would have thought one of
us would be talking about marriage?
We're really adults now.
Yummy!
Your pizzas really are the best!
Grazie!
What?
You need to hurry and learn how
to make pizza as great as me.
Why should I? You're here to do that.
You're still a kid, Syugo.
If you win over Mizuho-chan's stomach,
there's a chance she'll
be your bride. You know?
Huh?
If you like her, put in the effort.
Nothing will progress
if you don't make a move.
Mizuho...
Hm? Did you say my name?
Nah, never mind.
You're so weird, Syugo.
Inter-High Participant
Kizuki Hazawa
So cool!
He's so tall!
I'm really sad that I couldn't
make it to the finals at the inter-high.
I'm going to make up
for this disappointment
when I go to university.
Despite that,
what a fantastic performance!
Now then...
The news finally made it
to the local TV station.
So mega popular.
He's basically a star. A star.
The world's come to notice Kizuki.
His future's pretty much set now.
"A bright swimmer of the future."
What a guy.
Where are you going for uni, Syugo?
I'll just go to a school I qualify for,
start randomly looking for jobs,
and become a basic
salary man or something.
I don't really have anything I want to do.
You have it good, Airu.
Being popular and all.
This is just an illusion.
I need to find something
to be passionate about.
What about you, Chika-chan?
I'll go to pharmacy school
and be a pharmacist.
Careers with qualifications are best.
We're got a realist here!
Um, excuse me!
Do you guys know if Kizuki Hazawa-kun
in the swim club has a girlfriend?
Um, about that...
Don't look. Let's go.
Y-Yeah.
Shin-chan's so cool.
Ugh! Togo!
Yo.
Hoshikawa-sensei,
you don't even teach here.
What are you doing here
in the middle of the day?
Were you fired already?
Shut up.
I'm running errands. Come with me, Syugo.
What? Is Dad making us run errands again?
Later, Syugo!
Man. You're the worst
with social interactions.
You know I'm busy with exams.
Syugo. I need you to calmly listen to me.
Hm?
Dad's dead.
The Late Goro Hoshikawa
Funeral Hall
Thank you so much.
I'm so sorry.
You guys are suffering the most...
Sir...
Thanks for putting up
with that dad of mine.
Syugo didn't even cry...
Yeah...
Was I able to do anything for you...
when your mom passed away?
Of course you did!
Because you guys stuck
by my side like usual...
I was able to be happy.
But...
Mom...
What can I do for Syugo?
How long has this place
been in business again?
About 20 years?
I'm sure Mom wants
to keep this place running.
Temporarily Closed
Sorry for the inconvenience.
I...
The last thing I told Dad was,
"I don't need breakfast."
He put in the effort to make his
special sunny-side up eggs for me.
To think those were
my last words to him...
Is that so...
Togo, I...
I'm not applying to colleges anymore.
I'm going to culinary school
and take over the business.
Syugo...
No. Go to college.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take over the restaurant.
Huh?
I've already put in my resignation
letter to the school.
Wh-What's with that?!
You were finally able to be a teacher,
like you've always wanted!
Why are you giving up?!
I'll take over the restaurant!
It's not like I have ambitions
like Kizuki and the others...
It's all right, Syugo.
I'm the only one that can do it.
Right now, I'm the one who can take
care of Dad's restaurant and Mom.
You'll understand
when you're a little older.
We can manage by hiring
a chef for a while.
You just focus on yourself.
Go to college.
Don't worry.
You'll find what you want to do someday.
Sup, Mizuho.
Finished with school?
Yup. What about you, Syugo?
We finished cleaning up the shop.
I wanted to finish it much sooner, though.
I guess we're still kids after all.
What?
I told Togo that I'll stop taking
exams so I can take over the restaurant.
Then he said that I needed to go
to school and chased me away.
He's always messing around, but when
it comes to this, he gets so mature.
You have a tendency of focusing
on the things around you, Syugo.
That's why you look into others' hearts
instead of thinking about
what you want to do.
I think Togo understands that
you deeply care about your family
and it made him happy.
That's just my take, considering you
always see right through me.
Why so serious?
The weather's nice.
Hey, Mizuho.
Is heaven...
really somewhere out there?
Hey, Mom!
Take good care of Syugo's dad!
Syugo's dad!
Please make pizzas for my mom!
A Margherita pizza with extra tomatoes!
Do you think your dad heard me?
Are you stupid?
I know!
I made this for you.
What is it?
A good luck charm.
So that many good things
come to you from now on.
You're my precious
three-star chef, after all.
You really are a...
Keep this a secret from Kizuki.
Just for a minute.
Yeah.
Hey, Syugo.
You know how in stories they say
"Even when they die,
they live on in people's hearts"?
Whenever I'm drawing,
I can hear my mom's voice in my head
saying, "Wow, you drew so well, Mizuho!"
Because I wanted to hear
that voice over and over again...
Even after the mourning period, I didn't
go to school and kept drawing at home.
Can you hear him too, Syugo?
Your dad's voice?
Syugo!
Have some breakfast!
Here, sunny-side up eggs!
You can do it, my precious son!
Your flavors are so
straightforward and pleasant.
I can hear him.
Sorry, we already made our last orders—
Why are you here? Leave.
Syugo...
I'm busy right now.
About before... I'm sorr—
I was at fault.
Your favorite dry tomato panini.
No broccoli.
I'm sorry for hitting you.
That was delicious. Thank you.
I'll help with the dishes.
'Kay.
I'm glad I came here
and talked with you, Syugo.
Good luck with your return match, Kizuki.
Even if you hit a setback,
don't disappear on us again.
Yeah.
If it doesn't work out, then I'll come
back like I used to in the past.
I'll be like your little brother
and come crying back to you.
You're really dazzling. It makes me sick.
Here.
Whoa!
There, there. Don't cry.
I'm not crying yet.
You know, I...
I decided a long time ago
that I'd watch over you and Mizuho.
But...
Can I tell Mizuho about my feelings?
Kizuki. Even though I'm the third-lead,
I want you to take me on.
I've never once thought of you
as the third-lead, Syugo.
It's on.
# 21 The Declaration