Usaneko Club
Produced by: Usaneko Anime Production Dept.
Kirara-san...
There's someone I've taken
an interest in lately-usa.
The more I try not to think about her,
the more I think about her anyway.
Because of that, I can no longer
do things I used to be able to do.
I feel like such an airhead.
What is happening to me?
M...
Memeru...
So precious!
It pains my heart!
Oh, Memeru.
Precious girl...
Another episode that soothes the soul.
Mimimi's smile was more
mischievous than usual...
Huh? Mimimi?!
Usa-nya!
So?
Who will you choose?
Pardon the Intrusion, I'm Home!
Rinko Nakama
So anyway, this is my
sister Mao. She's visiting.
Hmm...
The more I look at her, the more
I see the resemblance.
Well, I did model Mimimi after her.
Really? No wonder!
Oh! It's Magi Merm!
Magical Mermaid
Whoa! You have the whole set!
Do you like Magi Merm, too?
Yeah!
I like the stuff that's on air now, too,
but back when I watched the
whole series on streaming,
my absolute faves were the Misaki sisters!
Magi Merm can really pull you in!
The Misaki sisters are super close,
and their link outfits are so cute!
And their magical pens match!
Uh-huh!
So does their Dream Color
during their Jewelry Time!
And also when the two of them
combine their power for...
Marble Star! Happy Happy Mode!
I totally get you!
Not to mention their
fairy-summoning smooth hair!
Whoosh!
I'm not following.
Usa! Nya! Usa! Nya! Usa-usa—
What's up?
Tada-Oja.
Search
Making Big Robots! Huge Robot Technology
Hormones for relaxing.
Hugs Can Release Relaxation Hormones...
Great Effects! Stress Reduction Through Embraces...
The Hug Effect | Hugs can activate immune cells...
Don't be Fooled! A Hug's...
Stress reduction.
Immune cells activate due
to their healing effects.
I guess that makes sense.
Satsuki-san was tired then.
That's why he...
Relaxing...
Healing effects...
But I'm losing my mind from a hug!
Can neighbors affect it, too?
Big Bro Haru!
Yeah?
Big Sis Rinko's great, huh?
Uh, sure.
I mean, this is fifteen years old!
Can I really have it?
Uh-huh.
Crush?
I'll take good care of this!
I'm glad I can pass it down to a new
generation of Magi Merm fans.
My classmates don't know older series,
so I'm happy I got to talk to you about
the greatness of the Misaki sisters!
Mao-chan...
Big Sis...
Well, get home safe.
Uh-huh!
Bye, Big Bro Haru, Big Sis!
Usaharu-sensei, it's time for dinner.
Huh?
Oh. I'll eat later.
Oh, okay...
Usaharu-sensei's been acting weird lately.
A crush?
Yup!
The Memeru episode that
just aired was a huge hit!
So the crush arc in the manga
the ep was based on
has been getting attention, too!
Oh, now that you mention it, readers kept
mentioning it on the questionnaire, too.
I wanna read something that
dives deeper into that plot!
So let's write a continuation
of that, Sensei!
There's no continuation
to that storyline.
Besides, there's something else I wanna—
What?!
You can't write it?!
Huh?!
But you're a genius mangaka, right?!
The acclaimed Usaharu-sensei won't do it?!
No way!
Wait, hold up!
I don't want to hear Usaharu-sensei
say stuff like tha—
Editor Kaneko
I just...
don't know anything
about having a crush.
Could this be...
love?!
Tada-Oja!
A crush, you say?
Frankly, I don't have a clue
what the big deal is.
I've never had a crush on anyone before.
Having a crush is just
a huge inconvenience!
My assistants have gotten
into fights over me before.
We couldn't finish
our work because of it.
Yikes... That's one heck of a backstory.
I only hired you 'cause
you're already taken.
I'm sorry it's all fake.
People with crushes need to
stop beating around the bush
and just ask them out already!
If you get dumped, move on!
But...
I don't think Memeru is that kind of girl.
I know that!
You're absolutely right!
Tada-Oja!
Usaharu-sensei is in full-focus
mode again tonight,
so I came over here.
You're more than welcome here.
You're my girlfriend, after all.
Sure...
Writer's block isn't that rare.
Writers and artists
aren't gods, after all.
Lunch is ready!
Leave it there.
Would you like to eat together?
You should eat, even just a little...
Shut up!
What's your deal?!
Are you my editor?! My mom?!
Or my girlfriend or something?!
I'm your disciple!
I'm also your chef-sistant!
It's my duty to make sure you eat!
I'll say whatever I have to so that you
can be healthy and write your manga!
I'm not hungry.
Then sleep!
I'm not tired!
Then go take a bath!
Tada-Oja!
Is it too hot?
Feels good.
I think he's calmed down a little.
I want Usaharu-sensei to go
back to his energetic self.
But what can I possibly do?
What's with you all of a sudden?
Hugs are good when you're tired.
Isn't that more for couples?
Y-You're right.
What? Do you like me or something?
I love you very much!
It's a problem when my
assistants fall for me, though.
As your faithful follower!
Thank you for bringing
Usaneko Club to life!
I'll forever be grateful!
These are some wild pick-up lines.
Rinko, maybe you...
like me more than that guy?
Huh?
Absolutely not.
Satsuki-san!
Nakama-san...
What exactly are you doing?
Yo. Your girlfriend's cheating on you.
Ch-Cheating?
I'm s-s-sorry!
I wasn't cheating or anything!
Calm down.
I know I'm the one you really love.
Um...
I...
Sorry. I know you have trouble
saying it in front of others.
Then you can just nod for me.
I'm the only one you love, right?
Satsuki-san is too amazing.
He gives off such boyfriend energy!
Good job.
Whoa! Satsuki-san!
H-He's being such an exemplary boyfriend!
What am I being forced to watch?
As you can see, Nakama-san
is obsessed with me.
E-Eep...
Tch.
Why'd she hug me, then?
I'm sure she simply wanted
to relieve your stress.
Exactly! I had no ulterior
motives whatsoever!
I was just wondering how I could help
you with your manuscript writing!
Well, whatever.
Just don't come to me crying
"we broke up becuse of you" later.
It'd leave a bad aftertaste.
Don't worry. We love each other.
Anyway...
How's your progress going,
Mr. Writer's Block?
What was that?
Let's take this outside!
S-Sensei!
Fine. Let's go.
Huh?
Eh?
What you need now is a walk.
It's not good for you to stay inside
hunched over your desk.
Instead of toiling away
with your brain, walk.
Unravel the stressors
in your brain by walking.
You didn't know this even as a creator?
Take a moment to put aside
any work that involves thinking.
I see! So you need to enjoy a walk?
I can help with that—
Nakama-san and I are
only here to chaperone.
Tsk.
It's so friggin' bright and too damn cold.
Also, I don't have writer's block.
I can write whatever I want at any time.
Damn it.
What's the big deal with crushes?
I'm freezing.
The slide! The slide!
Did you know I can go down the slide?
Wow, that's amazing!
I'm not scared of slides!
When did the wind get so cold?
Hey, no running!
There, there.
That was scary, huh?
I'm not... scared of the slide.
Aw. So close.
Let's go to the slide sometime, okay?
Well, I guess...
I can feel my brain unwinding.
But y'know, Memeru...
I still don't get how you feel.
Belonging to someone else sounds
like the most annoying crap ever.
Why bother falling for someone?
Usaharu-sensei!
Here!
Corn Potage
Thanks.
Sensei, do you remember episode 43?
I guess there was
an episode like that.
Sukoko won a whole bunch for
free from a vending machine!
She was so cute trying to get the last
corn kernel from her hundredth can!
Oh, yeah.
Ah!
This ginkgo leaf reminds me
of Mimimi from episode 112!
They drew everyone's faces
on gingko leaves.
And when Mimimi saw it, she said,
"That's not what my face looks like!"
She's so damn cute.
and threw a fit.
Rin—
Nakama-san!
I'm sorry! I disturbed you when
you shouldn't be thinking at all!
I'll take my leave!
Based on my whole life experience,
the reason Rinko looks so cute...
is probably because
she likes me after all.
Girls get cuter when they're
near the person they like.
Well, in Rinko's case, it's probably
my manga that she's in love with.
But same difference, right?
If she likes my manga, then she likes me.
Am I wrong?
Who makes a face like that at
someone they're not in love with?
Okay. One more time.
If Rinko catches me looking at her, then
turns around and smiles one more time...
It proves that she's
totally in love with me.
One more time...
If she turns around one more time...
Why isn't she turning around?!
Even after being all suggestive?!
What's with her?
Read the room!
You're making me feel this way...
Feel this way?
Feel this way?!
So this is it?
I see...
I can totally write this stuff.
Usaharu-sensei!
What's wrong?!
Do you feel sick?!
The...
"The"?
The baby's coming...
Are you in labor?!
Shit, the head's already out...
A-Are you giving birth to a story?
Memeru coincidentally shows up there...
And then Kirara...
But Kirara doesn't notice...
There!
It's coming...
Please hold on a little longer!
This...
This is...
This is what having a crush is!
That's why I can't
forget you!
Right, Memeru?!
It's done.
Already?!
You're amazing!
It's no sweat.
Congratulations on your birth!
You worked so hard!
Looks like you got something
out thanks to the walk.
Huh?
It's because I'm a genius, duh!
You really are amazing!
We were taking the same paths,
drinking the same drinks...
But you were able to give
birth to a whole story!
You really are a god, Usaharu-sensei!
You could say that.
Your "god" wasn't even able to eat
a decent meal until a while ago.
I wanna go home and eat Rinko's cooking.
O-Of course!
Let's have something warm!
Always by your side
Seven Mart
I'll go handle the grocery shopping first!
I'll go with you.
This is my job as the chef-sistant,
so please wait here.
Tada-Oja.
So how long have you two been together?
Frankly, you don't seem that close.
You're not even on a first-name basis.
So how'd you start dating? Who asked who?
Usada.
Didn't you say having
a crush is inconvenient?
Don't try unless you're serious.
I only wanted to chat
about your love life.
So? How's it going?
You guys do it yet?
Usada!
For a glasses-type character,
you've got quite a violent streak.
Am I right, Satsukiller-sensei?
I know I said not to break up
because of me, but I take it back.
Forget I said it.
Name
Rinko
Job
Location
Stats
Teacher
School
INT\h
Royalty
Castle
Elegance
Maid
Mansion
Kindness
Adventurer
Mountains
Luck
Witch
Forest
Beauty
Chef-sistant
Apartments
Otaku
Begin?
Translation: Karen Bildsoe
Rinko
Chef-sistant
Subtitle Timing:
Mariana Martinez
Editing & Typesetting: Elisabeth Crist
Quality Check: Geoff Mazzolini
Translation Check: Becky Cottrill
Rinko
Chef-sistant
Otaku
Rinko
Chef-sistant
Otaku
Rinko
Chef-sistant
Continue
Quit
Add to party?
Yes
No
Rinko
Chef-sistant
Otaku
Rinko
Chef-sistant
Otaku
Rinko
Chef-sistant
Otaku
Rinko
Chef-sistant
Otaku
Continue
Quit
Let's see...
I'll get fishcakes, too.
Oh! Green onions are cheap!
What a good deal!
Lucky me!
Next Episode
This Is a Work of Fiction, Okay?!
Next episode:
"This Is a Work of Fiction, Okay?!"