That's what you're into?
Yeah.
Huh, so guys like that are your type, eh?
Huh?
Hmm?
It's the song I like.
Oh.
I feel you.
Why do parents say stuff like that?
It's not like we're fantasizing
about dating them.
Right?
You know how I'm more
into girls? Like idols?
Apparently, my parents think
I want to become one.
No way!
They totally don't get it.
They're full of contradictions.
Our parents and teachers, I mean.
I know.
Asa.
You can do whatever you want.
Be whoever you want to be.
I hope I don't become an adult like that.
For sure!
I'll always be on your side.
Okay, Asa?
Oh yeah, could you pick up some
toilet paper on your way home?
Okay.
Mom used to do that too.
She'd always stand that way when I left.
Maybe we got it from our mom.
Hey, can I color my hair?
Huh? What gives?
Emiri told me I should.
No, not that. I meant you
don't need my permission.
As long as your school's
fine with it, go ahead.
Go Club
Band Club
Tea Club
Takumi-san, right?
We're in the same class.
Oh, Mori-san. You can call me Asa.
Cool. Call me Mori, then.
Have you decided?
Nuh-uh. What about you?
I dunno...
Were you in any clubs in middle school?
Choir.
Why not join that?
Apparently, the choir club's good here.
You pick yet?
Not yet.
Not that I really care...
Yeah, same.
I wonder how everyone else decides.
Aren't you interested in anything?
Um...
I used to be in the badminton club.
Not that.
Okay, then...
Oh, how about choir?
You like to sing, don't you, Asa?
Remember your fourth grade choir contest?
You worked so hard for that.
Choir, huh?
It's settled.
Mom knows best.
I say the checkered shirt.
No, we had tomatoes yesterday.
You still haven't decided?
Then I'll pick for you.
It's not in there, Asa.
You've got to learn how
to make choices on your own.
Good grief. What did you do to your hair?
You look like a boy.
That's so cute!
You look great, Asa!
You're the only one who likes it.
What? You mean your parents don't?
Guess not. I'll have to convince them.
How?
Well, I guess during
spring break, I'll just...
A car crash!
Should we call the police? An ambulance?
What happened?
Man, that doesn't look good...
Someone get an employee here!
It's not like we can decide
on the spot, you know?
Catch ya later.
Yeah, sure...
What's this feeling? I don't
know why, but I'm irritated.
At what, though?
I can't tell...
Smoke was coming out
of her sewing machine!
How is that even possible?
Emiri!
I'm serious!
But up and...
She isn't here anymore,
you know? Your mom.
...dying like that...
Asa.
...was her own...
Be whoever you want to be.
...fault.
Liar.
...was her own fault.
I'll always be...
___________________________
Contradicting yourself.
Screw you.
Journal with Witch
Makio Koudai
Makio Koudai...
Shuuei Blue Bunko Online
Works by Makio Koudai - "Sisal Twins"
"Dragon Charmer Series" "Magician Series" New Volumes
Tuwiiter
Makio Koudai - Novelist. "Magician Series"
now available through Blue Bunko.
Wiki Page
Makio Koudai
Debut Work: Sisal Twins
Amazom.co.jp
Makio Koudai: Books Delivery Today
Whoa.
Call
Just now
Grandma: Missed Call
Episode 5\h\h\h\h\h\hDecide
What?
To Grandma's. Next Saturday.
You mean you want to go?
She seemed worried when I called,
and I used to go with Mom all the time.
I probably haven't been
home in over five years.
Why not?
Huh? Just because.
Okay, let's go.
Koudai
My, my. Welcome, Asa-chan.
Have you been taking care of her?
I suppose.
Let's have some tea. I bought some cake.
Thanks for having me.
I'll go sort through my stuff first.
At least sit down for a cup of tea.
That one cup of tea takes forever.
I'll make some myself if I get thirsty.
Goodness.
She's a cold one, isn't she?
Don't be like her.
Now, come on in here.
You're still reading kid stuff like that?
You used to read it too.
Obviously not anymore.
Then I'll never let you borrow mine again!
Fine by me!
I don't enjoy all these
memories rushing back.
Hey, don't you take a right here?
There's definitely a hidden path.
Watch out! They're coming!
Sis, be quiet!
Go right! They're gonna get you!
Both of you, sit further
away from the TV!
What about college?
Have you decided?
I only just started high school, Grandma.
Oh, right. Of course.
Minori and Makio both chose early,
so I couldn't help myself.
My mom did?
Sure did. Minori was always
my best listener.
We used to chat together all the time.
Unlike, you know...
I'll go help Makio-chan.
You don't want to relax a bit longer?
I'll be right back.
Makio-chan?
Mom—
Asa?
Something wrong?
You've been in my sister's
room before, right?
Why not take something back if you want?
Did something come up with my mom?
Not really.
Okay.
Do you hate Grandma too, Makio-chan?
I don't hate everyone, you know...
But I have to admit...
she's become dull and snide.
Maybe it's because we left home, Dad died,
and she began spending more time alone.
Dull and snide...
Before, she used to compliment us.
She'd say Minori was caring,
and I was self-sufficient.
But somewhere along the line,
it turned into Minori lacking
independence and me being cold.
And that made me sad.
But I remember Grandma saying...
How could you die before your own mother?
She cried so much.
I remember thinking she
really cared about Mom.
If you felt that, that's what matters.
I wonder what Mom was really like.
What she used to think about...
That's not something you'd know
even if she were alive.
Because we're two different people?
Asa...
Remember her as the mother you love.
I don't share my subjective
view of her for that reason.
Guess I'll go have some tea.
Huh, so this is what she was into.
Asa.
Be whoever you want to be.
I will be the person I want to be.
So take that.
Journal with Witch
Koudai
Take this home with you. Go on!
I don't have anywhere to put it.
Just take it.
It's fine, really. Really.
I swear. You're always like this.
She cried so much.
Asa-chan, take care of yourself.
I'm off.
I'm off too.
Have a good day.
Watch out for cars, both of you.
Makio, you too.
Healthy habits, okay?
Mom...
Sis and I...
We were beyond repair.
So I can't share in the sadness you feel.
But if you ever need it,
I can at least lend an ear.
You always throw in some
unnecessary comment.
I doubt someone who's
barely hanging on herself
has the capacity to hear
anyone else's struggles.
Work together with Asa-chan
and live healthily, okay?
Is it that obvious?
Who do you think raised you?
You're not answering?
It's a number I don't recognize.
I settled on the craft club!
Excited
How about you? Have you decided?
Asa!
Morning.
Hey, do you have gym class today?
Why? Did you forget your jersey?
Nailed it.
I got you.
Thanks.
Hey, have you picked a club?
Nara-san, morning.
Morning.
This your friend?
Yeah, she's in Class B.
I'm Takumi.
I'm Sakurai.
See ya later.
So, hey, Ozawa asked you out
at graduation, right?
Huh? How do you know that?
Taka-chan told me.
You don't want a boyfriend?
Yeah... I dunno.
Did you go anywhere during Golden Week?
Nope. How about you, Koudai-san?
No, me neither.
And what about your little niece?
About that... I'm sorry
for needing to take time off.
Not at all!
It was a nice surprise
to get some time off myself.
So, regarding the cover for volume 2...
Do you have any ideas?
Actually, I had a design in mind.
I'd love to hear it as well.
Don't mind me if it's no good.
You know that scene where
Tol and Saika look over the map?
Oh, that one?
Here's what I'm thinking.
Emiri, here's my jersey.
Aw, thanks!
I can take it home and wash it.
Nah, I need it for fifth period.
You're a lifesaver.
Hi there.
Hiya.
See you at lunch?
Sure.
Sorry to keep you.
They sure make a splash, don't they?
Yeah. Weird, since Tamashiro-san
was bullied in middle school.
Wait, who?
The short-haired girl.
Huh...
So she made it in the cool circle.
She'll be safe now.
Look, if I had a face like hers,
I'd totally be cool with bullying.
Are you serious?
Asa!
You're wearing makeup.
I had a meeting. Then grabbed
coffee with friends.
You seem kinda tired.
Can you tell? I had to talk a lot.
Kasamachi-kun's coming over,
so let's grab stuff on the way home.
Nice!
Wait, Taiwan? And you're going?
It was Daigo's idea.
No real plans yet. Just talking.
Koudai-san.
Yes...?
Attorney
Sabanai Law Firm
I'm Tono. I oversee the guardianship.
We met once over the life
insurance policy paperwork.
Oh, did we?
Pardon me for not remembering.
Don't mind me.
More importantly,
I've called several times.
Have you been busy?
Well, I... didn't recognize the number.
And I've been working, so...
I see. Now, to get to business...
Right.
Regarding this copy of Asa-san's bankbook
you provided the other day...
Oh! I'm sorry for the late reply on that.
That's fine. About the document, though...
Account
Opened
Deposit
Cash
Automatic
\hTransfer
Cash card
On April 30th, there was a
withdrawal of 300,000 yen.
Can you explain what that was for?
Th-Three hundred thousand yen?!
In cash?
Yes.
F-From my sister and her husband's estate?
Yes, as I just said.
Do you have a receipt
for this transaction?
No...
Any records in a household
account book will suffice.
As I explained before, Koudai-san...
As guardian, you'll be obligated
to submit income and expenditure
reports from now on.
S-Sorry, I haven't been able to...
I assumed you were aware of this entry
when you submitted the bankbook to me.
Or were you not?
W-Wait. C-Could you slow down a bit?
All this at once is scaring me.
Scaring you?
I'm sorry about that.
I haven't touched this account other than
for school expenses and her allowance.
All our daily expenses
come from my account.
And I've set up an automatic
transfer for her allowance.
\hAutomatic
Transfer
Cash
Deposit
Cash card
Asa Takumi
I'd forget otherwise.
So to address your point...
I'm sorry. I didn't notice this when
I sent a copy of the bankbook.
So I have no clue what this
300,000 yen is about...
Pardon me.
I did come at you a bit aggressively.
I was so focused on the rights of
the child that I got too heated.
And since you wouldn't answer my calls,
I took you for the shameless sort.
The shameless sort
I'm sorry for being so shameless...
Oh, I didn't mean that! I apologize!
No, it's fine. I just can't do normal
things like a normal person.
It was a computer.
I bought a computer. A Mac laptop.
What?!
Was this something you needed for school?
No.
Did someone tell you to buy it?
Asa?
What's wrong?
I thought I could make some
music myself with a laptop.
That you might be against me
joining the band club.
What? But I told you...
Asa-san, has Koudai-san ever
restricted your actions before?
No.
How you feel is no one's
business but yours.
No one has the right
to shame you for it.
No matter what.
Never. Not in the slightest.
But she's an adult, so...
I thought she might say no.
...was her own fault.
Be whoever you want to be.
___________________________
I just felt... so confused...
Eel
I'm sorry...
Asa, we should talk about this,
but some other time.
Why not go rinse your face?
I told her she could join
the band club if she wanted.
But she said her parents
wouldn't like it.
She seems to be in the
midst of finding herself.
Understandable for her age,
even barring the circumstances.
If you ever need to talk to someone
not Koudai-san or a teacher,
please feel free reach out.
Oh, okay.
If there's anything I can do,
let me know.
I don't have much experience,
so this is my first time
meeting someone like you.
Someone like me
Someone like me...
Wait, I'm sorry! I just meant your job!
Doesn't answer calls
Barely makes deadlines
Someone who doesn't answer calls
and barely makes deadlines...
I'm here to support you
and your life together!
So, please...
Allow me to help from now on.
Sure, thank you.
Hi, Kasamachi-kun. Come on in.
Hey... I brought some oysters.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Tono, an attorney.
Do you happen to be Koudai-san's
significant other?
Eel
I have to return the laptop
A Mac, huh?
I'll buy it, if you want.
That would just make
things more complicated.
You're right.
But man, an attorney?
Tired?
Yeah... You could say that.
Just pretend you're getting
hugged by a big dog.
A Bernese Mountain Dog.
That big?
This reminds me, I did the same
thing to Asa the other day.
I must have picked it up from you.
I think Asa likes this song.
She sings it sometimes.
Asa!
Asa-san!
It's that group you like. They're on TV.
Wanna watch? Come on over.
We're squished.
You like this stuff?
Yeah, I like this song's bass line.
Good taste. You have a fine ear.
You're right.
Makio-chan...
Can I join the band club?
Of course. Do what you want to do.
Yeah, I will.
Right here! This bass line!
Pretty cool.