In the near future, e-Pulse is
generated by human thoughts and emotions,
and used as an energy source
for AI devices called "Sapotamas,"
leading to a new development for humanity.
But from its shadows,
terrifying monsters have appeared.
Monsters that evolve by consuming e-Pulse.
They are...
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
darenimo jama wa sasenai sono saki he
Beyond where no one can stop me
mayoinagara kotae sagashi tsukisusumu
I'll make my way there
As I seek the answer
kizamitsukero Emotion
Carve your emotion
hibiiteiru
It reverberates
tashika ni shinkurosuru Tempo wa
The tempo that synchs
sukoshi zutsu
kakureta sekai abaiteiku hakudou
Is a pulse that slowly reveals
The hidden world
yuraganai Baseline no ue de Rec
Record on top of the solid Baseline
Don't mess up tempo
futsuu ja monotarinee
Normal's not enough for me
Just keep howling, howling!!!
Howling like it's all you've got
shinjiru mono ga nijimisou ni natte mo
Even if what you believe begins to blur
nigirishimeru Riaru wa
uso janaku tsuyoku hibiku
The reality that you grasp
Rings strong and true
Metronome topparau ichido kiri kono JAM
Take away the Metronome
For this one and only JAM
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
kanjou no mama narasu kodou wa
The emotional beat that rings out
sou zutto hashiritsuzukeru BPM
Is the BPM that continues on and on
(Let the beat lead the way)
matenrou nomikomu Cloudy Rain
The Cloudy rain swallows the city
rinkushite rizumu yoretatte
Groove ni shichaeba ii
Even if I link and the rhythm warps
I just make it part of my groove
norikonase omoidoori
Ride it like you see fit
(Let the beat lead the way)
itami daite mo tomarazu ni
Even if it hurts, I won't stop
kizami tsudzukeru kodou
Won't back down
Keep carving the beat
bokura nara donna koto mo norikoerareru
We can overcome anything
tatakitsukero Emotion
Drum to your emotion
I...
My goodness, this is an unexpected
turn of events! The victors are...
Tomoro Tenma and Gekkomon!
Raito!
As I thought...
Everybody!
Tomoro, you better thank
that Hitomi friend of yours later!
Oh?
Kyo Sawashiro?!
I warned him.
Seems he's willing to risk everything
for his so-called "family."
Did someone bring Tomoro Tenma
into this to get Kyo to take action?
A Five Star and a former Five Star.
Let's let them crush each other.
I know.
If I take the easy route, Stella won't...
I know she won't forgive me.
An emergency summons?
THE ONE BESIDE YOU
Paralyze Echo!
Hurry!
We're leaving!
Wait! Raito's still here!
Raito?
We don't have time for that!
They're being Cold Hearted!
The Owners who lose here.
Despicable.
Watch your mouth!
Kyo Sawashiro!
So you showed up... Tactics!
Get up! What are you doing?
Don't let a single intruder escape!
Kanuma, find Raito Souda.
Eliminate on sight. Understood?
Roger.
Hotaruko...
It seems that this encounter
was set up by someone.
But...
now that you've seen our business,
we have to eliminate every one of you.
Gekkomon!
We're gonna rescue Raito, ya know!
Let's go!
Makoto! Reina! Go with Tomoro!
Right!
Let's dig in!
Go!
Pristimon Evolution!
Wolvermon!
You'll pay for laying a hand on my family.
Now's your chance! Scatter Rocket!
-Wolvermon!
-Thanks, ya know!
You're going nowhere.
What a drag.
Forget them!
They're the only ones who can open
a rift out of the Mirror World.
What do you want?
Where's Ketomon?
How should I know? They got dragged away.
What...?
There's something you need to know.
Ludomon!
No butting in!
His blade is even sharper than before.
Perfect...
is what Kyo Sawashiro used to be.
They regenerated?
Stubborn brute!
In that case...
I'll end it in one slash!
Granit!
It's time to follow
the order I once gave you!
Finally.
Gounozan...
Murashigure!
They blocked it?!
That tickles.
Finally... At long last...
Rapid Burst!
Wolvermon!
Give it up.
Are you okay, Wolvermon?
Reina, look!
Huh?
Granit?
What's happening?
No! Stop your attack, Murasamemon!
Kyo?
Granit!
Now...
At last... I can finally die.
Now it's my turn!
Raito!
He ain't here, ya know!
Tomoro, the basement!
Cold Hearted? Every one of them?
Chiropmon's identifying the victims.
They're bounties who went missing.
You?
I'm the one who captured all of them.
Raito!
I'm a genius.
So it was easy.
What's wrong? Fight back!
Is your foolish empathy stopping you?
There's nothing perfect about you!
No. I can't stop it!
So long as they're using Ludomon
as a shield, it drains his e-Pulse.
We need to pry Ludomon off.
You're such a drag.
Just leave me alone.
What are you...?
I'm fine...
with this.
Are you...
the bounty who wiped out my troops?
Will you...
offer me a place to die?
Your life has its uses.
You have my word.
I'll give you a proper place to die.
In return, use your life for me.
If I obey his orders...
I can die properly.
And Stella should forgive me.
What?
Hotaruko told me.
Naito never had any intention
of letting me return.
Laugh!
All my victories were for nothing!
Sure, I'll laugh!
After I get you out of here!
You're still on that?
It's Ketomon.
How did they get here?
They're saying let's run, ya know!
You...
Proganomon! What's it doing here?
What's that voice?
Now that this place is known,
we can't use it for business.
What?
Unnecessary branches...
should be pruned early.
You still plan to use Digimon for profit?
If that's what Sir Klay wishes!
Do it!
Is that really what you want?
To be ordered to die?
It's okay.
Stella...
Reina!
Return!
Stop it!
What?
Rapid Burst!
Stay back!
Let go! Let go of me!
Screw that! Screw orders!
Are you two really okay with this?
It's your life!
Decide for yourself!
Get off!
Wolvermon!
Reina!
Anyone in my way...
must be eliminated!
Fire!
What?!
Ludomon?
You! What are you doing?
A mere Digimon disobeying orders?
Preposterous!
Why do you resist?
Ludomon? Why?
Can't you tell? Ludomon is protecting you!
Just look at them.
They were born to protect.
Protect...
They've been fighting all this time!
Just to protect you!
Me?
Begone!
Ludomon!
You have to fight, too! Granit!
I don't want to be...
alone...
anymore!
No more!
What?!
Ludomon Evolution!
Tialudomon!
So what?
What?!
Granit.
Tialudomon...
This isn't where we die.
You're right.
Insolent brats.
Everyone!
We're leaving!
Murasamemon!
Reina!
Huh? What's wrong, ya know?
Tomoro! Hurry up!
Live to fight another day, ya know!
Honestly, I hate working for nothing.
But we didn't return empty-handed, did we?
I guess not.
Where'd Raito go?
He's not with us.
He...
Everyone.
I'm sorry. It was my fault.
It sure was!
What happened to you?
I got taken into the Mirror World.
It was the Digimon that stole
the Sapotama with Asuka's e-Pulse.
The monkey Digimon.
Sir Klay, look at this.
Gokuwmon.
And...
Is that Kanada?
What's happening?
We've got an emergency!
The client list for the Digimon auction
and the colosseum has been leaked
to the Ministry of Civil Protection!
What?!
How is that possible?
What's going on?
Managing things
with such outdated technology...
What shall we do?
Chairman Wong.
He's crossed the line.
As of this moment, Klay Arslan...
is a bounty!
atarimae wo atarimae ni shinai
Don't let the normal be normal
gakufu doori ja monotarinaindayo
Playing to the score is not enough
noizu sura mo torikonde
jibun dake no sesshon wo!
Take in everything, even the noise
And make it our own session!
hitomakase ja kawaranaishi
Boot! Boot!
Things won't change in others' hands
te nobase
Reach out your hand
machigai mo osorezu susume
Boot! Boot!
Don't be scared to mess up, go on
yuukan ni
With courage
ruuru ni tatakitsukeru NO
error, error
Go tell the rules NO
Error, error
sukeeru auto joutou
error, error
Scale out? Bring it on
Error, error
yosoku funou no koodo
error, error
An unexpected code
Error, error
puronpto nanka ja seigyoudekinai omoide
Prompts can't control these feelings
kamase shauto
Give it a shout
BRAVE! mou kowakunai
BRAVE! No more fear
utsumuitari mo shinai
Keep my head high
senaka azukeaeru kimi ga iru kara
I've got someone who's got my back
GROOVE! mou tomaranai
GROOVE! We can't be stopped
yunizon suru koudou ga
Our beats are in unison
kitto sekaijuu wo appudeeto shiteiku
We're going to update the world
bakuon de
With a bang
You have your family!
You have your Tactics friends!
You have Shakomon!
What's wrong with helping each other?!
Hotaruko, you're not alone.
Even if we can't win individually,
maybe we can win together!
We'll fight together with you...
So...
Next time on DIGIMON BEATBREAK,
"Defiance"