Morning, Milkit.
Good morning, Master.
I'll go get changed.
Sure.
I'll be waiting, Master.
Wait, you'll keep wearing
your bandages?
If they help you feel better, it's fine.
Sorry if I made you uncomfortable.
What if I say I'll take them off
when it's just the two of us?
Just the two of us...
Stare...
Wh-What is it, Eterna?
You look like a teenage boy
on the eve of his first date.
Wh-What kinda comparison is that?
I don't get it at all!
I don't get what's happening either.
Milkit's face is fine now.
I said it was okay
to take the bandages off.
Why, then, is she still bandaged up?
Oh, that? Why indeed...
Ah. I think I get it now.
Something smells nice!
It's a hot sandwich with fried eggs.
You seemed to have taken
a real liking to them, Ink.
Wow! I love you, Milkit!
STAB STAB
What's this stabbing pain in my chest?
My Milkit...
STAB STAB
Rest in peace.
What's wrong, Flum?
Are you all right, Master?
Don't worry about her. She's just
been possessed by her possessiveness.
FAMILY
SOLITUDE
SOLITUDE AND FAMILY
I'm pretty sure
today's job is around here.
What is this stench?
Excuse me. Let me through.
There she found grotesque monsters,
still alive and writhing.
They had arms, legs, and faces,
but none of them were
where they should have been,
and the numbers were all off.
These were but lumps of flesh
that used to be human not long ago.
This way.
Ed and Jonny...
We'll take care of these.
You guys get the crowd away from here.
Huh? But...
We don't want any more panic.
Understood, sir.
Apparently, the Church
is looking into those... things.
On paper, at least.
Normally, church knights from a nearby
station show up when there's an incident.
But those guys today?
Their gear marked them as bein'
way higher up the ladder.
And when I scanned them,
they were pretty much all B-Rank.
They were knights from
the pope's inner circle.
Meanin' those guys were here to cover up
somethin' inconvenient for the Church.
The Church pulled strings
to get a gag order issued.
It was swept under the rug.
This is an extraordinary case,
so they may have just sent powerful
knights because of the danger involved.
We still have absolutely
no clue what those things were.
Is that so...?
Also, you probably shouldn't be
out and about for the time being.
Yeah. Who knows where those
eyeballs could be lyin' in wait?
Eyeballs?
According to witnesses, the victims were
attacked by a large flock of eyeballs.
Eyeballs attacked them...
and turned them into that?
What does that even mean?
And the Church has a gag order out?
Could it be related to
their secret research?
I see! So there really is a Church
research facility in the capital, too!
The Church and its research...
How do I protect myself from that?
"Protect," huh?
Back when I was in the heroes' party,
I'd get targeted first
because I was the weakest.
Cyrill was the one
who'd always bail me out.
Now that I can fight too,
I feel like...
Cyrill must've been
anxious deep down, too.
But if she was,
how was she able to fight like that?
Meanwhile, I get worried sick
that I might not be up to the task.
I don't intend to pick
a fight with the Church.
I just want to protect
the people I care about.
I wonder what Cyrill's up to now.
We failed to reach our
planned destination yet again.
This is all because I'm weak.
You don't need to
feel responsible, Cyrill.
Let Jean stew in his own frustration.
I cast Flum aside, but as soon as she
was gone, I lost the ability to fight.
I'm the lowest of the low.
Leave the party?
Yeah.
Flum and Eterna are both gone, anyway.
What will we do after we leave?
Well, we could travel the world
and check out all my favorite sights.
That sounds like
a wonderful journey. But...
"I can't pursue my own happiness
until the demons are exterminated"?
Linus?
Sorry!
I looked into it!
So you know about my hometown?
Yeah. I found out it was destroyed
by demons ten years ago.
Correct.
The demons stabbed, tore apart,
crushed, and burned my loved ones,
and I remember
every last bit of that sight.
They are disgusting monsters
that can kill with a smile.
They are an evil that must be destroyed.
Maria...
I do not wish to lose anyone else
who is dear to me.
Some of them are in the capital.
Th-That wouldn't happen
to include a lover, would it?
They're like family to me. A younger
sister, and an older and younger brother.
Is that so...?
It is.
That's odd.
I'm getting a strange reading
specifically from her heart.
Say, Eterna. What are these floaty things?
Mana-Optimizing Floating Objects.
They're devices that boost mana.
Devices? They're not living things?
But they're so friendly.
After years of use,
they started to gain individuality.
They're like my buddies now.
Can I give them names?
If you answer my questions, sure.
I-I told you I have amnesia.
I dunno if I have the answers you want.
Just answer what you can.
Do you have a sickness
of the heart or something?
Huh? My heart?
I don't think so.
Are you taking any medicine, then?
Nope.
I'm not.
Got it.
I answered your questions.
Can I give this one a name now?
Like what?
Hmm... It's a Mana-Optimizing
Floating Object, so...
Mofo!
Nope.
Let's eat!
Huh? Sara, those guys
who always come to get you
aren't your real brothers?
Nope. I didn't have any family,
so Ed and Jonny took over the role.
They're like brothers who looked after me.
Oh, that reminds me. Ed and Jonny...
They were worried about you today.
With all this dangerous stuff
happening lately,
I don't want Sara out and about so much.
She doesn't listen to us no more.
It scares me how reckless she's bein'.
Hey, it's our job to keep her safe.
I think you should
stop annoying her, though.
You say they worry about me, but Ed
enjoys annoyin' me by messin' up my hair,
and Jonny's overprotective.
Besides, I'm the one
who's worried about them.
Ed's always actin' without
thinkin' whenever I'm involved,
and Jonny always puts himself
second after me.
They keep treating me
like a child forever.
You all care deeply about one another.
That's why you worry.
You worry, even though
you're not real family?
Huh? O-Of course.
Ed, Jonny, me, and Maria all
grew up together like family.
If you care and worry 'bout one another,
that makes ya family in my books.
Also,
Miss Flum,
Miss Milkit,
Eterna,
and Ink, too!
You're my friends, and I care about y'all
as much as I would my own family!
Wow, I didn't know you felt that way.
Ed and Jonny need to hear
what you just said, too.
Over my dead body! It's too embarrassin'!
Family... Friends...
You're utterly useless.
You good-for-nothing!
Ink, it's me.
Eterna?
May I come in?
What is it?
It should be ready.
That's sweet.
When you're feeling down,
rose tea really hits the spot.
How did you know I was feeling down?
Watching you reminds me
of the old me and my family.
That's why I just can't leave you alone.
The old Eterna?
Curry?
Hamburg steak?
Baked fish sounds good, too.
Man, I can't wait for dinner tonight!
Dein and Kahnis
are finally gonna face off.
Which one are you guys betting on?
Kahnis, obviously.
What about you, Badras?
Dein's still our leader.
Knowing him, joining the Church of Origin
has to be part of some master plan.
He's always had a plan, remember?
It's time. Let's go.
Heya, Dein.
Sorry for making you take time out of
your busy praying schedule to come here.
Show him who the real boss
of the West District is, Kahnis!
Kahnis! Kahnis!
He's acting weird.
He's gotta be on some kinda drug.
Maybe the stuff he was distributing
to the royal army?
This fight's as good as won.
What's the matter?
Get high on your own supply?
Victory is Kahnis's!
Dein! Please stand up, Dein!
Gents, as you see, the West District
has a new boss as of today.
And it's me, Kahnis Delphiny!
Kahnis! Kahnis!
Pathetic. Is this really the guy
who wanted to rule the West?
Witness my compassion!
I'll put you...
out of your misery!
Keep your distance
no matter what happens!
Get out of there at the
first sign of danger, Sara!
Gotcha!
Aw, you shouldn't have
reached out like that.
Relax. The next slash
will send you to heaven.
Among the countless voices in Dein's head
was one that seemed to whisper to him
to stand up and kill his foe.
H-He's a monster...
Flum... Apricot!
I did it! I went and did it!
I'd lost it all,
but with sheer strength of will,
with my own hands...
I killed her!
I killed Flum Apricot!
Flum? What's he talking about?
That was Kahnis!
It... wasn't... Flum?
Kah...nis?
This is for Kahnis!
Die...
You monster!
Monster! Monster! Monster!
They appeared out of nowhere.
Once the eyeballs entered their bodies,
it was all over for them.
Countless heads, arms, and legs
grew from their twisted flesh.
I can hear them!
Like bugs crawling through my brain!
They swirl around in a spiraling vortex...
Ah! What the hell did you put in me?!
Core, my ass! Children...?
Divine... power?!
It's my power!
Go away!
Run, you guys.
They're catching up!
Run for your life!
You two...
Go on ahead.
That's what Miss Flum would say
if she were in my shoes.
No—
No way!
Jonny!
Hurry up and run!
I'll buy you time!
I could never...
Jonny!
Ed, take care of Sara!
Take care of our little sister!
No! Jonny...
You need to live as long as you can...
for his sake!
We shook them off, huh?
Thanks, Jonny.
It's my fault that he...
I know he doesn't regret a thing.
He'd be happy to know he saved you.
But... but...
If I hadn't led you two there,
this woulda never happened!
Ed!
I gave Jonny my word!
So you need to live!
Sara, I hope a small part of you remembers
that you had two super-awesome brothers.
When you grow up,
get married, wear that dress,
and look real pretty,
I'll be there to mess up your hair.
Sara's late today.
Should we start without her?
No.
We can eat once she's here.
Sara desperately fled for her life.
Jonny... Ed...
So that the despair of losing her family—
her loved ones—to a gruesome death
didn't swallow her whole.
I'm gonna live.
For Jonny...
and Ed, too...
I'll live.
I'll live...
a full life!
What's wrong, Sara?
Didja have a bad dream?
After apologizing silently
to everyone she knew,
she took one last look at the skies
and closed her eyes.
A fresh breeze, wholly unfitting
of the dirty alley she was in,
gently caressed her cheeks.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
TRUTH AND REALITY