Stop grinning at me like
that while eating.
I can't help it. It's good.
Syugo?
Nothing.
You always make a scary face, Syugo.
I was so shocked
when you jumped at Kizuki.
I haven't seen you make
a face like that before.
As a chef, what will you do
if you hurt your hand?
Are you out of your mind?
You and Kizuki!
Throwing hands at each other like that—
No more talking about Kizuki.
Syugo?
Right now...
The person in front of you...
is me.
Out of anyone else,
the one by your side...
is me.
My apartment's small,
but make yourself at home.
Thanks.
What the heck were you and Syugo
doing in front of Mizuho?
Actually, I wanted to be
the one to lay it on you.
You abandoned Mizuho for three years.
I'm sorry.
Idiot.
The one you need
to apologize to is Mizuho.
Can I ask you something?
Why'd you break up with Mizuho?
I ran away.
Forget him.
Let's forget about Kizuki.
I bet everyone else thinks so too, right?
That's enough, Kai.
Yeah. Kizuki's our friend.
I hate that part about adults.
Kai-kun. Everyone...
I'm so sorry.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Start Again from Respawn Area
Return to Title
It's over!
You idiot!
We were so close to finishing that!
You're useless! You held me back!
You're no friend, Kizuki!
When are we ever going to
defeat the dragon at this rate?!
You guys...
How long are you going to play games?
What about making plans for Kizuki's birthday?
Why is Kizuki even here?!
What a mess!
Now, now.
You play the game
for us instead, Shin-chan.
I'll come back after I take a bath.
I'm going to bed!
Kai's angry.
Hey, Mizuho.
How should I have used this item?
I'm cramping from laughing so much.
Your timing was completely off.
Mizuho.
Let me see. For that item...
You need to go home.
What?
It's almost midnight.
But I told my dad.
You shouldn't be in the room of a guy
who isn't your boyfriend
this late at night.
Y-You're right.
I'll head home soon, then.
Kizuki. Go drop her off.
Oh. Okay.
Thanks for having me over.
As expected of an honor student.
No "I'll take you home"
or anything like that?
What are you thinking, Shin-chan?
What? It's common sense.
Leaving those two alone
on a day like this...
You don't need to pretend
that you're fine.
Wh-What?!
You surprised me!
Since it's going to be
tomorrow in ten minutes...
I wanted to give you one last kiss
while I'm still 16.
Kizuki.
Is there anything you want
for your birthday?
Nothing, really.
But there's something I want to know.
What about me made you like me, Mizuho?
Um, well...
This is so sudden.
Hm?
Huh? Wha—?
Then let's take the scenic route.
We're not going home until you tell me!
I have a ton of things I like
about you, Mizuho.
What?
The way you chase your
dreams of writing manga.
How you cheer me on when I'm swimming.
How your hair is a mess because
you're too tired in the mornings.
Hm?
Aren't you dissing me in the last one?
What I...
Like about you...
Why it had to be you...
I can't think of a word
that perfectly describes that.
But...
"Hope."
Ever since we were kids...
No matter the hardships, you never
gave up and swam towards your dreams.
You're a ray of hope to me.
Can I leave it at that?
That was the time I thought to myself...
"I'll continue to swim
for Mizuho no matter what."
I wanted to continue
being her ray of hope.
It's past midnight now.
That was your first kiss as a 17 year old.
Happy Birthday, Kizuki.
I really did think that.
Here. From our first year in high school.
Oh yeah, the inter-high preliminaries.
I was so frustrated that
I placed 3rd on that day.
You also accidentally wore
your senpai's sandals, right?
Why did you even record that?
Aren't you practicing too much, Kizuki?
The virus finally calmed down, so new
matches could start up again this season.
Really?
This is my last chance.
I want Mizuho to see me swim
at the inter-high finals.
Kanto High School Championship
Swimming Competition
And now for the 52nd program.
Boys 100 meter freestyle final.
In Lane 6,
3rd year Kizuki Hazawa
from Aogasaki High School.
Kizuki! Give it your all!
You gotta win and make the inter-highs!
What a bold declaration of victory.
He's unstoppable.
His eyes are totally just on Mizuho.
Take your marks!
Back then...
I was enveloped in a blue light.
I felt like I was able to go
anywhere within that light.
Boys         100 Meter                     Freestyle                       Finals
1st  Kizuki Hazawa           Aogasaki
Hey, Kizuki?
Did you get that?
Yup! I did.
Be sure to come back home during
the Koigahama Fireworks Festival.
We absolutely have to go together.
Wh-What is it?
You miss me because I got into college
and live in the dorms now, right?
Nuh-uh! I can visit you
whenever I want to!
You're not that far away!
You're so cute, Mizuho!
Stop teasing me!
We somehow made it.
I'm so glad we made it just in time.
So Mizuho's job searching now?
Yup.
She said she had an interview today, too.
She's applied to 20 or 30 places by now.
And you, Kizuki?
I think I'll go to graduate school
for sports science next year.
I'm still disappointed that I couldn't
make the Japanese national team
at last year's championships...
I want to see how much
I can push my skills
and fight against all
those amazing people
with such high levels
of effort and talent.
You make me so mad with how cool you are.
Ouch.
It's no good at all.
Hazawa's generation hasn't improved.
But the kids after that
are getting stronger.
Could it be because
they missed out on practice?
They are the pandemic generation, after all.
That crucial time when they could gain
the most experience as a player
is practically a blank slate, yeah.
Your eyes used to
light up so much about it.
To think you'd quit swimming...
I panicked.
Hey! Kizuki!
I'm telling you this as your doctor!
You've been practicing
without permission, haven't you?!
Your shoulder's not
in good shape right now!
I understand you're in a rush
to improve your results.
But overworking will take
a toll on your life!
I know about my body better
than anyone else.
Gather around!
Huh? Where's Kizuki?
Here you go.
The usual goodies.
Thanks.
Take it easy.
I have plans with Chika,
so I need to go now.
Good luck on your practice!
Hey...
It's almost the qualifying match!
You've been waiting for this day forever.
I'm sure you'll do amazing!
I'm rooting for you!
Thanks.
I'll do my best for you, Mizuho.
It's no good at all.
Hazawa's generation hasn't improved.
But the kids after that
are getting stronger.
Could it be because
they missed out on practice?
They are the pandemic generation, after all.
That crucial time when they could gain
the most experience as a player
is practically a blank slate, yeah.
What do I do?
You need immediate surgery.
But if I undergo surgery,
wouldn't that mean
I won't be able to swim for a while?
Exactly.
Then what about the qualifying match?
Unfortunately, you're going to
have to sit this one out.
For now, you need to rest
and think about recovering your body.
Please wait!
It's not just the qualifying match.
What about the next season?
When would I recover?!
I can go back to normal, right?!
I'm sorry, but I can't make any promises.
But if you don't do anything,
you're going to stay like this.
Please...
Rehabilitation Center
That's it, Kizuki.
Does it still hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Let's try three more.
Yes.
Kizuki.
Don't rush, okay?
Take it slow.
Slow and steady.
Resigning this season due to injuries
Kizuki Hazawa (Athlete)
Taichi Aida (Athlete)
And now for sports.
Some bad news for Kizuki Hazawa, who
has been gaining attention in swimming.
Due to a previously
reported shoulder injury,
it was announced that he will miss
all remaining events this season.
At this time, there is
no confirmed date for his return.
I...
What I...
Like about you...
Why it had to be you...
I can't think of a word
that perfectly describes that.
But...
"Hope."
Ever since we were kids...
No matter the hardships, you never
gave up and swam towards your dreams.
You're a ray of hope to me.
Can I leave it at that?
I can't be Mizuho's ray of hope.
You quit the swim team?!
But you had surgery. You went to rehab.
You've worked so hard!
And your shoulder was
getting better little by little.
It was all pointless.
It's not pointless!
I know you don't really want to quit!
You can't decide that for me.
Why are you giving up?!
What about you?
You gave up your dreams to write manga
and ended up an office worker.
You don't have to give up.
Keep going.
If it gets hard and you want to cry,
I'll wipe your tears away for you.
I decided to start job searching.
What?
I'm starting so late that
I'm worried I won't even get to be
a normal office worker.
But Mizuho...
Are you okay with that?
Yeah.
I can just read manga as a side hobby.
I want you to chase your dreams
in my stead, Kizuki.
Can't I finally give up, too?
What?
I'm not a kid anymore.
I'm tired of foolishly chasing dreams.
You're not a kid anymore, yeah. But...
Well then.
Wait!
What about us?
That day...
I hurt Mizuho...
and ran away.
Then I got a job.
Cut off contact with you all.
And tried to forget everything.
But...
I just couldn't forget
about swimming and Mizuho.
In the end, I'm still
that timid younger brother.
Kizuki. It's okay.
I'm sorry I brought this up.
It must have been hard for you.
I found this where you
and Syugo were fighting.
This old keychain...
How long have you held onto this?
I saw this and immediately figured it out.
That your feelings for Mizuho
haven't changed at all.
You're the youngest.
You do things at your own pace.
You're a weakling.
Too honest for your own good.
Graduation
Koigahama Municipal Elementary School
I knew that you only had eyes
for Mizuho for a long time, Kizuki.
That's because Mizuho's
always been looking my way.
Even when I was weak with my asthma,
or when I couldn't improve my time,
or when my soul was crushed...
She made me stronger
when I was at my weakest.
That's why I'm so happy that
my feelings were able to reach her!
You were always looking straight forward.
That's what I loved about you.
Here.
Airu...
Stand up, Kizuki.
If you still love Mizuho,
you need to take a stand once more.
# 20 I Don't Want to Lose You