This ain't how I expected my life to go.
Sorry about that.
It's too dark to see nothin' in here.
We need to find a way out.
Right you are.
LIGHT
DARKNESS
DARKNESS AND LIGHT
Another dark room.
And it looks completely deserted.
Sara.
There's a passage this way.
Comin'.
This room's a lot bigger.
Miss...
There's a magical lamp here.
You're right.
This type is activated by mana.
I couldn't use it before.
It's lit.
This place is kinda crazy.
Is this...
some kind of research facility?
That looks familiar...
What's the matter?
N-No! Don't look!
O-Okies.
Anyway, miss, look at this.
What is that?
I found it by the entrance.
It's dirty, but it doesn't look that old.
What's it say?
"Two days have passed
since it went out of control.
Were the links not robust enough?
They did seem quite weak.
To hell with divine revelation.
To hell with the good of the nation.
I am me.
Nobody but myself.
Will I pass on? No, I won't.
I want to connect.
I want to be linked.
That's the only way I'll attain wisdom.
True wisdom—true peace—
requires judgment,
maybe even total control."
Huh?
On that dirty sheet of paper,
written in spiraling letters...
were the words "Flum Apricot."
It's your name again.
How?
PAY F0R Y0UR SINS FLUM APRIC0T
Why?
Why is my name here?
...lp.
Help...
What's up, Sara?
Didya hear somethin' just now?
Help...
Yeah, hear that?
There's somebody else here?
Let's go help.
Yeah.
Help...
I think she's this way.
This way.
Help...
I hear it coming from here.
Let's go inside.
Help...
Miss Flum!
There you are! Are you okay?
Let's get out of here together.
Come on.
Found you.
The woman had no face.
In its place was a spiral vortex.
No!
Stop that! Let me go!
What the heck?
It ain't budgin'!
Sara, cast a healing spell on my arm!
But if I do that...
Hurry!
Gotcha.
Recover!
Are you okay?
Thanks to you making it quick,
the pain's gone already.
That's good...
But not that!
You're not catching us that easy!
Did we lose it?
Dunno...
I don't think we can just run away.
But I'm not strong enough
to take that ogre down.
We'll have to up your attack stat somehow.
Sara, we're heading back to that lab.
What are you thinkin' of?
Just come this way.
Let's go, Sara.
Go where?
Not this again!
What's this stench?
A-Are these all corpses?
Sorry. I didn't want you to see this.
Come this way.
What're you lookin' for?
Cursed gear.
With so many corpses here,
I might find something.
Ah, you want it for Reversal, right?
Yeah.
I'll help!
You don't have to.
I can't ask a nun to rob corpses.
Nah, I'll do anything it takes to survive.
We'll survive, find that kialahri,
and save Mr. Leitch's wife.
You've got Miss Milkit
waiting for you, too!
Yeah, you're right.
It was then, as their fates
faded into darkness,
that a ray of hope manifested itself.
It came after us?
That thing just doesn't give up.
Duck!
Miss!
You did it!
NAME: GOD HATER LEATHER BOOTS
GRADE: EPIC
THIS EQUIPMENT LOWERS YOUR TOTAL STATS BY 2,203.
THIS EQUIPMENT FREEZES YOUR BODY.
You found somethin', didn't ya?
Don't celebrate just yet, Sara.
How is that possible?
You lopped its head off.
So why?
Why won't it go down?
A vortex!
Just getting close to it breaks things.
How am I supposed to fight that?
Flum.
When you're up against an enemy
several times stronger than yourself,
this method will help you unleash
a power that surpasses your limits.
Cavalier Arts...
Huh? What's that?
If this works, I might be able to kill it.
You have a plan?
Yeah. It's just...
I'll need some time.
Let me buy you some time.
I ain't all that good at defensive
magic, but I'll do my best.
Sorry to ask this of you, Sara.
Divine Protection!
Gadhio... Gadhio?
Gadhio!
What are you doing so early?
Oh, a light workout of sorts.
I need to practice this daily, or it
won't come in handy when it counts.
Cavalier Arts.
It's a technique that converts your
stamina to a power called prana
and uses that to boost
your physical capabilities.
Now that my stats are higher,
I might be able to pull it off.
Prana is more fluid, smoother,
and purer than magic.
So it requires a clear mind and soul,
free of all wicked thought.
I'm not done yet!
Once you've grasped it,
the rest is simple.
When your body is filled with prana,
unleash it all...
and swing your sword!
Flum's swordplay was far from perfect.
It was nothing but a makeshift copy.
Thus, one could call the move
"Prana Shaker Imitation."
You did it!
One more time...
Miss... I'll...
Sara...
She had already hit her limit,
having used every ounce of energy she had.
If it's not enough, then squeeze out more.
If I can't do that,
then try to figure out why.
I was powerless for so long.
And yet...
Nobody ever needed me.
And yet?
I wasn't allowed to live a decent life.
And yet...
Deep down, I'm scared and I wanna cry.
And yet!
Milkit...
I'm not gonna roll over and die just yet!
I'm gonna live on...
and I'm gonna make Milkit happy!
Please tell me I got it this time.
You did it, miss...
You can't be serious.
Crimson Sphere.
I can't believe they created
something so nasty.
Humanity is such a handful.
Oh, my.
Is that Flummy?
Where am I?
Yo.
I'm glad you came to, Flummy.
Wha... One of the Demon Chiefs?
I'm happy you remember me. We haven't met
since that one time in the demon realm.
Why is a demon here?
NAME: NEIGASS
AFFINTY: HEMATOPHAGE
TOTAL STATS: 33,624
Her total stats exceed 30,000?
She's the real deal.
How could I be anything else?
Oh, and I'm not going to hurt you.
In fact, I saved you.
Die!
No fair! You murderin' monster!
What an awful accusation.
Listen, we demons don't kill humans.
Lies!
Sister Maria and I had our homes destroyed
and our loved ones killed! By demons!
Really? And did you see that
with your own eyes?
W-Well...
But the people from the Church
who saved me said so.
The Church, eh? Then let me ask you...
The Church of Origin's performing shady
experiments out here in the sticks.
Can you really trust them?
Why bring up the Church there?
Oh, you didn't notice?
It looks like she did, though.
The relief on the ceilin' at the start
had the Church of Origin's symbol on it.
I had a bad feelin' about that.
And the writin' in that notebook
resembled the scriptures.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to bring it up,
but I just couldn't believe it.
Wait, so that underground facility
belonged to the Church?
That's what I came here to investigate.
The things the Church was researching
pose kind of a problem for us.
Research? Then...
Those were experiments?
That ogre, and that other beast...
There were monster
corpses in that heap, too.
Were they all... manufactured here?
All that aside, why are you here, Flummy?
And isn't that mark on your
cheek meant for slaves?
Well...
How positively cruel.
I knew it! So you really were
the hero Flum Apricot!
You knew it?
I'm just another adventurer now.
We came here on a job to collect herbs
when that beast attacked us.
Miss Flum killed it.
Only with Sara's help.
Hang on. Did you really kill it?
How?
Sheer will?
I put everything I had into a swing
and broke some crystal-like thing,
which put a stop to it.
The core broke?
You smashed this, Flummy?
Yeah, that's it.
Say, can I have this core?
If you let Sara out of there.
I'm sorry!
I...
I got too emotional and acted out.
I gotta apologize to you too, Miss Flum.
Why me?
If I hadn't passed on the Church's
shady information to you,
none of this woulda happened.
I'm so sorry. I did a really bad thing.
You don't have to apologize.
I have to! It just won't
feel right otherwise!
You've been nothing but a huge help to me.
But that's just...
That's enough out of you two.
The gloomy air's gone.
The wind blew it away.
Got it?
Can't believe a demon's trying
to make me feel better.
Didn't know demons could try
to make people feel better.
Yeah, I wasn't bein' myself!
By the way, I woke up here.
Did you bring us up here, Neigass?
I did.
I couldn't let two little girls sleep
in a place full of dead bodies.
Neigass...
Thanks a whole bunch!
You are...?
I'm Sara!
Should a nun with the Church
of Origin be collecting herbs?
Isn't it forbidden?
We also need medicine to help
people sufferin' from illnesses!
Guess I'm a naughty li'l nun!
I'll get rid of the boulder
blocking the exit for you.
See you again.
Um...
Do demons really not kill humans?
I'm sure the human-demon war
wasn't without casualties.
But I swear...
A demon would never kill a human
for their own benefit or pleasure.
That I can say for sure.
Who are you swearing by?
Hmm... Gods can't be trusted...
So you, Sara!
Me?
You're like a goddess,
so I'll swear it by you!
Wh-What?
Don't say that!
I had a feelin' the Church
was hidin' somethin',
but I wasn't expectin' it to be
a buncha messed-up research.
If that was a biological weapon,
the kingdom must be involved, too.
Why the kingdom?
Given how big and old that place was,
there's no way the Church
could've built it themselves.
And now we're told demons
don't kill humans.
I don't even know what to believe anymore!
My head's all a mess, too.
Look, miss!
Is that the kialahri flower?
We can finally head back!
Yeah!
I can't wait to go back
and eat Milkit's cooking!
Same!
Welcome back, Master.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
CRUELTY AND CAMARADERIE