Hey Mama,
what's for dinner tonight?
Hmm, let's see...
Since Dad won't be home,
Let's get
some yakitori from Torishige?
Really?! Yay!
Then I want...
Gizzard and cheek, and neck,
and esophagus, and chicken tail!
Your palate is something else.
You take after your father.
Wait!
Also their chicken offal stew!
How old are you, really?
What is it?
- A Demon?
- It's a Demon!
Boy...
My...
- Where are you?
- Help!
My boy!
Mama!
Yuki!
I found you!
Mama!
Yuki!
My...boy!
Mine...all mine!
Yuki!
Give him back.
My boy...
That's enough of you Demons
having your way.
Where is...the boy?
Where are you, boy?
- All of you...
- Boy?
...are going down!
This...
Is the story of how one rooster...
...saved humanity.
ONE YEAR AGO
Wait!
Are you leaving?!
I was born to wander.
Peace and quiet doesn't suit me.
Were you just toying with me?
No...
I just gave in
to my animal instincts
EPISODE ONE:
A ROOSTER AMONG CRANES
Delicious!
The savory aroma and
the perfect amount of bitterness.
Nothing like stink bugs
for breakfast.
Also...
They're great for digestion and
promote healthy bowel movements.
Delicious and good for your health.
Truly two birds with one stone!
- Oh, a chicken!
His comb is so cute!
Do you think it's a stray chicken?
Where did you come from?
Probably the zoo?
- That would be funny!
- I hate kids.
They're rude, stubborn and loud.
Hey, do you want some?
It's fried chicken!
It's good!
Is she for real?
What a cool find!
Stop it,
you're hurting the poor thing!
Shut up, you brat!
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Whoa, his comb's so cool.
You're still brats too!
That's right!
What should we do with him?
I wanna eat him.
You idiot, what if he's got
some weird disease?
You're right.
How about we feed him to my cat?
Oh, good idea!
Whoa!
Wait!
Hey, wait!
Don't waste my time,
you little punks!
Stop, dang it!
They just won't quit!
Hold it!
What's going on?
That rooster's ours.
Huh?
Well, that's odd...
That rooster lives here with me...
What?!
Mr. Cluckers!
How many times have I told you
not to leave the yard?!
Mr...Cluckers?!
Sorry, we'll be more careful
in the future.
Let's get out of here!
You saved my feathers, Old Man.
Do you think that chicken
really belongs to the old man?
You idiot, of course he's lying!!
- That old geezer!
- My quota...
-Think he's gonna
-My quota.
gonna eat him all by himself?
This month for sure,
I'll definitely...
Meet my quota!
My quota!
Much obliged,
Old Man.
But I've got things
to take care of.
I'm so sorry.
This is all I can give you.
Brown rice, corn and shiso leaves?
Old man...
This is undeniably a special
and bountiful feast!
Is it good?
I'm glad you like it.
My wife would always
feed the sparrows
that would come and visit as well...
Looking back...
I should have retired
from teaching sooner,
and spent more time with her.
Come on now, don't fight.
Don't eat too fast, now.
Sorry for rambling.
For some reason I feel like
I can talk to you about anything.
I understand, Old Man.
I should've spent
more time with them as well.
Big Brother!
Big Brother!!
S-Sarah!
Big Brother!
Sarah!!
What was that?!
Model upgrade!
High-value trade-in!
Emergency evacuation alert.
A Demon has appeared
Evacuate the area immediately.
A Demon!
This month, I will
meet my quota!
- Help!
It's those brats from earlier!
Hiroshi!
Ow!
Quota...
Hurry, run!
...achieved!
Old Man!
A recall?
Now's our chance!
Come on!
Hey you!
What do you think you're doing
to those kids and old people?
It really makes my crown curl!
I achieved my quota!
You're going down!!!
Special edition model!
Hybrid vehicle!
Hydrogen engine!
My goal...
...is to be first
in national rankings!
Domestics!
Imports!
Amazing...
Finishing move!
Take this!
Ko...
Ke...
Kok...
Ko!!!
KOKEKOKKO
Sales report!
What just happened?
Is it possible?
It might have been the phenomena
known as resonance.
R-Resonance?
You've seen it on TV
and in the movies, haven't you?
Where people shatter glass
with just their voice?
Wow!
If I'm not mistaken,
resonance occurs...
...when the frequency of one's voice
matches the wavelength
of an object.
But could such a phenomenon
be powerful enough
to defeat a monster of that size?!
That rooster...
Who is he?!
There's no mark.
It wasn't this one, after all.
Whew...
This is bad!
Your yard's destroyed, Old Man!
Are you saying
you want to help clean?
Is anyone hurt?
Please be careful!
Injured, coming through!
Are there anymore garbage bags?
Yes, we still have more.
There we go!
Phew, we're done!
You know, defeating Demons,
helping us clean...
...you're one hell of a rooster!
Huh? Where did he go?
Huh?
Mr. Cluckers...
MAX CLEARANCE 2.4 METERS
...is not my name.
It's Keiji.
I'm a born wanderer.
It's time I left this town.
Old Man, I hope
I've paid you back for the feast.
I've defeated the Demon.
And...
I cleaned up the mess I made
in your yard.
I leave no unfinished business
behind.
That's how I roll.
Now then...
Are you leaving?!
Leaving a woman crying
isn't my style.
Sorry for the wait.
I'm back.
The next town awaits me.
Hey, look!
Check this out!
- Gross!
- Flasher!
Now that I have your attention...
No one wants to see...
your dirty body!
THUNDERBIRD
Thunderbird!!
Disgusting.