Step right up and have a look...
It's time for Yamishibai.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
Password
This is the story of some
grade schoolers on their way home...
Hey, it's Ohashi and Iwata!
Mine now!
Haruto!
We're gonna tell a teacher!
Wait up!
What's up?
Has this old building always been here?
Now that you mention it...
Looks deserted. Let's check it out.
Sounds fun.
Come on, we'll get in trouble if
we take too long getting home.
It's fine.
What a big yard!
Whoever lived here must've been rich.
Hey, it's not locked.
This place is a real mess.
There's graffiti.
Unite!
"Unite"?
Let's make this our password.
What're you talking about?
When we leave, one of us will
ask, "What's the password?"
And you've gotta answer,
"Unite," or you're a ghost.
I get it.
What's his problem?
Probably just saw his own shadow.
I could see Ryosuke doing that.
Who were those people I saw
looking into the house?
Someone's coming.
Hey! What's wrong?
What happened?
Is it really you?
What do you mean, "is it really you"?
Let's go home already.
What's the password?
If you're really them, you know it.
The password?
What difference does it make?
Come on out already.
She's right. Open up.
You're impostors!
I'm not opening this door!
We're just messing with you.
Ready? And...
Unite!
Happy now?
Guys, don't mess around like that.
You should've seen the look on
your face, Ryosuke. Hilarious!
Why did you run away like that, anyway?
Like I said, it was nothing.
Huh? It won't open.
That can't be right.
What's the password?
There's someone on the
other side of the door.
Come on, say the password.
It's pretty suspicious
that you won't say it.
Yep, something's wrong.
It's them...
Who?
Just open up already!
Let us out!
You're impostors!
I'm not opening this door!
Hey! Let us out!
Should we go?
I think so.
Hey, what was the password again?
"Resolve."
No, it was "Speak the secret."
I thought it was "Assemble."
I guess it doesn't matter!
Produce Center
Unite!
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
The end.