Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 10: Hide-and-Seek Isn't Scary
There's something seriously wrong
with that Namu guy!
Ch-Chie-sensei, what's your problem
with my master?
He's ridiculous!
What's my "problem"?
He tried to kill Kaya-chan!
That's a false accusation.
You wouldn't call exorcism
"killing" evil spirits, would you?
Why are you looking after him, Mob-san?!
He asked to see my files on Kaya-sama.
Zero abilities
\h\h\hWhere did
\h\hKaya-sama
inherit her
abilities?
Kaya-sama
and her family
\hWhat
is "It"?
A mysterious
specter?
Derived from
the fetus?
Huge black
shadow
What? What on earth are you up to?
Something feels off.
A bunch of things just don't add up.
Named after the head family's tradition.
Eldest daughter and a psychic.
So she's clearly the next successor.
Yet she's out there living a normal life.
And to top it off,
her true form is that monster.
Um, you said "head family."
So you're an Ebisumori, too, then?
I'm from a branch of the Ebisumori clan.
My side uses a different kanji.
The head house
holds the spiritual lineage,
Head
Family
Ebisumori
(Warrior/Shrine grove)
and the branch family descends
from the non-psychic line.
Branch
Family
Ebisumori
(God of fortune/Defense)
The branch families near worshiped
the head house's shrine maiden
and served her faithfully.
Or something like that. Probably.
Why is that part so vague?
What do you expect?
I was kicked out of the house
when I was about four or five.
I guess it's some kind of atavism,
but I've been able to see
the shrine maiden's true form since birth.
Soon after I spoke up about it,
I was put into foster care.
I saw something they would do anything
to hide, including ruin a child's future.
And now, something far
more monstrous even than that
has slipped its leash and
is living as a kindergartner.
Well? Now do you see why
I feel I have to take it out?
So you're still dead set on
getting rid of Kaya-chan?
If that's what needs to be done.
You put that thing back into
its human vessel and kept it alive.
So it's on you to make sure
it stays human.
That'd make things
a lot easier for me, too.
As if I wouldn't!
Aunt Nana!
It's just Nana, Kaya.
Ebisumori Nana.
Kaya-chan's aunt, who's head of
the main Ebisumori clan and a psychic.
Chie-sensei.
Huh? Oh, uh, yes?
Kaya seems rather listless lately.
Any ideas why that might be?
Huh? Uh, let's see...
What should I say? There's a possibility
she doesn't see Kaya-chan as human.
What if she has the same motive as Namu?
If you find out anything...
Or rather, if you feel like talking,
please let me know.
S-Sure.
Fun
Origami Lesson
Hey, Aunt Nana—
Just call me "Nana."
Can you beat up ghosts, too?
No. Only someone as exceptional as you
is capable of that, Kaya.
But it didn't work the other day.
I couldn't beat it up.
So I won't fight ghosts anymore.
When I was about your age,
specters were simply terrifying.
All I could do was hide
behind my mother.
It's not something a small child
like you should have to face.
So you're right to avoid conflict.
But in case there comes a time when you
need to confront them, keep this with you.
It's a talisman.
It'll protect you from specters.
Butt.
It's a heart.
Thank you.
Nana.
Is this a butt?
It's a heart!
Just kidding.
Jeez!
Aunt Nana.
Sorry for saying it looks like a butt.
Oh, no. I just have something
in my eyes, that's all.
Who wants to play hide-and-seek?
Me!
Rock, paper, scissors!
You're it, Kaya-chan.
One. Two.
Where should I hide?
Three. Four.
Five. Six.
I'm gonna hide in here.
Saku-chan.
What is it, Ma-kun?
I know a good hiding spot.
You do?
Ew, here? I don't like the dark.
But you wanna win the game, don't you?
I guess I can hide in here for a bit.
Nineteen. Twenty.
Found you, Ken-ken.
What?
Found you, Yuzu-chan.
Aw.
Found you, Ma-kun and Saku-chan.
You two aren't the Ma-kun
and Saku-chan I know.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Weirdo.
She's so weird.
You're a weird kid
that says weird things.
Saku-chan would never say that to me!
Forget it.
There's nothing you can do.
Go away. You can't play with us.
When you climb all the way up—
Huh? Where's Kaya-chan?
She said she doesn't wanna play anymore.
So let's keep playing
hide-and-seek with just us.
Ken-ken!
I give up! You can come out now.
Where did he go?
Who cares? We're gonna be late
for pickup. Just leave him.
No! We were playing together,
so you have to help me find him.
Ken-ken!
It's time to go home!
Come out already!
Oh.
Found you, Ken-ken!
Let's hurry back to class.
Hey, Yuzu.
You look like you're gonna cry.
Is it 'cause you saw it?
Everyone, time to go home.
Okay!
It's time to go.
Kaya-chan!
They're all acting weird!
Help—
Oh, Yuzu-chan!
You don't like monsters, do you?
Be good and nothing scary will happen.
Forget it.
There's nothing you can do.
But in case there comes a time when you
need to confront them, keep this with you.
You couldn't find us
'cause we found an amazing hiding spot.
No! Stop it!
Let me go!
Nobody will ever find you in here.
Let's hide together.
We can hide here forever and ever.
Because nobody will find you.
Forever and ever.
Kaya-chan?
Run!
Aw, she got away.
Well, whatever. This one will do.
Wh-What?
Stay away!
I don't want you!
I won't let you be mean...
to my friends!
It won't open! Somebody, help me!
Hey, don't shut the door! Open up!
It's so dark and scary!
Huh?
Found you.
Hey!
What are you all doing over there?!
Huh? What?
Kaya-chan! You guys!
Oh, good! You're all back to normal!
Wh-What's going on here?
Come on. Let's go back to our classroom.
Kaya-chan.
I beat up the ghost.
I'm not sure why,
but she seems like herself again.
You did? Thank you.
Look. Aunt Nana gave me this.
From Nana-san, huh?
It's a talisman.
Huh. That's a surprise.
Kaya-chan, can I see what's inside?
Okay.
This is...
Cameras Aren't Scary
You're really good, Kaya-chan.
I heard she wasn't herself lately,
but I'm glad she's okay.
Is this your usual thing, Osamu-kun?
Sorry for making you come along, Master.
No. We're dealing with the head family.
Who knows what could happen
if I leave you alone again?
Let's use this next.
You listening?
Snap.
I bet you don't know this, but when it
comes to recording spiritual phenomena,
analog is the way to go.
I don't see anything.
It takes time to develop the image.
Oh, yeah. Now I see—
Analog methods can sometimes reveal
truths the human eye can't detect.
I'm thirsty, so I'm gonna
buy us some drinks.
Cold
Stronger
Scent!
A Golden Gift
Apple
"Truths the human eye can't detect," huh?
Yay! Hop, hop.
I'm not seeing any irregularities
that Chie-sensei or Master mentioned.
Does it only manifest
under certain conditions?
Hey, wait. That's...
Just as I thought.
It's something not of this world.
Analog really makes a difference.
But since Kaya-sama left it alone,
it likely hasn't developed into a specter
that can harm people yet.
Is it looking at me?
It noticed me!
My bad, Osamu-kun.
I dropped the photo some—
Why are you standing stock-still?
M-Master, please take a look
at these photos.
It moves every time I look away.
I bet it's the kind of specter that
attacks when you take your eyes off it.
You can see it, right, Master?
Can you please take it out?
I really need to blink soon.
My eyes are drying out!
I wish I could, but I don't see
any specter around here.
What?
But in reality...
That's strange.
Osamu-kun sees it, but I don't?
Osamu-kun.
Y-Yes?
Don't look.
Master, you mustn't!
The specter will attack if you don't—
There it is.
Gotcha.
That was careless of me.
I should have seen you.
Hiding inside the camera is
pretty slick, I'll give you that.
That was close! I still have my eyes.
Are you all right, Osamu-kun?
Oh, thank you very—
It multiplied. But how?
I see. You're pretty clever, aren't you?
M-Master!
I can't help you right now.
Get out of here while it's focused on me!
I can't!
Master!
Don't bully...
Mobuo's friends.
Mobuo, are you okay?
Kaya-sama!
Please do that again so I can take
a picture. Wait, no. A video!
You're always the one who protects
Osamu-kun, aren't you?
The boy Aunt Nana.
Oh, Master! Where are you going?
Master!
I didn't think it would get this bad.
I can't protect Osamu-kun like this.
I don't like it,
but I guess I have no choice.
Aunt Nana Isn't Scary?
Um, Ebisumori-san?
Yes? What is it?
This may sound ridiculous,
but Kaya-chan can see ghosts.
Not only that, she can
get rid of them, too.
But something out of this world
is giving her that power, right?
It sounds like you also know
about Ebisumori's shrine maidens.
I'll tell you what I know about Kaya-chan.
So please tell me what you know about her.
Why have you decided to
trust me all of a sudden?
Because she showed me.
I saw what was written
inside her talisman.
Let every curse
be laid upon
Ebisumori Nana
My abilities are limited. That thing
is little more than modest comfort.
I'm no different. So please...
I want to make sure Kaya-chan
can stay with her family,
and that no one will ever
call her a monster again.
Conference Room
Kaya-chan is Ebisumori's shrine maiden.
That's what a person named Namu told me.
So the son of the branch family
is doing well. That's good to hear.
Namu is half correct.
Half?
Husband
Ichi
(Ebisumori
family
ancestor)
Futaba
Mitsuba
Husband
Shiho
Heita
Hatsu
Jyukichi
(Yebisumori
family
ancestor)
Sosuke
Fumi
Michiko
Husband
Mutsu
Nana
Mirai
Ebisumori
Family Tree
"The eldest daughter of
the Ebisumori clan becomes a psychic."
Strictly speaking, this is incorrect.
They bear children in a way that ensures
the firstborn becomes a psychic.
So they're deliberately creating psychics?
It's hard to believe, but the Ebisumoris'
ancestor was said to be divine.
And it was her supernatural gifts
that led the family to great prosperity.
However, her power wasn't passed down
to the next generation.
Even so, the Ebisumori family refused
to give up on preserving their power.
Pursuing the shrine maiden's rebirth,
the family tried all manner of ritual,
and finally discovered a method.
And that was...
Curse
Gestation
Curse Gestation.
Children born by this method
were always female,
and as they matured,
their looks and abilities
mirrored the founding shrine maiden,
allowing the Ebisumori family
to flourish further.
The shrine maidens naturally desired
to beget the next generation,
and a lineage where the eldest daughter
inherited psychic powers was born.
The potency of our powers varies,
but we're all copies of her.
\h\h\hIchi
(Ebisumori
family
ancestor)
Given that we're nothing more
than vessels for psychic power,
Namu calling us "specters"
isn't entirely wrong.
He said Kaya-chan's inner self
had completely turned into a specter.
Does that mean the girl who was
the real Sato Kaya is no longer...
Don't worry.
Like Namu said,
Kaya seems to have inherited the shrine
maiden's powers more than anyone else.
But who she is inside?
That's unquestionably all her.
Really?
I'm positive. Because Mirai
gave birth to Kaya and she...
Nothing.
That's a relief. But why did Kaya-chan's
mother go through that ritual?
Perhaps it was an act of defiance.
She felt inferior because
she didn't possess psychic powers.
And there were signs she resented
our mother for treating us differently.
Perhaps after learning
of the ritual somehow,
she wanted to free herself
from those feelings
by making her daughter a psychic.
That's probably why
she named her daughter "Kaya,"
using the kanji for "God"
and the "number eight."
Oh, that explains her second baby.
What? Second baby?
Yeah. A psychic guy I know said
Kaya-chan's mother is pregnant
with a specter.
So she went through
another Curse Gestation, right?
She probably wants her daughters
to be psychics because she couldn't.
That's not possible.
There's no doubt Kaya was born
as the shrine maiden.
Because Mirai ran off with my...
But if she wanted another baby...
Uh, Nana-san?
I'm sorry. There's something I need
to go check. If you'll excuse us.
Huh?
Uh, hey!
Bye-bye, Chie-sensei.
Nurses'
Station
I'm here to see Sato Mirai.
End of the corridor, to the right.
You know where she is, right, Kaya-chan?
Show her the way.
Don't go.
You're such a strong girl, Kaya.
You've been dealing with your mom
all by yourself.
I'll handle it from here.
I'll be right back.
To tell you the truth,
before asking for your help with Kaya,
I asked Mirai how she felt about it,
because you said things were complicated.
But Mirai said with a smile...
Show her to my sister.
She'll be surprised.
Mirai, what are you trying to do?
Sato Mirai
Nana-chan.
What just happened?
Aunt Nana!
Your nose is bleeding. Are you okay?
Y-Yes.
Was it a hallucination? No, there was
definitely something in that room.
And it attacked me.
How am I still alive?
Hello, Ebisumori speaking.
Yes.
What?
Nana-san?
U-Um, is everything okay?
Just now?
Yes, I'm afraid to say your mother...
passed away moments ago.
Let every curse be laid
upon Ebisumori Mutsu
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka