Arthur-kun's light is extinguishing
the flames of the Great Cataclysm!
Arthur must've beaten Dragon!
Well done, Arthur!
The hope that Dragon saw
is exorcising the despair.
Dragon, renowned as a calamity...
That kid showed the Great
Wyrm of Despair hope?
Has the Cataclysm died down?
Are we safe now?
But the despair will not end!
Because I,
Great Cataclysm Execution Officer
Faerie, will not allow it to end!
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Episode 22
"Hero Resurrected"
For now, it looks like the
Great Cataclysm has stopped,
but will it really wrap up like this?
I'd like to think so, but I can't
imagine it'll end this way.
Arthur will come back to us, won't he?
Of course he will.
Vulcan, isn't there any way for us to
look for Arthur's location from here?
Space is too vast.
I can't capture all of it.
Licht!
Something of insane mass is
approaching from a high altitude!
Mass [Large]
It can't be.
This is...
Haijima Industries
What's wrong, Kurono?
There's gonna be a replacement here.
I, the fake, am gonna replace you!
Is this... how people see me?
Huh?
You're like a psycho from
a third-rate writer's script.
This is the image that people have of us.
There are two differences
between you and me.
The first is that no matter
how much power I may possess,
I don't plan to use that power to
stray from the path of being human.
And the other...
I am an honest, virtuous salaryman.
I am not a psycho!
What are you talking about?
You torment children!
I am only doing so in the form of work.
I have received the company's permission
to pick on the child called Takkun.
You're just gonna bully him
until you kill him, right?
Even I would be forgiven for
swapping places with you!
I'll bust your guts wide open!
I'll fweet your fweet and fweet with it!
Loud laughter followed
by a violent statement.
What's wrong with you?
You started to sound like Pan
from the 4th in the middle there.
Is this really what the people
around me think of me?
That's how it goes.
If you're not close to someone,
they'll sloppily categorize you and then
feel like they understand you. That's all.
Still... a cliché psycho like that?
Since it affects salary assessments,
even I worry about how others judge me.
Stop licking that blade all the time.
You're scum that bullies the weak!
I am the image of you that
reflects exactly that.
And since I have no interest
in my social standing,
I know no restraint, so I'm strong!
Is that so?
If you seemed too strong, I thought I'd
give up my social standing and run away.
But that doesn't seem to be the case.
Don't try to act tough, original!
I am not acting tough.
You and I are fundamentally
completely different.
Tell me how we're so different!
I am self-centered,
but I don't fight alone.
And that's the reason you're stronger?
My strength doesn't come
from insane psychopathy.
I am a professional. A salaryman.
Section Chief Oguro, your orders.
Get him.
Understood.
I can push the responsibility onto
my boss. That's why I can fight.
You can only act on your boss's orders!
Such a restrictive way to live!
I'll set you free!
You're desperately copying me.
Trying to replace me...
But if that's true,
then the one you need permission
from is the person in charge, me.
Do you like me?
Of course I don't.
I just want the benefits that
come from replacing you.
I see.
Then we'll just say that it
wasn't meant to be this time.
I ask that you leave this world.
So this guy is people's image of me?
Seriously, what a nuisance.
What kind of monster do people think I am?
You know that only despair
lies ahead for you.
Why are you fighting it?
I'm an observer.
I can't die until the very, very end.
Really? You're standing up?
That image doesn't fit my image, though.
What do I do?
Oh, come on. Are you serious?
Already out of cards to play?
I can't possibly take on two of you.
I give up...
Burns.
All this time, I've seen
Adolla through your eyes.
Though, with just one eye,
I guess I can't try to show off.
Your eye and mine were
separate but the same.
I'm glad I got to see you
again here at the end.
If you're the one who kills me,
it's the best thing that could
happen in the worst situation.
Do it.
You thought I was a doppelganger?
Burns...
Are you still the same Burns?
I haven't seen you since
Fuchu, right, Five-Two?
But how? I'm certain that
your doppelganger...
Back then, I was dragged into Adolla,
but I suppressed my doppelganger,
and I was able to merge with it while
maintaining my own consciousness.
You're one tough, stubborn old geezer.
At last, it seems he's appeared.
Yeah. I can tell, too.
He's up against the strongest.
If he can't handle it, it's game over.
Hey.
Hey!
If we're gonna do this thing,
let's hurry up and do it, Original.
Isn't it a little too soon to decide
which of us is the real deal?
The one to lead Asakusa has
to be the absolute strongest.
The one who wins is the real original.
This has gotten crazy.
Waka, who's stronger than anyone,
and Waka's fake, who's stronger
than anyone, are fighting.
Who do you think will win?
How should I know?
What those of us here in Asakusa
and those guys throughout the Empire
think of as "the strongest"
has taken physical form.
That's the real King of Destruction.
But no one can beat Waka!
Of course not!
Waka won't lose!
Are you stupid?
If you guys believe in Waka,
won't that just make the fake stronger?
But you know, Hina, Waka won't ever lose!
This really is a pickle!
This has turned into a real tale of wit.
You hate stuff that takes
too much effort, don't you?
If you're gonna blow me away, some
half-hearted attack isn't gonna cut it.
I know that better than anyone!
Hey, now.
Hey, Mister Provisional Original!
Your Nichirin is a sham of a copy!
I'm gonna take this whole planet
and blow it all away with a kaboom!
Now this is the real Nichirin!
What's that?
This is Shinmon Benimaru's
once-in-a-lifetime great firework!
Farewell, Original!
It only took a second! Yeah!
You fake! Come back never, you hear me?
Seriously. He didn't even
give us time to worry.
Don't go getting cocky
just because it's Waka!
Waka's the strongest in
everything but gambling!
Oh, come on. What's going on here?
I'm the image of "the strongest"
built by everyone in the Empire.
Just look at that lot down in Asakusa...
I am the manifestation of all of
that unshakable belief, so why...
Hmm.
I guess more people think of
me as weak than I thought.
Hey, you goons!
Why was that guy so weak?
You really had me fooled.
Don't you dare look down on me!
W-We're sorry!
I am Asakusa's Shinmon Benimaru!
So you're stronger than what all of
humanity considers the strongest, huh?
Next time, I want to take on a version
of me that reflects a proper assessment.
Well...
my fight ends here.
You take care of the rest...
Shinra.
Fire Force
Chapter 3
Kurono-san!
That was dangerous.
Takkun, where did you go?
Adolla.
But I was suddenly released just now.
Someone with an Adolla Burst was released?
Has the Great Cataclysm died down?
No. This world and the world of
images, Adolla, are still connected.
Where am I?
This is Adolla.
Are you Amaterasu?
That's right. We meet at last...
my doppelganger.
So I was right. I'm really not human.
Why do you look sad?
Huh?
I've burned for 250 years.
While you were at the convent,
while you were with those fire soldiers,
and while you laughed and
giggled... that whole time.
What does the kind sister think?
So that all of you could live,
you sealed away an innocent girl,
worshiped her, and feared her.
What do you think of the humans
who continued to burn her as fuel?
Help me.
Amaterasu...
But it doesn't matter anymore.
I've finally been set free.
You should do as you like, too.
Yes. That way...
Why did I...
A doppelganger's instinct is to kill
the original and take their place.
No...
I don't mind.
You can have this crappy life.
You should kill me. Kill me. Kill me.
Kill me!
I can't do that.
I love my big sister, Shinra-san,
and everyone in the 8th.
But while I was out there,
you were all alone.
You suffered inside Amaterasu
as you continued to save people.
I'm not the one who should
exist in the world.
Iris...
I...
So you've emerged from the pillar,
Sho?
Hope has returned to the world.
The connection to Adolla has weakened.
The Great Cataclysm will end.
And you will die here, too, Faerie.
Will you stop ti—
What? Why can you move?
Now that Adolla is so close, it isn't just
you two brothers who can control time.
By using gravity to bend spacetime, I, too,
can meddle with the passage of time!
What's wrong?
If you're not the only one who can
stop time, you can't do anything?
No.
I was just thinking, "Is that all?"
What?
All you've done is manage to step
onto the same playing field.
You won't be able to see my sword work.
Don't act so full of yourself!
I was supposed to be your Guardian!
You can't possibly measure up to—
This is goodbye.
Don't get too full of yourself, scum!
Don't think you've won just because
you've killed me, you rotten little runt!
And you call yourself a Great
Cataclysm Execution Officer?
Don't you have a more
respectable parting threat?
Exactly. I am a Great
Cataclysm Execution Officer.
It must have been hard work.
The Great Cataclysm won't end!
Here comes the despair again!
What's this shaking? An earthquake?
No. Look up there!
The moon?!
The moon's so close!
You!
I won't leave a single
seed of hope behind.
Bringing down the moon will
make everyone remember despair!
You expendable weaklings!
And now, no one... can stop the moon.
Sho...
Take that.
Hinawa! Maki!
Can you do anything?
Of course we'll do everything we can!
Maki, we're going to shift
the moon's trajectory!
Yes, sir!
This stupid m—
Mmm... Mmm—
We have to push it back!
The overwhelming mass will crush us!
Karim!
Can you do anything with
your Thermoacoustic Cooling?
I'll make it work somehow!
Somehow... Will it work?
It stopped?
He went and did it.
He went and stopped the moon!
That's gotta be Shinra, no question!
It does seem very close to Earth, though.
It's stopped for now, right?
It doesn't look like
it'll fall any farther.
I guess it's fine.
It's too bad, Faerie.
As long as the Hero exists,
hope will never die out.
Even if my brother has to change the
laws of reality, he will save the world.
What a disgusting fellow.
Big Brother!
Sho!
I guess things aren't just
going to end like this, huh?
Settling things with Saint
Haumea and the Evangelist
is something only my
brother the Hero can do.
And you're the one who guides
me, my guardian angel, right?
And there's our mother, too.
Everything is in Adolla.
Yeah. I can't lose the place that
Arthur's gonna come home to.
Let's protect the world, Sho!
This is the final battle in this story!
This is...
The history of humanity's despair.
Since they're depicted differently,
they're from the world before
the Great Cataclysm, right?
Human history has always
been the history of despair.
Anger and hate...
Anxiety, man-made destruction,
natural disasters...
And now,
that image of despair is trying
to merge with the world.
We must stop it in its tracks, brother.
Yeah. No matter what it takes.
This is...
Adolla.
Are the other Pillars here?
I hope the sister met up
with the rest of the 8th...
It looks just like Amaterasu.
Humanity may have projected
this image unconsciously
when they built Amaterasu.
That's right.
We're always receiving God's revelations
and acting upon them. No more than that.
So you showed up...
Haumea.
Apologies for keeping you waiting, you
who carry the burden of being the savior.
The fate of this world hinges upon you.
Are you really the same Haumea?
That's how Haumea should be.
Should be?
Haumea was warped by taking in people's
wickedness, but she was originally a saint.
She hears humanity's unconscious
and the revelations of God.
I've used this crown to block my
eyes and listened all this time.
And that's how I came to
realize it all over again.
Let's end this world along with myself.
To Be Continued
Fire Force Chapter 3
To end the chain of
salvation and despair...
Next Time
Can you give any means of
relief other than death?
I won't give up hope!
How the Great Cataclysm unfolds is
up to you, brother, as the Hero.
Next time, "Despair Saintess."
Episode 23
Despair Saintess
Return to the great flame of fire. Látom.