Emma Greene in the 624
crosses the finish line!
She puts herself in provisional third!
Her time was nip and tuck
with the pair at the top!
After day six of qualifying, four drivers
have beaten last year's course record!
MF Ghost
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
The King's
Impatience
Oh, the camera's on me.
Yay! Make sure I look cute, okay?
Marie, this is dangerous now.
Your costume's so tight, we're a breath away
from a wardrobe malfunction.
Out on the course, the final day
of qualifying is underway.
Wading through the Hydro Trap
is the 6 car,
driven by the original cornering wizard,
Yanagida Takuya.
He negotiates the high-speed S-curve
beside Benten Rock.
And while he looked unsteady earlier
in the season, he's in better shape lately.
This powerful front-engine RWD BMW
is like an extension of his limbs.
It's his belief that the only way
to turn properly is with rear-wheel drive.
And he's dead set on
confirming his conviction!
Yes, it's our solitary
rear-wheel drive specialist,
who's always near the top of
the popularity charts: Yanagida Takuya.
You need more than complete control
over a car to call yourself a pro driver.
You're not a racing driver
until you post times that show it.
The final day of qualifying
should be underway in Atami.
I'm certain Mr. Beckenbauer
will set an impressive time,
but my real concern is...
Mr. Moroboshi.
The 885 shoots away!
He qualified eighth
on his debut at Peninsula,
but managed to climb
to fifth in the race.
Overshadowed by Katagiri Kanata,
who made 10 overtakes in one race,
his drive didn't get much attention...
...but no one can deny that finishing fifth
on debut is deserving of high praise.
As the graduates of England's RDRS
steal the spotlight...
...here we have a domestic thoroughbred,
born and raised in Gunma.
Let's keep an eye on him.
Beckenbauer. Katagiri Kanata.
And Sawatari Koki.
The three of you are damn fast.
But compared to how my boss drives
when he's serious on public roads?
You three are no big deal.
I know he's got you beat.
When I think about it in those terms,
I feel a lot more relaxed.
The Godly Fifteen's big three
are nothing to sweat over.
And I'm gonna make it a big four.
And he's through the Hydro Trap!
The 885 gains an attention flag!
I've been wondering this
for a while, but...
Isn't MFG's flag system
a little, well, funky, boss?
You're only noticing that now?
What took you so long?
The algorithm might assign the flags,
but the actual judgment?
It's based on one man's theory
about maximum speed street racing.
The man who built MFG.
So basically,
the system rewards people who drive
in a way my brother would approve of.
Makes sense.
I guess that's why Fujiwara's student
is always getting attention flags.
The blonde girl from yesterday
proved that pretty clearly.
And Sena's starting to reflect that, too.
Did something happen
between you and Sena, boss?
Nothing major.
I just gave him a big dose of something
that'll keep him stable.
I have no idea what that means,
but it seems to have done the trick.
Have we ever had a hotter crop
of rookies than this year's batch?
The 86 on day five! The 624 on day six!
And today, we have the 885!
These big-numbered cars are thriving!
How far will these supernovas
burning with potential go?
Sena roars onward!
In this end-of-summer, high-speed battle,
we've almost reached the climax of
qualifying for Seaside Double Lane.
And here to wrap it up is this man,
his golden number 12 shining
on an all-new white chassis.
The overwhelming favorite
to win it all this season.
Reigning undefeated
on a three-win streak.
A driver strong enough
to see off all challengers.
Yes, the absolute king,
Michael Beckenbauer, has arrived.
That German hottie is
undressing me with his eyes.
It's embarrassing, but fantastic.
Five, four, three, two, one!
And he's off! The invincible
Porsche is on its way!
Ogata Automotive Ltd.
That's a Cayman GT4.
It's only the fourth race, but
we're already facing a "last boss" car.
The vehicle selected by
the absolute king for this race
is, surprisingly, a three-pedal manual
transmission with an H-pattern shifter!
That's just like ours!
Sorry, Wakana. I was hoping
to get some advice.
I don't mind. I wasn't doing
anything this Sunday, anyway.
Well, after what you said, I went home
and rewatched the third race,
and the guest analyst said Kanata
was only participating for one year.
Oh, so Yuka was right?
It's a real shock.
It hasn't come up at home?
My parents took in Kanata assuming
he wouldn't be leaving for a while.
So unless he brings it up,
I doubt they'd even think to ask.
Which means Kanata-san's
the only one who knows for sure.
You'll have to find the guts to ask him.
I could never. I'm too scared.
I don't want to think
about life without Kanata.
Something inside me just wants
to preemptively reject the truth.
I don't want to know.
I don't even wanna think about it.
I've never seen you so worked up
over something, Ren.
It's not confirmed he's leaving yet,
so don't let it get you down.
What would you do, Wakana?
I'd find the courage to ask him,
even if I was afraid.
If he's gonna leave one way or another,
the sooner I accept that and make
the most of the time that's left,
the fewer regrets I'd have.
You're so strong, Wakana.
Well, going through seven boyfriends
teaches you a thing or two.
Wait, seven? She added another
while I wasn't looking.
I really loved some of them.
Just thinking about it makes me
wanna cry to this day.
You really oughta tell him how you feel,
Ren, or I know you'll regret it.
He zooms into Sector 2!
He's managing to keep pace
with the 4 and 86.
What a thrilling run.
This is the usual fare
from the absolute king.
His driving may not look aggressive,
but one glance at his time
has your jaw dropping.
He usually matches his rivals' pace
over the first half,
then kicks it up a notch
and blasts his way to the finish!
No writer could concoct a narrative
so full of catharsis as this man's driving.
Booth to Michael. Things are going
according to your plan so far.
You went through the checkpoint
within two-tenths of the 4's time. Over.
This is easy. Sawatari and Katagiri
are both unremarkable.
Or is it because the GT4
is simply on another level?
He enters Sector 3!
And I feel this is where...
...we'll see something spectacular.
The absolute king's absolute sprint
is about to be unleashed!
He's on the attack!
The 12's clearly moving
differently now!
Booth to Michael.
Time to kick it up a gear.
You're currently 0.3 seconds
behind the 4 car. Over.
What? That can't be right.
Wait a minute. Crap.
Sawatari, you bastard.
I walked right into your trap.
I should've expected your trickery.
I'm going radio silent now.
Keep me updated on our times. Over.
There's still time.
This is where it really begins.
He's now in the middle of Sector 3,
and he's lagging behind
the 4 by 0.28 seconds.
Will he be able to turn this around?
This is odd. This isn't what
we've come to expect from him.
Is the absolute king
struggling here on Double Lane?
Beckenbauer seems to be panicking.
It was the same for Kanata.
Towards the end of Sector 3,
he started losing time to the 4 car.
That means Sawatari Koki
was going uniquely fast.
But how did he manage it?
That braking error is going to cost me.
I've lost this head-to-head.
Now you've done it, Sawatari.
You have my thanks for helping me
find motivation for this race.
And I intend to pay you back
with interest.
He approaches the final corner.
And he's 0.13 seconds behind
without enough road left to catch up!
The king, Beckenbauer, finishes his lap
0.02 seconds off the top spot!
And so, it is Sawatari
in the 4 car
who grabs a second
career pole, the first
of this season.
We also see
that six drivers
have beaten last season's
course record.
Better, but still a way to go.
I'm really scared about
telling Kanata I love him.
Once I do, it could mean
the end of everything.
If I am going to tell him,
it's going to be at the very end.
But if Kanata's gonna go far away...
If I'm never gonna see him again...
Will there be any point
in telling him how I feel?
I have no idea what to do.
I guess I really am a lonely only child
who knows nothing about romance.
I feel sick. Grandma, help.
MF Ghost.
I have to say, that was the most
exciting qualifying I've ever seen.
Everyone's leveled up so much.
I mean, six drivers managed
to beat last year's course record.
Sawatari Koki, in particular,
was absolutely on it.
Speaking of that, how do you think
he managed it, Okuyama-san?
He gambled on a long shot.
The three sections of Double Lane each
place different demands on suspension.
The toll roads of Sector 1
are smooth enough that suspension
set up for circuit racing will work well.
But Sector 3 is the exact opposite.
The roads are a patch job,
sending cars bouncing all over the place.
Now, standard procedure would be
to optimize the suspension for Sector 2,
which is sort of halfway between,
but I'm guessing the 4 was set up
for Sector 3's bumpy roads.
Why would he do that?
Beckenbauer tends to pace himself
based on laps set by his rivals.
The plan was to use that against him.
He probably thought it was a breeze
as he entered Sector 3.
The fact he didn't notice
Sawatari's trap earlier
may have been carelessness from the
absolute king. Or maybe overconfidence?
By comparison, Sawatari tackling
Sector 1 with a flexible suspension
set up for Sector 3
probably deserves praise.
He'll likely go with a more standard
setup for the actual race, but...
Damn, Sawatari.
He's a real tactician. Talk about shrewd.
It's said that out of all five courses,
Double Lane is the hardest on tires.
It'll be tough for Sawatari
to stay ahead even starting on pole.
I imagine Beckenbauer will be raging
after his pride took a knock.
And our own driver clearly
left a lot in the tank, too.
Tomorrow's race is gonna be a wild one.
Please, God. Don't take
Kanata away from me.
I've always thought it strange we haven't
found the backdrop to this picture.
We've found some similar buildings,
but we could never get the right angle.
Don't give up. I know we can find it.
I'll never stop looking.
I'm gonna keep searching until I find it.
When you're trying so hard,
I can hardly give up the search,
since I'm the one who started it.
Right. It's a promise, then.
This might be my last hope.
So, honey, do you have a girlfriend?
I know some girls.
But I'm bad at talking to them.
Why do you ask, Mum?
Can you recall the faces
of those friends clearly?
Of course! You and I are good
at that. Right, Mum?
That's true.
But there will come a time
when you're older and in love
where you'll try to recall someone's face
and struggle to do so.
When people are in love,
something in the brain stops them from
accurately recalling their love's face.
Why does the brain do that?
Well, you get anxious when
you forget something, right?
The anxiety makes you want
to see them again.
You want to be able to look
at your love whenever you want.
That's how the brain works
when you're in love.
Did that happen to you, Mum?
Of course it did.
When I was in love with your father,
that's how it was.
What about me?
Can you remember my face?
Now that I can do.
Do you realize how many portraits
of you I have in my studio?
I don't like that.
Don't be silly. You're the one I care
the most about in the world.
No one else comes close.
But that's a different feeling
than romantic love.
You understand, don't you, my boy?
What Mum told me was true.
I never took a picture like this
before coming to Japan.
Being unable to recall
a certain girl's face clearly...
That's never happened to me before.
I'm in love with Ren.
I'm not sure when it started,
but I'm realizing now that it's true.
I should be happy,
but I feel so unbelievably tense.
After all, I have to leave
Japan eventually.
I'm not sure what to do.
And I have no one I can talk to about it.
I wonder what kind of advice
Mum would give me.
What would Dad say if he were here?
I miss them both so much.
Welcome to all 37.2 million
MFG fans out there.
I'm your commentator, Tanaka Yoji.
The end of summer heralds
a high-speed battle.
The Seaside Double Lane race
is about to begin.
Today's guest in the booth
is Sudo Kyoichi-san.
Sudo-san's had a long career as
one of All-Japan Rally's top competitors...
...and is a trustee on
the MFG steering committee.
Sudo-san, thanks for joining us.
It's a pleasure to be here.
I come from the world of rally,
meaning I won't have much to share
regarding overtaking tactics
and techniques,
so I might not be the best of fits.
But when it comes to driving
at high speeds on public roads,
I know a thing or two.
So I'll do what I can
to share that knowledge.
I hope to enlighten and entertain.
Ren. You're Ren, aren't you?
Emma-san?
I thought I'd seen you somewhere before.
I watched the third race in London and saw
you give Kanata his congratulatory kiss.
I remember thinking, "That girl's got
a nice figure," so you left an impression.
I had no idea.
Huh? Emma Greene's talking to Ren-chan?
I had no idea her English was so good.
I have a request for you, Ren.
If you care about Kanata...
If you care about his future...
Don't try to keep him in Japan.
Racing drivers with talent like his
are incredibly rare.
But the longer he stays here,
the more opportunities he'll miss out on.
And I can't just stand by
and let that happen.
So I'm begging you, Ren. Please.
That's not fair, Emma-san.
That's really, really unfair.
Something wrong, Ren-chan? You look
like you're about to burst into tears.
Kyoko-san.
Being a woman is about being able
to smile even when it hurts.
And our job as Angels is to smile.
Right. Of course.
That's better. You've got this.
Now, let's get to work. Step lively.
It's almost time for the race to start.
Right.
Five minutes to the race start.
The competitors leave the paddock
and head to the start line.
Sudo-san, what will you be
looking out for in today's race?
Good question.
First, I want to see how the big three
interact in the early stages.
In terms of total distance,
Double Lane is the longest of all five races.
There's a major risk of punishing the tires
early on if the pace is too high.
So with their uncanny sprinting skills,
how will this trio play it?
And what will the rookies in fourth and fifth
do as a result of what happens ahead?
Moroboshi Sena and
Emma Greene, you mean?
If they can insert themselves into
the trio's tussle, it'll be absolute chaos.
It's an exciting setup, that's for sure.
Is this a polygon of MFG rivalries
in a new Warring States period?
Ren, give me strength.
I have three cars ahead of me.
And Katagiri Kanata's right in front of me.
I couldn't ask for a better spot.
I've had a plan in mind for this
since qualifying ended.
Katagiri is my sole target for this race.
I'll cling to him like a plunger
and won't let go, no matter what.
Then, on the final lap, we'll duke it out.
I don't care about the other cars.
Or the overall positions in the race.
This is a one-on-one
between me and Katagiri.
The Angels are all lined up.
Sawatari Koki in pole position is guided
slowly through the gate by a drone.
Next comes Beckenbauer in the 12 car.
Then, it's Katagiri Kanata in the 86.
Moroboshi Sena in the 886.
Emma Greene in the 624.
Akaba Kaito in the 2.
Aiba Shun in the 9.
Suppressing the urge to speed off,
these 15 drivers focus
on the drones in front of them,
waiting for that light to turn green.
And the 16, our final competitor,
passes through the gate!
And there's the green!
Listen to that cacophony!
The waves in Sagami Bay will be sent back
to the sea by the sheer intensity!
Next time, Turn 35: The Strongest Train.