Commencing final graft.
It's stable.
Once this phase is complete,
Knives will reawaken.
When he does—
He will absolutely and utterly
return this world to nothing.
You mean he has the power he needs
to enact the Genesis Flood Big Fall?
More than enough.
After merging with countless plants...
he is a cluster of unfathomable energy.
And so...
Lord Knives will write
a new Book of Genesis.
He will become a true god.
Indeed.
It's been a long, long journey.
All that remains of Knives's followers
are you, Elendira, Ninelives, and myself.
Vash the Stampede must be returned to us.
The twins are only complete when together.
They need each other to fill
what's missing of themselves.
Same for the Eye of Michael.
Hey, Ninelives...
It's odd, isn't it?
Lord Knives is about to achieve his goal
of turning this planet
into a paradise for plants, but...
Somehow, he seems to be sad about it.
Tell me, Lord Knives.
Are we, well...
not good enough?
He's right here,
yet he feels so distant...
I hope I'm just overthinking.
Is this...
What is it?
I feel it.
Feel what?
Vash the Stampede.
What is this?
I see. He's cornered
and trying to lure us out.
That saves us the hassle of looking for him.
Okay, let's go.
Wait, hold on. You can't just—
Doctor, you just shut up and fly the Ark.
Elendira, where is he?
Where's Vash the Stampede?
He's at...
How'd it go, Vash?
Yeah, pretty sure I got through
to him... I think.
Then now we wait.
This is where you first landed, right?
Where our journey...
Where this hell began.
How could you?
You killed even Rem!
You're my accomplice.
Right, Vash?
It's the appropriate place
to put an end to everything.
This hell, our journey...
Rem's regrets.
Yeah. Let's settle things
with Millions Knives.
Still... what really is this "paradise
for plants" he kept talking about?
What?
Well, he said he wanted to wipe out
all humans on the planet
and make every plant an Independent.
But is that truly a paradise for plants?
Is that what the plants want?
I don't know.
Some emotions come through to me.
But their inner hearts,
what they truly think and desire...
Not even I can know that for sure.
If you really don't know,
then nobody does.
Then what is Knives basing all of this on?
It's just what he wants.
What Meryl said before...
The desire to learn is what's important.
Have I really tried to understand plants?
That'd include Knives...
Wait, did I say something weird?
Well, no.
There's no need for that.
Who'd blame us for not wanting
to understand that?
I don't see anything yet.
Meryl? Is something wrong?
Three years.
Huh?
It feels like a long,
long time has passed...
But it's only been three years.
Ah, since Lost JuLai?
One, two, three...
Wow, you're right! Only three years!
It feels like such a long time ago.
It weighs on even us like that.
For Vash, these three years...
No, the past 150 years...
Just how long and painful
was that journey?
I can only hope that wherever he reaches
at the end of this long,
torturous road is peaceful.
Razlo?
All these fools lack faith.
I'll take this.
I need to vindicate myself.
What was that for?
Remember, don't kill him.
Did you hear what I just said?
I'm going to vindicate myself.
Vash the Stampede needs
to be punished appropriately.
Punished?
That's why I'm going to use this.
I must show how deep my faith runs.
Thank you for your kind invitation.
Or rather, shouldn't you be thanking me
for coming all the way out here?
Legato Bluesummers.
You're not the one we're here for.
I know that, of course.
But if you want to stop Lord Knives,
you'll have to get through me first.
What a cliché. I'm almost
disgusted with myself—
So hasty. People don't like that.
Whatever!
Warnings are useless.
If you're going to shoot, shoot to kill.
Whoa there.
Razlo the Tri-Punisher of Death...
We raised you. Is this how you thank us?
This is my way of returning the favor!
Also, my name isn't Razlo! It's Livio!
Why are you fighting with that weapon?
I must volunteer to bear
the cross, feel the pain,
and climb the hill of Golgotha
subjected to ridicule and scorn.
And when I reach the site
of my execution, I shall perish.
You should study up on the
history of Earth. Of mankind.
I'll get right on that...
after I take you down!
Is this all we can do?
Just watch from here?
But what can we even do from here?
I know! I know, but...
It's almost like we could just hop on.
Huh?
Vash the Stampede!
Legato Bluesummers!
Stupidity in numbers.
What a useless pile of big oafs.
But they're almost invincible.
We've gotta take out the blue-haired freak
and get to the Ark...
I'll handle Ninelives.
Nico, please help Vash!
Huh?
I can't fell them, but I'll hold them off!
Don't push yourself too hard, Livio.
You watch out too, Nico!
Not supposed to worry
about your big brother, dumbass!
Take this...
and go down!
That idiot.
Like I said, shoot to kill, okay?
Vash the Stampede,
you still don't want to kill anyone.
That's right.
That won't do.
You have to want to kill me.
It's the only way to cleanse
your sin-soaked body.
From the transgression of tormenting and
saddening Lord Knives for over 150 years.
I know all too well how saddened
he was when you betrayed him.
Don't be stupid. Nai would never—
Lord Knives is sad!
Why don't you understand?!
Have you ever even stopped
to think about how he feels?
Instead of just forcing your feelings
and empty words onto him...
Have you ever really, actually thought
about how Lord Knives feels?
Have you, even once?
Vash the Stampede!
Wolfwood...
Bluetop! I didn't realize
you were such a brat.
Huh?
No matter how much you talk,
people never truly comprehend one another!
Grow up!
But... can you teach me?
I want to understand.
I want to try to understand.
What you're thinking...
What Nai is really thinking.
Sure, I'll teach you.
If you can defeat me, I will then!
Wolfwood!
This is...
the end!
Bluetop...
I'll be honest. That was close.
So I'll be generous.
I'll tell you how I really feel.
Wolfwood...
The Eye of Michael's teachings are simple.
They say, "Praise our two gods."
Two of them. The first is,
of course, Lord Knives.
The other is...
Yes, Vash the Stampede.
I met our god Lord Knives
and was fulfilled.
I am compelled to believe, worship,
and follow the word of Lord Knives.
How blessed that is.
And on top of that,
to have yet another god!
It's... It's so wonderful!
Which is why, Vash the Stampede...
I couldn't wait to meet you!
What are you even...
Yet you turned out to be
the god of betrayal.
You saddened and tormented
our other god, Lord Knives!
Your sins are too grave...
And so you must be punished.
You must pay the highest price thinkable,
endure the worst pain imaginable.
Only then will you be cleansed of your sin.
What...
Then, when you are pure
of heart and body at last,
you will finally be ready to stand
beside Lord Knives as our other god.
Our gods will finally descend upon
the Eye of Michael and wipe out the world.
Oh, could there be any greater happiness?
The hour of judgment
is upon you, Lord Vash.
The only thing you can move now
is your trigger finger.
The Punisher will soon die.
If you want to save him...
You must, by your own will,
pull that trigger and kill me.
Needle-noggin...
Now, kill me! Kill a human!
For the first time of your own will!
This is my Golgotha.
And Lord Knives will know
how deep my faith is.
Someone has to bring the fangs.
Otherwise, someone else pays in tears.
Year 113, July 20th
One day until the immigrant fleet arrives
It's you. Just you and me.
That's all this world needs.