HAPPY BIRTHDAY
Happy birthday to you!
Okay, blow out the candles!
Happy birthday!
What's this about?
Ramaga told you, remember?
"Gai, you turn fifteen today."
We ignored it then,
but it's a shame to waste a birthday.
Here. For you.
MISTER YAKISOBA NOODLES
CREAM SODA FLAVOR, PINEAPPLE FLAVOR,
CHOCOLATE BANANA FLAVOR, CHOCOLATE PARFAIT FLAVOR
Now this gets me all fired up!
I got you a retro game from the 80s.
Whoa!
I got you my favorite face massager!
You mean the one you've been using?
Yeah! Give your face a nice,
good rub every day. Rub, rub, rub!
I'll pass.
What gives?!
It even cleans your pores!
Listen, nobody wants a massager
some dude's been using.
Here. From me and Kaito.
"Rock Hara Junior College"?
But Kaito loves this!
Are you sure? He bit my head off
when I tried to watch it.
Oh, really?
I just rummaged through his room
and thought it looked good.
You don't mind, right?
Nah.
Seriously?
Hey, is it me, or has Kaito been
acting weird since yesterday?
That bombshell Mr. Ujihara
dropped hit him hard.
Oh.
It's no coincidence that you orphans
were brought up here
nor that you've come together
again after leaving.
It was all predetermined.
It's your destiny.
Ujihara...
This guy went through
the same training I did.
For real?!
Samurai Troopers need righteous spirits
and advanced combat skills to don armor.
You, in particular, were chosen to...
No! I'm losing control!
The mirror is about to possess me!
I'll record more when I'm myself again!
Yeah, that was a bombshell all right.
Who knew that Shion and Kaito
were orphans, too?
We must now perform the ritual to
invoke the Armor of the Supreme Emperor!
Now, Armor of the Supreme Emperor!
Rise again!
What's the holdup?
That's weird...
O Armor of the Supreme Emperor, awaken!
Come to us! Get over here! Pretty please?
Come on, little Supremy-wemy,
what's the matter?
This is going nowhere.
Hey, why don't you ask
that Sagume girl from before?
Don't call her "that Sagume girl"!
Still, I bet asking her would save time.
Y-You think so?
Oh, fine.
O Divine World! Reveal to me the path!
We have the Three Sacred Treasures,
yet the Armor of the
Supreme Emperor eludes us.
Would you please deign to tell us why?
The Three Sacred Treasures
you possess are not yet complete.
What do you mean by "not yet complete"?
The Sword of Domination remains
little more than a Demon Sword.
To restore its rightful luster,
you require the aid of White Blaze.
White Blaze...
Go to its dwelling place.
There, the way will open to you.
What's White Blaze?
A sacred beast that saved Japan alongside
the Samurai Troopers 35 years ago.
He was especially close with Jun.
Great. Where is he now?
He's gone.
White Blaze...
is dead.
I met White Blaze during
the Demon Outbreak 35 years ago.
We overcame many trials together
and strengthened our bond.
EPISODE VIII
AGAIN
Even after the battle ended
and peace was restored,
White Blaze and I were inseparable.
At home,
at school,
even at job interviews.
Were you nuts?!
Hence I could never land a job.
I'll bet not.
Then, on Nasti's advice,
I went on a spiritual training journey.
And again, White Blaze came with me.
I endured grueling ascetic practices
and gained a calling as a conduit
between the Divine World and ours.
SENGOKU UNIVERSITY
But five years ago, while researching the
Sacred Treasures at Sengoku University,
I heard a revelation
from the Divine World, and...
What?!
What did you push him off for?!
That heartwarming story took
a sharp turn into psychological horror.
I only did what the revelation told me to.
What exactly did it say?
No comment.
Whatever.
You did it to save your own skin.
It wasn't like that!
Now, now. So, that's how White Blaze died?
No.
He came back in a second.
Wait, so he's alive?
Yup.
I ended up selling him
to the head of a zoo for 30,000 yen.
Why did you say he was dead, then?!
I sold White Blaze!
I cut ties with him! He's dead to me!
Gimme a break!
But we need White Blaze to make
the Sword of Domination count, right?
So we've gotta go anyway.
Well, when you put it like that...
Inmei, Gomei, Shimei, Gaimei.
I trust you know what must be done.
Please, allow me.
So, now Anayama has fallen...
Despite interference
from the Divine World,
the plan is proceeding smoothly.
Emperor Ramaga, I beg your leave
to ask a question.
Sasuke!
You commanded us to stand by
in order to obtain the Armor
of the Supreme Emperor.
So tell me...
How was Anayama's death
part of your plan?!
Because after the fact, I—
You be quiet!
The Armor of the Supreme Emperor
will lead all the world to its doom.
However, Gai lacks the capacity
to wield it as he is now.
So I shall use the Ten Warriors
to discipline him
and create a Puppet worthy of me.
You would command us
to sacrifice ourselves?
Not all of you.
You mean the Last Name Group?
If the Last Name Group
were to defeat the prince...
I would abandon Gai.
I have no need of such a feeble Puppet.
Rock Hara Junior College rules.
Yeah, they get me all fired up!
Who said you could watch that?!
It's mine now, so what's the problem?
I already told you that was a mix-up!
What's your deal?
I was just getting into it.
Lend me something else, then.
This is all I've got.
Rock Hara Junior College is a mystery
idol group who could pop up anywhere.
They don't announce their shows,
and they never archive anything.
It's a miracle a Commoner
managed to record this one.
A "Commoner"?
It's what we call serious
Rock Hara Junior College fans.
Then from today on, we're Commoners, too.
Don't you dare use that name lightly.
Damn it. Why now of all times?
Still not over being an orphan?
Doesn't it bother you?
I knew my parents and I
weren't related by blood.
At this point, I'm like, "So what?"
That's pretty rock 'n' roll.
Those were my grandmother's last words.
"Live a rock 'n' roll life."
I always trusted her,
but she had me totally fooled.
And?
My dad's out to kill me.
Compared to that, it's no big deal.
What would you know?
They say it's time we got
looking for White Blaze.
Is something wrong?
Hey, what gives?
Please, wake up.
Where's Jun?
He and the boys went to the zoo
where White Blaze is.
I see.
I hope they find him.
White Blaze is here?
Talk about grisly.
All the animals have either
escaped or been killed.
I bet White Blaze is gone, too.
He'll be here. I promised
I'd come back for him.
I'm amazed you're that confident
after selling him for 30,000 yen.
Since the Puppets all woke up at once...
One of the Ten Warriors must be here!
Unno...
So it's your turn!
My prince, I must ask you to die here.
Oath of Faith, emissary of Water!
FAITH
Armor of Water!
So all of us Last-Namers
are to be sacrificed to the prince?
But he said he will give up
on the prince if we win.
Th-Then let's all go after him together!
No. Emperor Ramaga won't
sit idly by if we defy his orders.
Let me see to this.
Are you sure you don't want to go?
I don't want to lose any more
comrades if I can help it.
Sasuke, so long as Unno is your
comrade, have faith in him.
They just keep coming!
Our only shot is to take down
the guy controlling them!
Kaito, don't get ahead of yourself!
Mimic Arrow!
Kaito!
I have only begun to fight!
Damn it!
Fine! I'll try again!
Stop! You can't take him alone!
Try to stay calm!
I am calm!
Oh, yeah?
You look like you're feeling desperate
and betrayed by your grandma to me.
Shows what you know!
WISDOM
Secret Art:
Gale Force Break!
TIGER FOREST
Stop!
White Blaze?
That's White Blaze?
What is that power?
Something's wrong.
That's not the White Blaze I—
What happened to you, White Blaze?!
Jun!
Don't worry about me!
It's all my own fault.
You were always there for me, but I...
Jun Yamano,
your actions will cause disaster.
The Divine World...
Those you trust will be cursed,
and the world will hurtle toward its doom.
If you wish to avert this,
keep all at a distance
and hide yourself away.
You'd have been cursed if you'd stayed
with me, so I pushed you away!
I thought I was doing right by you!
But I was wrong!
I was just running away
without even trying to protect you!
I'm sorry, White Blaze.
White Blaze...?
To think that my Heavenly Arts
would have no effect...
Who're you?!
I am Inmei of the Divine World.
I have come at Lady Sagume's command.
I cast my Heavenly Arts on
White Blaze to test your strength,
but it appears I miscalculated somewhat.
SENGOKU UNIVERSITY
What the...?
What's that black stuff?!
The power of Corruption.
When it fully suffuses the beast,
it will prove fatal.
Cut down White Blaze with the Sword
of Domination before that happens.
Thus may you cleanse the Corruption.
We cannot entrust the Armor of
the Supreme Emperor to the helpless.
Please wait!
Even if you're from the Divine World—
Relax. I promise we'll save him.
You guys...
Hey.
Listening to Jun's story got me thinking.
Sometimes you lie to someone 'cause
you want them to be happy, huh?
What's your point?
Maybe fooling you was tough on her, too.
Humans sure love to make
things harder for themselves.
Hey, that's a Rock Hara
Junior College song!
Like I know what that means!
Wait, what?!
Huh? How come Musashi
knows the words, too?
FAITH
JUSTICE, RIGHTEOUSNESS,
FAITH, WISDOM, GRACE
Secret Art:
RIGHTEOUSNESS
Blaze Slash!
White Blaze!
So this is its "rightful luster."
Damn it!
We suffered a brief interruption,
but my prince, your life is mine!
What?!
I can see! I can see everything!
I call this Operation: the Sword of
Domination Just Made Me Untouchable!
Yeah, that's not an operation, but go you!
Get him.
Burn!
I cannot afford to lose!
Get him, Gai!
Forgive me, my friends...
U-Unno!
You were awesome, Gai!
Now we can—
This power... belongs to me.
Uh, Gai?
Such is the power of
the Sword of Domination.
Gather the Three Sacred
Treasures and pray.
You will bring the armor's power
nearer to awakening.
However, to manifest the Armor
of the Supreme Emperor,
RIGHTEOUSNESS, JUSTICE,
GRACE, WISDOM, FAITH
all five of you must harmonize
your energies at their peak.
So we can't bust out the Armor
of the Supreme Emperor yet?
I know that you will
succeed in obtaining it.
White Blaze...
White Blaze!
Ow, ow, ow!
Why are you biting me?! That hurts!
Maybe he took you selling him
for thirty grand personally?
Oh, come on!
That was the first time you
called Gai by name, wasn't it?
He helped me get over myself.
Granny, I'll live a rock 'n' roll life.
I've followed your instructions
all this time.
Now it's your turn to keep
your end of the bargain.
Who are you talking to?
What do you mean?
Don't try to play dumb.
I visited Sengoku University, where
Jun studied the Three Sacred Treasures.
The Jewel of Conquest can communicate
with other worlds, can't it?
Who are you working with?
Translation\h\h\h\h\h\hWilliam Varteresian
Timing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Editing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRiley Dalton
Quality Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSMR
Translation Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMichelle Tymon
EPISODE IX
OUTBREAK
Armor races through your heart.