Thanks for waiting.
So, my fave's doing a bunch
of shows on their national tour.
Uh-huh.
I can't go to every show, but I want
to at least try to go to the ones nearby.
Hey. Are you listening?
Huh?
You've been answering me
with simple responses.
Sorry. Something's on my mind.
I'm here for you if something's up.
Recently, someone told me,
"That's not fair." And...
Were they right?
I think so, yeah.
I couldn't say anything back.
I've been thinking about it since then,
and I still can't find the answer.
Before I know it,
I start thinking about it.
I see.
It seems like you've experienced it, too.
The deeper you go into adulthood...
No matter how much you fall in love,
the feeling of sadness when you part
or the pain when you hurt someone...
It gets harder to find
an answer for them.
Why do you look so troubled?
Here.
Wow! Looks yummy!
A Margherita pizza with extra tomatoes.
Is that something off-menu?
Yup. A special service.
You remind me more of Hoshikawa-sensei.
Ugh.
Well, enjoy your meal.
Oh. By the way, Mizuho.
Hm?
Are you free this weekend?
Sorry for the wait, Mizuho.
Hop in.
We're taking your car?
Are we going somewhere?
Yup. For a gourmet tour around Enoshima!
You said you were working
on new menu items.
I thought you'd feed me
a bunch of stuff at your restaurant.
It's important to try different foods
when developing new menu items.
You're right.
Wait. But what about the restaurant?
Yeah. Big Bro's got it covered today.
Togo!
Yo. It's been a while.
Have fun. You can leave things
to your magnificent big bro.
Thanks, Togo!
We should catch up sometime, too.
For sure.
Let's get going, Mizuho!
I haven't seen him in a while,
but I'm glad he seems to be doing fine.
Yeah. He's having fun as always.
Does he occasionally help out
with the restaurant like that?
Yup.
Mostly on holidays and during busy seasons.
His students and their families
visit as customers, too.
Is that so?
I'm not surprised Togo-sensei's so popular.
You're right.
I'm thinking of dropping out of college
and taking over the restaurant.
What?
So go back to being a teacher.
That's what this is about?
Don't worry about me.
I'm not attached to being a teacher.
I like what I'm doing
with my current work.
Not that there's anything
I can't do in this world.
Stop hiding your true feelings like that.
You always try to carry
the workload all by yourself.
Just tell us.
There are types of "love"
that aren't spoken, you know.
I suppose from your point of view
it looks like I'm the only one
shouldering everything.
But this is something I decided on my own.
Because family is important to me.
So this isn't something
you should worry about.
I also decided this on my own.
I'm even licensed to be a chef now.
I'm not doing this for you.
This is something I want to do.
That's why I want you to do
what you want to do, bro.
Go back to being a teacher.
You got me.
I always thought I had to
protect you. But now...
Before I knew it,
you also became an adult.
I admit defeat.
Thanks.
Oh yeah.
I'm leaving the
welcome-back-to-work gifts to you.
Maybe something like
homemade Italian flan?
Why's it on me?
Can't you do this for your kind big bro?
Cut it out.
If we want food we can walk
around with, this is the place!
Is there anything you want, Syugo?
Nah. Let's go to places
you want to go.
Then we should get takoyaki first!
Watch out! Mizuho!
Be careful. You need to look ahead.
Sorry, sorry. I'll be more careful.
Syugo?
I just thought that maybe we
should keep holding hands like this.
I-I'm not a little kid.
This is embarrassing.
Takoyaki, right?
C'mon. Let's go.
Wait up! Syugo!
You've got nori on you, Mizuho.
What? No way!
Kidding!
Hey!
These are viral on social media.
They are?
But it tastes average, right?
Nuh-uh! They're delicious!
Why don't you try making something
that looks interesting, too?
I'll think about it.
So good!
We ate a lot.
Let's take a break.
Okay!
The breeze feels nice.
Yeah.
Oh! Look!
There were hang gliders back then, too.
I love this view the most.
Do you remember?
Is that so?
Back then... I remember
wanting to be number one.
Well, guess you top-ranking guys
wouldn't understand.
The real thrill of romance...
Is the bystander!
Understand?
And what truly makes romance is...
one-sided love!
Syugo?
Nah, nothing.
Let's hit up the next place.
What's next?
The aquarium.
Yay! I haven't been there in a while!
We saw the dolphin show
last time with everyone.
Well, today it's just you and me.
Hm? Yeah!
Excuse me. Can you take a photo of us?
Would you like to join our picture
while you're at it?
Sorry, but I'm with someone important.
Let's go, Mizuho.
I used to go up and down these steps
effortlessly back in the day.
You need to work out more. Here.
Today... Syugo's acting a bit...
Actually, you're right.
You've changed from when
we were younger, Mizuho.
You've gotten prettier.
Careful!
You okay?
Sorry, I think I've done it now.
Did you twist it?
My bad. I forgot
that you're wearing heels.
You must have been exhausted
from all that walking.
That's not... It's not your fault.
Stay still.
Whoa! Syugo!
If you move, you'll fall.
Put me down!
I can walk just fine!
Even though you twisted your ankle
and are wearing heels?
Wow! Look!
It's like a drama!
Dang! He's so cool!
The car's not far.
We can go to the aquarium some other day.
Let's go home for today.
I'll... be in your care...
Thank you, Syugo.
Want me to take you to the hospital?
Nope.
I think it'll calm down once
I apply a compress to it.
Then let's tend to it at home.
I can cook you something good
while I'm at it.
Something's off about him after all...
Okay.
Let me help.
I told you to stay put.
The pain's not so bad
since you treated me.
Then you're on soup duty.
Roger!
Wanna taste test?
It's good.
Right?
I'm the one who made it,
so of course it is.
Your meals are really something special.
Sure, the pizza we had
in Enoshima today was great,
but your pizzas are still the best.
If you like them that much,
want me to feed them to you every day?
You'd do that?
I'd be the happiest girl.
Yeah.
I can make you happy.
I could have made dessert
if we had more time.
I'm just happy I got to
eat your delicious food.
Next time, I'll make you
a special full course meal.
Yay!
You're the greatest, Syugo-sama!
That's me.
The most generous and humorous
chef of all time: Syugo-sama!
I didn't say all of that.
Do you think that the current me
is more like the main lead
instead of a bystander?
What's this about being a bystander?
This is yummy.
Everything you touch
turns delicious, Syugo.
What's that supposed to
mean, Mizuho? Huh?
Oh. This?
The manga writer
I'm in charge of right now is...
She just uploaded the draft.
Take a look.
You can definitely do it!
You're gonna win today!
This setting. It's the
Mitsuman Swimming School.
That takes me back.
Right?
You can definitely do it!
You're gonna win today!
I joined the writer there
for an interview the other day.
Oh.
Kizuki?
Turns out that the interviewee was Kizuki.
She took a few photos for reference.
How was he?
He was super lively.
Almost blinding.
I felt like I'd been transported back to
our high school days just looking at him.
Even in the future, Kizuki's
always gonna be on Mizuho's mind...
How nostalgic.
Back then, every day was shimmering...
I'm sure those days
were my adolescence...
I want to tell her.
Something I've been meaning to say.
Mizuho—
I was able to think about
how I don't want to lose, either.
You're right. I also don't want to lose.
I want to be the one closest to Mizuho.
I want to be her number one.
Mizuho.
There's something I've been meaning
to say to you for a while now.
Syugo?
Even if Kizuki's all she sees...
Even if this is something
that would bother her...
Mizuho. Will you...
Oh. I think it's my dad.
Your dad?
Is he in Tokyo right now?
Yup.
Kizuki?
Why's Kizuki here?
I-I don't know.
Sorry for showing up suddenly, Mizuho.
What's wrong?
You see...
Why's Syugo here?
That's my line.
Hold on, you two.
So? Did you need something?
Well...
I thought I'd stop by before practice.
I wanted to tell you something, Mizuho.
Kizuki!
I'm gonna be in a competition.
Really?
Congratulations, Kizuki!
Thanks.
I wanted to tell you directly, Mizuho.
I also wanted to see your face.
I see... You'll be able to compete.
I'm rooting for you, too.
Do your best, Kizuki.
What are you doing with Syugo, Mizuho?
Huh? Um...
We went on a date around Enoshima,
made dinner together,
and now it's our post-meal coffee break.
Right? Mizuho?
Uh-huh.
Maybe I'll even spend the night
with her while I'm at it.
What?!
Come on!
He's just spouting his usual jokes!
This might be my work calling.
Sorry, I'm going to go check.
Nishino
Um...
I'm going home.
Oh, okay.
Oh. I almost forgot.
I love you, Mizuho!
He always does as he pleases.
For real. What do we do with him?
He always acts impulsively
and does whatever he pleases.
By the way, Syugo.
You were about to say something before.
What did you want to say?
Mizuho. I...
I want to tell her.
I don't ever want to let Mizuho go.
I...
I want you to keep smiling.
I want you to be happy.
What?
What's up with you, Syugo?
Nothing.
Isn't it common sense to be nice
to my childhood friend
who tagged along with me
for work research?
You were a big help today. Thanks.
I also had a lot of fun.
Let's do it again sometime.
What's wrong? Did you forget something?
Oh, no. It's nothing.
Be careful with your leg.
Later.
Yup. See you.
Kizuki...
He's always straightforward
about his feelings
and hogs Mizuho all to himself.
Sorry, Mizuho.
I can't let this one thing go.
But I'll end these feelings.
Next up is this song:
"My Regretful Heart."
Shiraishi-chan.
If I put up my courage but get rejected,
would you comfort me?
No.
But...
I'll play this song for you.
He'll definitely regret it
when he's older.
Nope.
I don't regret anything at all.
Hello? This is Nishino.
This is the To-Ou Medical
University Hospital.
Your family member, Tsuyoshi
Nishino-san has been hospitalized.
What?
He's currently being examined
and treated here at the hospital.
But we're calling you to ask that
a family member can come to the hospital
so we can explain the patient's condition
and discuss future treatment options.
Emergency Entrance
Nishino-san!
Sir! Can you hear me?
# 23 The Proposal