Okay, then. I have no other option!
A head-on fist fight!
This is a duel between two chiefs!
Come at me, head on!
Or are you scared?!
You dare call me scared?!
He took the bait!
Get wrecked!
I'm reaching my limit.
This is my...
Dragon Counter!
Dragon Punch has gone
from level two to level three.
I won!
He countered me back?!
You have received 162 experience points.
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
you have earned an additional
162 experience points.
Young Plague Dragon
has gone from level 37 to level 39.
You have gained
the title Clan Boss, level one.
Oh pain, become stronger and turn into courage
What was I born as?
The world I reached out and touched
Shines sadly and delicately
That is exactly why, no more pains
The pulse of the future in this place
Once felt, cannot be stopped
Chase after the light
Gliding Claw
Now wanting to protect someone
Right... There's no losing and no giving up
Gliding Claw
I understood that little me has changed
Oh pain, become stronger and turn into courage
Where am I?
Black Lizard!
Is this our cave?
Uh... let's see...
I was battling the Giant Orangurang,
we started fist-fighting, and then...
View stats!
Young Plague Dragon
Status: Normal
My level went up?!
So does that mean...
I won?
Heck yeah! I did it!
You're the one
who brought me back here, huh?
How in the world did you manage that?
What is it?
Why are those guys here?!
Oh, I get it!
They've come to avenge their boss!
W-wait a darn minute.
Am I crazy?
They're acting like I'm the boss now!
Oh, let me guess...
Title Skills
Clan Boss
And there it is.
I beat the big guy
and then obtained this title...
which means I've become their boss.
Calm down.
They don't want to fight.
It looks like
they want to be my followers.
This is lucky.
We can use them as gofers
to handle the busy work!
Sound good?
Did you guys bring all this here?
This is awesome!
You guys are amazing!
You want that?
Go ahead, eat it.
No need to go out hunting today.
Guess I'll refresh my supply of jerky.
Are you curious about this?
Since they're so hungry for it...
I'll make THEM do the cooking!
Ready? First, cut the meat.
Then, put the sliced meat into the pot.
Next, add salt and spices.
After that, mix and rub it all in...
and let it rest for a while.
That'll make a good start. Got it?
Good. Now give it a try.
Something feels weird...
What's up with her?
Anyways,
I can put them in charge of my jerky.
But shucks, if I don't have to hunt,
it leaves me with nothing to do.
Considering I have a bunch
of new roommates,
I guess I'll have to store even more food?
In that case, I need more pots.
You wanna know what I'm doing?
I'm going to make one of those from clay.
Wanna give it a try?
Nimble
Come to think of it,
these guys have a skill called "Nimble."
And they've got long, slim fingers.
I hate to admit it, but they
can make these better than I can, huh?
Okay, let me show you how it's done.
And that's it!
Now it's your turn.
The clay's right over there.
Sweet.
Now I've got someone
in charge of ceramics.
What are you doing?
You can't do anything with those hands...
or, front legs, can you?
Was she interested in ceramics as well?
Gosh.
She could've just said so.
You two are next.
Take these.
Clay bear clay is the real deal.
I made these on a whim
and they turned out tougher than expected!
You're in charge of widening this cave.
Got that?
They're already damn good at using tools!
The crew still isn't here yet, huh?
Daz and Romeena
should have already gotten the message.
I'm sure they'll hurry over
after their current request is done.
It's still crazy
we ran across a Plague Dragon.
It really scared me.
That cave was suspicious enough.
Something is definitely going on
in the forest.
We must look into it more.
I Went on a Date and Got Ditched
What, morning already?
What's wrong?! An enemy?
M-my body feels heavy.
Well, no wonder I can't move.
And worse yet, they stink.
Hey guys! Gimme some space!
Also, wake up!
Yeesh.
They're not getting up anytime soon.
Guess I'll give up and go back to sleep.
What is it?!
What's wrong with him?
View stats!
Special Venom (Major)
Now you've gone and done it!
Uh, nice?
No, not nice!
Hurry up and give him the antidote,
please!
I get you're frustrated
with the Orangurangs.
But poisoning them like that
is taking it too far.
Oh, I get it.
Sorry I haven't been giving you
any attention.
I know!
Let's go out hunting today, 'kay?
You and I can team up!
Like we always do!
She'll feel better if we spend
the whole day together, I'm sure of it!
It's been a few days since
those adventurers went into the forest,
but there's been absolutely
no word from them.
It's up to me.
I have to look for Mr. Doz.
I'm sorry, Miss Marielle.
Now that I think about it, I'm just
one level away from evolving again.
So I wanna farm more experience.
And get more stuff to spruce up my cave.
And find more fruits and veggies!
Man, exploring the forest is really fun!
You agree right, Black Lizard?
Huh? What's got you down?
Everybody else is having a good time.
They just can't get enough
of using those weapons, huh?
Seems like it gives
their attack power a pretty big boost.
I can't wait to see
how strong they are now!
Let me know if you spot any prey.
Okay, Black Lizard?
You good? Uh...
Black Lizard? Buddy?
Weird. Did I do something wrong?
It's nothing new, but it still sucks
that we don't speak the same language.
What's wrong?! An enemy?
This'll be a good warm up.
Let's get 'em!
Whoa! They can really kick butt!
Don't you think they're amazing?
Eh?
Wait a second, hey!
No luck here, either.
I think I've gone a little too far.
I need to turn back soon.
Mr. Doz!
Please wait!
Mr. Doz! Mr. Doz!
I'm sorry for giving
the Orangurangs so much attention.
But I'm their boss now, you know?
It's nothing personal, okay?
Black Lizard...
Okay!
Next time,
we'll go hunting all by ourselves.
The others will stay in the cave.
Sound good?
I'll keep you safe.
It's a promise!
Just so you know,
I consider you the
most important thing in my life right now.
No matter what happens in the future,
that will never change.
Ever.
That voice. I've heard it before.
It's Myria!
Is she in trouble again?!
Whatever the case, I gotta get to her!
But what if she's with other humans?
Oh, come on!
I'm not a threat to you!
Help!
No, I'm just-
Please, listen to me!
I'm trying to help her!
You just stay here. Got it?
Hang tight, Myria! I'm on the way!
Aw, jeez!
I told you to stay put!
Better speed up!
Hey!
It's dangerous
to go that fast at your level!
See? What did I tell you?!
Are you all right?!
You've got plenty of HP left. Good.
Myria!
I'm sorry.
I meant it when I said
you're important to me, Black Lizard.
But if Myria is in danger,
I have to help her!
The title Itty Bitty Hero has gone
from level two to level three.
Wrongdoer has gone
from level three to level four.
Gee, thanks, Divine Voice.
You have the most
charming personality ever.
Myria, please be okay!
I just barely made it in time.
That figures.
She doesn't recognize me.
Why would she?
Mahawolf. Rank D-.
It can use its third eye
to share visual information
with nearby members of the pack.
They use this ability
to cooperate and hunt down prey.
Okay. So, I should expect
more of them coming soon.
What are their stats?
There is some information
that the View Stats skill
cannot provide at level five.
Status
What's up with this weird status?
Hold up, I remember
something like this happening before.
Baby Breath!
Oh crud!
I release a poison powder
when I spread my wings!
View stats.
Myria
Earth Human
Status: Normal
Thank goodness, looks like she's okay.
Maybe because my skill
is such a low level?
N-no...
Stay away from me!
Sigh.
She's acting like the Demon King
just barged in while she was
getting robbed by bandits.
Definitely hurts a little.
Myria, it's me! Please recognize me!
You have gained 36 experience points.
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
you have earned an additional 36 experience points.
Oh, come on!
This is hardly the time!
Young Plague Dragon
has gone from level 39 to level 40.
Please, just shut up for a second! I'm begging you!
You have maxed out your level.
Huh? Eh?
You have met the requirements for evolution.
I said shut up, you damn voice!
Huh?
R-rooarr!
Roarr!
Rar. Rar. Rarr!
Could she be...
imitating what I did back then?
Raarr! Roar rarr rarr!
Roaar! Rar rarr!
Roaarr! Raarr!
I will protect you, Myria.
No matter what!
Can you tell me? The words I believed
Our changes can be never ending
Always remember the page that's lost its promise
Of our eternal story
Don't let nobody bring you down
Release the break of dawn
If the memory is still beautiful
Left there, through the rain
Even emotions from feeling the way forward
Always keep them in mind
There's no going back
Branded onto the heart
On first impulse
Until it overwhelms
A quiet expression of determination
Is the beginning of the revolution, now
Let's start 3, 2, 1 GO!!
Can you tell me? The words I believed
Our changes can be never ending
Always remember the page that's lost its promise
Of our eternal story
Destiny yet to be fulfilled
And the possibility it presents
We fly together to somewhere that isn't here
Until morning comes
Spread your wings
Until you someday disappear into the sky
I Realized I Had No Name
"I Realized I Had No Name"!
Get stronger.