m 0 0 l 0 102 32 102 b 3 75 3 32 32 0
OSHI NO KO
Hikaru Kamiki.
When Ai got pregnant at sixteen,
he was a fifteen-year-old middle schooler.
And you'd have to go even further back,
to twenty years ago.
So Himekawa-san was conceived
when he was... eleven?
Oh my god.
Showbiz has a checkered history with
tons of revolting scandals like this one.
It's a world of beauty and glamour,
but it also has a dark, ugly side.
I guess this is why they say
to let the sleeping dead lie.
Even if Kamiki is the mastermind
and is forced to confess,
he would've been a minor at the time,
so he wouldn't get jail time.
Should Aqua-kun find him, he'll have
no way to legally bring him to justice.
Meaning the only way for him to get
revenge will be with his own two hands.
I can't let Aqua-kun and Kamiki
make contact, no matter what.
I'll have to deal with this myself.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Do you know what time
rehearsal is tomorrow?
I think the old man said
it'd be later in the day
So around 4 PM? Got it.
Thank you very much!
Today
Can we meet up for a chat?
There's something I'd like to ask you
This is ultimately just guesswork.
If we can do it near the studio, sure
It's entirely speculation on my part.
Aqua Hoshino
Hikaru Kamiki
But I've found the guy
who ruined Aqua-kun's life,
and I'm not gonna let him get away.
For now, I have to investigate.
Get to the bottom of this.
Hikaru Kamiki
Started an agency at 25
Was in Lalalai for six years,
from the age of 10 to 16
No details on later activity
College grad, majored
in the sciences
178cm tall
Meeting Kamiki reeled in
her self-destructive urges
Likely an abuser
Aqua Hoshino
Been in showbiz since childhood
Thinks the target of his revenge is dead
Must not be allowed to come in contact
Hello, Aqua-kun?
You sound sleepy.
I've had to walk around
a lot lately, so I'm exhausted.
I thought you were on break
until your next shoot started.
What are you up to?
Oh, uh... I'm trying to lose weight!
That part's true.
Why? You're plenty slim already.
Okay, but I'm pretty sure
you'd hate it if I put on weight.
I love you however you are, Akane.
I knew I made the right choice.
I'm glad I'm going out with you.
Right now, I feel like the
luckiest girl in the world.
Akane.
Meeting you has been nothing
but a positive for my life.
You know what I'm like, but you
accepted me and stood by me.
You told me when things weren't okay,
and little by little, you gave me hope.
It's made me reluctant to let go
of the times I'm spending with you.
What should I do?
You decide for me.
Should I just forget everything
and try to live my own life?
Or should I...
What should I do, Akane?
That's not right, Aqua-kun.
You need to make your own decisions.
I don't own you, and you don't own me.
This only works if we're two independent
people choosing to be together.
Any other kind of relationship
would just be an addiction.
But...
Once you've made your choice,
I'll help you as much as you want.
I know I've told you this before.
I want to help carry your burdens—
together with you.
Thanks, Akane.
Aqua-kun's still being held prisoner
by his mother's death.
But I know the day will come
when he's freed from it,
and I won't let anyone
get in the way of that.
I'm sure it'll happen soon, Aqua-kun.
What's wrong?
You've got a face like a wet weekend.
It's my VTuber sister...
People found a video from back
when she streamed with her real face!
Oh, so her past life was exposed.
Eh, that's more common than you'd think.
Nothing to worry about.
Well, in that video,
she went off on people she hated and made
a whole bunch of problematic statements!
She's got that corpo backing, right?
She's a total ****, then! Lmao!
Naturally, she got mega-canceled
and has to stop streaming for a while!
Yikes.
Hey, I've got an idea.
If her real face is out there,
she might as well join B-Komachi.
She's got the looks and the gift of gab.
I think it'll work out.
Oh, uh, urgh...
I mean, it depends on what she wants.
Ask her!
That girl, huh?
I'm not against it or anything,
but she's a girl
with a bit of a toxic side...
A similar gimmick to mine.
And I'm already the least
popular B-Komachi member.
B-Komachi
B-Komachi Channel!
970,000 subscribers
Videos
Shorts
Live
Our subscriber growth
has stabilized our revenue,
but it's not like I'm in this
for the money.
B-Komachi's success
is entirely down to Ruby.
February
Schedule\h
Outing Schedule
Ruby, congrats
on your award!!
We have interviews for mid-career
hires scheduled this month.
Please keep the office clean.
I haven't landed any
acting gigs at all lately.
What's more, I only get idol gigs
as part of a package deal with Ruby.
I'm just an added bonus—
a hanger-on leeching off of Ruby.
Is this what I wanted to do?
Why did I become an idol?
Rookie idol, my ass. So much for
becoming his one and only star.
I feel like such an idiot.
He totally hates me.
Heya, Arima! It's been ages!
Actor
Mako Azami
Uh, you didn't mention
it was this kind of place.
Didn't I? Sorry about that.
I'm an idol now. I don't think
it's a good idea for me to be here.
I'm gonna head out, if you don't—
What are you, some goody-two-shoes?
You know a ton of idols
come drinking around these parts.
Our jobs are damn stressful.
We deserve to cut loose sometimes.
I saw your new music video! It was great!
Heck, that girl over there
is a member of Masterpiece.
Really? Thank you so much!
Everybody does this, I swear.
What'll you have?
Uh, oolong tea, thanks.
Come on, drink with me.
Wait, Mako-san,
have you even hit drinking age?
I feel like you were only
a year older than me.
Y-Yeah, I just got there!
Yikes. I call bullshit.
Anyway, don't be so uptight.
Here, cheers.
So now I gotta drink,
or I'll be killing the vibe.
Dibs.
There you are, Shima!
'Sup.
Heard of him? He directed
Blazing Fluids and Snake Eyes.
Of course I've heard of him.
If I hadn't been told he was coming,
I would've ignored the invite
from this depraved bitch.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Are you free rn?!
I'm having dinner
in Roppongi
Director Shima's
gonna join me
Wanna come??
Masanori Shima.
He won a film award just this year.
He's the fastest-rising director around.
If he takes a liking to you,
you could land an acting gig.
If this guy takes a liking to me,
I could land an acting gig.
That naïve hope is why
I put myself in this situation.
It might not be playing fair,
but in Japanese showbiz,
this is what actually works.
At this point,
this is pretty much all I can do.
So I'm gonna go down swinging.
You're Kana Arima-san, right?
I saw you in Family Breakdown.
You sure have grown up.
Thank you. I had the privilege
of seeing Snake Eyes, too.
It was a marvelous movie.
Oh, don't be so stiff.
I'm a fan of yours, Kana-san.
You can drop the formalities.
Oh, I couldn't.
She's a popular idol these days.
Have you heard of B-Komachi?
I sure have. Ruby Hoshino's group, right?
My producer said he wanted to cast her.
How lucky.
I could never be an idol,
but Arima's always been a charmer.
I'm so envious.
No, I'm just a bonus extra to Ruby.
She's the amazing one.
I've got nothing.
That's not true.
Everyone in this business knows
you've got real talent.
You just don't have anyone
who can draw it out.
If it were me, I'd use you right.
Oh, why don't we trade LINE IDs?
Go for it. He's not a playboy or anything.
I hope we can chat again sometime!
Thanks for tonight, Shima D! Let's hang out again
No, thank you! I'll contact you
Today
Can we meet again for drinks? When are you two free?
Thanks for tonight, Shima D! Let's hang out again
No, thank you! I'll contact you
Today
Can we meet again for drinks? When are you two free?
I'm free this Friday and Saturday
No, thank you! I'll contact you
Today
Can we meet again for drinks? When are you two free?
I'm free this Friday and Saturday
I've got shoots
on Tuesday and Thursday...
Can we meet again for drinks? When are you two free?
I'm free this Friday and Saturday
I've got shoots
on Tuesday and Thursday...
And I won't know about other days
until the day before...
I'm free this Friday and Saturday
I've got shoots
on Tuesday and Thursday...
And I won't know about other days
until the day before...
Oh, yeah?
I'm free this Friday and Saturday
I've got shoots
on Tuesday and Thursday...
And I won't know about other days
until the day before...
Oh, yeah?
How about next Friday, then?
I'm free this Friday and Saturday
And I won't know about other days
until the day before...
Oh, yeah?
How about next Friday, then?
Let's get some good food and talk shop
What do I do?
Should I run this by our manager?
Huh?
Why do I have to tell you
my Insta password?
Isn't that an invasion of privacy?
Your socials belong to the agency.
We have the right to manage them.
It says so in your contract, too.
I know what this is!
You lose your accounts
if you switch agencies!
That's how you keep your talent trapped!
Exactly.
By the way, we've also
trademarked your name,
so you won't be able to go by
"Ruby Hoshino" anywhere else.
But that's my real name...
Help! Help! I'm being exploited!
I'll move to a bigger idol agency!
That'll show you!
This makes no sense!
Just so you know, the major agencies
are even more restrictive.
That's right.
You'll need your manager's permission
to even give out your contact info.
They'll monitor who sends you
DMs on social media.
If you get the "pure girl" role,
they'll keep all men far away from you.
They'll delete your blog posts
or rewrite them from the ground up.
They won't let you hang out
with your friends from back home.
And if you start dating someone,
they'll sneakily pull strings
to make you break up.
Huh? Do idols not have human rights?
And for some corpo VTubers,
NDAs ban them from putting their work
on their resumes after they quit.
They rank pretty low
on the rights scale, too.
Compared to that, we're pretty easygoing.
If you start dating someone,
we won't meddle as long as you tell us.
And we don't keep tabs
on who you're in contact with.
When most of your work
is online like mine,
the "no boys allowed" thing can make
collabs all but impossible sometimes.
Even if you take all the precautions,
lots of girls mess up around year three.
The more you restrict them,
the bigger the blowback is
once the novelty wears off.
You're not children anymore,
so we won't meddle in your love lives
if you know where to draw the line,
but talk to us if anything goes wrong.
Please keep in mind that protecting
our talent is our biggest priority.
Oh, but Ruby, we will
meddle in your affairs.
You're not an adult yet.
Boo!
I'm eighteen already.
I can make my own decisions.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Gotcha! See you in a bit!
Where are you?
I'm nearby, but sorry
This other party's popping off
I'll finish up here
and head over ASAP!
This bitch!
My wife grew up in the States,
and she always says,
"The actors' guilds practically
hold the reins of showbiz overseas."
But because Japanese agencies
aren't that powerful,
actors here have to shut up and do
whatever the showrunners say.
Basically blue-collar workers.
That's painfully accurate.
In Hollywood,
if a production breaks the rules,
the guild hits the studio with a fine.
They ensure actors are so well protected,
if an audition makes you wait an hour,
you can bill for that time.
Wow, lucky. I wish it were
like that in Japan, too.
With Japanese movies, the budget doesn't
trickle down to the actual productions.
The distributors have too much power.
Internal politics, ageism,
connections, and agency clout have created
an environment where projects only get
greenlit with proven box-office stars.
It's unsustainable.
Japan cares far too little
about actual acting ability.
Maybe it'd change with a guild monitoring
auditions like they do over there.
But as things stand now,
we won't develop good actors.
You really care about the actors, huh?
Why wouldn't I?
I want to make good films,
and I can't do that without good actors.
I want to bring
real change to this industry.
I'm relieved. He doesn't seem to be lying.
He's a pro who cares about the business.
And besides...
I swear!
Models who get into film are so
demanding when they can't even act!
Say it louder!
One of them made the bus come
all the way to their front door,
He's the right amount of bitchy.
I feel like I'm in the acting world
for the first time in ages.
started complaining to their
makeup artist about their coactors,
I can discuss art and acting
and basically ruined the mood on set.
and listen to drunks moan
about bad shoots and coworkers.
I really want to come back here.
You see,
I want to bring about an era where
real actors like you are valued.
I want my next film to make full use
of the skills of people like that.
There it is.
Huh? Are you saying you'll cast me in it?
Uh, I'm not sure about that yet.
It'd be a shame if we worked together
and wound up having creative differences.
So I'd like to get to know you
better before I decide.
I want to know what's inside you—
your soul? Your philosophy?
My philosophy?
Excuse me. It's almost time.
Oh, right. Thank you.
I'd like to take this elsewhere,
but I can't drag a kid around so late.
No, it's fine.
I can't drink yet, but I am an adult.
All my idol work did was leave me
feeling powerless and empty inside.
I was never meant to be
part of that world.
I have to land a big role here
and use it to get back into acting.
Let's continue this chat!
Hmm, in that case...
My office is right around the corner.
Wanna come over?
I'm sure people are still working,
so let's get together and chat.
I love your beauty spot. It's so sexy.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
This other party's popping off
I'll finish up here
and head over ASAP!
Got it! I'll be waiting
Arima!
I'm so sorry!!
This is taking forever.
I'll be a while yet
Understood.
We'll go ahead and start,
so let us know when
you can make it!
New messages
We're heading over
to Shima D's office next
Huh? Really?
Yeah. Did you know that there's a meaning
behind where you have moles?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
This is taking forever.
I'll be a while yet
Understood.
We'll go ahead and start,
so let us know when
you can make it!
New messages
We're heading over
to Shima D's office next
His staff are still there
What? I had no idea.
Wow, that sounds fun
They say you get 'em where your
beloved kissed you in your past life.
Are you still held up?
What the heck? That's so romantic!
Yeah, probably a bit longer
You wouldn't know, huh? But I...
Is this okay?
Won't the staff be surprised
if I show up out of nowhere?
Yeah, I bet they'll jump for joy
that the Kana Arima is here.
Oh, yeah, where's Mako-chan?
I don't think she's coming.
Huh...
Huh? Did everyone leave?
What a lovely studio.
Mind if I take a look around?
Go for it.
Wow, it's so big.
Yep, should've seen it coming!
There's a bed and everything.
What'll you have?
Cola, please.
Should I contact Miyako-san?
Nah, I'm an entertainer.
I'm used to these sticky situations.
I just need to be a fun drinking buddy.
And if the director gets horny on me...
Sorry, it's that time of month! Teehee!
teehee :P
What? Aw, that's too bad.
I'll use the magic words to get out of it!
You look like someone
pulled a fast one on ya.
Relax. I'm not some dumb college kid.
I know where to draw the line.
Right, of course! You wouldn't look
at little ol' me that way!
Oh, I would. Totally.
I only work with people who interest me.
I can't be all-out unless I'm interested.
Not in love, and not in work.
I want to work with people
who make me go all-out for them.
That's all.
You're a player, huh?
I don't deny it.
Aren't you married? What would
your wife say if she knew about this?
Oh, she plays around
pretty much every night, too.
We've got a "don't ask,
don't tell" thing going on.
Why do so many creative types
have zero common sense?!
You're free to slap me
and leave if you wish.
Think for yourself,
and do what's best for you.
That said, I'm not going to hurt you.
I'm showing you my respect and interest
as a fellow human first and a man second.
I swear it won't be some minor bit part.
I'll give you your ultimate role—
one that will define your career.
Kana Arima, you're an actor
right down to your soul.
You've felt the pressure of the cameras,
the feeling you only get
when you let a role take over you,
and that sweet release of laying
it all bare for everyone to see.
Those things are not
something you can forget.
I can make it back there again?
If it really gets me back there,
I'll do anything...
I'm sorry... I can't do this!
I...
I have somebody I like!
You like a guy enough to cry about it?
Yeah...
What's he like? Tell me about him.
Ugh! That guy!
He always acts like
I'm not even on his radar!
But then he gets all nice on me,
so I get the wrong idea!
I keep trying to forget him,
but I just can't!
How annoying can you be?
Die, you stupid piece of trash!
Oh, yeah?
That's actually fascinating.
I'm entertained!
There's nothing entertaining about it.
That's where you're wrong.
You've tried and failed for a year
to get over this guy who has a girlfriend,
and you're still here screeching over him.
Women like that are oh-so entertaining.
What the hell is wrong with me?
Never again. I'm sticking to getting
jobs the right way, with my skills.
Time to grab some ramen and go home.
Episode 29
Casting
Translation
Sriram Gurunathan
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check
Gabriella Alabanza
Translation Check
Michelle Tymon