What...
is that thing?
Impossible!
That's a really powerful person, Mr. Jack.
Yeah.
But what we must do hasn't changed.
Your command, Master.
Okay, then...
let's stop that person!
Where is the child
with the Heroic Spirit within her body?
If we tell you, what will you do to them?
Of course, following the rules
of the Holy Grail War...
I will face her...
and slaughter her.
Stop joking—
If you cannot answer, that is fine.
Don't get in my way.
If any stand in our way, bite them dead!
Dammit!
Who is that? Hey, wait!
Oh brother.
What's wrong? What's wrong, police force?
I'm in trouble if you
don't put in more effort.
It'd be a problem for me, as well,
if Tsubaki Kuruoka were to be murdered.
Some sort of demonic creature?
Ah well...
What is your problem?
Are you also what they
call a "Dead Apostle"?
What...
is Cerberus doing?
The same face?
Who...
are these guys?
Ridiculous! This is...
There is nothing ridiculous about this.
I'm originally a slasher
who claimed to have come from Hell.
Being repeatedly gnawed to death
by the guardian dog of
hell is only appropriate.
To have the guardian dog
of the underworld as your subject...
Can it be that Hades himself
has materialized?
O weak one...
Never again compare me with the fools...
known as "the gods"!
Would you like to pay a price
worse than death?
Pardon.
I apologize for trying to probe.
I see.
Indeed, you do not seem to be a god.
If you had any ties with gods,
I could have forcibly
connected you to karma
and perhaps mimic that guise of yours.
But it seems that I cannot become you.
However, I understand your true nature.
Great hero who denies the gods.
I'd venture to say that once,
their blood flowed through
your veins, as well.
Then, I shall treat you as a human.
And...
I shall kill you off...
as a human.
How about you come inside?
If you stay out in the open
like that, they'll target you.
It's fine! I'd like to see Mr. Ja—
Mr. Berserker's hour of triumph...
without using Strengthening on my vision.
Oh?
That person wearing fur
seems to not only be a Heroic Spirit
but is as strong as a Divine Spirit.
But Mr. Berserker won't
lose to anyone here!
What am I doing? Get it together!
No need for intervention.
That is my prey.
Your job is to take custody of
and protect Tsubaki Kuruoka.
Please don't waste the conviction
of my Master in vain.
Weak one...
Tell me your name.
No name exists for me.
O great hero,
a living legend from mythology
that continues to exist with the times...
A being who keeps living...
You must have some reason
to harbor such determination.
However...
if you are saying you are going to deny
the authority of the divine...
and you'll deny all doings of the gods,
evil or good, and toss them all away...
then your current self is a human
just as you wished.
You are a hero who has stooped
to a scoundrel and risen to a human!
No matter what kind of
great hero you are...
no matter if you have
the power to destroy the world...
so long as your true nature is human...
you will be hunted
by an ordinary slasher with no power.
From Hell.
Can it be...
Jack...
It's Jack the Ripper!
The folklore of a powerless Anti-Hero
painting the night's shadows
with fresh blood!
Not even the Night of Wallachia
could catch up with his speed...
An incarnation of corruption
propagating terror to the entire world!
You just can't get enough of this world!
My beautiful Assassin!
I offer this comical hell to you!
A demon...
I see.
This is what humans imagine
when faced with a tragedy or ill will.
The manifestation of Hell
that a warped desire brings forth.
There are just as many desires and fears
as there are humans.
The center of this metropolis
is the tastiest of hells for him.
Had I not known he was a Heroic Spirit,
I would have asked the Burial Agency
to head over here.
Well...
I didn't expect this.
Without the blessing of Hades...
you're still beneath a Divine Beast.
Hmm?
So, you are here, powerful king.
The King of Heroes...
Gilgamesh!
They appear to be toying with you
quite a bit, mongrel.
I thought I saw quite
an outlandish sight and came by.
But to think your opponent
was mere human delusions...
A quality piece of irony for you.
You amuse me quite well.
You may have the talent to become a clown.
What's with this?
This is ridiculous!
Oh no!
Wh-What the...
Hey!
What exactly is going on here?
Isn't this a bit different...
from what was planned?
Wasn't this supposed to
be a covert operation?
The situation changed
while we were in transit.
That's all.
I see. Then there's nothing
we can do about that.
H-Hold on. Is that okay?
The Saber that broke out of jail?
That's...
Assassin!
Why?
Why is the beautiful Assassin's body
not corrupted with my Magical Energy?
Goodness, I'm at a loss here!
Servants can summon man-eating fiends now?
"Man-eating fiend," you say.
Indeed, those are suitable words
for my current state.
No, I'll take that back.
You seem to be a good guy.
Oh?
You're the second person
to say that I am a good guy.
I see!
That person has a sure eye for things!
But...
it looks like this isn't a situation
where we can waste time much.
I'm sorry, can I trust you with Ayaka?
I would like you to deliver her
to that church over there.
What are you going to do?
I'm concerned about that Heroic Spirit
covered in gold...
but that murky one
was targeting the little girl, right?
Then, I have to stop him first.
No, I'd like you to take on
the golden Heroic Spirit.
I will do something about that bowman.
I see.
I understand.
I'll put my faith in you.
Know your place, mongrel.
Who gave you permission
to gaze up upon my glory?
I got permission from my heart!
I see that you are a famous hero
that is worthy of looking up at!
From how you speak, you must be a king.
I am grateful for being able
to stand here today!
Mongrel, you think you appraised me
with those substandard eyes?
I don't need gratitude. Disappear at once.
Disappear? You mean from this world?
You're a funny guy!
You who I know not the name of...
Though you are a man
in the shape of a demon...
the weak are simply hunted.
That arrogance...
You indeed are human.
Thank you.
You should give thanks to your Servant.
Jeez...
We're technically only
supposed to protect Masters
who have abandoned the Holy Grail War.
Sigma, what are you going to do?
I'm going to take this chance
to find Tsubaki Kuruoka and protect her.
Then, young lady...
please come this way.
Oh, okay.
I shall go with you.
Are you sure?
I thought your objective
was the destruction of the Holy Grail War.
With my inexperience, I'd need to put
everything on the line to destroy them.
However, right now...
the objective is rescuing a child, right?
Why do you...
Why do you go so far to save a child?
Rationally speaking, this operation
should have no merit for you.
That's right, you are not one of faith.
There is no greater good
than saving a young child...
whose heart has not been filled yet.
I don't get it. Though a child,
we're talking about a stranger, right?
I may still be inexperienced,
but the devout do not think
about things like merit.
They simply hear the greater voice...
and choose that path.
You are trying to save a
child in this situation...
because you are devout, right?
I could not do away with anger
against the heretics...
and could not become open-minded.
So long as my wish to save others
is mixed with my faith...
my faith is nothing but arrogance
that thinks lightly of destiny.
But none of that matters.
My inexperience is no reason
to not save the young child.
I see.
So, that's how things go.
No one...
came to save us.
I'm sorry.
That was a slip of the tongue.
I could not save your young self
due to my inexperience.
I could not come across that situation
and could not save you.
That is precisely proof
that I am still inexperienced.
You are a Servant.
You existed in a different place and time.
There's no way we could have met
when I was a child.
The difference in time and location
is all but trivial.
As proof of that...
you and I are standing here
right now in the same space.
Oh, I get it.
I...
wanted someone to save me.
I see, I see!
With such a masterpiece,
you cause a calamity simply by
thrusting it into the ground!
What about this wonderful ornamentation?
Hey you!
This is amazing!
Are all the surrounding weapons
of the same tier?
If you have so many of them,
can you give me a few?
I thought you were a fly buzzing around,
but you turned out to
be a shameless beggar.
Asking to receive it for free
was rather audacious of me!
If I could pay something equal in value,
I'd love to purchase them from you!
I wish to borrow these weapons as I please
while I fight you lot, so how about it?
How dare you mouth off
such nonsense, mongrel!
Yeah, I'm risking my
life for this nonsense!
Mongrel, I will allow you
to answer my question.
What an honor!
Looking at how you dodged
that, I can tell.
You've experienced something similar
in the past, haven't you?
Yeah!
I was in a similar situation yesterday.
Though sky and earth were reversed.
What happened to that opponent?
We became friends.
Masters... no...
I mean, the contractors got along, too.
I see.
Despite being my friend, they are still
a softie when dealing with others.
Huh?
It looks like...
I'm going to die here.
Mongrel...
I acknowledge you as a seeker of truth
suitable for me to provide a trial.
If you survive it,
I acknowledge you as their ally
and thus a clear enemy of mine.
Then, I'll grant you the honor to be
the muck dripping off of my prized blades.
You should be proud of that.
This is a Holy Grail War after all.
Once we meet, it naturally turns
into combat, I guess.
Don't deceive yourself, mongrel.
The one enjoying this
situation most of all
is none other than yourself, isn't it?
I see. Yep.
You seem to be a king who knows
about the world even more than I imagined.
A pledge has been fulfilled!
I shall take our words just now
as declarations of war...
and I will commence my invasion!
You said that because I
am human, I will die...
weak one?
However, the Demonic
Beast you have become...
is what human hands
should be defeating, right?
Incorrect.
That is not so...
one who has risen to become human
from a slave to the gods.
Humans do not defeat us.
Humans are the sages
who create us. They are fools.
And they are merely feed
that cannibalize each other.
Damn you!
Natural Born Killers.
Did he do it?
Marvelous.
That was marvelous...
weak one.
I commend you for running this body down.
I commend you for rising to the pinnacle.
Your power is not something worthless
to simply be shot down.
What the hell are you—
O slasher who I know not the name of...
With respect...
I will despoil from you.
You are worthy...
of pillaging!
Reincarnation Pandora.
You...
Can it be?
Mr. Jack!
You took...
my Noble Phantasm?
Feel free to hold a grudge if you'd like.
I am used to being
vilified as the usurper.
Retreat!
We're canceling the operation!
Can you hear me?
Absurdities created by heresy...
can only be kept in line
with similar heresy.
You guys are...
justice!
We are justice!
John!
You are brave, son of man.
That is no mere recklessness.
But for that, you are also so pitiful.
John!
EPISODE 9