Kukuru...
Is that...
You should train him, Azaki-sensei!
You're the class rep, right?
It's up your alley.
Absolutely not!
You know why I hate flamebaiters!
You're doing this
to spite me, aren't you?!
And that reason is...
Hey, Ren.
Let's run away.
Rota's death was merely the trigger.
I really just hated everything.
I wanted to run away from
those oppressive days of training.
I wanted to have fun.
I wanted to vent all my pent-up feelings.
Hey, hey, Kukuru-kun, Renri-kun.
Come join us at Miden Academy!
Buzz off.
Hey, check out the monk.
It's like a cosplay! Funny.
You wanna pray with us?
I don't want to let promising
youngsters slip through our fingers!
So? C'mon!
We're done with that shit. Get lost.
I don't have any talent anyway.
Way to get shut down, monk man.
Now beat it already.
You absolutely do have talent!
You just had a stupid teacher.
Don't ignore—
I'll really help you shine!
Shuji!
Damn you!
Enough.
You don't stand a chance
against him, even in a group.
The great Yoimaru Azaki
came personally to scout us?
So you really did become a teacher.
You got a demon inked on you?
Is that your way of saying
you'll never be an exorcist?
You wanna be bad,
so you start with the look.
You youngsters sure are cute!
But did you know? In Buddhism,
snakes are considered good—
Piss off!
Hey, Mr. Monk.
Y'know, he's actually pretty hot!
Yeah! Hey, wanna come
for a drink at our club?
U-U-Um, you...
Y-Y-You're showing a bit
too much skin there!
Too funny!
He's looking at your tits!
Let's go, Ren.
I'm sick of this exorcist crap.
I'm never going back.
Let's go!
Call me anytime!
Your mom wants to see you, too!
My only regret...
was leaving my mother behind.
The one person in the Manase
household who was ever kind to me.
Kukuru.
You can take any path you'd like.
Just become a good man.
Karaoke
Kukuru.
Your mother...
House Manase
Funeral Site
It was my first time back in a year.
I only intended to stand before her spirit
and apologize for not being
there when she passed.
Kukuru...
How dare you show your face here.
Nothing he said could possibly bother me.
Or so I assumed, anyway.
I saw this nonsense.
What a farce!
[Topic] Delinquents wreck a local restaurant lolol [Harassment]
You're a disgrace to the Manase family!
It was a video of me raising hell
in some restaurant.
Some idiots picked a fight,
and I was all too willing to oblige.
Someone had filmed it and posted it online.
Like trash boiled in sewage
Sub-maggot behavior
We got flamed.
Early grave for these morons
Your mother was severely
aggrieved by this video.
The shame and disappointment
were the death of her.
She died because of you!
Stop it, old man!
She was always in poor health—
Stop, Ren.
That's enough.
I knew he just wanted someone to blame.
But I was haunted by the thought
that it might be true.
Just become a good man.
I knew you'd look better with black hair.
I mean, black hair and a white button-up
are classic for turning over a new leaf.
You really do start with the look!
It's good that you're so easy to read.
I'd advise you not to mock
someone's dedication, Sensei.
I'm not.
I'm happy.
So, what led you to rejoining
this world that you hated so much?
Making it up to your mother?
Punishing yourself, perhaps?
I don't know.
I just decided I want to do things right.
I'm glad to have you,
Kukuru-kun and Renri-kun!
Don't call me Kukuru.
Manase-kun, then?
My dad disowned me.
Not that I mind that one bit.
Then what do I call you?
Kasubata. Kukuru Kasubata.
My mother's maiden name.
Post
Tea Butter To: Gqrnnpwm
Just breaking people's things without a care in the world.
Not only is it destruction of property, it's an attack on the feelings
of the owner and the person who made it. Irredeemable garbage.
Ever since that day,
I started smacking down flamers.
I wanted to make them realize
how foolish they were being. To stop them.
Tea Butter To: qprosomanll
Garbage. You look like you're still in school, so that's not
even your car. Deregistered, then? But it still drives well.
Disgusting asshole.
This "Aoringo" guy is absolute garbage.
I Smashed Up a Car
No... I was just putting on a front.
I was really punishing myself.
Reprimanding myself.
Yeah, this feels good!
Quit right now
Control yourself, trash
Striking down these
flamebaiting bastards!
Don't you realize how pathetic you are?
Face reality, you mindless barbarian
You're hurting people with your actions
Striking down my own foolishness.
The reason I hate flamebaiters
is because I was one of them.
Your cyberkinesis evolved?
But a hammer of flame...
Kasubata-kun!
You're letting your true
colors shine through!
I'll take your arm and
that hammer with it!
Sever!
He burned up the slash?!
Wagari's right.
No matter how I try to go straight,
I can't hide who I really am.
Why can't I stop swearing? Damn it.
Every time I curse, I hate myself.
Slice!
Sever!
Damn it! This is impossible!
The person who's put in the most
effort can't possibly lose!
That's completely right.
Wagari never ran, while I...
I did, so I could never win.
I always assumed that, and yet...
Why am I now so desperate to...
He didn't run from his flames.
He faced them and turned them into power.
Why should I train Enishiro?!
I just think it'll go better this way.
For Enishiro-kun...
and for you, too.
I don't want to admit it.
That the reason I decided
to hang in there...
was because of him!
Don't think you've won yet.
You're still just a coward who
ran away and came crawling back!
I'll hit you with the ultimate Sever,
infused with my remaining spirit power!
That's right. I ran away.
But running wasn't the end.
I'm not you.
I'm me.
The past I wanted to erase...
I've taken it all on...
to be the man I am now!
Asshole, asshole, asshole,
asshole, asshole, asshole!
You're a flamebaiter like me?
I don't think so.
Let me show you what makes us different.
Not only do I lose your hatred,
but I also lose to you?
And I'm gonna lose Minoru's love, too!
I can't bear it!
Flames Falling from Heaven!
Just as I thought.
You didn't run.
Still, I can't forget my desire
to do things right.
Beg pardon.
I didn't mean to use such vulgar language.
Minoru Wagari
Out of the fight
Can I assume you're all done now?
After all, if I kill you, we lose.
I'm done!
You won't have any fun with me,
and Minoru's gonna abandon me.
I wanna die!
Wh-Whatever. You brought this
on yourself, you know?!
Just apologize for burning
Akari's hairpin already!
Okay. I'm sorry.
Man, I dunno what to do with this guy.
Well, I guess I'll forgive you.
But...
Next time you make fun of 1-B,
I'm murdering your ass.
Dei Surugi
Out of the Fight
Wagari and Surugi both...
How can this be?
Soji Enishiro...
Soji Enishiro, eh?
The ghost account signal was
detected near here, right?
The signal's getting stronger!
What's this all about?
Let's check it out immediately.
Sorry. I...
Please. That was like a toothpick
compared to what Wagari did.
Quit sulking already.
If you hadn't gotten us away
with your windows,
we might have all been
out of the fight by this point.
Kukuru...
Hey!
Enishiro?
Kasubata, you're all messed up!
Shut up.
You seem to be thriving, though.
Yeah!
I made that Surugi bastard
apologize for mocking 1-B.
You dominated Surugi! Amazing!
You guys did great yourselves.
Look at the beating you laid
on that Wagari guy!
No, it was a tie.
Kukuru and I are both down for the count.
Next to no battery left.
Nah.
You won!
Enishiro.
Thank you.
Hey, c'mon, it's just the truth, man.
Not that.
I'll tell you the rest later,
but you're the one who opened the window
he kept shut from me for so long.
That makes me so happy.
A little jealous, really.
So the fighters out now are...
B
A
Kasubata\h\h\h\h\h\h\hHasumi\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hUrusugawa
Wagari
Surugi
Namekawa
Kusaba
Owada
Three from 1-B and five from 1-A.
Which means...
There's only one of them left! Ban Ashina!
What's this Ashina guy like, anyway?
He thinks of himself
as a living work of art
and uploads tons of selfies
to social media.
I have a responsibility to share
my beauty with all of humanity!
No part of my body deserves to be hidden!
My beloved followers, look at all of me!
Naturally, his account has been frozen
by mods time and time again.
He has freezer-type cyberkinesis.
He's extremely stupid...
But he's powerful.
Cyber out.
Millennium Suspension.
Title: "Chain of Beautiful Ice."
Chain of
Beautiful Ice
Cyber out.
Millennium Suspension.
Title: "Curtain of Beautiful Ice."
Curtain of Beautiful Ice
Even ghost accounts
can be elevated to art!
My cyberkinesis is a beautiful thing!
A freezer, huh?
Flames and ice... A hot-and-cold battle.
He probably burned a lot of
spirit power on that initial ice sculpture.
It's still there, too.
He'll be no match for you now.
Enishiro.
The rest is up to you.
Yeah! You guys get healed up
and prepare for the afterparty!
Looks like I'm the last one left.
This will make me even more beautiful!
Behold my face, tinged with sorrow!
The perfect aesthetic born of solitude!
I must share this with my followers!
Post
If I post this, my account
will be frozen again.
How unreasonable!
Is it truly a sin to be so beautiful?!
Aid Room
All done!
We're totally winning this one.
Don't be so sure.
It's true that we're
at a disadvantage right now.
But Ashina-kun can take it!
He's got impressive cyberkinesis.
Though he is pretty stupid.
Ashina is a real great guy!
He makes shaved ice for me.
Though he is very stupid.
I wish I could see that dummy's ice
send Enishiro's blood flying...
Hey, Enishiro's every bit
as stupid as he is!
Wait, that's what you're arguing about?
Kochi-sensei, please!
You kids get banged up too often!
The A-B Battle... is coming to an end.
Azaki-sensei...
Master...
Emoto...
Urusugawa...
Hasumi...
Kasubata...
They all got me this far!
Damn it!
My precious class 1-A... Damn it!
Well, we've reached the endgame.
Let's watch until the end, Nanzo-sensei.
I don't accept this!
Have you forgotten, Azaki-san?!
How my brother and all those students
were scorched by K's demon flame?!
How could I forget?
He was my best friend.
But Enishiro-kun isn't K.
You know that, Nanzo-kun.
I have a report.
The formerly faint ghost account
readings are rapidly increasing.
There's a ghost account
in the fake Kusatsu.
What about the staff monks on the scene?
Weren't they investigating?
We've... lost contact with them.
Ashina! You're the last member
standing of class 1-A.
Now, let's do this!
Look.
I just finished it.
Title:
"The Frozen Weak"!
The staff monks?!
They're... dead?
As their creator, I regret to say...
It's no good.
Not up to my standards.
What did you do?!
We can't do the A-B Battle like—
No.
We're just getting started.
I'm sick of things.
I can't be suspended anymore!
Tears of blood!
I've wanted this for so long...
An account that couldn't be frozen.
A body that wouldn't age or die.
And wings!
A-Ashina?
So that's what we picked up?
He's already dead.
He's a ghost account!
Title:
Rebirth in Bestial Beauty
"Rebirth in Bestial Beauty"!
Ban Ashina
A ghost account?
And tears of blood?
Don't tell me...
Look at my incredible body!
I can even do this!
Title:
The Great Hot Springs Town Freeze
"The Great Hot Springs Town Freeze!"
What a beautiful sight!
Thank you so much, K.
Sad Boy K...
You had him turn you into a ghost account?
Wh-What now? A blizzard?!
It's cold!
It's a barrier.
It's covering all of the fake Kusatsu.
No one can enter... or leave.
Ashina-kun...
Wh-What do I do?
Master K, you seem quite pleased.
Yes, the thought of my dream
coming true makes me happy.
Master K, seeing you so happy...
It makes me happy, too!
He really is special to you, isn't he?
How could this happen?!
Ashina... A student of
1-A has been killed?!
K turned him into a ghost account?!
No, Nanzo-kun.
He wanted this for himself.
Azaki-sensei.
I can't enter the fake Kusatsu.
It's an extremely powerful barrier.
I think he's a mid-level ghost account...
No, high-level!
Ban Ashina...
I heard you were stupid, but I didn't
think you were this stupid.
Soji Enishiro...
I'll kill you and make you
an artistic offering to K!
I'll exorcise you here and now!