You're back?
Hello.
Even with my barrier, I can feel the
stifling magicules around me again today.
Good grief, you're just
increasing my workload.
That should be my line...
If your branch had submitted its
income and expenses report on time,
there would be no need
for an investigation.
That whole business is
entirely for you, isn't it?
Besides, the Church exists
outside the kingdom's authority.
Who do you think you are,
demanding we submit
yearly income and expenses reports?
This is their attitude
after being designated
as the kingdom's primary religion
and receiving subsidies?
I'd really like to meet whoever's
in charge of your accounting.
Brother Cipriano isn't here.
The royal palace is investigating,
and the person in charge is absent?
When will he return?
He went to a meeting in another
town with Bishop Mateus,
so he won't be back for a while.
This Bishop Mateus again...
I'll show you around the church,
so make sure you keep up.
ISEKAI OFFICE WORKER: THE OTHER WORLD'S
BOOKS DEPEND ON THE BEAN COUNTER
I've grown used to working in the palace,
but the church has a completely
different feel to it.
EPISODE 8: I WENT TO WORK ON MY DAY OFF
There are more statues than just Abran.
Are they important religious
figures or perhaps gods?
There's a barrier around them to keep
anyone from messing with them.
So that was from magic
just now, not magicules.
Either way, I'd better be careful.
Let's get on with the next explanation.
He sure likes to talk a lot
when it comes to the church.
The fire hour, huh?
We don't really have
anything here for you...
But, well, since you're a representative
from the royal palace,
we've no choice but to feed you.
Oh, there's no need for that.
I brought my own lunch,
so please don't worry about me.
Damn it!
Okay. It's time for lunch...
which means I have some free time.
The civil servant...
Pleased to see you again, Priest Siegvold.
Where is Selio?
He went to eat lunch.
And left you behind?
No. He invited me to join him,
but I declined since
I brought my own lunch.
I see.
Where are those documents from?
They're visitor logs
from the assembly hall.
Please get permission before
removing any documents.
I attempted to speak with the
person in the assembly hall,
but I will make sure to
get permission next time.
Have you finished your lunch?
Where are we?
This is a flower garden created
by the holy maiden before last.
She said that flowers soothe the human
heart and cared for this garden herself.
The holy maiden of two generations ago...
I believe records say she became a nun
on the outskirts of the kingdom.
She must have settled down at this
church after fulfilling her duties.
Could it be... that he's monitoring me?
I heard that you're the otherworlder
who was summoned alongside
the current holy maiden.
Yes, that's right.
I see...
Actually, I was present at
the time of the summoning.
Come to think of it, were people
from the Church there then?
Thank you for answering Abran's call
and doing your utmost with the
holy maiden to save this kingdom.
No, I was just dragged into—
I mean, I happened to come
along with Shiraishi—
Her Holiness as a normal person
with no power whatsoever.
I don't deserve such thanks.
No. The summoning ceremony manifested
divine revelation
bestowed upon us by Abran.
There is meaning to your arrival here.
If that's the case,
I wish you'd taken better care of me.
You are, after all, a disciple
sent to us by Abran.
I'm nothing so grand...
This must be what it feels like to have
a mission unconditionally thrust upon you
and high expectations placed
on your shoulders.
This was Abran's will.
What is it, Pavel?
Norbert, we haven't gotten very far
on this. Will we be all right?
Sei-san won't be back for a whole month!
We have plenty of time!
When did I say that this was all
the work you'd have for the month?
S-S-S-S-Sei-san?! Weren't you
temporarily assigned to the church?!
Today's my day off.
Then what're you doing here?
I came to see if you were slacking.
I'm kidding. I only came
to do my own work.
No, you should rest on your days off.
Then when would this backlog get done?
Am I allowed to tell
Commander Indolark about this?
Won't it be bad if you
run into each other here?
It'll be fine. Aresh-sama
never comes here alone.
Oh, you shouldn't eat that!
It's not that I can't
eat such foods forever.
I'm slowly building up a tolerance.
You are?
Then do you wanna go drinking tonight?
Have you been listening to me?
That's too bad.
I wanted to hear about the church.
Oh, I actually wanted to ask
you about that myself.
Have you been to the church before?
Of course!
All citizens are baptized by
the Church at the age of six
and undergo a coming-of-age
ceremony there at eighteen.
As I'd expect of a national religion
that 90% of the populace believes in.
We even give offerings to the
Church during seasonal festivals.
The Church feels closer to people
than the royal palace.
Nobles who own land
support their local churches,
while nobles who don't either support
the one in the royal capital
or the orthodox church.
Now that I think about it, I saw many
noble family names in the visitor logs.
Also, a lot of the positions in the
Church are normally held by nobles.
As I suspected,
that priest must be a noble.
The only ones allowed to work in
churches are those who graduated
from the almshouse or nobles
with lots of magical energy.
That's because you need plenty of it
for prayer ceremonies and sacred relics.
So the magicules aren't just from
the barriers around the sacred relics.
No wonder I felt so uncomfortable.
If it weren't for Aresh-sama's barrier,
I might have collapsed on the first day.
It's you again...
Thank you for all your help.
Selio is... I suppose
there's no need to ask.
What a troublesome child.
Do whatever you want!
He's very devout in his faith,
but his honesty to his own
emotions is a bit of a problem.
I believe it's quite normal at that age.
Besides, it would seem he
never liked me to begin with.
True...
He's always had an inferiority complex
toward nobles and civil servants.
If they assigned him to me knowing that,
the church must feel very strongly
about the royal palace indeed.
Of the monks in training, some have no
families, and the majority are commoners.
They instinctively reject
anyone from the royal palace.
I wish I could reassign you another guide,
but I cannot go against the
orders of Bishop Mateus.
No, please don't worry about it.
The church is open year-round.
Their jobs and lives here are intertwined,
so they learn as they work every day.
Being raised in such a closed-off
environment from a young age
is bound to instill a biased
set of values in them.
The church can prepare meals for you.
Many foods disagree with my constitution,
so it's easier to bring my own lunch.
I have no resistance to magicules
or magical energy,
so I show symptoms of overdose if
I consume foods containing them in excess.
Overdose?
Yes, holy magic and recovery spells
have the opposite effect on me.
Though they'd heal injury or illness,
I'd break out in a fever
from magic-sickness.
But the holy maiden...
I suspect she received divine protection,
as she was formally summoned here.
Yes, divine protection... That's true.
Then that must mean...
You are the tribulated disciple.
Come again?
Your inability to adapt to this world
must be a trial given to you by God.
I think I just flipped a switch!
What an incredible sense of déjà vu!
If I'm not careful, I might get
strong-armed into monastic training...
I just happened to tag along when
the holy maiden was summoned!
No!
Everything God does has meaning.
Is that right?
Ist-san...
Ist-san.
It's Kondou.
I've come to get a progress
report on the return spell.
Oh, Kondu! Long time no see.
The otherworlder is amazing.
BLABBER BLABBER BLABBER BLABBER
Even we can't understand some
of the stuff Ist-san says.
Are all otherworlders like that?
I think something's just wrong with
him. He's similar to Ist-san...
Not only do you lack manpower,
but you also lack the funds to buy
tools required for your research.
Huh?!
Are you going to buy them for us?
When? Tomorrow?
I didn't say we'd buy them yet.
I'll be at the church tomorrow,
so I won't be able come by.
Then bring me back one
of those sacred relics.
That's obviously not happening.
Good grief...
Kondou-san! It's been a while!
It certainly has.
Likewise, it's been some time,
Prince Yurius.
I don't wish to see your face.
Kondou-san, I heard you wouldn't be
around because of a temporary assignment.
I am indeed on a temporary
assignment elsewhere.
I'm just back on my day off.
It's your day off, but you came
to work in your uniform?
You must be quite busy...
Still, your temporary
assignment must be close
if you can stop by here
on your day off, right?
Yes. I'm working at the church
in the royal capital.
Huh? The church?
I've been visiting the church myself!
Is that so?
How is your work going there?
I've been purifying those who feel
sick and healing the injured.
I'm really happy there's somewhere
I can be of so much help!
She looks so spirited.
She must find it quite rewarding.
And then there's Selio-kun!
He's one of the children training to
become a monk, and he's so beautiful!
On top of that, he's a very good boy
and teaches me all kinds of things.
Oh?
But I've never run into you at the church.
It's a large facility, and I'm
mainly doing office work,
so I hardly visit the chapel.
Oh, that makes sense...
Yua.
You're the holy maiden,
so there's no need for you to work.
Yurius-sama...
As I've said many times before,
I want to do what I can.
I've told you that
you only need to purify—
And I've told you I don't want that!
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Come with me for a bit.
Why?
Why has Yua come to reject me?
Why does she depend on someone weak
and powerless like you instead of me?
Answer me, Kondou!
He pronounced my name correctly.
Ask me all you'd like,
but the answer is obvious if
you consider what's led to this.
Perhaps the two of you are drifting
apart due to a difference in values.
A difference in values?
Yua's from a noble family.
Our ideals cannot be so different.
No, the class system was abolished
in our country and no longer exists.
Is that so?
Even so, Yua is the holy maiden.
She should be treated with great care.
Yet recently,
she's begun to spurn even that.
She's likely showing restraint.
She probably doesn't want to
feel she owes him anything.
In simple terms, she doesn't
want others to just serve her.
She wants to return to her own world.
However, the kingdom wants her to stay
as a political and diplomatic symbol.
Quite the impasse,
no matter how you look at it.
Enough. Leave me.
Then if you'll excuse me...
Good grief.
I was planning on doing some
research in the palace library.
I need to hurry...
Commander Makovska of the second
royal order. Nice to see you again.
Do you have some time?
I'm very sorry. I actually have
something to do after this.
It won't take long.
Please just let me work.
Don't worry. There are no longer any
knights who'd dare lay a hand on you.
So, what is this about?
Well, it's about Prince Yurius...
Is there another problem with him?
Is there any way you could mediate
between His Highness and Her Holiness?
I'm leaving.
That guy...
Wasn't his name Kon...
Kon...ou?
What about Seiichirou?
Aresh, don't startle me like that.
You startled yourself.
So, what about Seiichirou?
Sei...ichiro?
Didn't you just mention his name?
Oh, just now?
Well, since we just found out
about the next expedition,
I was wondering if Seiichiro
would be coming along.
He participated in the first
due to demand from above
and to investigate for the
miasma containment project,
but someone of his constitution
should never go near the demon forest.
I'll never let him do it again.
Since when did Aresh have the final say?
Oh, come to think of it, we finally
received the documents for the expedition.
Could you take a look at them?
Got it.
No one other than myself needs
to call him Seiichirou.
His family name is Kondou.
Call him that.
This goes beyond just being protective.
He always puts Kondu first,
and now they're even living together.
There's no doubt about it.
Aresh's first love is definitely
Kondu the otherworlder.
The bishop and accountant,
who are away on business,
should be returning shortly.
I'd like to have all the church
documents in order before then.
The problem is that I'm unfamiliar with
the politics of the Church and nobility.
The Church...
The nobility...
Nobles should have family names,
but the priest didn't give me one.
Milan-san.
Yes?
Do nobles who enter the
Church cut ties with their families?
That depends.
Some nobles still receive aid
from their families once they join.
Sometimes children from good families
are also entrusted to a church
temporarily to learn manners.
So not everyone cuts familial
ties when they enter.
Pardon me.
Milord has returned.
Would you join us in greeting him?
That was close!
We would have crossed paths
if I'd come home any later.
Either way, he's home awfully early today.
Valtom-san has been taking care of
Aresh-sama since he was a young boy.
He's practically a father figure and
the only one who can reason with him.
If a man like him is asking me
to greet Aresh-sama with them,
this must mean...
I don't have the courage to ask,
but I wonder what the servants
of this house think of me.
Welcome home, Aresh-sama.
What are you plotting?
How rude. It's the least I can do
to welcome my landlord home.
What kind of person do you take me for?
An extreme workaholic.
I don't think I'll be welcoming
him home anymore.
I have the documents for the
next expedition. Want to see?
I do!
The purification should be complete
with the third expedition,
so I proposed to have barrier sorcerers
and builders join the expedition
and stand by in a local village,
but it seems that was rejected.
The completion of the
purification isn't certain.
We'll need to confirm things
after the purification,
and there's already
a shortage of sorcerers,
so I'm sure they weren't able to gather
enough to cast the barrier spell.
Then we'll need a separate expedition
to put up the barrier...
One needs a certain level
of magical energy
to be appointed as a
royal sorcerer, right?
The number of people who have that...
...are few.
On top of that, if they're
to work in the demon forest,
they'd best have high magicule resistance.
The third royal order boasts
mental and physical strength,
and we're skilled at
controlling our magic.
There's no point in having magical
energy if you can't control it.
Does that mean magical
energy can go out of control?
That's right.
That's why children with such tendencies
are usually left in the care of churches.
Churches?
Come to think of it, there are barrier
spells cast all over the church.
Moreover, nobles, commoners,
and orphans all work there together.
That must be bringing together people
with strong magical energy
and resistance to magicules,
regardless of class.
Wait, Aresh-sama...
I'm casting another barrier layer.
Look at me.
I don't mean like that.
Huh?
Aresh-sama! I'm too heavy!
You aren't.
Let me down!
Seiichirou...
How about this?
Huh?
You don't like being in my lap, right?
Oh, yeah...
Wait, why did you push me down?
We're already done, aren't we?
You've put on a bit of weight.
You're checking my body?
The next expedition is in six days.
We still have mountains to move.
I need to pull myself together...
Don't think about it! Don't think about it!
Aresh-sama is the commander of a
prestigious order and naturally clever.
He's quick to learn and has
a keen sense of intuition.
Rather than him being swept up in things,
I feel like he's clearly targeting my
aversion to wasting time and my desire
to get the most out of a situation.
This isn't the kind of decision
to be made based on efficiency.
He's a troublesome opponent...
Anyone else is way off-base
to be coming to me for advice.
I haven't even been able to face
my own feelings properly...
EPISODE 9
I MADE A PLAN