Is that...
Surely not.
They're humans?!
Flaming arrows?
Look out!
The barricade's on fire!
Sentenced to Be a Hero
What the hell's going on?
More faeried humans
like the ones in the mine?
No. This is something else.
They've sided with the Demon Blight.
D-Do you mean...
There are faeries capable of
communicating with humans?
Yeah.
Apparently, there's a few that can.
If that is what they are, Xylo...
I cannot attack humans.
Even if they serve the Demon Lord,
it is structurally impossible
for me to do so.
I know.
Kivia! You getting this?
What is it?
Your sacred seal communication is more
garbled with non-heroes. Speak slowly.
What's going on out there?
Who sent those riders?
I have no idea. But...
It's clear they're some noble
family's private army.
They're skilled horseback archers.
They're pulling back. We're too
heavily armored to give chase.
Damn. They're heading for...
The underground passage.
They're coming this way.
Xylo, we've got a mess on our hands!
Something's coming our way!
What do we do? If they make it to me...
If I die here...
...I'll never stop haunting you!
Is your own neck all you care about?
Chill out, Mr. Venetim.
Mr. Tatsuya's got your back, right?
Still, Your Majesty could do
with getting off the front lines.
We've got kyracks incoming.
That front gate won't hold much longer.
Unthinkable.
If the king retreats,
who will motivate his subjects?
Chancellor! Where are my reinforcements?
I don't have any for you. Besides...
You're not even king of anything.
In that case...
Open the embrasures!
Opening embrasures!
What are those?
Runtels.
Sacred seal cannons created by
Verkle Development Corporation.
Prepare to fire!
Preparing to fire!
Fire!
Their aim could use some work.
We'll need time to reload.
The next wave will reach us first.
In that case...
Commander Xylo, it's your turn!
Strike down the enemy general!
Guess it's come to that.
I'll handle any humans we come across.
Ready to go, Teoritta?
Xylo.
Do you truly intend to enter this fight?
What are you getting at?
You are constantly gambling
with your own life,
yet you tell me not to do the same.
It's fine for me to do it.
They can bring me back to life.
No.
Even if that were not the case,
you would still fight.
What's your point?
For the Holy Knights and miners
still in the fortress...
For the nameless masses
you have never even met...
You always fight for someone else.
In the end, you are
no different than a goddess.
So when you claim to despise
the goddesses' fundamental nature...
It is because you see yourself in us.
Damn it.
Let's just get this done.
The Demon Lord's finally here.
Yes. You are a hero and I am a goddess.
It is essential that I bless your battle.
We each have a duty that must be done.
We have no other choice, yes?
Yeah. You said it.
Xylo. We must make sure we win this battle.
Right.
Let's go.
What are humans doing here?
Will this place become our grave?
H-Hey.
What the...
Where'd that come from?
I-It's an ambu—
O-Offer support!
All forces, fire!
H-He disappeared?
What the hell is he?
He's not human.
That thing...
It's a demon.
There it is.
That's Iblis.
Let's keep engagements to
a minimum. We'll go around.
Understood.
Proceed, my knight.
Right.
Just how we planned it!
Eat this!
Xylo!
Take that!
A kyrack, huh?
Take this!
Teoritta, time to fly!
Right!
A boggart?!
X-Xylo! I shall call the rain of swords!
No!
Save your power for Iblis.
I cannot simply—
Damn it all to hell.
Teoritta! We're going!
Xylo. What is that?
Venetim! What are they doing here?
I told you to refuse their aid!
Uh, you're not mad at me, are you, Xylo?
You lied to me, didn't you?
Well, let me turn that back on you.
What made you think
I would tell you the truth?
Xylo! Help! I'm in trouble!
They're gonna kill me!
I'm a dead man!
Dotta! What the hell are you doing?
I'm being chased by mercenaries!
Kill the bastard!
Get back here!
Huh? Why are they after you?
I told you to hire them!
You told me to steal money to pay 'em.
I thought I'd save time by stealing it
from them in the first place!
Oh, whatever! Shut up now!
Give us our money back, you bastard!
Harry the faerie horde!
They've confused the Demon Lord.
Guess it's dumber than I thought.
Let's fly, Teoritta!
Now's the time. Can you do it?
But of course.
I prioritized size and power
with this sword.
It will not hold for long.
I know. It's more than enough.
Are my blessings not a sight to behold?
Xylo?
Let's win this thing.
Indeed.
Ready.
That's right. Come get me.
Xylo. What is this?
It's the trap I set while scouting.
They're weathering seals.
Teoritta!
Right.
This shall be your end!
These swords will last for some time.
I'll ask Kivia's forces
to bring the goddess's poison.
You rest here for a bit.
There wasn't a single damn reason
to sacrifice the fortress.
All the fight's gone out of it.
Now we can...
Teoritta!
Get out of there!
M-My knight.
T-Teoritta.
Run away.
Is this all we can do?
My people! Retreat at once!
Run!
It's hopeless!
We cannot afford any more sacrifices!
Tsav! Clear an escape route for them!
Not happenin'!
We're in trouble here, too!
We're done for! Run!
Hey!
Does that mean I can run, too?
Just don't come down here, please.
Hold the line up there.
Wait! Someone save me!
These mercenaries are gonna kill me!
Xylo! Your wound...
Teoritta. Go.
But I—
The faeries can't come here right now.
I can see you're at your limit.
It's blatantly obvious.
You were right about everything.
I see myself in you, and it repulses me.
I...
I want to win a battle that matters.
I want to think I'm an impressive person.
I want to believe I still have
something to offer.
It's a stupid, selfish thing to want.
But...
This is the battle I'm fighting.
My knight.
Regardless of your feelings on the matter,
I shall fight by your side.
Because...
I am the mighty goddess, Teoritta.
Yeah. Almost forgot about that.
Xylo. If you do not wish me to die,
you need only protect me.
You are a mighty knight, after all.
All right, then.
Help me out here, Teoritta.
I'll decide where you gamble your life.
Yes.
And when you die, it'll be on my order.
Without a doubt.
So let's win this!
I shall prepare you a special sword.
A truly special sword.
Can it slay an immortal opponent?
Yes. This is the Holy Sword.
There is nothing it cannot destroy.
I summon it from outside this world.
I guarantee it will hold,
even if not for long.
So I'd better make sure
the strike lands true?
Leave it to me.
Yes. We shall never give in,
nor fail, nor be broken!
Xylo!
I lost the mercenaries!
What are you doing?
We gotta get out of here!
Oh, hey.
Was wondering about the radio silence.
So that's where you are.
This is my last shot, anyway.
Teoritta! Now!
Just die and rot already!
There is nothing...
the Holy Sword...
cannot destroy.
You see?
Am I not truly great?
Yeah.
You sure as hell are.
Xylo!
Teoritta's with you, right?
If you're hurt,
we'd better get you back fast!
Took you long enough, moron.
Hey! Xylo!
Where am I?
Oh, I see you're awake.
How are we feeling, Xylo?
Who are you?
Rest easy.
I'm happy to say you aren't dead.
Although you came awfully close, I reckon.
Your body's been restored enough that
you won't need to visit the repair shop.
Although I can't promise
there won't be a little memory loss.
Who the hell are you?
Consider us allies, if you wish.
Either way, I'm very relieved you're safe.
The hero unit is
our trump card, after all.
Leave.
How cruel.
It wasn't easy to arrange
this confidential visit, you know.
I worked hard to bring you
your gifts as well.
Expressions of thanks
from the nearby settlements.
It seems you've gained
a very positive reputation.
They call you the "Soaring Lightning."
Get out now.
Very well. I'll respect your wishes.
But I want you to know...
It's not just civilians.
People in the Temple and the military
are noticing what you heroes are up t—
Leave.
Oh, and one last thing.
Be careful about disobeying
too many orders.
There are powerful people
who view you as a thorn in their side.
One particular faction
has its eyes squarely on you.
Yeah, I'll bet.
They're known as "coexisters."
They seek harmony with the Demon Blight.
Well, goodbye now.
I'm finished.
You're free to enter, Lady Goddess.
Xylo!
My knight?
Why are you looking at me like that?
I, a mighty goddess, have granted you
a personal audience.
I will be angry with you, Xylo.
If you do not wish to praise me...
If you do not wish to pat my head...
I accept that.
But of all things...
If you were to forget me...
I would never forgive you.
I haven't forgotten you, Teoritta.
So don't cry.
I am not crying.
Okay.
I am much too great and powerful.
Yeah, you are.