In the near future, e-Pulse is
generated by human thoughts and emotions,
and used as an energy source
for AI devices called "Sapotamas,"
leading to a new development for humanity.
But from its shadows,
terrifying monsters have appeared.
Monsters that evolve by consuming e-Pulse.
They are...
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
darenimo jama wa sasenai sono saki he
Beyond where no one can stop me
mayoinagara kotae sagashi tsukisusumu
I'll make my way there
As I seek the answer
kizamitsukero Emotion
Carve your emotion
hibiiteiru
It reverberates
tashika ni shinkurosuru Tempo wa
The tempo that synchs
sukoshi zutsu
kakureta sekai abaiteiku hakudou
Is a pulse that slowly reveals
The hidden world
yuraganai Baseline no ue de Rec
Record on top of the solid Baseline
Don't mess up tempo
futsuu ja monotarinee
Normal's not enough for me
Just keep howling, howling!!!
Howling like it's all you've got
shinjiru mono ga nijimisou ni natte mo
Even if what you believe begins to blur
nigirishimeru Riaru wa
uso janaku tsuyoku hibiku
The reality that you grasp
Rings strong and true
Metronome topparau ichido kiri kono JAM
Take away the Metronome
For this one and only JAM
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
kanjou no mama narasu kodou wa
The emotional beat that rings out
sou zutto hashiritsuzukeru BPM
Is the BPM that continues on and on
(Let the beat lead the way)
matenrou nomikomu Cloudy Rain
The Cloudy rain swallows the city
rinkushite rizumu yoretatte
Groove ni shichaeba ii
Even if I link and the rhythm warps
I just make it part of my groove
norikonase omoidoori
Ride it like you see fit
(Let the beat lead the way)
itami daite mo tomarazu ni
Even if it hurts, I won't stop
kizami tsudzukeru kodou
Won't back down
Keep carving the beat
bokura nara donna koto mo norikoerareru
We can overcome anything
tatakitsukero Emotion
Drum to your emotion
They're both fast asleep.
They were pretty drained.
We'll leave after they're rested.
Is something wrong, Cougarmon?
No...
It must have been my imagination.
DEFIANCE
Curse you, Kanada.
Placing a bounty on Sir Klay.
Relax.
Gather all Tactics forces.
I think Chairman Wong...
needs to be removed.
I still have unfinished business.
If you'll excuse me.
Oh?
I promise you that I will return in time.
As you wish, Sir Klay,
everything will be perfect.
Do as you will.
What do you intend to do?
Kyo Sawashiro of the Glowing Dawn.
I'm the only "perfect"
that Sir Klay needs.
Kanuma, find the traitor Granit
and eliminate him.
But...
The rules of the Tactics. Rule!
None shall disobey an order.
Should we lose here, your path to being
a researcher will be gone for good.
So much for supporting your family.
Roger.
Are you sure?
Do it.
Stop!
Hotaruko?
What... are you doing?
What's that?!
That's...
What's taking so long, Kanuma?
Were my orders too difficult for you?
I'm sorry, Sir.
What do you want?
You're my target, Kyo Sawashiro.
Do it!
Cougarmon!
Evolve!
Cougarmon Evolution!
Murasamemon!
Oh my. You actually blocked it.
Not bad at all, Mr. Naito.
Who's that?!
A Five Star!
Five Star, Star of Water.
Honoka the Abyssal!
On orders from Chairman Wong,
the bounty Klay Arslan and the Tactics...
are my prey!
Klay Arslan is a bounty?
Wait, a Five Star...
I've never met her.
But...
she's telling the truth.
I know about you.
You're Kyo Sawashiro, right?
You seem pretty boring.
What does Kaito-sama see in you?
Oh well. Right now
it's Tactics clean-up time!
Gigasmon!
Kanuma.
At the very least, act as a shield.
Take her out, or die trying!
You said I'm your target.
What do you want?
I'll eliminate you.
I won't have you interfere
with Sir Klay any further!
Hurricane Bomber!
Murasamemon!
Jyunozan Tsukishigure!
Earthquake!
Torpedo Attack!
Makocchan!
We'll take Granit and the others!
We're counting on you!
Okay!
Tomoro, can you walk?
Chiropmon!
Here goes!
Fly!
Chiropmon Evolution!
Nightchiropmon!
Providence Scan!
Shadow Arts!
What?
Aqua Viper!
Giant Rang!
This isn't your fight!
They're an Ultimate Digimon!
Hotaruko! We have to work together!
I don't need help!
There's no escape!
Yes!
Using cheap tricks
because you can't win fairly?
Such a boring way to fight.
Textbook strategy of a goody-two-shoes.
Whoops. Too bad.
Nightchiropmon!
I...
I've never stopped running.
My family was poor.
It led to constant ridicule.
I studied as hard as I could
to get them to shut up.
Hotaruko.
Congratulations on your internship.
You're finally a researcher.
I'm so proud of you.
This is nothing, Mother.
You don't have to send money, you know.
The store's getting by
thanks to our regulars.
All I want is for you to be happy.
I know.
I wanted to ease Mother's burden.
I just wanted to be independent.
I can do this. I'm fine on my own.
I desperately told myself that.
Miss Kanuma, we can take over.
You should get some rest.
You've been cooped up in here.
I'm fine.
All I need is today's test data
and I'll be good.
And then... one day...
Your e-Pulse readings are abnormal.
Please ensure adequate sleep.
Oh be quiet.
Error! Error! Error! Error!
W-What?
Shakomon was born.
I couldn't remain in college.
Ever since the Klay Foundation
took on my debts, my life has been chaos.
If I can repay my debts and get results,
I can be a researcher again.
I don't have time to stop.
Hotaruko...
We can endure any ocean,
no matter how dark or cold.
Makoto Kuonji.
Unable to make hard decisions.
Always dependent on your friends.
I'm made of stronger stuff
than a spoiled kid like you.
I can be strong on my own!
That's what I always believed, but...
Oh come on. This is boring!
You're so weak it's pathetic.
Shall I just end it for you?
Is that okay?
I'm sure it is, isn't it?
Kill.
Hotaruko, are you okay?
Can you stand? Let's go!
I can't.
I can't win. I can't escape.
Just...
leave me.
Hotaruko...
Why should I?
Even if we can't win individually,
maybe we can win together!
You have your family!
You have your Tactics friends!
You have Shakomon!
What's wrong with helping each other?
Oh! There you are!
The Tactics aren't some big,
happy family like you guys!
They never help...
Take them out!
Tialudomon!
Huh?
They ain't alone, ya know!
We're here, too!
Makocchan!
Are you okay?
Reina! Tomoro!
Granit...
Why?
I... I tried to...
I don't know either.
But...
I don't think I'll sleep well if you die.
Just say you want to protect your friend.
Hotaruko, you're not alone.
I don't like you.
But... if Makoto wants to protect you,
I'll help.
Time to make up your mind!
We'll fight together with you!
So, please trust us!
Wait! Stop it!
I'm allergic to cheap melodrama!
I can't stand weaklings standing up
for each other! Gross! I'm getting chills!
I'm bored. Bye.
What?! Hey!
I'll get you for this.
What the heck?
Do you think she let us go?
Forget her! We need to help Kyo!
I didn't speak up
out of respect for your wishes, but...
rather than enduring
the dark and cold...
I think swimming in the open sea
suits you better.
Shakomon...
No matter what you choose,
I'll always be with you.
Thank you.
Okay. Let's go!
Hunt them all down!
Shakomon Evolution!
Tylomon!
Gounozan Murashigure!
What are you doing?!
Defeat is not an option for the Tactics!
Sand doppelgangers?
Murasamemon!
It's over!
Torpedo Attack!
What?
Kyo!
Kanuma. Granit.
So both of you are betraying the Tactics?
You ungrateful brat!
Have you forgotten your promise?
What about your family's...
I'll protect my family no matter what.
I'll repay my own debts.
Team Seven will never
follow your orders again.
I hereby tender my resignation.
How dare you...
Get lost, you piece of filth.
You're not much of a leader
if your team is betraying you.
I am true perfection.
I am the one worthy of Sir Klay!
I'll erase all of you
from my perfect world!
That thing's bad news, ya know!
We need to run!
No we don't.
You tried to hurt my family.
It's time to pay!
Tsuinozan Kokuu!
Impossible.
You're fleeing?!
Wait!
Did you use the monkey Digimon
to lure me to the colosseum?
We'll eliminate that Digimon!
It's none of your concern!
Oh dear. Back to the drawing board.
We'll be fine. We're capable.
What will you two do?
We'll look for Raito.
We'll return to the Mirror World.
He's a fellow Tactics member after all.
Look after him.
Thank you for everything.
Good job!
What's this about?
I'm just glad you're all okay.
Let's get some expensive meat today.
Meat!
We can't! We're still cutting back!
Let go already! You're suffocating me!
I'm hungry, ya know!
Chairman Wong.
The Tactics have been
almost completely wiped out.
atarimae wo atarimae ni shinai
Don't let the normal be normal
gakufu doori ja monotarinaindayo
Playing to the score is not enough
noizu sura mo torikonde
jibun dake no sesshon wo!
Take in everything, even the noise
And make it our own session!
hitomakase ja kawaranaishi
Boot! Boot!
Things won't change in others' hands
te nobase
Reach out your hand
machigai mo osorezu susume
Boot! Boot!
Don't be scared to mess up, go on
yuukan ni
With courage
ruuru ni tatakitsukeru NO
error, error
Go tell the rules NO
Error, error
sukeeru auto joutou
error, error
Scale out? Bring it on
Error, error
yosoku funou no koodo
error, error
An unexpected code
Error, error
puronpto nanka ja seigyoudekinai omoide
Prompts can't control these feelings
kamase shauto
Give it a shout
BRAVE! mou kowakunai
BRAVE! No more fear
utsumuitari mo shinai
Keep my head high
senaka azukeaeru kimi ga iru kara
I've got someone who's got my back
GROOVE! mou tomaranai
GROOVE! We can't be stopped
yunizon suru koudou ga
Our beats are in unison
kitto sekaijuu wo appudeeto shiteiku
We're going to update the world
bakuon de
With a bang
Let's go, Kyo!
We're counting on you!
You're gonna make a world where
Digimon and humans live together, right?
Kyo...
You're no longer the same
as when you were a Five Star.
-Am I right?
-Yeah.
Klay, I will not lose to someone
who gave up on dreaming!
Next time on DIGIMON BEATBREAK,
"The Power to Take"