This year's fireworks were amazing!
Let's make sure we all go again next year!
Yeah!
Come on, Eiyu, don't get lost.
S-Stop it! I'm not a kid anymore.
What's with you?
You think you're all grown up
now that you're in junior high?
Walk faster, or we'll leave you behind.
I always thought they only saw me
as their childhood friend...
Meet me at the torii gate at eight.
M-Meet me at the shrine grounds
at the south entrance...
I'll be waiting for you!
They want me to pick between them?
They're both waiting for me?
Oh geez. I can't stand watching this.
What a mess.
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
Huh?
Wait, hold up, hold up, hold up!
This is Shio and Akari
we're talking about!
They're my childhood friends!
This is way too sus.
This is probably one of
their schemes to mess with me!
Don't let them fool you.
I want to watch the fireworks
with just you, Eiyu!
Don't let them fool you!
Me too. I want to watch
the fireworks with just you, Eiyu!
Don't let them fool you!
Don't let them—
You have to choose one of us.
I... I can't even...
Wait, stop. Calm down!
Calm down and think!
Oh my gosh!
What should I do...
What should I do... What should I do?
Oh my gosh, what should I do?!
What?!
The couple who kiss during
the final, massive fireworks...
...are destined to be together.
A k-kiss... really?
Okay, well...
I just have to go for it.
Should I close my eyes?
Smooch... smooch...
smooch
Or be a little forceful?
Smooch... smooch...
Like this? Smooch.
Or like this? Smooch.
Smooch...?
Why are you here?!
Why the heck are you here?!
Hey! That's dangerous!
Don't throw rocks at me!
Seriously, what are you doing here?
W-Well!
Um, so...
Kissing?
She was, right?
She was practicing kissing, right?
Wait, but why?!
Hey, it's almost time!
Time for the eight o'clock legend of love!
The couple who kiss during
the final, massive fireworks
will be destined to be together, right?
You've got this!
Eight o'clock
Destined to Be Together
Kiss
Just the 2 of Us
Legend of Love
I'll Be Waiting for You
Kiss... eight o'clock... fireworks...
You have to choose one of us, Eiyu.
Gosh, cut it out. I'm getting nervous!
Was that...
What?!
Hey! Wait, Akari!
Stop following me!
Hey, why are you running?!
Shut up, you perv!
Why are you chasing me?!
Why?
I don't really know, myself!
Could this be...
Actually...
The start of our rom-com?!
Hey!
Huh?
What do you think you're doing?!
Playing dumb, huh?
This pervert's harassing this girl!
What?!
Um, actually!
Get him!
You disgusting bastard!
Hey, do as we say!
You pervert!
E-Excuse me!
You're mistaken!
He's actually... my friend.
Stay right there!
Police! Over here!
U-Um...
P-Please listen to me!
Help!
I'm very sorry for causing a scene.
Good grief, it was only a couple's quarrel.
A couple...
Akari... I'm...
Stop.
Now's... not the time.
Akari...
It's almost eight o'clock.
You have to pick either me or Shio.
If you come to me...
I want to tell you about everything.
Everything I've been hiding from you.
I'm ready to face it.
Akari...
Shio
Shio?
Hello?
Shio, what's up?
Hey, about earlier...
Wait, what? It's hard to hear...
What?!
You can't make it?
What do you mean you can't make it?
So sorry!
Something came up all of a sudden.
Enjoy the fireworks
with Akarin... okay?
Seriously, don't worry about me.
Talk to you later!
What can I do?
Meet me at the torii gate at eight.
I did it! I told him!
There's fifty-three minutes
until the fireworks...
Sunday, August 15
This is gonna take forever!
Eight o'clock feels so far away!
Oh no! At this rate...
My heart's gonna explode!
Shio! Shio!
Mommy! Daddy!
What's wrong?
Did you get separated
from your mom and dad?
All right!
Don't worry, I'll help you
find your parents!
Mommy!
Bye-bye, Miss!
Bye-bye!
Ouch...
Oh no, my back...
Are you okay?
My back started aching...
I should be fine as long
as I sit down for a bit.
Please get on my back!
Thank you, you were a great help.
It's my pleasure.
The baby's coming!
What?!
A-Are you okay?!
I-I need to get to the hospital...
We're almost there!
O-Okay...
KODAN GENERAL HOSPITAL
You made it, it's going to be all right.
Let's take it slow.
Th-Thank you so much!
Of course!
Best of luck to you and your baby!
You've got this!
Oh no!
What am I doing?!
Th-There's only seven minutes left!
Maybe I can catch the same taxi...
I don't have enough money!
Shoot!
What if I walk back?
I-It'll take thirty minutes...
Still... I can probably make it
in time for the finale!
I want to watch the fireworks
with just you, Eiyu!
Hello? Eiyu?
Um... Sorry.
Wait, what? It's hard to hear...
I can't make it to the fireworks show.
So sorry!
Something came up all of a sudden.
Enjoy the fireworks with Akarin... okay?
Seriously, don't worry about me.
Talk to you later!
With Akarin... huh?
What else could I have said?
There's no way I could've
told him the truth.
Yonosuke-kun.
Take good care of Shio, okay?
Dad!
See you later, Dad!
Take that! Take that!
All right!
Yonosuke-kun.
It's late now.
You should probably go home
before you get scolded!
Your mom's still at work, right?
Huh?
I'll be here until she comes back.
But...
I can't leave you by yourself.
Okay.
All right!
Player 2, you win!
I won!
Hey! You just want to play the game!
Come on, let's play another round!
Yeah, there's no way I can tell him.
He'd rush over, worried sick.
Akarin and I finally
mustered up the courage to ask.
So I don't want to mess things up.
It started...
The couple who kiss during the final,
massive fireworks...
...are destined to be together.
Eiyu...?
Um, excuse me.
Are you the one who helped
my wife at the festival?
Oh, yes.
I knew it was you! Thank you very much.
I really can't thank you
enough for your help!
Oh, please... I was happy to help.
But... is everything okay?
Huh?
Didn't you have plans with someone?
Plans...
No hard feelings to each other, okay?
Meet me at the torii gate at eight.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Is something the matter?
No.
It's nothing, really.
I couldn't have just left her.
I'm sure Eiyu would've done the same.
"I can't leave you by yourself."
That's right!
Eiyu was always generous.
If you're ever feeling lonely,
just let me know.
Eiyu was always there to support me.
I know you were getting even
more nauseous than me, you dummy.
In my heart... it's always been Eiyu!
Sorry... Akarin!
I knew it!
We have been friends since childhood.
I want to watch
the fireworks with Eiyu, too!
And be with him during
the final, massive fireworks!
This concludes tonight's fireworks show.
It's over...
The fireworks... ended...
Eiyu... The truth is...
I... I wanted to watch them with you...
The fireworks... together...
Then you should've said so
in the first place.
E-Eiyu?!
What are you doing here?
Where's Akarin?
Didn't you watch the fireworks with her?
Akari's...
behind you.
You dummy!
Huh? But why?!
What do you mean?!
What was with that call?!
How could we even
enjoy the fireworks
knowing there's something
going on with you?!
Yeah!
Don't hold it in.
If you need help, then say so, you dummy!
Oh my gosh, you're barefoot!
Hey, you're all scraped up! Are you okay?
Shio?
I'm sorry... both of you...
I ruined the fireworks...
There's still time.
Let's go!
What?
Let's try this again!
It's fireworks time!
Isn't this a little wasteful?
We never get to do this.
We might as well go all out!
But...
How did you know where I was?
Oh, about that. Listen to this!
Talk to you later!
Hey, Shio!
She hung up on me.
Let's go, Akari!
What?
Okay...?
Wait, Eiyu!
Where are you going?!
Wh-Where should we go?
Seriously?
Let's just go!
Hey, wait!
Eiyu was so flustered.
Sh-Shut up!
And when we were looking
around at the festival...
Shio! Where are you?
Shio!
Excuse me, young lady.
Are you that girl's friend?
Huh?
You must be.
She was wearing that same hairpin.
The elderly woman told us
everything she saw.
She was really grateful for your help.
But seriously, ditching
a date to help someone?
You're such a Shio, Shio.
Yeah, well...
It's all good. We can always catch
the big fireworks next year, right?
So for now, let's put
on our own big show!
This fireworks show is for us,
childhood friends!
Yeah!
All right, let's do this!
Our fireworks are tiny.
That's why we should've
launched them all at once!
Like I said, it's a waste!
But, come on!
Thanks, both of you.
This turned out to be the best summer!
I'm sorry, Akarin.
I ruined everything.
After we finally mustered up
the courage to ask Eiyu out...
Huh?
Why are you worrying so much about me?
I mean...
I was the one who initiated all of this...
And you're an important
childhood friend, Akarin.
You really are a dummy!
What?!
You're the one who said you wanted to
be honest and have no hard feelings.
When you say, "no hard feelings,"
do you mean a romance
where you're constantly on edge
with other people's feelings?
I don't need you to do that.
I'm not that weak anymore.
I won't let it happen like this.
I'll win fair and square!
Understood.
He fell asleep.
Look at that dumb face.
He's always been like this.
He wore himself out from
all the excitement earlier.
Seriously, he's still such a kid.
Why on earth did I fall
for someone like him?
Right?
It would be easier
if he weren't my childhood friend.
Akarin... Wanna mess with him?
Let's do it.
Being in love with my childhood friend...
Isn't easy...
But it's kinda fun.
Yeah.
Oh my gosh.
What are we doing?!
That was so embarrassing.
Wh-What are you two laughing about?
Hey, he woke up!
Let's run!
Huh? What'd I miss?!
I've got to cherish...
Did I do something?
Why are you running away?
This whole rom-com thing...
Episode 8
Kept Running and Missed the Fireworks?
Hey! Hey!
Since It Matters Too Much, It Still Won't Start a Rom-Com
...with my childhood friends.
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
That had to be Eiyu, right?