Papa...
Papa!
I think the trastorm... is coming this way.
"Trash storm," you mean.
Don't worry. We've got
that big outer wall to protect us.
The trash made it into the city?!
Are... Are we gonna be okay?
Wh-What's with her?
Her appearance... I see.
She's willing to affect us too.
Interesting.
We should go.
We'll get caught up in it at this rate.
Rudo.
Watch and see what can be accomplished
by one who has cast away
what's precious to them.
When this is all over,
I'll retrieve the Watchman Series entries.
Hold it, asshole!
You haven't told me about Amo yet!
Looks like he really doesn't know.
That's just fine, Zodyl.
I'm a Raider now.
Nothing but your pawn.
So I'll give all my hair has...
to make sure you people...
can't escape this place!
Episode 22
The Power of Protection
Last burst!
They left me behind.
Because I couldn't do anything...
I know they left me behind!
It's because they wouldn't give me any orders.
My correction completely failed...
I'm hopeless! I'm even more pathetic
than those two newbies!
Zodyl will never give me orders again!
I hate this! I've been abandoned!
Left in a world without guidance...
I miss the shine of Cthoni's Manhole.
You're disgusting.
I can't take this anymore.
You really can't do shit without me, huh?
You disgusting weakling.
Master Hii...
Let me take over.
I'll take charge from now on.
If we've really been abandoned,
I'll get us out of here.
Okay!
Hurry...
Hurry... Hurry...
Get over the border...
Get over it and kill them!
Before my hair burns itself out...
Hurry up...
and get there!
Dear...
Noerde...
So the "time limit"
on her static electricity...
It's because her hair itself
can't withstand it for longer.
She's using her power
without concern for that now.
I really should've killed her back there!
Now I... can't...
move anymore.
You bastard!
How are you moving?!
How...
How can you still be moving?!
I tapped into this power
by abandoning what's precious to me!
So how?!
I'm gonna smash it.
That core...
I'll smash the shit out of it!
The wall that Rudo's weapon cracked before...
Right now... we're...
in the middle of the trash storm!
No way...
I got them this far, Zodyl.
What did you just say?
What did you call my hair?
We get travelers like you from time to time.
You see it's a village of women
and think we'll fall for some cheesy lines
from anyone with a dick.
Sorry, but we're Sileia, the warrior tribe.
Go get your rocks off with some
sweet little thing somewhere else.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I merely said what I think.
It's beautiful.
Zodyl, the border...
It's so beautiful.
Zodyl...
I have to tell you about this.
When you cross the border...
Everything precious to you is...
I got them this far, Zodyl...
stolen from you...
The border... is...
That thing is...
The Watchma—
C'mon, everyone! Stay strong!
Don't let it suck you out!
Son of a bitch.
We're gonna end up crossing the—
That was Noerde, wasn't it?!
Yeah? Guess she reached
the border a little before us!
You think Zanka and Guita got blown out too?
It looked like it all got dark for a second.
The electric shock must
have everyone exhausted.
They won't hold out long.
We need a way to take this trash beast
down before we cross the border!
Will I have to use this?
Thank goodness! They're still here!
What the hell are you doing?!
You'll get sucked out!
Hey! Grab on to something already!
It's not safe! Come over here, Guita!
You're going to get sucked out!
Sorry, all.
My head hurt a bunch.
But I had a nap, and now I feel better!
Did Zanka hit his head too?
Oh, that's right!
Yeah, that's right, that's right!
Silly me! Guita doesn't have to
worry about getting sucked out!
Bro, how far am I allowed to go now?
Three! Nothing higher than that!
Got it?!
Okay!
You mean, her vital instrument...
It's just what it looks like!
Vital instrument...
Guita!
Maybe I shoulda gone bigger after all!
Gotta seal that hole now...
There.
Now you guys won't fly out.
Man, you never fail to amaze me!
Such a stylish vital instrument!
Anyway...
We'll have no more delays.
The trash storm is dying down.
I have to know...
What made you think an imitation trash
beast could make it across the border?
People have tried all kinds of ways,
and nothing's ever crossed it alive.
Why would that imitation trash beast
would stand a chance?
Company secret, I guess?
That creature...
had the power of protection.
This was its core?
I forgot! These things fall apart
when you destroy their cores!
That slipped my mind!
Someone grab Zanka!
I'm on it!
Grab on to me, everyone!
I'm nice and plushy,
so it should dampen the impact!
I think...
I'm relieved and terrified all at once!
Great work, everyone!
Cleaning complete!
It stinks!
Stinky, stinky, stinky, stinky!
Masks, masks, masks, masks, masks!
Hey. I don't think this is a No Man's Land,
but we probably shouldn't hang out
too long in a polluted zone.
Look, man.
We were just on the way back
from Penta, remember?
It's been non-stop since then, you know?
Even stinky trash is like a nice bed to me now.
Penta...
I never got to find out what happened to Amo.
What was it...
My name
is Zodyl Typhon.
Want to take down the Sphere with me?
He gave me that invitation, then...
Don't tell me...
You can't be satisfied with things
as they are now, can you?
You want more than this facsimile
of friendship, don't you?
He said that, and then...
This has all been an experiment.
We're going to ride this
trash beast across the border.
He dragged us into his crazy experiment
on that huge trash beast,
and what I got was...
The Watchman Series.
I'm tired.
Wanna eat something sweet.
Sweets...
We were...
so worried!
No... pressure.
Is everyone all right?
Anybody need first aid?
Anyone badly injured?
Zanka. Zanka got the worst of it.
Riyo, too.
I'll be fine. Look after Zanka first.
I'm so glad you're safe.
Big Brother.
Big Brother?