This is it.
How the hell's he live out here?
There's jack shit around.
He's got the mountains and the river.
That's plenty.
Sounds plenty inconvenient.
But perfect for training, I guess.
Sorry for dropping in suddenly.
We need to stay here for a while.
I brought some food!
Whoa!
What are you doing?!
Bastard.
You have the nerve
to show your face to me?!
What?
W-Whoa...
I heard from Mitsuba!
Apparently the Bat Man got
the better of you?
And Tackle was injured
badly in the fight.
Th-That's...
Transform! V3!
Wh-Whoa! Let's not fight!
You have no right to call yourself
a Rider right now!
Now, on your feet!
I'm going to beat your
Rider love back into shape!
V3...
Screw Kick!
That was for Tackle.
And this...
Is for me!
And so is this!
Also this!
And last...
One for me!
Wh-Whoa...
So, you put your tail between
your legs and ran here?
It's not that! I was bringing him to—
No excuses!
Risking your life against evil
organizations to defend the world!
Isn't that what a Rider does?!
I like the look in your eyes.
I guess your Rider love
isn't dead after all.
In that case, give me everything...
that you have!
Rider...
Transformation!
Kamen Rider!
V3 Screw—
Rider...
Punch!
Impressive!
But the fight has only begun!
Okay, knock it off!
V3...
Rider...
Dammit, fine then!
Yeeeenough already!
Electric Heat Chop!
Punch!
You're that Shocker combatant
from the other day.
What're you doing here?
You just noticed?
He's been through a lot,
and now he's determined
to take Shocker down.
Please. It'll be a while...
but let me hide here.
Besides...
We brought food!
So be it. A temporary ceasefire.
For now, come in.
I see.
That explains why a Shocker combatant
is determined to bring Shocker down!
Yeah.
My guys sacrificed themselves
to let me get away.
But I'm their aniki. I'm supposed to
be the one who protects them!
Tojima knows this story, but...
This house used to be
where my grandparents lived.
When I was a kid, they were
both killed by the Bat Man.
Ever since, I've been
determined to get strong!
And if you're frustrated, too,
then you need to get strong!
I'm sorry about before.
Attacking you out of the blue like that...
The Bat Man.
Was he as strong as I remember?
The way Shocker waged battle
was incredibly organized.
I think we can't beat them
if we try to do it individually.
We're allies. We need to work together.
Allies, huh?
I'll never live down the fact that
I turned and ran from Shocker,
even if it was to protect my allies...
I don't ever want to run again.
So, I need to get stronger!
Please. Let us train with you.
Thanks for the food!
We'll start training tomorrow!
Don't expect any mercy!
That works for me!
What's wrong? You're not gonna eat?
Well, the inside of my mouth
is all torn up
from when you two laid into me...
You won't have any strength
if you don't eat!
You need to do it,
for the sake of your so-called guys!
You've taken such good
care of us until now...
He's right! This is the least we can do!
Thank you for everything!
Why'd they let me escape?!
Wh-What's wrong?
Giving their lives
for a scumbag like me...
You stupid idiots!
It's only natural to risk everything
to protect someone you care about.
Th-They care about me?!
When I couldn't do
a damn thing for them?!
Okay.
Why don't we have another match
with these bento boxes on the line?
Sounds good.
Let's do it!
Do what?
The three of us will fight. The winner
gets the remaining two bento boxes.
But... there's two of them!
Why don't you just each eat one?
Not the point!
The winner... gets to eat both.
Who gives a shit?!
And who'd wanna eat three lunches?!
You're so pitiful, Shocker!
Are you seriously fighting again?!
It's because you refused to eat!
This will help us train
and build strength.
Two birds with one stone.
Can I really keep up with these freaks?
This is the Combat Girls' agency.
It's huge!
A building like this, in Tokyo?
They've gotta be rolling in it.
According to Tojima-san,
their manager-slash-agency
head is the Bat Man...
Morio Koda. That's apparently his name.
Have you heard of him, Yukarisu?
No, this is all new to me.
I see. He seems pretty well-known
in the industry, though.
He makes plenty
of appearances in the media...
And seems to use his position
to do whatever he wants.
What a creep!
And is it me, or are there a lot of pics
of him with girls in swimsuits?
Ew! They're all Shocker combatants!
EVENTS SPONSORED BY MORIO KODA
Ugh, he's running
all kinds of events, too.
JEWEL NIGHT COMBAT GIRLS CUP
Jewel Night? I wonder
if that's another idol group.
THIRD JEWEL NIGHT COMBAT GIRLS CUP
HOSTED BY ACRUX ENTERTAINMENT
It's not that.
Jewel Night is a popular
online battle royale game.
This agency even runs events
for video games?
Looks like there's one
coming up this Sunday.
Okay. There might be clues.
I'll check it out.
It sounds dangerous,
so you should stay home, Yukarisu.
No way! I'm going too!
Okay.
I won't let what happened
before ever happen again.
Next time, I swear, I'll protect you.
Mitsuba...
I'll work hard not to hold you back, too!
Huh? But this event...
THIS EVENT IS ONLY OPEN TO MEN.
It says it's limited to men only.
You're right.
What should we do?
Leave that to me.
I'll figure something out!
Yukarisu?
Okay, let's talk about what's going down.
What's the deal?
We climbing trees or something?
Wrong. We punch the trees,
and that's all we do.
Kicks are good, too.
Seems kinda basic...
Fundamentals are important, after all.
When you hole up in the mountains,
this is what you start with.
Is that right?
Your tree seems kinda torn up.
Is that from...?
Yes, well, if you strike it every day,
this kind of damage is only natural.
If the tree isn't big enough,
you risk knocking it over.
Seriously?
Okay, let's get started!
Ow!
This... hurts a lot, don't it?
But those two...
Dammit!
How about this, then?!
Nah, it still hurts!
Ninety-eight... ninety-nine...
One hundred—
One hundred ninety-nine...
Two hundred...
You still good?
Of course.
Are they for real?
In that case...
How about now?!
You son of a—
Not bad!
But we're not done!
Wh-Why?
V3...
Big Wheel Kick!
What are you doing?!
What is this?
Aren't you like, good friends?
Are you just playing around?
Sure don't seem like it!
Dammit, you guys...
Should you really be unloading on each
other if you're on the same side?
You're all messed up. Damn.
Come on, time to get up.
I made some hotpot.
Smells good...
There's no beef in it.
Looks good!
Thanks for the food!
Delicious!
This really tastes incredible!
It's good!
Thanks...
It really is good!
Wait, didn't you make it yourself?
Are you good at cooking?
I wouldn't say that.
But when you live on your own,
you can whip up something like this.
Can you?
Not at all. I either get
takeout or frozen food.
I cook, but everything I make
just tastes like the ingredients.
Did you season this or something?
With what, exactly?
All you've got in this place is salt.
All I did was put it in water,
add some salt, and boil it a bit.
Is the secret ingredient love?
Why the hell would it be?
When I was in elementary school...
I ended up in the hospital once
because of how cool Kamen Rider is.
In the second episode,
when he was facing off against
the enemy in the darkness...
Kamen Rider's eyes lit up!
And it was so cool...
That I passed out
and hit my head on a table!
I get you!
When my mother found me,
she took me to the hospital.
W-Well, passing out is a little extreme...
But even for a Shocker fan like me,
that scene was awesome.
Their whole bodies didn't light up
the way modern heroes' do,
but that's what made it so good.
There was nothing more exciting!
That was... the light
that lit my soul on fire.
In the same vein,
I once ended up in the hospital
because of how I looked up to V3.
You too?!
In episode seven of V3,
Pops was operating a wrecking ball,
to help V3 train to withstand hundreds
of kilograms with just his body.
I-I think I remember that one...
I tried to mimic it by filling
a sack with a bunch of rocks,
hanging it from a tree branch,
and having Mitsuba swing it
at me from up high.
I get you!
The bag was heavier than I expected,
and I ended up knocked off a cliff.
That... is not something a kid should do.
Grandpa and Grandma were furious with me.
I used to get injured training
to become a Rider, too.
I'm amazed you guys survived this long.
There's something crazy about
the way you guys play Rider.
I have never once in
my entire life "played" Rider!
Likewise!
Being a Rider means living
under the shadow of death.
I mean, if you're the real deal...
I am V3!
I'm Rider 1!
Yeah, okay.
Even as we speak, we're engaged
in a battle against Shocker!
He's right!
I mean, as weird as it is, you're right.
I wouldn't even mind dying
in battle against Shocker.
Come on, you don't wanna die.
You understand how I feel, don't you?
Kamen Rider risks his life in battle,
for the sake of the people and his friends.
That's the kind of life I also aspire to!
It's only natural to risk everything
to protect someone you care about.
You've changed.
And yes, Riders 1 and 2 both sacrificed
their lives to defeat a monster,
protecting V3 and humanity.
You're talking about the Turtle Bazooka
fight from episode two of V3!
I was in tears.
Mitsuba and I both were bawling.
I guess I can see why.
That's what it means to battle Shocker.
Death can come for you
unannounced, at any moment.
But...
IT'D BE AN HONOR TO DIE AS A RIDER
It'd be an honor to die as a Rider!
Okay, we've got more training tomorrow.
Let's head to bed.
Right!
I...
will get stronger!
Tackle...
is not dead!
NEXT EPISODE
I WAS CRAVING
A BATTLE
WITH SHOCKER
I WAS CRAVING A BATTLE WITH SHOCKER
ILLUSTRATION BY: YAMAGUCHI BIRU