Taro.
Nio.
Hajime.
You brats...
...grew into fine young men
while I wasn't looking.
I remember someone
called you a trio of wolves.
Well, now you truly live up to the name.
Um...
Taro.
You don't need to feel
indebted to me anymore.
You've done your loyal duty,
and done it well.
Serizawa-sensei.
Nio.
I thought you were an odd,
uppity little novice at first, but now?
You want to protect the weak,
and get stronger.
That's the root of it.
But you know, if you insist on ideals,
life will only get harder.
The Miburo aren't what
you want us to be anymore.
I know you see that.
Hajime.
You have skill,
but don't follow in my footsteps.
Don't let the ghost
of the samurai trap you.
You're all free now!
Live however you like!
Blue Miburo
Serizawa-san, if you would.
Sure.
My dear ronin of Mibu!
You've served well, day in and day out.
The Shogunate has granted us
a special reward.
Drink the night away.
"Get to know" any woman
who strikes your fancy.
Don't worry about money.
Just enjoy yourselves in style! Cheers!
Drink up!
What's wrong, Sir Kondo?
A leader's gotta cut a fine figure.
Set an example.
Serizawa-sensei.
We're so glad we joined you
in the Miburo, sir.
It makes us feel like we're really living
and getting things done.
That feeling counts for a lot.
Next.
I never thought the day would come
when I'd wear two swords!
With the right spirit,
anyone can become anything.
Next.
Man, I can't believe you set up
such a great party for us.
We had you all wrong.
Yeah. We had you pegged
as a rough-and-tumble tyrant.
Never mind. Anything goes here.
Next.
I can send money home
to my ma in the country!
I can feel proud of myself!
Yeah? Glad to hear it. Next.
Serizawa-sensei, let me say a few words!
And me!
Sensei!
Come one, come all!
Are we really going through with it?
If we wait to ambush Serizawa's litter
in all this wind and rain,
can we be sure we won't miss it?
We can.
Is killing Serizawa really
the right thing to do?
I mean, I'll kill him
if you tell me to, of course.
But I just...
I can't help thinking it'd be a shame.
Heisuke, back out of the plan.
No, I—
Back out!
What now, genius?
We're down one guy.
I know you were thinking of Heisuke.
Still, this will make the attack
considerably more difficult.
I don't want to take anyone
who will have regrets.
It'll come back to bite us.
It poured like this that day, too.
Back when I was a kid.
I spotted a kitten swept away
by the river current.
My older sister, who was with me,
dropped her umbrella and ran after it.
The current was swift. Anyone could see
she'd never save the kitten.
I told her...
It's hopeless. It's gonna die anyway.
So what?
The way she answered without hesitation
struck me as beautiful.
And I learned then...
that just because a storm is raging
and something seems pointless,
that's no excuse not to try.
We can't let it become known that
we're acting on orders from Aizu.
If word gets out,
Aizu will withdraw support,
and we'll lose our Shogunate backing.
With the thread of our great cause cut,
we'll go back to being the gaggle of ronin
we started as. Just a gang of ruffians.
If that happens, the Miburo is finished.
So we need to prove the Miburo
had no hand in what we're about to do.
We need to come through
without a scratch on us.
But if that fails, we'll say
the four of us acted alone,
and that none of our comrades
knew about our plan.
Well, that part is true.
Don't worry.
The Miburo can rise again as long
as we have Kondo-san to rally around.
If we fail tonight,
we'll slit our bellies there and then.
If we take responsibility immediately,
the rest of the Miburo can avoid blame.
I'll do it. Alone, if I have to.
Don't come with me unless
you're prepared for the worst.
I don't want to force you.
I can't say my feelings have changed.
Looks like we're the Hijikata-gumi now.
From here on, we walk the path of Asura.
I'm leaving.
You there. Call a litter.
Yes, sir. At once.
Whoops.
Rest easy. I already
have a litter waiting.
Take this gentleman to Mibu.
Yes, sir.
What are you thinking?
I won't dance to your tune.
I didn't like the look of these bearers.
I'll catch another litter.
Yes, sir! I'll hunt one down!
We'll go back to Mibu for another round.
We've got women waiting for us.
That's our Sensei.
No man in Kyoto can wow
the ladies like you can.
Hey, what do we do now?
The whole plan just swerved off-course.
This is a dilemma.
We can't have their litters left
in the fields before we strike now.
Wait till half past the fourth watch.
What?
They'll disappear tonight.
We'll make sure of that.
Hey, where are you going?
For a piss.
Three litters?
Who for? Serizawa-sensei
and his buddies?
Nio!
They're heading for Mibu.
It really must be them.
Wh-What should I do?
That lead litter looks heavier
than the others.
Serizawa-san must be in it.
This road leads to the Yagis' house.
They don't plan to stop on the way.
That's strange.
I don't see any assassins.
In fact, none of the other Miburo
have even left Shimabara.
So how can they waylay
Serizawa-san's group?
Is today not the day? Was I wrong
to think something would happen?
I'd better turn back for now and—
There they are.
I knew it.
Hijikata-san.
Okita-san.
Harada-san.
Kondo-san?
No.
Yamanami-san?
Kondo-san isn't with them? Why not?
Was he never one of
the assassins to begin with?
Serizawa-sensei and his buddies
really were in those litters.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Something's coming.
Something terrible's about to—
Nio? Why's he going back?
I don't get it.
Aw, who gives a crap?
I've got bigger problems.
I need to get to Serizawa-sensei fast.
Who's that?
Looks like a kid.
Hm? What's up? Oh, Nio! It's you.
Hey now. You know kids
aren't allowed in here.
Make way.
Nope.
Aw, forget it.
Nio.
What are you doing here?
Kondo-san.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about Serizawa-san.
As commander,
you must know what's happening.
Not another word.
I'm angry, you know.
Uh, what's up?
Is there trouble?
Okay, gentlemen!
I'm about to tell you all a tale.
Ten years had passed
since the Black Ships came.
Through our millennium-old capital, Kyoto,
rogues swaggered,
law and order a thing of the past.
The Shogunate put out a call in Edo
to do something about it.
And 234 samurai rose to the challenge.
Hey, something's starting up.
Entertainment?
Let's hear it.
Yet they were all ruffians,
confident in their skill with a blade.
Their journey to Kyoto
could not pass without incident.
Hear what we Miburo faced on the road.
It's sure to leave you
on the floor laughing.
Now, listen up!
Oh, a story?
Great! Start telling it!
Angry, you say?
Be calm. Be calm.
Why did you allow something like this?
Why did you send your allies to do it
without taking part yourself?
It goes against the sincerity
we made our emblem.
But more than that, Kondo-san,
it doesn't seem like you.
Because Serizawa-san has strayed
from the path of humanity.
The path of humanity?
What do you mean by that?
Serizawa-san...
seems to be suffering from an illness.
He hasn't had a doctor examine him,
but he said he can feel it
spreading through his body.
There are times he can
barely hold his sword.
He said he's running out of time.
Kondo Isami was charged
to arrange lodgings,
but somehow, he forgot to book
a room for Serizawa Kamo.
Serizawa raged.
Kondo could only apologize.
They stared each other down
amid the flames.
Now, what could fate
have in store for them?
Hurry up and tell us!
I understand the position you
and your allies are in. After all...
Do something about Serizawa.
Aizu takes this seriously.
I was at that meeting.
But getting rid of Serizawa-san—
Nio.
Not another word.
Don't brush me off
just because I'm a child.
I can't hold it in anymore.
I insist you hear me out.
Tell me, then.
Why didn't you take action
as an inspector?
You could made this affair public
if you had the mind to.
How can I possibly tell anyone?
Even I have enough sense to see that.
"The path of humanity." I see.
You mean Okiku-chan's fate.
But that wasn't Serizawa-san's fault.
You asked him?
I did.
But he wouldn't tell me
any more than that.
I don't believe Serizawa-san killed her.
It isn't in his nature.
Then—
But he did know something.
In which case, should he not have
told the truth, at least to the Yagis?
That is why I waited a month.
Why couldn't he tell them?
He was frightened.
He surely held his tongue
to put his own safety first.
He acted so unlike
the Serizawa-san I know.
Not everyone can be as strong
as you are, Kondo-san.
People get scared sometimes.
I placed this matter in Toshi's hands.
I won't interfere. I promised him that.
I did it to preserve the Miburo.
I don't want to hear something like that.
Maybe it's because I'm a kid,
but it doesn't resonate with me.
Is that...
because deep down,
it doesn't satisfy you, either?
My own wishes are beside the point.
Then what about Serizawa-san's wishes?
He told me...
The measure of a samurai is his death.
I have nothing more left to do.
But if I possibly can...
"I want to face Sir Kondo
in a final duel."
This won't end unless you go to him.
Will you take even that wish
from Serizawa-san?
Leaving him to your allies?
Pretending you had
nothing to do with it?
Niimi-san is gone now, too.
Once Serizawa-san dies,
you'll lead the Miburo, won't you?
No. I lack what it takes.
You will anyway!
Everyone will follow you because
you're truly strong in body and mind.
I know they will. I think I will, too.
Deep down, everyone wants to be strong.
To be diligent, earnest, and righteous.
Looking at some, you wouldn't think it.
It's all right to let loose
once in a while.
You shouldn't need me to tell you that.
Because we're weak.
We want to slack off.
To take the easy way out.
But...
Sincerity
Isn't forgiving that weakness,
and reaching out to it,
what sincerity is all about?
What good is a commander who
can't even grant a comrade's request?
You're about to step off the
"path of humanity" as we speak.
If you're going to bear
the burden of the Miburo,
bear all of it.
Forgive me for speaking
so insolently.
Listen, Sir Kondo.
What tomorrow holds for the Miburo is...
My dear ronin of Mibu!
What's wrong, Sir Kondo?
A leader's got to cut a fine figure.
Set an example.
Nio.
Do you have an evening star?
I mean a north star.
I'm told all sailors navigate by it.
It never wavers.
While they can see it,
they will never lose their way.
He has been my guiding compass.
In fact, he stands above
all other samurai.
Let us go.
Kondo-san.
Look at you, Kondo-sensei!
You're falling down drunk!
You shouldn't have had so much.
Nio, lead him to the outhouse.
Y-Yes, sir.
I'll handle things here.
Todo-san.
Go on.
We must hurry.
Yes, sir.
The Path of Asura
Wh-Who's there?
Next time
It's me, Harada Sanosuke.
Serizawa, I won't let you off the hook
for what you did to Hasumukai.
Stabbing you in the dark isn't my style,
but Soji's got a point.
We gotta go with
whatever works at this point.
I'll show you what I can do when
I've got a spear in my hands.
Huh? Hang on. Something seems off.
Don't tell me Serizawa
and his crew are...
Next time: "The Arena."
The Arena