If I take this Silver Key...
You thief.
Racio...
Good grief. Your foolishness
never ceases to amaze me.
So basically, my warnings
meant nothing to you.
I know, I know. But...
What are you going to do about
the dual-existence problem?
If you go over there, your dual existence
will become a possibility once again.
Hah! So you were planning to leap
before you looked, were you?
Not to mention, if you become its host,
you'll be trapped once again within
a time loop you may never escape.
It's basically a miracle that you were
able to end your loop and stand here now.
Do you really think you can make
that miracle happen again?
I don't know... but I'll have time.
Time?
Yeah.
The longer I keep looping, the more time
I'll have to figure it all out.
And...
I won't be alone.
Even if I'm looping,
you'll all still be with me.
You'll help me reach ideas and decisions
that I never would have alone...
and most importantly,
you'll give me courage.
I don't know how much time it'll take.
But... If I have all of you,
I'm certain I'll make it.
To an ending where no one
has to be unhappy.
You've reached a level of foolishness
where it's actually somehow refreshing.
Take it, you thief.
This is actually the second time
I've gotten the Silver Key from you.
Unbelievable. Then I guess
you're twice the thief, then.
EPISODE 20: WORLD OF STARS
A time loop?
So you're gonna go on a journey
through time with that thing?
Yeah.
I'm going to fill this Silver Key
with information once again
and open the dimensional door.
Then I'll find Setsu and finally
connect cause and effect.
Man, hearing you talk
just does my head in, Yuri.
U-Um, what do you mean
by cause and effect?
What the heck's going on?
It appears that an
explanation is in order.
You are the narrator, are you not?
Explain so everyone can understand.
Right.
None of you have any memories
of my past loops or of Setsu.
Okay.
The Setsu that was in this world
used my filled Silver Key
to open a dimensional door,
crossing over to another dimension
with its own, separate cause and effect.
But their own Silver Key still isn't full,
which means they can't escape the loop.
That's why I'm going to fill
this Silver Key once more,
open the door, and go
over to the other side.
So that Setsu can close their loop.
Will going over there be enough
for you to close Setsu's loop, Yuri?
It should, if they give me
their Silver Key.
But filling up a Silver Key
is really difficult, isn't it?
Are you sure you'll be able
to find them again?
I have no idea.
But I have to try.
Nothing ventured,
nothing gained, I suppose...
You keep spoutin' off all these excuses,
but you're just chasin' after some chick
you have the hots for, aren't ya?
What?! For real?!
W-Well, Setsu's non-binary, though.
But they get you excited,
don't they? I sorta get it.
Yeah, I have a feeling you'd like them.
Sounds A-okay to me!
You cheater!
Huh?
I can't believe you strung
cute li'l SQ along all this time.
Ch-Cheater?
You'd better take responsibility for this!
For that night when we totes
shared a bed during warp!
Yuri... How could you?
Yuri, you... You're just a...
W-Wait! That's not true!
Come on. Knock it off with the jokes.
It's not a joke.
I always thought... cute li'l SQ was
actually someone special to you.
At least, that's what your eyes said!
SQ...
You're very precious to me.
You and everyone here.
But the reason I'm even able to be here
right now is because of Setsu.
So I can't bear the thought
of them suffering all alone.
Yeah...
I just can't let that happen.
Well... We should probably do a toast?
Yeah. Let's send them off with a bang!
Have fun preparin' and stuff.
I'mma go back to my room.
Nope.
Lemme go!
I will start the preparations.
Jina, will you assist me?
Sure.
I'm so sorry!
Nope.
Your forehead's gotta
be glued to the ground!
Like this!
I'm so sorry!
The heck are they doing?
Yuri wanted to learn how to grovel.
Well, that's, uh... different.
They were saying it'd be
an essential skill for their future.
I said that hurt, damn it!
But this was your idea, Shigemichi.
You said, "I'll show you just
how tough my skin is!"
Well, well...
Yuriko...
What's with that getup?
Is this not a costume party?
You're so cute, Yurikocchi!
You piece of trash. You deceived me.
Tee-hee!
What chaos.
But I suppose observing from the eye of
the storm is also a form of entertainment.
Here are some snacks Jina prepared.
Disgusting.
That's brutally honest.
The Gnosia incident that
took place on Planet Liu-An...
And the fifteen that just happened
to take refuge from it on this ship...
This is one heckuva party!
Everyone's having fun!
I've started to think that it wasn't just
coincidence that brought us together.
For myself, for everyone here... No,
this was a vital part of
the whole world's destiny.
It couldn't have happened any other way.
And each and every one of them
was an irreplaceable part of it.
They're all my precious friends.
Seriously, I'm at a
complete loss for words.
Racio?
I guess staying in my room
was the right choice.
What is this?
I was bored, so I compiled it all.
Everything that'll happen henceforth,
and everything you'll need to do.
Seriously, you truly are a fool.
I honestly can't see this ending well.
Of course.
If I start looping again,
these things will happen...
This is amazing! You're amazing, Racio!
I'll explain everything you need to know,
so drill it into that brain of yours.
Because that's the only thing you
can take with you on these loops.
R-Right...
You're exactly right.
And there you have it.
Wow! That's a perfect plan!
In what way? My reasoning itself
was perfect, I'll give you that,
but in practice, I'd say it's nearly
impossible for you to pull off.
That's true. But I'll do my best.
I can't let your efforts go to waste.
Seriously, I just don't understand you.
To go to so much trouble
and put yourself in so much danger
all for another's sake... It's beyond me.
You sure about that?
Wh-What are you trying to say?
Just so you know,
I didn't do this for you.
Thank you.
When I first awakened here,
I felt nothing but despair.
I had no memories,
there was a Gnosia on board,
and everyone was suspicious of each other.
And you were the coldest
out of everyone, Racio.
You constantly treated me like a Gnosia
and tried to send me into cold sleep.
To be honest, I couldn't help
but think time and time again,
"If only they weren't here."
And I'd like to tell my past
self that they were wrong.
That the unfriendly, sharp-tongued
individual standing before them
is a genuinely kind person,
not that they'll ever show it,
and will help them when no one else can.
Hmph. Don't get the wrong idea.
I just came to laugh at the
poor, pathetic guinea pig
that the Silver Key
is about to make its new host.
Of course.
Yurinchy...
Goodbye.
Jina...
I feel like... I've said goodbye
to you many times before, Yuri.
Same here.
Goodbye.
I have no further hesitations or regrets.
I'm going to reach Setsu...
and bring about a conclusion
where all our loops can end.
Doubt not. Fear not. And know.
Knowledge will save all.
Let's begin. This discussion will
determine whether we survive.
I wonder how much time
has passed since then.
As I continue looping over and over,
I've noticed a lot of things
that are different from before.
Oh!
You're awake. Are you feeling okay?
Yeah.
First, no matter how many loops I do,
Setsu isn't present in any of them.
But I expected as much.
After all, when Setsu went
through the dimensional door,
they ceased to exist in this universe.
But also...
Comet... Is there anyone named
Kukrushka on board this ship?
Kukrushka?
Doesn't ring a bell.
I see.
Along with Setsu, Kukrushka
also seems to have disappeared.
She won't show up regardless
of how many loops I do, either.
Well, technically, she hasn't
disappeared completely.
She's asleep in storage as a doll.
But she hasn't once awoken or moved,
and she hasn't gone
on any killing sprees, either.
What's going on? Could this have been
caused in some way by Setsu's absence?
Yuri.
Huh?!
Let us begin the meeting posthaste.
Oh, right. Of course.
Not good. I can't let myself
get distracted now.
I have to do everything I can to fill the
Silver Key so I can see Setsu again.
LeVi, can I get a count
of the Gnosia on board?
Certainly. I am detecting two Gnosia.
And so, my looping continues anew.
I've eliminated all of the Gnosia,
and both you and I have survived.
You said that if I fulfilled both those
conditions, you'd tell me the truth.
To think you'd actually win.
You seem quite intelligent
for a bit player.
Well, I have looped through
all this many, many times...
in order to reach this world line.
A Silver Key...
Yeah. And that's why I know...
exactly what you're about to tell me.
Oho. What an interesting thing to say.
Well then, do enlighten me.
You're going to tell me what I really am.
I'm a Bug—
something created by Gnos that
shouldn't exist in this world at all.
I see. Apparently I was wrong
to call you a bit player.
If you knew all that already, why did
you persist in winning this game?
I have a request.
The Hoshibune?
Yeah. If we can get within
communication range,
it should be possible
to hack into their system.
What a foolish plan.
If you fail, we won't get off lightly.
Oh, no...
If that happens,
you can blame it all on me.
You can just say I hijacked the ship.
And my compensation?
I, Jonas, am not so charitable
as to work without recompense.
He has you there.
Of course, I don't have money
or any other form of payment.
Hmph.
But...
With this, you and your ship will have
another heroic tale to add to your legend.
You can tell of how you confronted the
Hoshibune, infamous for cyberization,
when even the military
held back on facing them.
You'll go down in history.
Stella.
Yes?
Set a course for the Hoshibune.
He may seem like a jaded,
cold-hearted adult,
but deep inside, he still loves
adventure and competition.
I've watched him long enough to know...
that Jonas is still a boy at heart.
Let's get there safe and sound.
But the route to the
Hoshibune is unknown.
Please guide us.
Who are you to command me?
But I suppose this will make
for an adequate diversion.
So this is the Hoshibune.
Cyberization?
Indeed.
The key to solving the dual-existence
problem likely lies within cyberization.
If you can travel between dimensions
by cyberizing your consciousness...
Then the whole dual-existence
thing won't happen!
Correct.
But that means you'll have to find
and make use of them.
Are you certain about this?
Even if you succeed in
cyberizing your consciousness,
there's a possibility that Gnos
will instantly swallow you up.
If that happens, there's nothing I can do.
But I want to believe
that Gnos won't do that.
Send a call sign to the Hoshibune.
Send the call sign.
As you wish.
Now, go to the pod that we prepared.
Thanks.
Please... let this go as planned.
If Gnos swallows me up, it's all over.
And not even Yuriko or Racio
knows if that will happen.
All I can do is pray.
Here we go.
Please... Please... Please... Please...
Sha-ming.
Remnan.
Otome.
Kukrushka.
Jonas.
Chipie.
Comet.
Yuriko.
Stella.
Shigemichi.
Jina.
Racio.
SQ.
Setsu!
Gnos...?
It's full.
Yes, I know.
Thank you.
Do you understand?