Careful not to fall, all right?
I know!
I'm afraid your shop, Succubus Wings,
has gone out of business.
Did sales crash that hard?!
No, the shop more crashed literally.
Literally?
Th-The damn building collapsed?!
Must be karma, I'm telling you!
I started out in the slums with nothing,
and I finally had a place of my own!
Y-You don't gotta cry...
Please, Hajime.
Would you come with me
when I head back to the city?
I need to rebuild, so I can't
afford to pay you much...
But I'm so anxious!
Yanago, huh?
Please, Hajime!
You're twisting my arm here.
Thank you, Hajime!
It will be a relief to have a man's help.
Got 'em.
The girls are all okay, right?
Yes. The one silver lining in all this.
Well, that's good.
But if someone was behind all this...
I will show them hell.
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
EPISODE 6: DECISIVE BATTLE
IN THE DUNGEON ATTACK!
That's one big building!
Sure enough.
Heck yeah!
Wow!
Come on, hurry!
Good thinking!
Man, these walls still cast
the longest shadows.
Okay, enough trying to sound
profound. Let's move along.
I wasn't trying to sound profound!
My store!
It's pulverized.
Someone made a real mess of things.
Hey! You're supposed
to stay behind the line!
Wait, boss?
If it isn't Maribel! What're you doing?
Part-time work!
Things've been a real mess, y'know?
The store got flattened!
And would you believe...
Why, it's been ages, Veronica!
Jessie Freckles...
HIDDEN WITH MAKEUP
Do not mention my freckles!
Anyway, it's a real shame what
happened to your store here.
You did this, didn't you? You're dead.
I-It wasn't me!
A mist dragon trying to take roost
just happened to land on it!
It's the truth.
The guild made an announcement
of it this morning.
A mist dragon flying through overnight
tried to roost on the roof,
but the weight was too much
to bear and it collapsed.
Damn it!
The dragon policy was the one option I
didn't take when I got monster insurance!
You should honestly be grateful.
I'm taking good care of all your girls
now that they've got nowhere to go!
Lucky you, Veronica.
This lady seems real nice.
She's not doing this out of the
kindness of her heart! Not her!
All part of the deal.
I'll take care of your girls until
you're ready to employ them again,
and in exchange...
You will release Master
Rishat from his slavery!
Rishat?
Oh, Spot.
This is what I mean! You need
to stop treating him like that!
Come to think of it, you're
in love with him, aren't you?
Well, then...
If you front me the entire cost
of rebuilding, I'll consider it.
How greedy can you be?!
Well, I had a feeling you
wouldn't agree readily.
So why don't we settle this
over a dungeon attack?
If you win, I'll furnish half
your reconstruction expenses.
But if you lose, then you'll
set Master Rishat free,
and you'll work for me from now on!
Fine. You're on!
I mean, I said that,
but this is actually kind of terrible...
Huh? But the food's great.
I didn't mean our meal.
Your opponent makes a habit
of buying up all the dungeon maps,
and she has Toraverse in her employ.
Yeah, that sums it up.
TORAVERSE: PARTY SPECIALIZING IN
THE DUNGEON "GOWEN'S ALTAR"
Well, then she's definitely
got the upper hand.
I hate that woman!
You needn't worry!
If you lose, I will also lose
my place at your side.
Therefore, I, Rishat...
will be getting serious,
starting tomorrow!
Maybe it'd be okay if you lost?
No! I'm going to get my
rebuilding costs comped!
These rabbit cutlets in miso
sauce are tasty, Hajime!
Sure are.
DUNGEON: "GOWEN'S ALTAR"
So, you've come, Veronica!
Ready to do this?
Not at all!
Thank you so much!
What are you hitting Master Rishat for?!
This will be a five-on-five team battle.
The team to defeat the boss
of the middle floors,
the Resurrection Monster,
will be the winner.
Let the dungeon attack begin!
The order was for maximum speed!
Then let's go all out!
Yeah!
Hey! Don't leave me behind!
Master Rishat!
Ba-dump! Oh, Master Rishat...
What are you doing, idiot?!
Don't go getting your masochist on
in the middle of a showdown!
Beg your pardon.
The trap just looked so appealing...
I couldn't resist.
Hey! What do you think you're
doing to Master Rishat?!
Oh, put a sock in it!
What a joke.
Those tiger people ran ahead!
Our lady's gonna lose!
Hey!
Harder, please!
Looks like a dead end.
Rirui the bronze-rank adventurer...
has hit a dead end!
A h-hidden opening?!
MEANWHILE...
A treasure chest!
Aw, those are for grown-ups.
Just try it on.
The gear you find in dungeon chests always
sizes itself for whoever finds it first.
I'm so strong!
Yeah, I dunno about that part.
There's no time to stand around!
We must make haste!
Sure, sure.
THE RESURRECTION MONSTER
SHACHIHOKO WALKER
Hajime, look at that weird gold thing.
I figure that's gotta be the boss monster.
What'd I just say?!
Don't try and stop me, Hajime!
Yeah, tough luck.
You've got no shot tackling
that head-on at your level!
If you're that determined, keep your
distance and use some damn magic.
But Hajime...
Rirui's magic is just a shower.
Well, give it a try anyway.
You've leveled up,
and you've got new gear.
Rirui thinks she's stronger with
a blade than a bo staff, but...
That's a real staff. No bo about it.
So just give it a try, okay?
Yeah, looks like you've got more
potential in this department, Rirui.
What?!
Our prey!
Rirui landed the finishing blow!
You're a feisty one, aren't you?
You brat...
I'm impressed, little cub!
You did a great job striking opportunely.
At your age, that's amazing.
Rirui is better with a sword,
but I'm good with my bo staff too!
They're not mad about being bested?
Wait! It's already dead?!
Wh-Who did it?! Hajime? Toraverse?
Wait, Rirui?
You're kidding! That's amazing, Rirui!
Well, yeah!
Rirui's pretty awesome!
I lost...
Yahoo! Half off, half off!
Thank you two so much!
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
Wow, Hajime, you're so manly!
And cool!
Ain't I, though? Tell me about it!
You fought for our sake, didn't you?
Of course I did!
You're so reliable!
Guess I am!
Hajime! We're buying souvenirs, right?
Wh-What do you want, Rirui?
I'm in the middle of something!
Besides, there's no rush.
We're leaving town tonight, aren't we?!
What? You're leaving so soon?
I wanted to talk more!
We can talk, we can talk!
We're going! Now!
No! But the boobies...!
Damn it, I was enjoying the
harem vibes back there.
Didn't Miss Olive ask us
to buy her some perfume?!
Perfume, eh?
Oh, you're going to Yanago?
And for five days?
I guess so.
I see... Five whole days, huh?
Dreamberries.
Perfume made from dreamberries
is all the rage.
In Yanago, I mean.
What's "per-foom"?
Why in the hell is smelly
water so damn expensive?
I'm just a guy from the slums,
so I don't have a clue.
The slums...
What was that about slimes, Hajime?
Are we gonna go fight some?!
I said slums. The slums!
It's where I used to live.
And since we're here in the city,
might as well pay my respects.
Oh. At your mom and dad's grave?
Nah, a friend I used to run with.
I never even met my parents!
Want me to be your mom for today?
Nope. And that's a weird
way of showing concern.
Th-There sure seem to be a lot
of scary folks watching us.
They're not looking at you, dummy.
They're looking at tasty
little Dragon there.
It's not food!
Not food at all!
Hajime, they sell trash here.
Trash!
Did you hear that, Old Pom?
Pipe down, scourge of the slums.
Scourge?
So, what is this?
You move back or something?
Not quite. Just in town for work.
And is this your kid?
Nope, just a squirt I picked up.
You picked her up?
Well, ain't you a sweetheart!
Maybe I oughta call you
the angel of the slums instead!
Only if you wanna die, old man!
You never change, boy.
Grandpa, do you know Hajime?
Sure do! From back when
he was as little as you.
The first time I ran into him,
he was trying to steal from my shop.
From here?
And when I tried to take it back,
he hit me in the head with a rock.
And that pissed me off,
so next time I saw him,
I kicked him square in the butt!
I remember that!
Quit making it sound nostalgic, boy!
This place is scary.
But...
I see.
This is one place that Hajime grew up in.
Dragon thief!
Hajime! Dragon was...
Better get going!
What are you laughing at?!
Meat for me!
Dragon!
Now I'm angry!
Rirui Super Miracle Shot!
Damn it!
Who did that?!
Hey! You!
Who's turf are you from?!
Oh, it's you, Lotton.
Look at you. Expanded your turf, huh?
Guess you've been working hard!
Y-Yes!
Um... what brings you
back home, Mr. Hajime?
What're you afraid of, Lotton?
Hey, I don't recognize you.
Who're you supposed to be?
Do you understand who's turf
this is? Lotton here--
You idiot! Stop—
THE SLUMS' FAMOUS HUMAN SKEWER
Give my regards to Salman!
Harris!
Wait up, Hajime!
Hajime, weren't those your offerings?
That's just how it goes around here.
I used to do the same thing!
When people die, they're cremated.
As ash, they're carried away on the wind,
all the way to the sun.
I wonder where they are right about now.
Did they make it to the sun?
Here's hoping they're not hungry.
What're you doing?
Rirui is your mom today.
I didn't ask for that, remember?
Honestly...
If only you had Rirui around
when you were little.
Then I could've worked hard
to make things easier for you.
Such a shame!
I get the feeling things
would've been even harder.
That was great.
Just helping myself to some booze!
Well, don't overdo it, Old Pom.
Really hits the spot after so long!
Hajime, what're they doing?
Fishing for rats.
It's a way for slum kids
to make some spare change.
Did you do that too?
Back in the day, yeah.
Rirui wants to try!
Just once, okay? The other kids are
trying to earn money for food.
Hey, that big one looks pretty good.
You'll wanna tie it up with the
line in that box over there.
O-Okay.
Then you lower it off the bridge...
And after a while,
a big old rat will come this way.
So you grab a big rock and kill it.
That way, you don't get hurt.
Don't wanna hit the caterpillar, either.
They're valuable bait and can be reused.
Wanna stop?
I'm gonna do it!
We're going to have a
barbecued rat party today!
All right. But don't kill the caterpillar.
Hey, Hajime! Come have a drink yourself!
Sure.
Not yet. Gotta wait...
There! Here it comes!
"If only Rirui had been around
when you were little," huh?
Definitely would've meant more trouble,
which I sure didn't need, but...
You dummy!
Hajime! My caterpillar!
But I bet, on some level...
It would've made things more fun.
NEXT TIME: RIRUI AND COCKO