Where is this?
What are these animals?
So, you have awoken.
As far as I can tell,
you seem to be unharmed.
What happened to that vampire?
What the hell happened?
It seems as though he has disappeared.
Evidently, we have been brought
to the outskirts of this town.
What is their purpose?
I don't see Watcher.
You're awake.
We were just talking about
whether or not to carry you onto a bed.
I believe my daughter found you both...
collapsed in the garden.
You are...
I am Tsubaki Kuruoka!
Now, go ahead and speak up, Richard.
Why did you sneak out of the castle
without permission so late at night?
Mother...
I am afraid.
That's...
Saber?
This is his past?
Afraid? Of what?
That I am able to become
proficient at everything.
I can do anything well.
There is not a man who can win
against me in swordsmanship.
I had thought they were
all going easy on me,
so I snuck out of the castle and attacked
bandits infamous for their violence!
Oh my.
However, I easily trounced them.
No matter what skill I take up,
I master it immediately.
People soon become unable
to win against me in contests.
At this rate, I will not be able
to make a single friend.
Is it better if I go easy on them and
pretend as if I am not adept at anything?
Man, he has no charm.
You said you wouldn't laugh, Mother!
Richard, you are indeed a genius.
However...
being a genius alone will
not make you a hero.
A hero, you say?
Just how King Arthur and the
Knights of the Round Table were as such,
people only become heroes
after staying firm to their own path.
So, if you truly are
able to do everything...
cherish the ability to pass on stories.
Pass on...
Now, I shall tell you...
the story of the King of Knights who raced
through Britain with
a sacred sword in hand!
But before that...
As a mother, I must reprimand you...
for leaving the castle without permission.
Ayaka?
Are you okay?
Adult...
Wha...
Ow!
A-Are you all right?
What about you, Saber? Are you okay?
Yeah.
Not perfect, but I can move around.
Healing Magecraft by our allies—
The reason you left me at the Church...
was because they could protect me
when you died, wasn't it?
Oh...
My apologies.
If you have time to worry about me,
then you can take
better care of yourself, Saber!
I mean, that thing earlier...
You should have been able to dodge it.
The ceiling has been repaired.
Is this your Magecraft, too, Saber?
If I could do such a thing,
I would have fixed
that opera house long ago.
There are things I can't do, you know.
"Mother, I am able to become
proficient at everything."
Or you said.
You saw that?
Your mom was really pretty.
A-Are you okay?
I hear that a Master can have dreams
about a Servant's past!
Saber, do you still think
you can do anything?
I mean, you actually don't
look like you're terrible
at anything other than reading the room.
That's going a bit too far!
There were things I was
not able to do in life!
Like what?
English.
Huh?
I was terrible at English!
And I was the King of England!
Ayaka!
Laughing about what people
are not good at—
Saber...
Thank you.
I'm glad you're still alive.
All right! Switching gears!
Now that you know my past embarrassment,
there is nothing left to lose!
I can even win against
that golden one next time!
And no matter what you tell me,
I will protect you, as well!
Because I am a man who can
become proficient at everything!
Saber...
and Ayaka Sajyou?
You all are...
Hey, John...
There really is nothing
wrong with your body?
And that thing earlier... That power...
I had a peculiar dream.
A dream?
Yeah.
I don't really understand it myself...
but one thing is for certain.
The author Caster gave me some strength.
This is...
The signs of combat are completely gone
from this part of town.
We are likely quarantined within a realm
similar to a Reality Marble.
"Reality Marble"?
We would like to suggest
a temporary joining of forces...
in order to escape.
To think they'd set their daughter up
to become a Master...
And Tsubaki Kuruoka's Servant
caused this incident?
Correct.
Plus...
there was the mysterious Magecraft
that made everyone
on the scene disappear at once.
Some of the Servants managed to escape,
but most of them were swallowed whole.
On top of it, a Servant powerful enough
to annihilate the King of Heroes showed up.
Have you come to defeat the king?
I did not.
Then...
are you here to pass judgment on me?
I, who has tarnished the dignity
of your close friend, the king.
That's not it, either.
Do you know about me?
The king said you were a friend.
I can only think of
one hero who my king calls
"a friend" and compares
his strength against.
If you're thinking I've come
to save King Gilgamesh,
I'm unable to meet those expectations.
If you are the king's friend—
It's because I am his friend.
Gil and I spent irreplaceable
days together.
An eternal farewell
and the sadness that comes with it...
are already done and over with.
If I were the one laying there,
Gil would not be shedding tears.
Nor would I want such a thing.
You can revile me
as much as you want...
if that will provide
peace of mind.
That's not it.
I'm sorry.
I do not have a grudge against you.
I didn't do anything!
You used two Command Spells.
One to bring him back.
One to attempt treatment.
That is a good decision as a Master.
The reason I came was because I wanted
to know a bit more about the two of you.
About us?
Gil made no attempt to kill the one who
was trying to use him, so I got curious.
I thought I'd be able to lend a hand
to a Master like that.
In order to get rid of that fiendish god.
Well, it's not bad for a temporary shrine.
Ishtar, the goddess of Venus...
I thought beings with full Divinity
could not be summoned in a Holy Grail War.
Yes, you're right.
Ordinarily, you can't with a Holy Grail.
I manifested because the powers
I had left behind were activated.
Why did you do such a thing?
I burned a blessing onto the world.
If that disrespectful king and cheeky doll
were to meet once again...
I will use all of my
divine body and soul...
to protect humans!
Damn!
What the hell is he doing?
What about contacting Miss Tohsaka?
Lady...
do you think Miss Tohsaka
will resolve this problem?
I can bet that very devil
will amplify the problem!
That idiot...
If it turns out that he
dozed off for all of this,
he will never hear the end of it!
Oh!
Did you find something out?
Roulettes are lighter than I thought!
I see.
I couldn't think that far.
Oh, how was it?
It seems there is electricity.
What about your end?
We couldn't find any core for creating
a bounded field in the surrounding area.
Perhaps it is hidden in
a very clever manner.
Once we can find that, there might be
something we can do about this.
I'm planning on heading
up to the top floor.
You think the core is there?
Hmm, well, I'd be lucky
if it was up there.
But I was hoping to find a place
that's not so well-guarded.
Mister, Miss, I'm glad you got all better!
You have our thanks.
Yeah. You helped us out.
What's that thing?
Oh! Mr. Black!
Mr.... Black?
Yep!
He's my friend!
Come over here.
Is that really a Heroic Spirit?
Is it possible it's a demonic creature
or some kind of phantom?
No. I can't feel any conscience
from that being,
let alone ill will or hatred.
Those parents are Mages.
Even if under mental domination,
we might get some information if we talk.
He got away!
What's wrong?
No.
It's nothing.
No clues, huh?
We can't even find their corpses.
A majority of the Clan Calatin's
whereabouts are unknown!
The King of Heroes disappeared,
but you look depressed.
I'll contact you later.
What are you doing here?
I was helping out a bit
until a few minutes ago.
If I hadn't taken a step back to observe,
I would've been in that black fog
right about now.
Wha...
I don't remember ever giving such orders!
Yeah. I don't remember
receiving them, either.
If you, the Servant,
were to be taken down,
that signals the end
of our faction, remember?
You have so many other options...
like recreating a pact
with an unemployed Heroic Spirit.
Are you going to fudge your answer
on that assumption?
If you're the one that set your foot in,
don't be so rash to say that it's over.
You're right.
My apologies.
I like that part about you, ya know!
The cop squad guys are still all right.
How do you know?
It just means there was a Noble Phantasm
that I didn't inform my brother about.
So, how about it, Brother?
I'll go help out if it's
somewhere I can infiltrate.
I didn't give orders
for you to go that far.
No, you did!
You requested me
to create weapons for your cop squad.
That means providing
power in order to fight.
What power can I give
you guys as an author?
That's right! A story!
What does that have to do
with you risking danger?
John Wingard.
Vera Levitt.
Annie Cuarón.
Don Hawkins.
Chadwick Lee.
Yuki Capote.
Adelina Eisenstein.
Their names...
Not just names, you see?
Faces, voices, origins...
Everything I found out,
they're all in here in their entirety.
You learn all the names
of your subordinates, don't you?
They're all central
characters in my piece now.
And they're acting out
the most supreme of scenarios.
If that's the case...
you just wanna have front
row seats to watch...
don't ya?
We believe that in order to escape from
this world, we must defeat the Mage...
who is at the root of all this.
Ms. Vera...
was it?
Do we really have to
defeat them to get out?
Maybe there's a way to
secretly and safely escape.
I believe that's difficult.
If you are a Mage yourself,
I think you would understand.
Oh no, I'm not anything like that.
In other words, someone is executing
this great a level of Magecraft!
This is such an amazing bounded field!
The Servants surely are—
Are you really a Servant?
You seem to be pretty relaxed.
You are?
I'm John Wingard.
John...
I see, John!
This is a chance encounter of sorts!
Let's get along, shall we?
Hey, you guys were talking about
eradicating the Mage or Servant
that started all this, right?
There are many of my allies who would be
relatively averse to doing so.
Myself included.
The girl you tried to protect...
Tsubaki, was it?
There's still the possibility...
that the one who locked us in
was that girl's Servant, right?
If that little girl is
the root of all evil...
will you guys be able to kill her?
Mr. Black...
Do you remember when we first met?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Father, Mother, I'm sorry!
I will do a proper job!
I will endure it better!
So...
please, don't abandon me!
I ASK YOU
I ask you.
Are you...
my...
ARE YOU
MY MASTER?
Master?
Who is it?
I am...
Tsubaki Kuruoka.
We'll be together forever, right?
Mr. Black?
I'm not saying it's the right
answer to kill a girl...
nor do I want to kill.
But...
we might end up in a situation
where someone has to do it, right?
I have braced myself for that possibility.
I...
We...
When the time comes, I'll do it.
In the end...
I couldn't be the knight that I adored.
But you guys are different!
You are skilled knights!
Against that fearful bowman,
you fought and survived!
All in order to save a single young girl!
Then you lot must be the kind
that will protect the innocent!
Besides...
after doing that once...
pulling the trigger becomes easier.
I should be the one
shouldering that burden.
Saber...
It looks like the base for some faction.
This room really feels like
it's the least guarded.
Right here.
The location closest to
outside the bounded field.
I only see it as an empty magical circle.
Hmm...
I think that this is a bounded field
"world" that recreated reality.
If the slot machines and
such aren't moving...
it's not continually reflecting
upon a real-life city...
but copy-pasting the world periodically.
Perhaps something that couldn't be copied
is right here in reality.
Someone... is here.
You really are as always, Gil.
You draw the destiny of the world
even after you have stopped functioning.
What's happening?
I merely serve...
as a tool for someone.
If I were to put it in your words,
I guess I'd be a booster.
Huh?
Something wrong?
It's like we're in a subway train,
but I've got three bars
on my cell reception.
I might be able to do it right now.
Is this an altar?
A simple one at that.
If I can get the cell circuits
and the external forces to...
Got a connection!
Found you!
Ayaka?
What's wrong? You're completely pale.
Saber, you can't.
Ayaka?
I don't plan on
saying or have the right to say
selfish things like, "Don't kill anyone."
But...
you laugh at all times...
and never abandon anyone!
You're different from me!
Even if you ultimately soil those hands,
the fact that you saved me
will not be erased!
So...
"I will do the dirty work"...
is the one thing I don't want you to say.
If you need someone
doing the dirty work, I'll do it.
I'd like to say that you worry
about the trivial things like always...
but that's not the case.
Of course not.
My encounter with you
isn't a trivial matter anymore.
I must risk my life to
save that girl, then!
In this world, we're
starting off at the Church!
In place of the priest...
we will protect her!
Church...
Protect...
I...
have met that golden guy—
Ayaka?
What's wrong?
We were scouting the city streets
when that beast suddenly...
Beast? It can't be!
What...
is that?
Is everyone going to go
somewhere else again?
O girl...
can you hear me?
Mr. Black?
Good morning, girl
bewildered within a dream.
Who are you?
I am Tsubaki Kuruoka.
Thank you.
I am one that was once called
"a god of a particular place."
Nowadays, I'm merely that
which remains of said deity.
But really, I'm so glad
I got through to you!
I understand your situation.
For the time being,
I'm fine as long as you're all right.
One confirmation, though.
Did you see Ayaka Sajyou over there?
What? Ayaka is over here?
Sajyou has been witnessed in Snowfield
for the past few days.
I contacted her myself.
She is apparently...
in Romania right now.
If so, then...
EPISODE 11
who is this girl?