There won't be any skilled minions around.
They'll all be guarding
the Coffin Count of Storms.
I need to drag them down here first.
Sara, Jogamine.
I'm going to make an exception
and teach you a fundamental move.
Watch close.
Scum of the Brave
A Brave's Instruction
So, here's what you call a bind.
And once you get out of it...
You cut off their fingers.
I think there's a similar move in
traditional Japanese kenjutsu, too.
The trick is to twist the blade
once it hits the guard.
Once they can't hold a sword,
there's nothing to fear.
If you follow, give it a shot.
You guys take care of the cannon fodder.
Understood! I'll make an attempt, Master!
You really shouldn't.
Cutting fingers is a move you attempt
when you've locked swords with someone.
If you can read minds,
you oughta get in close by reading
when they're gonna step forward...
Nah. That's not possible
at Jogamine's level.
Using that shield to parry while keeping
an eye out for unprotected vital spots...
She has a ways to go before
she can pull that off, too.
Sara's moving well enough.
I guess this is how she performs
when she outclasses the enemy.
You can tell she was drilled by
first-rate swordsmen from an early age.
Nothing like Jogamine.
Which means the problem here...
Idiot, go on the offensive!
Even if he throws you off
balance, you've got two hands!
Fight back! Make the other
guy realize he could die!
Those wide, reckless swings...
It should be simple to create
an opening by fighting back
with the speed a one-handed sword offers.
Now!
What the hell are you doing?! Kill him!
Idiot!
You stupid asshole!
It hurts!
Well covered.
You picked the perfect
timing to step in, too.
As for you... what the hell was that?
I tried to fight as I would
in real combat...
How, exactly?
You weren't ready to kill.
But Master, shouldn't a Brave—
Doesn't. Matter.
You think this is a game?
"I'm not like these murdering scum.
I'm so much fancier and
respectable." Is that it?
You expect someone else
to save you every time
and never have to dirty your own hands?
It's not that!
I—
Read my mind.
Because I'm furious.
M-Master...
Instructor.
Quiet. I'm...
No, that's not the point. This idiot...
Instructor, look. Who's that?
There's a shock.
I didn't think...
she'd show up in person this soon.
It seems the hundred invitations
I sent you this month have born fruit.
Welcome to my party, Yashiro-sama,
and your cadre of strange girls.
I bid you the warmest of wishes,
having joined the festivities.
Scum of the Brave
The Dark Lord known as the
Coffin Count of Storms.
They say she used to be an executive
from a yakuza group in Kansai...
But the details of her
background are unknown.
After the BFE conflict two years ago,
she started assimilating orgs
that had lost their leadership,
and before long, she was one of the most
prominent Dark Lords in the country.
I first met her six months ago.
I was on a gig to kill another Dark Lord
and just ran into her...
I didn't have a lot of options,
so I killed two or three of her
minions and got out of there.
Ever since, she's been
persistent in how...
Well, I guess you'd say
I got her attention?
Who the hell is she?
This is crazy.
Yeah. You can tell, huh?
She's strong?
Oh, yeah.
Can I go first?
We're not fighting her tonight.
And the three of you
wouldn't stand a chance.
We wouldn't? Who's stronger, her or you?
Depends on the situation.
Are you finished chatting
with your exotic animals?
Exotic animals?!
We are proud
students of the academy—
Stop talking, Jogamine. I'll kick you.
I am so honored you accepted
my invitation, Yashiro-sama.
Has the ten million a month I've
been sending finally paid off?
I didn't show up because of the invite.
I need to ask you...
Actually, first, I'm gonna complain.
Sending all these letters
and muscle after me...
And I'm obviously not gonna
use any money you send me!
Quit trying to launder your
cash with my account, damn it!
You wound me.
My sincere wish is to engage with you
and develop a relationship based on trust.
Is Pincers not here?
He's on leave.
He seems to be worn down from
the previous day's events...
I'm sure he will return
in strength soon enough.
Given the support he has.
I'm sure he told you the details.
I'm looking for the Half Dragon.
Then you're here regarding your pursuit
of vengeance for Ishino the Musician?
You knew?
Yes. The Half Dragon...
The truth of the matter is they've
been a nuisance to me as well.
They've been strengthening
the unruly masses
and attempting to sabotage
the established order of things.
Basically, they've been making a mess
of your turf using that E4 stuff, right?
I'm pleased to see you understand.
Yashiro-sama, you are no less than
the ideal swordsman I've dreamed of.
Should you join my royal guard,
we can unite in our struggles
against these people.
I guarantee you'll be taken care of
for the rest of your days
with the kind of welcome I'd give you.
This is going nowhere.
I'm not gonna be one of your peons.
You have to know my nickname, right?
I choose who I kill.
I just wanna know where
to find these people.
If the Half Dragon are your enemy,
then we're after the same thing.
Am I wrong?
Yes, but in that scenario,
I wouldn't be able to enjoy the exploits
of Yashiro the Reaper with my own eyes.
Suppose we do this, then...
Four of my most elite
soldiers, the Stormguard...
If you will fight them,
in exchange, I will tell
you everything I know.
A party needs entertainment, after all.
Actually, given that they're here,
why not have your trio
join the festivities?
Hold up!
These three are too weak
to be any entertainment.
Oh, my. You seem to actually care
for this little menagerie, then?
Now I'm curious about the...
nature of your relationship.
Shit.
Pairing with Indo to fight
wouldn't be a problem.
But if anything happens to Sara,
King Arthur and the Round Table
will be out for my blood.
Should I have Jogamine read what
I need to know, and then we bail?
No. At this point, if I
don't agree to her offer...
It'll just make things even worse.
Sensei!
Settle down. I'm figuring things out.
Not that! Above us!
And behind us... we're surrounded!
Oh my, and just when I was
looking forward to the show.
So many visitors today.
Great.
I guess I wasn't the only one who thought
today would be the best day to strike.
It is such a shame I won't be able to give
you my undivided attention, Yashiro-sama.
Until we meet again...
Move!
Nobody move without my say.
Especially you, Jogamine.
That's...
a Nephilim.
Four in the rear.
Seven flanking us.
Just getting past them
wouldn't be that hard.
Do we go after her?
If they're after the
Coffin Count of Storms,
then the Half Dragon
might be up there, too.
Yukine!
Damn! Stay close, Sara!
Yukine! Master's order!
Stop! Stay put!
Are you stupid?
What're you doing?
Stop. Let me go.
What. Are. You. Doing?
Those... are Nephilim...
Big models, with claws.
Sara, we have to support Yukine!
Take formation!
Go!
Sensei!
Damn it, why can't any of you
do as you're told?
Leg's still intact.
Probably five minutes until
it knits back together.
Left leg, left arm...
A handicap like that would be bad,
no matter how tough I was.
Wh-What do we do, Sensei?!
Your limbs are all screwed up!
We break through!
Defending Master as we secure—
Knock it off, stupid!
Forget about me for now.
I can handle myself.
Listen!
I need to adjust your crummy teamwork.
The way they were moving
before made it clear...
They've been trained to fight as a trio.
Indo goes on the offensive,
Jogamine backs her up,
while Sara lands the killing blow.
That's how the academy
taught them to fight.
But from what I could see,
they're not great at it.
The academy probably
wanted to make sure that
the Chairman's daughter, Sara,
was in the safest position.
Especially since Indo could take
out most enemies on her own...
And if Indo does go down,
Jogamine won't be able to make up for it.
All this adds up to Sara not having
a lot of chances to get involved.
What a damn joke.
I need to give these three
effective commands, or I die.
I need to come up with
something in one second.
The best way to capitalize on their
abilities in a situation like this...
All right.
Jogamine. You take the lead.
Target their knees
to put them off balance.
Sara, you aim for their backs.
Don't give them a chance to fight back.
If you choke and the combo
falls apart, we all die.
Indo, you're to intercept any attacks.
Sara and Jogamine, back her up.
If you screw up, the others will die.
You hear me?
I need you to bust your butt out there.
And if you fly off the chain again...
I know.
This time... I'll do a good job.
Good.
This might be an impromptu lesson,
but it's nice and tense, right?
And don't pay me any mind.
I'll be seriously pissed off.
But, Master...
This is a live exercise!
Get to work!
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Next Time
The time has come to display
the power of our friendship!
Do you three even hang out
outside of school?
We learn together, and encourage
each other to greater heights!
Next time is Episode 11,
A Brave's Teamwork
a "Brave's Teamwork".