Because I—this me—
hasn't given you the Key yet.
It's time for me to repay you.
With a world that you can keep living in.
Because you're precious to me.
"Setsu"?
That person doesn't exist IRL!
Huh?
I'm not really sure, but...
Setsu's already gone,
but don't they still have to give the Key
to the you of this universe?
What is this?
I was bored, so I compiled it all.
Everything that'll happen henceforth,
and everything you'll need to do.
So this is the Hoshibune.
Setsu!
Do you understand?
EPISODE 21: END POINT AND STARTING POINT
I guess you wouldn't, considering how
dated this instant learning system is.
EPISODE 1: STARTING POINT
Can you get up?
Let me ask you this first.
Do you think humanity should
be erased from this universe?
No...
They shouldn't.
What?
No matter how many liars are among them.
Yuri, you're...
Otome remembered you.
Apparently she felt a pain in her lip
when she heard your name.
It can't be... N-No...
But why?!
I used the Silver Key
to open the door again.
So I could end your looping, Setsu.
"Again"?
Yeah. This time it took really long.
At least ten times longer than last time.
Why would you do that?
I told you already. To end your looping.
The others made me realize something.
If you don't give me the Silver Key,
you'll never stop looping.
You need to give it to the me
who lives in the other world,
like you did at the very start,
or cause and effect will never connect.
That doesn't mean—
You need to hurry.
Right now, I'm basically
a ghost—my consciousness alone
has been transferred into
the body of the real me.
But I can't stay for long.
Once the real me regains consciousness,
I won't be able to stay here any longer.
So you need to give me the
Silver Key before that.
The Silver Key that opened the way here
should be looking for a new host.
I'm sure it's still nearby.
This is...
We're too late.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Ah, the guest of honor has arrived.
Oh, right. This is when I first woke up.
Before I first received the Silver Key.
Good work, Setsu.
Has their memory come back?
Er, n-no...
Wait, what? So they've got,
like, zero memories?
Doesn't that make things difficult?
Actually, it's rather simple.
We just need to put them
into cold sleep.
If the meeting keeps going like this...
Racio will end up in cold sleep.
It's not like we have any way
of knowing who it is for sure,
so let's just go ahead and... vote!
W-Wait!
I have no idea what's going
on here! Vote for what?
What are Gnosia?
Feigning ignorance even now?
You embarrass yourself.
LeVi, you heard our conversation
just now, didn't you?
Yes. I heard everything.
Could you give us just a little
more time before the meeting?
We don't have much time.
If you're going to explain,
hurry up and get it over with.
I'm going to make some coffee.
Then use this.
Someone gave it to me in Liu-An.
That's weird. I could've
sworn I put it here.
You can't find it?
Yeah, I think it's in my room.
Go ahead and start talking.
I'll be right back.
Come on, now.
What're we supposed to even talk about?
How 'bout what we did that night?
Actually...
First, could you tell me
all of your names?
Go and get the Silver Key.
And give it to me before
the meeting is over.
Then your Key will be filled
and leave your body,
and your looping can end.
We all basically just met, too.
They say that Gnosia'll lie about
anything to save their own skin.
So let's just go with our gut
and decide in a flash!
You're a real slowpoke, Setsu.
Sorry. It took a while to find.
It is time.
Please begin the meeting.
I guess the coffee will have to wait.
Now Setsu just has to give me
the Silver Key they have.
You're being suspiciously sneaky.
Huh?
I'll be keeping an eye on you until
we get to the main control room.
You won't be sneaking away this time.
S-Sure, got it.
Crap. I wanted to get away from the others
so Setsu could give me the Silver Key...
This is a bit drastic,
but I have no choice.
Setsu.
Huh?
Setsu, is this...
Huh? Wha?
Wait, that Silver Key...
Setsu, did you go into my room
without permission?
Hey! Come back here!
What?
Sorry!
We have a thief in our midst!
Capture them!
Seriously... how reckless
are you planning to be?
But I mean... It did sorta belong
to me in the first place...
You're too slow!
This is no laughing matter.
Now they think I'm a thief.
Sorry.
But I'm pretty sure
Racio will forgive you.
Really?
Yeah. In fact, I'm certain of it.
Now we'll finally both be able
to stop looping.
We'll be able to connect
all of the cause and effect.
Finally.
Setsu?
Really?
I know that I'll finally be able
to stop looping.
But what's going to happen to you, Yuri?
If you accept this, you'll have
to start looping again...
It's okay.
The only one who has to
end up as its host is me.
I came from another universe, and I
shouldn't even exist in the first place.
I'm just a Bug that'll disappear soon.
Disappear?
Yeah.
That's what I asked for
when I came over here.
I asked them to make me disappear
once everything was over.
To return the universe to a Bugless state.
When that happens, the Silver Key
should disappear along with me.
No. That can't happen.
As a Bug, I threw the universe
into chaos by existing,
so I'm going to return everything back
to normal like nothing ever happened
and disappear.
I can't imagine living a more
beautiful life than that.
Please...
Let me see this through.
There's no time left.
Setsu!
Thank you.
-Doubt not, fear not, and know.
-Yuri...
Knowledge will save all.
I think... I'm still okay.
Yuri...
Yuri, Setsu.
It is past time for the meeting to begin.
I repeat.
Yuri, Setsu.
I guess we still have
something we need to do.
It is past time for the meeting to begin.
You're late, you thieves.
We just finished deciding
to send you both into cold sleep.
We didn't decide anything.
That's just what you think we should do.
Who wouldn't?
They had the nerve the commit
grand larceny on this tiny ship!
How can they be anything but Gnosia?
Your logic is failing.
Sounds like you just have
a grudge, to be honest.
Please begin the meeting.
See?
Hmph!
My apologies.
In the interest of ending this meeting,
there was something we needed to do,
so we were a bit late.
Ending this meeting?
That's right.
I'm going to end this meeting
without sacrificing anyone.
Hmph. You're just making stuff up now.
Kukrushka?
Yeah.
In the universe where you didn't exist,
Kukrushka was also never part of the crew.
She remained a doll.
Do you have any idea why?
I see.
Let's go to the main control room.
We'll settle all of this
through conversation.
I've relied on you entirely too much,
so let me handle it this time.
Setsu...
Let me say this right off the bat.
The Gnosia is SQ.
Huh?
Who, me?!
Why, though?
There it is.
Yuri and I already know
without even having to discuss it.
That's my...
Take a closer look. It's already
filled to the brim with knowledge.
It's not the one that I got
from your room earlier.
This Silver Key is already full.
Do you know what that means?
I see. So you've already
experienced looping.
Looping?
Yes. I've already experienced the
same period of time hundreds of times
and obtained all kinds of information.
And that's why I know it's you,
Manan.
"Manan"?
You see, Manan...
I've looped many times, and I've spent
more of them than I can count with her.
The real SQ that you failed
to transfer your consciousness to
who always refers to herself
as "cute li'l SQ."
The real SQ?
Yeah. The one who's here
right now is Manan.
She's SQ's mother, who transferred
her consciousness to SQ's body.
The proof is... that she hasn't once
called herself "cute li'l SQ."
Is that true?
Welp, looks like the
cat's out of the bag.
You've really done your homework.
So you're admitting it?
Seriously, though, wasn't there something
more worthwhile to spend your time on?
Yup! You bet your ass I'm Manan!
So you do admit it.
Yeah, but... so what?
Even if I'm Manan, that
doesn't make me a Gnosia.
It does, actually.
As I continued looping, there was one
thing I always wondered about SQ.
The real SQ that resulted from Manan's
transfer of consciousness failing,
and the fully Manan SQ that
resulted from it succeeding...
What determined which one appeared?
I wanted to know the answer, so I
gathered data across hundreds of loops
and finally figured it out.
Manan... only appears when
SQ is infected by the Gnosia.
How amusing! So that's why
you said she was a Gnosia.
She fell right into your trap.
She's just making stuff up!
There's no proof behind
anything she just said!
I can't deny that.
If the others decide I'm lying,
I'm the one who'll be chosen.
The votes will tell us everything.
It is time.
We will now change over
to the voting process.
You may not veto the result.
The voting result will be deemed
to be the will of all present,
and you will abide by it.
Do you agree?
Then it is time for the verdict.
Who is the Gnosia?
Voting has completed. Five valid votes.
The voting rate is 100%.
The votes will now be tallied.
It has been decided.
SQ will be put into cold sleep.
No, there's no need for that.
I'm going to settle this
without the need for cold sleep.
Seriously? You're still not done?
That's right. I said I'd end this
without sacrificing anyone.
This meeting—and this story.
LeVi, could you open
container 1375 in storage?
I'm terribly sorry.
The ship's hold is locked
under the captain's authority.
But Jonas isn't here.
I'm with the military. I have the right
to perform a search of the cargo on board.
But...
You heard everything we just said,
didn't you, LeVi?
Or should I say... Stella?
Stella... So you're going
to call me by that name.
Yes. I'm asking you...
Stella.
So you're telling me to enter
this doll's body instead?
Are you serious?
And then I'll have you
go to another universe.
This will open the door.
I know you're no stranger
to transferring your own consciousness.
Sure, but I mean...
Let's just think about this.
Your sense of self is
a super-delicate thing.
If I transfer over,
it's possible my personality
might get ripped to shreds...
So isn't this penalty a bit harsh?
Penalty? Don't get the wrong idea.
This isn't a penalty.
Huh?
I told you. I have no intention
of sacrificing anyone.
I think you'll actually agree to transfer
into that doll and go through the door.
Are they okay in the head?
Just think about it—
why it's better for you
to transfer into that doll,
and why you're better off
on the other side of that door.
You'll no longer have to keep
transferring your consciousness,
since a doll's body doesn't deteriorate.
And once you're through the door,
you'll have the Silver Key to yourself.
You'll be able to use it to turn
back time as much as you want.
And, unlike me, you want eternal life
and to be young forever.
Sounds perfect for you, right?
I see. So that's how you're
gonna reel me in, huh?
Don't worry, Manan.
Sure, you might fail and have
your personality torn to shreds,
but at the very least,
no one will miss you.
That's so mean!
I see you can be sharp-tongued
when it counts, too, Jina.
Shut up, you stupid Glyze bougie!
Was the transfer successful?
Yes. It must have been
for her to be moving now.
Once you go through this door,
you'll end up in another universe.
This is goodbye.
Manan.
Let's meet again someday.
Hopefully under better circumstances.
I guess all the causes and effects
have finally been connected.
Yeah.
We will soon be commencing warp.
Yuri, Setsu, please return to your rooms.
No, we're fine right here.
As you wish.
But please at least lie down.
Do you understand?
I'm hungry.
Setsu...
You see, Yuri...
When I went through the door before,
I was prepared...
to never see you again.
And I was going to keep looping forever
in a world where you didn't exist.
Or so I thought.
But then...
You came to see me again
and you saved me.
You helped end my looping.
Well, you worked hard, too, Setsu.
I wouldn't have been able
to pull that last part off by myself.
You're right. We both worked hard.
Through all the world lines, we crossed
universes and ended up here.
I finally figured it out.
You really are an irregularity.
You're a one-of-a-kind existence
that shows up in a universe
that was warped by the Silver Key.
A Bug.
No, that's not it.
You're not a Bug.
You're...
You're my...
Beginning warp countdown.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six, five,
Setsu...
four, three, two, one...
Hey, Yuri.
I'm right here.
And you're right there, aren't you?
That's all I need.
So...
Thank you... for being there for me.