m 0 0 l 0 102 32 102 b 3 75 3 32 32 0
OSHI NO KO
What do you mean, "set up"?
Are you implying I masterminded it all?
No way I could've planned all that.
I'm not a god.
Though I guess I wasn't
entirely uninvolved.
Okay, you are my bro, so I'll tell you.
I got the idea from you,
so it's only fair.
From me?
Yep. You used Love for Real's controversy
to get Akane-chan on your side
and promote yourself,
so I just copied that.
It really was super effective.
You caught the attention of the
whole audience and then some.
So, you know,
I figured I could do the same thing.
But why?
Somebody once told me...
"Be nice to assistant directors.
They'll be directors in the future."
It made a lot of sense.
But I don't have time to sit
around and wait that long.
I need to hit the big time
as soon as possible.
Hoshino-san!
I hear you pitched this episode.
Thanks to you, I got through
this by the skin of my teeth.
How can I ever repay you?
Hmm, well, if you want to repay the favor,
use me in your projects as much
as you can, Director Urushibara.
There's no need to win over ADs.
I can just go straight for the director.
So you got the show in trouble on purpose
just to get Urushibara on your side?
That was a happy coincidence.
When I was doing research
for my pitch to get on the show,
#DigDeepChaseTheImpawsible
I found out that there were issues
with the show's production methods.
I agreed to appear on this show called Dig Deep,
but that was a huge mistake.
It was nothing like the original pitch.
Dig Deep or whatever just doesn't take no for
an answer. How desperate can you be lolol
One of the guys on Dig Deep's production crew
was a total asshole. He kept yelling at a younger
staff member (an AD?) and I felt so sorry for him
And I knew a magnet for controversy,
so I suggested bringing her on.
Meiya-san's done this kinda
thing a few times before.
If anyone gets on her bad side,
Meiya
@77xxxxmeiyaxxxx77
Yeah, screw TV. They think you're trash just because
you show some skin. I agreed to appear because they
were covering Tokyo Blade cosplayers, but then they
have the gall to ask for an original costume the day
before. They clearly have no respect at all for cosplayers.
Do they have any idea how much work we put into this?
I feel so hurt and betrayed.
I think I'm going to take a break from cosplay for a while.
5:03 PM    Aug 17   3.0M Views
she calls them out on her socials
and sics her fans on them.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
She's helping out,
so what's with the attitude?
I feel so bad for Meiya-san!!!!
Do they think costumes
grow on trees???
It's so joever for TV
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
tf? NSFW creators deserve respect too
Those assholes! I feel so bad for Meiya-san.
I'm definitely not watching the show
how could any professional act like this lol
Why do these men always act so high-and-
mighty when they're the ones being done
a favor?
I had a feeling she'd do it again.
Isn't she your friend?
What? No way.
I hate blabbermouths like her.
Leaks and whistleblowing
can make the world a better place,
but now people just use them to call out
individuals they have a grudge against.
Post
And then you have online mobs dogpiling
on whoever's getting canceled for fun.
Both sides are messed up.
They made Mom's life hell too, remember?
Someone uploaded a pic of her with
an old classmate she'd just run into,
Rising Idol Group B-Komachi's Ai
On Secret Date with a College-Aged Hot Guy?
Share      View Comments
A photographer with the Weekly Rittou
snapped some shots of them boldly
meeting up in the middle of a
commercial district. Ai, one of the
hottest idols around, was with a man
not in showbiz. They happily chatted
away with smiles on their faces before
disappearing into the night crowd.
[Photos] Ai and Hot Guy Getting
Up Close and Personal
(Photo: Rittou Photography Department)
Rumors of Tokyo Dome Concert
B-Komachi, the idol group Ai is part of, is in the public eye thanks to her incredible
popularity. One industry insider hinted that a Tokyo Dome concert might be in the works.
A scandal at such a crucial time must have fans scrambling.
and people just assumed
he was her boyfriend.
Are you kidding me? This sucks.
Sorry, I can't stan her anymore...
They jumped to conclusions,
invented messed-up stories in their heads,
fr???
So the money we spent on her
is just going to some random guy...
Aight, peace
I can't process this
Seriously?!
blocked. blocked. blocked.
none of you are free from sin
my tummy hort
no wai
gdi management
screw this shit
how trashy
I can't accept this
Who's this fugly?
idols are idols, after all
What a traitor.
No more concerts for me.
Sigh... another betrayal.
It's all over
She's like all the others
it's over, it's all over. screw this
Talk about bad timing
I'm burning
all my merch
Dating... scandal?
If this is true, she's done
At least don't be
stupid about it
Quit being an idol.
You're not cut out for this.
She's getting it on
like everyone else
I can't accept this
bet she's jumping from one dick to another
my fave... has a boyfriend...
she's so guilty lol
Apologize to the other members!!
I always loved her
what's her agency doing? wtf
nasty af
can't believe anything
about her anymore
and started calling her a slut.
They always date
like this in secret
way to turn on your fans,
you piece of shit
Gimme back
my money and time
gross. don't wanna be
her fan no more
why meet up in the middle of town?
gross. i can't
can't believe our money's going
to this guy. they're probably laughing at us
it should have been me!
not him!
the guy's at fault too,
not that i care
No more concerts for me. Goodbye
I loved her, but I'm done
It's all over
If the group suffers because of her,
I'll hate her forever
i liked her singing and dancing,
which makes this even worse
How good am I, though?
I vetted the info for Meiya-san
and gave her a chance to talk things out!
I mean, she was totally in the right.
She helped improve the industry.
Minami got to appear
on a show with lots of eyeballs.
And Urushibara-san's turned over a
new leaf. Nobody was hurt by this.
So why?
Why do you look so disappointed?
Was what I did really so wrong?
Sure, I gave it a little push,
but this was always gonna happen.
It just happened to play out
the way I hoped it would.
I've got luck on my side!
Maybe the gods really do love me!
Are you happy?
Are you really okay with this?
I thought you hated lies
and manipulation more than anything.
Didn't you want to be true
to yourself and others
and aim to be an idol
with love and passion?
Is this the kind of idol you wanted to be?
You said you copied me.
But my methods will only bring you—
Hey, Aqua.
Mom was a liar too, remember?
She covered up her own kids
to continue being an idol.
Love and passion aren't enough
to make it in this business.
And it's looking like this kinda thing
is more up my alley, anyway.
Just watch me.
I'll take the spotlight in no time.
And she was right.
Work started to pour in
for Ruby soon after that.
Bye, Minami. I'm off to work.
O-Oh, okay. Take care.
Top
Showbiz
Entertainment
Fashion
B-Komachi Stocks Rising!
Web/Television
Who is Ruby Hoshino,
This Year's Hottest Ticket?
Release-Day Event
After-School Monster Movie's
Release-Day Event Announced!
A panel of nine writers, producers,
entertainers, and other experts
Who is Ruby Hoshino, This Year's Hottest Ticket?
Back
gather to present the Women's Idol Awards,
which go to the year's hottest stars.
The Newcomer of the Year Award
went to Ruby Hoshino of B-Komachi.
B-Komachi's a reboot of a legendary group
that broke up over a decade ago.
Naturally,
people see a bit of Ai, who lost her life
to a deranged fan at her peak,
when they look at Ruby.
People wonder if she may even surpass Ai,
which is far too much to expect of her,
and yet she has the potential.
Dig Deep!
Chase the Impawsible!!
She first attracted attention on the show
Dig Deep! Chase the Impawsible!
Digging Deep! Pikachu-kun's Friends Encountered!
Dig Deep!
Chase the Impawsible!!
which gained many viewers six months ago
when it had its big cosplay controversy.
She boasts gorgeous good looks
and a silly, scatterbrained gimmick,
Dentures
but it's her savvy communication
and ad-libbing skills
B-Komachi
Ruby Hoshino
that make her a hot commodity
in the industry.
Her brother Aqua is also
an up-and-coming actor,
and the two stunning twins are making
more guest appearances as of late.
B-Komachi
B-Komachi Channel!
970,000 subscribers
Subscribed
Home
Videos
Shorts
Live
Playlists
Posts
Latest
Popular
Oldest
B-Komachi is also popular
as a YouTuber group.
B-Komachi
B-Komachi Channel!
970,000 subscribers
Subscribed
Home
Videos
Shorts
Live
Playlists
Six months ago,
they had 300,000 subscribers,
but now that number's
on the cusp of hitting a million.
Pulling triple duty as YouTuber,
idol, and TV entertainer,
Ruby is truly an idol
who symbolizes the Reiwa era.
In an interview, she said this...
B-Komachi and Ai had their dream taken
from them, but we'll make it come true.
B-Komachi will take
the stage at the Tokyo Dome!
"We'll keep a keen eye out for
what Ruby Hoshino does next."
Ruby's become kind of a big deal, huh?
I mean, she's always had the looks.
If she'd debuted with a major agency,
she would've made it
much bigger, much earlier.
Ruby's rise over the past six months
has been eye-popping.
B-Komachi
B-Komachi Channel!
970,000 subscribers
Subscribed
This exponential subscriber growth
is entirely down to Ruby's popularity.
970,000 subscribers
It's really something. The group's sub
count beat my channel's in no time.
It almost makes me wonder
what I put in all that work for.
MEM...
Hey, this may be bittersweet,
but it's more sweet than bitter.
I laid the groundwork
for all this growth, after all!
I guess this is just how a star is born.
What do we do about today's video?
Ruby's out on a shoot, so she'll be late.
We'll just have to wait.
The comments get nasty
when she's not in a video.
Yeah, Ruby's booked all day that day.
She's available in the AM on the
22nd or 26th the week after.
Right.
Oh, okay...
I'll see if I can make it work.
You seem to have a lot
on your plate, President.
It's neverending!
There's so much happening all at once,
my brain's this close to exploding!
Sleep
Buster
Schedule adjustments,
meetings, B2Bs, contracts...
February
Schedule\h
Outing Schedule
Ruby, congrats
on your award!!
We have interviews for mid-career
hires scheduled this month.
Please keep the office clean.
And I have to go drinking
with a station head later.
I'm so glad we brought in Yoshizumi-kun.
Without him, I would've died of overwork.
Shun Yoshizumi, the AD
from the production company,
left his job to become Ruby's manager.
I don't know how she talked him into it
when he seemed so passionate about TV.
But Ruby now has the clout
to influence other people's careers.
One word from her is enough
to get people to quit their current jobs.
I wish I could accompany Ruby to her gigs.
I can't help when things go south
if I'm not there with her.
Why don't you close
your eyes and rest a bit?
I'll wake you up when it's time to go.
Yeah, thanks.
I was always better suited
to hands-on work.
After Ichigo left, I took over
his role because I had to.
But I get exposed
by busy periods like this.
On shows where major agencies
would land main roles,
I can only get us guest appearances.
I'm lacking connections and experience,
so they look down on me.
Our agency's on the verge of producing
a star, and I'm only holding her back.
You know that's not true.
Ruby's getting work left and right—
That's just luck.
Seriously...
We've been getting so lucky, it almost
feels like someone's orchestrating it.
I'm getting a lot of visitors lately.
How'd you find me?
Ruby keeps disappearing on her days off
without telling anyone where she's going,
so I followed her.
You've grown up to be
real weird about your sister.
You're the one putting all those
ideas in her head, aren't you?
That's not all.
You're getting her jobs, too.
I'll never forgive you for leaving
Miyako-san high and dry after Ai died.
But...
I'm starting to think you're still
clinging to the Tokyo Dome dream.
To the place where you and Ai
were supposed to stand.
You want to get back into
idol management, right?
Wrong.
Yeah, I'm helping Ruby out with her work.
I'm getting jobs from
people I did favors for
and people who sympathize with me
because of what happened to Ai.
I've got connections, after all.
But I'm doing this because I feel bad
for what I did to Miyako.
I'm not clinging on to anything.
If you still care so much
about Miyako-san,
why not just come back to Strawberry
Productions instead of sneaking around?
I've got unfinished business.
I can't drag her into it.
"Unfinished business"?
You of all people should know.
I need to murder the bastard
who did that to Ai.
But you were just her agent.
Why go that far?
Ai's Fan for All Eternity!!!
Ai may have been your mother,
but she was also like a daughter to me.
Oh...
I get it.
That's why I went into showbiz, too.
The mastermind was someone close to Ai.
So I thought joining her business
would get me closer to the truth.
But here's the answer I found.
The man who killed Ai is dead.
I met someone who I shared
paternal DNA with.
Private DNA Test Report
Result: It was determined that there
is a high possibility the individuals
are half-siblings who share the
same biological father.
Bodies of Married Couple Found
In Apparent Double Suicide
Our dad was Seijuurou Uehara,
and he's already gone.
So our quest for revenge is over.
There's no need to keep doing—
Kid...
What are you talking about?
I remember that incident well.
Plus when it happened,
and how I found out.
Signs Point to Double Suicide
Breaking:  Actors Airi Himekawa and Seijuurou Uehara Found Dead in Villa
It was when I was having a prep meeting
with Ai for the Tokyo Dome concert.
Signs point to double suicide
Breaking:  Actors Airi Himekawa and Seijuurou Uehara Found Dead in Villa
Seijuurou Uehara, Actor
Airi Himekawa, Actor
Seijuurou Uehara masterminded
Ai's murder? That's impossible.
He died before you guys moved.
How could a dead guy
have known your new address?
The timeline makes no sense.
But the DNA test...
Did you consider the possibility
of paternity fraud?
The mother could've had the kid with
a man other than her husband, you know?
Bodies of Married Couple Found In Apparent Double Suicide
A man and a woman were found unresponsive
in a cottage in Karuizawa. They were taken to
a hospital where they were declared dead.
A statement from the Nagano Prefectural Police
identified the deceased as actor Airi Himekawa
and fellow actor Seijuurou Uehara.
The Uehara deaths
could've been a murder-suicide
caused by an enraged husband who'd just
found out about his wife's adultery, no?
Before all that, why are you so convinced
that your dad was the mastermind?
Someone at the agency
could've leaked the address, too.
This isn't over. Not even close.
You've always been a smart kid.
If you'd thought about it for one second,
you would've realized this yourself.
And yet...
You've got it wrong, Ichigo-san.
You're overlooking something crucial.
Something crucial? What's that?
You have to be!
There's gotta be something!
It can't be... This can't be right.
I was sure it was all over, finally...
It's over, right?
I mean...
My bad. That was all just guesswork.
You go home and get some rest.
I've decided to start dating
Akane for real.
Sorry, let me off here.
No... there's no way. It was all over.
Ai's already been avenged.
If not, then I...
Isn't that great? We have our goal back!
We can be driven by hatred alone,
find the guy who killed Ai for real,
and put him through all the suffering
this world has to offer.
Ai's Fan for All Eternity!!!
I deserve to suffer.
I have no right to enjoy my life
after I let Ai die before my very eyes.
This is punishment. Retribution.
No! I finally got the chance
to live my life!
The peace you've had lately
was just a passing dream.
Forget about it.
After all, we haven't put
an end to anything at all.
Take revenge.
Get payback.
Think of what Ai went through. Punish him.
Aqua...
Aqua?
For what we lost forever!
Aqua!
Shut up!
Did I...
Did I do something to make you
hate me so much?
I'm so stupid. I didn't have a clue.
I'm so sorry, Aqua.
Hello? Aqua-kun?
Is now a good time?
Oh, you've got the Japan Film Awards
ceremony tomorrow, huh?
Yeah, though I'm only one of the several
rookie actor award recipients.
Still, it's a red-carpet event!
I'm getting nervous!
Even you still get nervous sometimes, huh?
Of course I do.
So...
Can we meet up tomorrow night?
It'll have to be quite late
because there's a wrap party,
but I want you to see the dress
I'll be wearing—
Sorry.
I kinda don't feel like
seeing anyone right now.
Really? Okay, I understand.
If it ever gets too much,
I'm always here for you, okay?
Thanks, Akane.
Sure. Bye.
Aqua-kun
Aqua-kun had been in
good spirits lately, too.
Aqua-kun
Call ended
According to Ruby-chan,
he wasn't always this gloomy guy.
I bet things changed after Ai-san's death.
Aqua-kun has panic attacks
whenever he remembers her.
His childhood scars
always remain with him,
almost like a curse.
Now that he's free from avenging his
mother, his guilt is fading gradually,
Hey, that's mine!
aah
pout
Just kidding.
and he's becoming the person
he was always meant to be.
I can't help but hope...
that he remains oblivious
and lives a peaceful life.
Then I'm sure Aqua-kun will...
With the acting chops
cultivated by her years in theater,
Rookie Actor Award
Kurokawa-san has shone brightly
in a variety of roles and productions.
Congratulations on winning
the Rookie Actor Award.
I'm so happy for you.
You're crying more than me.
Aqua-kun?
Nah, there's no way.
Wow!
The flower stand from the agency is huge!
If not now, then when?
Wow... the one from Lalalai is tiny.
Times are tough for us
theater groups, okay?
Celebrating the Rookie Actor Award
Theater Group Lalalai
Akane Kurokawa-sama
White roses? Who are these from?
A former member of Lalalai.
He runs his own agency now
and sends flowers any time we're involved.
All kinds of people are
congratulating me, huh?
Never forget to stay grateful.
Of course!
Man, who'd've thought Akane would
make such a rapid rise to stardom?
It's all thanks to
Kindaichi-san's coaching.
Please.
She's always had the skills,
but in this business,
you need to make a positive impression
on the people with casting powers,
or it's hard to land lead roles.
President, your decision to put her
on TV no matter what is paying off now.
It seemed like an awful call at first,
but ever since Love for Real,
her public persona did a 180.
What is it, the look in her eyes?
She's usually so gentle,
but when the cameras are on her,
her eyes take on a glint like no other.
You see people with eyes
like that every once in a while.
Eyes that trick people.
The power to make lies seem like truths.
For an actor, they're the ultimate gift.
We had one of those in the past, too.
Really? Who was it?
The one who sent those roses back there.
He was one of our best actors.
I'd love to watch him!
Do we have any footage?
Playlist
There's probably something in the
oldest rehearsal video playlists.
Lalalai Rehearsal Recordings
17 subscribers
Created playlists
"The Starry God"
Unlisted
View full playlist
Play all
Rocking the Boat 1
He looks like him.
He really looks like him.
Aqua-kun thought the mastermind
was part of Lalalai.
It was a guess based on the workshop
Ai took part in before she got pregnant.
That's not very conclusive.
Bodies of Married Couple Found In Apparent Double Suicide
A man and a woman were found unresponsive
in a cottage in Karuizawa. They were taken to
a hospital where they were declared dead.
A statement from the Nagano Prefectural Police
identified the deceased as actor Airi Himekawa
and fellow actor Seijuurou Uehara.
But what if Taiki Himekawa isn't
actually Seijuurou's biological son
but another man's child?
Himekawa-san and Aqua-kun's
biological father
could've very well been part of Lalalai,
since Seijuurou and Airi were too.
Plus, his style of acting
is very similar to Ai's.
If Ai learned how to act
directly from him...
why has nobody ever mentioned that?
It was covered up.
Celebrating the Rookie Actor Award
Akane Kurokawa-sama
White roses.
The flowers the killer is thought to have brought,
white roses, were found strewn about...
The flowers the stalker had
when he stabbed Ai...
were also white roses.
Somebody told a rabid fan
that Ai had children, enraging him.
He gave him Ai's address
and incited the murder.
He set the stage for it all to happen.
Ai's recreated emotions
are stirring inside me.
If it was him,
I can see why Ai kept
her partner a secret,
and why he used someone else
to commit the murder.
More than anything,
he looks just like him.
His face and Aqua-kun's
look so much alike!
Hikaru Kamiki.
When Ai got pregnant at sixteen,
he was a fifteen-year-old middle schooler.
Episode 28
Blind
Translation
Sriram Gurunathan
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check
Gabriella Alabanza
Translation Check
Michelle Tymon