I'm not All Might.
There's a limit to the amount of
power that a single person has.
I couldn't even save a single cat.
That just leaves Aizawa...
Well, I think he's trying very hard.
But I will say that
for as hard as he tries,
I think he doesn't have an image
of what he wants to accomplish.
With a Quirk like his... makes
me wonder if that's part of it.
You are such a pain, Aizawa!
I don't care what that Erasure
of yours is supposed to do.
When you're involved,
the battles get lamer.
Which makes me look bad!
What does he want from me?
That's just how my Quirk works.
So, all this stuff about making
the most of your Quirk,
what its applications are, and
what I want to do with it...
I really don't have a clue.
Why not just make life
harder for villains, then?
With superhuman combat, it often
boils down to how Quirks interact...
But with your Erasure, it doesn't matter!
It'll always boil down
to regular melee combat.
That's a talent!
My boss says that anyone who doesn't have
a work study can come work with us.
And when you say your boss...
He's the boss of the agency
that I'm doing my work study at!
The head of the Purple
Revolution Agency!
The noble hero, His Purple Highness!
flashback
Recollections of the past.
During a story, they will sometimes act as an
interlude to show what happened prior to current events, as in a "flashback scene."
Glass Sky
Receiving reports of a robbery
on Golden Street in Tasomiya.
Copy that. TS1 through 3, along
with any PMs in the vicinity,
head to the investment office on
the fourth floor of 2-12 Tasomiya.
This is TS-1. We're
arriving on the scene.
Cops got here too damn fast!
One of you musta called
them. Who did it?!
Just had to make things harder...
Hold it right there!
What the—
Glittering like a jewel,
and as flexible as a rose...
Work Study Student
Midnight
Team Purple Revolution...
...is on the scene!
Work Study Student
Loud Cloud
Great, so it's not just
the cops, but heroes too!
But...
A smokescreen?!
Stinging my eyes...
Shoot! He's getting away!
Cloud!
We gotta follow him!
Hold it! This smoke could be poisonous!
And we need to get these
people clear first!
Right.
Shota!
You've gotta stop the villain!
Roger that! Hold it!
Work Study Student
Eraser Head
You little twerp!
This smoke...
The safe?!
Baby, if you're thinking about smashing
one of my little hatchlings...
It's gonna cost you.
Head of the Purple Revolution Agency
His Purple Highness
He's getting away!
So be it.
Let the police chase him down.
We should head back to the building.
Have neighboring departments on
the lookout for that villain!
Put out the call for local
hero agencies as well!
Yes, sir!
If they do find the villain, let
them know to not make a move.
Wait for the heroes to show up.
The smart move.
Sorry, boss!
We were late providing backup.
Wrong, Midnight. You made the right call.
If all that mattered was
fighting and winning?
We'd just be bounty hunters.
We keep the people safe, even
if we don't take home every W!
That's what makes us heroes, baby.
I gotta say, Loud Cloud, you never
hesitate before making your next move.
Initiative like that gets you big points!
Even if your judgment isn't too hot,
experience will make up for that in time.
But Eraser Head...
You are no good, baby!
Do you even get what it
is that's messing you up?
Well, yeah...
I'm slow at making
split-second decisions.
I let the other guy use
his Quirk first earlier,
which is how they got away.
Wrong.
You look like someone died!
My look?
Listen up.
Heroes are supposed to be rays of hope
to people in the throes of calamity!
But you practically radiate
how tense you are!
If heroism is the name of your game,
you gotta smile, baby.
Trust in what you can do.
Until that strength inside you
is blooming like a flower.
Now, let's see that smile, Eraser Head!
Show me your grace and confidence.
Not even close, baby!
He wants me to smile.
But I don't see how I can after
letting a villain escape.
I think he was trying to tell you to
keep a cool head and not freeze up.
It's when you screw up that you need to
keep it light like you always do, y'know?
That's how it works for me!
I don't keep it light in the first place.
Yeah, you don't!
Kayama is messaging me.
What is it? Something urgent going on?
No. Cat pictures.
A whole lot...
Why send these now?
That's it, Shota! That's
the face you need!
You're grinning like crazy!
I am not!
And would it kill you to put on underwear
before getting out of the shower?
Relax, would you?
I'm plenty covered!
A few days later
It's him again!
The smoke villain!
What's in this smoke?!
Dammit! My eyes are burning!
Outta the way!
It's a hero!
Please, stop him!
The twerp from the other day?!
It's not gonna turn out any different!
Idiot!
Say, Shota...
What're you gonna do if you run
up against that villain again?
Y'know, I'm not sure.
His smoke can make your eyes irritated
even from being in its proximity.
But if you stay too far back, it'll block
your vision so much you can't see him.
That's a bad match for your Erasure,
since it projects from your eyes.
And smokescreens make it hard
for me to operate, too.
How about I lend you my goggles?
That way, your eyes will be
protected even if you get close.
I'll teach you the hard way...
Then you can use your Quirk.
Erasure!
I'm not getting any more smoke?!
Son of a...
Those eyes... you did this, didn't you?
I dunno what kinda crap you pulled,
but I don't need no smoke
to kick some kid's ass!
Shirakumo!
On it!
Cloud!
More of them?!
I knew you boys had it in you.
Nice teamwork, Loud
Cloud and Eraser Head!
If you two work together, you might
add up to a half-decent superhero.
Thanks!
Good work, boys!
Are they heroes?
They're students at Purple's office.
They're waiting for a smile, now!
Right on!
Still waiting! Loosen up a little!
The next term
Yo, yo, yo!
What's up with the goggles, Aizawa?
You and Oboro doing a pair look now?
Sure are!
We're working as a duo, after all!
Not really. But since
my Quirk needs my eyes,
we figured it'd be good
to protect them...
Say what?
You trying to rip me off?
Hey, it's Sensoji from Class B!
Great, just who I wanted to see.
Rip you off how?
My Quirk, Blast, is pretty powerful,
but has some issues with accuracy.
But with these sunglasses, my own
blast doesn't blind me anymore,
and I get way more effective in combat!
Learned a thing or two
about eye protection.
I'm on the same level as him...
For the record, homeboy here
copied my own sunglasses look!
Happened while we were
at our work study together.
Oh, you two were at the same agency?
You guys should be grateful.
You might be trash, but I'm gracious
enough to use you as references.
But I better not see
you stealing my ideas!
That's kinda self-centered, isn't it?
He's just running his mouth.
Ignore him. Let's go.
Today's combat training
will be two versus two team battles.
As for the pairs... looks like
we'll be making that call again.
Sir!
Since I've been doing my work study with
Shota, can we practice together today?
That's fine. Try and operate like
you would in actual combat.
If any of you are in a similar
situation, go ahead and pair up.
Hey, teacher!
What's up, Yamada?
I gotta say no thanks to the
idea of teaming with Sensoji!
I'm in the mood for something different.
Too bad! Your mood's not a priority.
He might complain, but they really do
come across as an impressive team.
Sensoji's Blast and Yamada's Voice...
Both Quirks are flashy and work
well as suppressive weapons.
Just spamming them could
potentially take a villain down.
Compared to that, Aizawa and Shirakumo
have a really technical style.
Downright tricky, even.
Let's have it out, Aizawa!
If I win, you ditch the goggles!
They piss me off for some reason!
And I'm supposed to care?
You're on! Our goggles
versus your sunglasses!
Why have I been dragged into this?!
These goggles are like the
symbol of our friendship, Shota.
Let's protect them!
You're enjoying this,
aren't you, Shirakumo?
You stay out of it, Yamada.
I can take these wimps on my own!
Time to blow away the trash!
Catch!
That's a little cloud in your eyes!
Nice try!
Time for a pop quiz!
Where are we hiding?
Stupid gimmicks...
If I blow away all your clouds,
that'll take care of it!
The answer? Shota's behind you, and—
I'm in front!
This ain't over!
Enough's enough.
Besides, two on one isn't exactly fair.
The bet's off, too.
You didn't beat me.
And I don't need those stupid sunglasses!
Dammit, Sensoji, do you even understand
the point of this exercise?!
It's a team battle!
Shirakumo, Aizawa!
You two are making good use of
those hard-to-handle Quirks!
Good work! Keep it up!
Hold it, Sensoji! I'm not done with you!
We got praised in passing!
Man, what am I supposed to do
without my trademark sunglasses?
This, actually! Whatcha think?
Do I look good or what?
Why are you wearing goggles now, too?
Well, the three of us are gonna
work as a trio some day!
Yamada's coming to the
Purple agency too?
That seems sudden.
No, man, we're talking long-term.
Our boss...
He likes to raise rookies up
so they can go indie, right?
He loves putting youngsters
through their paces.
Yes. I do like to push hard.
So what I figure is...
The three of us start our own
agency and go independent.
That's my plan.
I think we've got good chemistry!
Take Shota.
You never take the initiative, but
you're really detail oriented,
and are a perfectionist with
the stuff you do take on.
Definitely can't say that
about me and Hizashi!
I guess not. You two are
basically slackers.
Then there's your Erasure Quirk.
It can't cinch a battle on its own,
but it can throw just about any enemy off
their game, and set up our advantage!
Which is where the two of
us come in and nail 'em!
Yeah, sounds like a winning strat to me!
Still, having no initiative, and being
unable to win fights on my own...
All that really means is I can't
do anything without help, right?
It just means you're suited to teamwork!
We'll handle all the idea
and initiative stuff!
And then you do all the hard work!
Hold it. That sounds like
absolute hell for me.
Besides, I never agreed
to work with you two.
You don't wanna?
Aw, Aizawa's just playing hard to get!
Is that it? You're hard
to understand, Shota.
You two...
I love the smell of youth in the air!
Hey, Kayama! What's up?
The way you bicker so playfully...
it's magnificent!
I'm totally serious over here.
Wanna see some kitty pics?
Damn, you're easy, Aizawa!
Isn't he adorable?
Say something, Aizawa!
So, we were discussing setting up
an agency for the four of us...
The four of us?!
Sorry to break it to you,
but once I've gone independent, I'm
going to run my agency like a castle,
with all sorts of boys
seeing to my needs!
I love it! Gotta appreciate someone
who's honest about their desires!
Maybe I should go work for her...
What about our plans, man?
Are you all wearing those goggles now?
You wanna try them on?
What do you think?
I think you look good
no matter what you're wearing!
You guys do whatever you want.
How about like this?
Absolutely fantastic!
Yeah!
The wind seems to be blowing the
clouds along at quite a clip.
I used to think I'd never get anywhere,
but now I'm on the verge
of being carried away.
The sky I saw from beneath
those goggles...
was bigger and wider than I anticipated.
One week later—
A violent villain has
made it into Tasomiya!
Over 300 buildings have been demolished!
Current number of injured is unknown!
The expanding area of conflict has led
to a need for civilian evacuations.
All PMs available are to attend
to a speedy evacuation.
It looks like the hero who responded
to the attack, His Purple Highness,
and one of his students were seriously
injured in combat with the villain!
Requesting immediate backup!
As soon as possible!
I knew that, rationally,
there was no way I could take
down a giant villain on my own.
But my heart was in a frenzy.
Spurred on by his voice,
and by his encouragement.
Next time: A Sky with No Rain Left.
You can do it, Shota!