Gregory!
Damn it, we're done for at this rate...
There's gotta be something I can do!
Run away.
r u n
R U N
Divine Voice
Lv 4
The Divine Voice skill has gone
from level three to level four.
You can now access the
simplified simulator rendered by Laplace.
Laplace
Simplified
Simulator
What's the big idea?
Whaddaya mean
the Divine Voice leveled up?!
But I imagine...
you will not run
no matter how much I warn you.
You were an exception to the rule,
in so many ways.
It's unfortunate
this is where we must part.
So you leveled up
just to tell me this crap?!
I never got tired of watching you.
Rest peacefully now.
I'm so sick of your condescending babble!
Just who the hell are you?!
The Divine Voice cannot provide
explanations of that nature at level four.
Screw that noise!
I'm gonna prove you wrong!
I still have my last resort...
Evolution.
But it'll change how I look,
which means Myria and the black lizard
may not recognize me anymore.
There are four different evolutions
I can choose from now.
Which one should I choose? Think!
Jormungand.
I might stand a chance at winning
if I pick that,
but its deadly poison
is seriously bad news!
Rolling Dragon!
It specializes in the Roll skill, right?
Is that actually powerful?!
Dark Drago-human!
But are demi-humans good in battle?
I have no idea what to expect!
Little Arc Dragon!
Can white magic be used to attack?
Is it enough to beat that bastard?!
Which one?
What should I choose?!
Which one is most likely to win?!
What was that just now?
It's like all my MP got taken from me...
You have received the title
"Laplace Authority Interference."
Little Arc Dragon
If you evolve into Little Arc Dragon,
your odds of winning are 4%.
There is a less than 1% chance
of you saving all your injured allies.
The hell does that mean?
Are you telling me I can't win
even if I evolve?!
Jormungand
If you evolve into Jormungand, your odds
of ending the battle in a draw are 98%.
There is a 94% chance
the village is totally destroyed.
What's the point
if I can't protect the village?!
Rolling Dragon
If you evolve into Rolling Dragon,
you have less than a 1% chance of victory.
Your odds of a successful escape
are over 99%.
So you're still telling me
to run away, then?!
I don't get it.
Why are you giving me
all these predictions?!
You stupid voice!
Tsuyoku nare itami yo yuuki ni nare
Nani ga umaretan darou
Te o nobashi fureta sekai wa
Kanashikute moroi kagayaki
Dakara koso no more painess
Kono basho de mirai no kodou
Kanjitara mou tomerarenai
Hikari oikakete
Gliding Claw
Dare ka no koto mamoritakunatta
Sou... dakara makenai makerarenai yo
Gliding Claw
Wakatta no wa chiisana jibun ga kawareru koto da to
Tsuyoku nare itami yo yuuki ni nare
I heard a loud noise
coming from the village.
Let's hurry.
The Rock Dragon is going berserk.
Have all the villagers evacuated?
No, quite a few of them
haven't shown up yet.
Oh, Jean!
Where's Gregory?
In the center of town.
He and a couple others said
they were going to stop the Rock Dragon.
I'm heading over there too.
Myria, you provide aid
for the villagers here!
No.
I've already helped everyone I can here.
I'm going with you.
But...
I'm sure there are
plenty of injured people over that way.
All right. Come with me.
Which one should I choose?
I gotta be quick
or this will just get worse!
If I help Gregory first,
evolve into the Little Arc Dragon,
and use recovery magic...
If you evolve into Little Arc Dragon,
your odds of winning are 4%.
Odds of Winning 4%
There is a less than 1% chance
of you saving all your injured allies.
Saving Injured 1%
Shut up!
You really think anyone believes
whatever stupid crap you say?!
Gregory, are you okay?!
He's bleeding out!
Just hold on.
I'll evolve into a Little Arc Dragon
and heal you.
Don't worry about me.
Huh? What do you mean?!
What reason could a Plague Dragon
like you have to help humans?
I have absolutely no clue.
It makes no sense,
but there is one thing I'm convinced of...
It's fine, stop talking!
I'll heal you very soon!
You...
aren't using your true power, are you?
Hey... do me a favor.
Eat me.
You're a Plague Dragon, right?
You eat people,
and then get stronger, right?
No, no, no, never!
I'm not that extreme of a monster!
I don't eat people!
And I don't power up like that!
The only way I get stronger
is through evolution!
Wait...
My evolution tree...
Young Plague Dragon.
The first stage of an Evil Dragon
that spreads disaster.
However, it has not strayed too far from
the righteous path, and may yet backtrack.
You have received the title
"Itty-Bitty Hero" level one.
A light-type!
Hard to believe a Plague Dragon
can evolve into something so righteous!
You have received the title "Wrongdoer."
But like, why is there no Plague Dragon
evolution even though I'm a Plague Dragon?
No Plague Dragon...
There's no... Plague Dragon.
Even though you helped Myria,
I stabbed you with my spear,
and you're still fighting the Rock Dragon
to help us humans.
I wanted the humans to accept me,
as the hero who saved their village!
You're really not at all
how a monster should be.
But...
if that's the reason
you can't beat the Rock Dragon, then...
Gregory, what are you...
The village...
Protect the village, Illusia...
Because you have maxed out your level,
you cannot gain experience points.
The Wrongdoer title
has gone from level four to level five
The Calamity title
has gone from level one to level three,
and the Dastardly King title
has gone from level one to level two.
That was a major level up.
There really is
no turning back for me now.
Would you like to view the evolution tree?
Show me right now.
Plague Dragon, Rank B-.
An evil dragon that brings disaster
wherever it roams.
It has destroyed many human villages.
It bathes itself in a sea of blood,
and sleeps atop
the resulting mountain of corpses.
Plague Dragon
It is one of the three
great Calamity monsters.
I will...
evolve into a Plague Dragon!
Don't worry.
I will make sure to protect the village!
With the power
that your sacrifice gave me!
Status: Enraged (Major)
Attack:
Defense:
Magic:
Agility:
Crap, you are way too heavy!
It figures that I can't beat this guy
in a shoving match.
But...
Take this!
Yeah, that's some thick skin!
But I'm not done!
Okay, the stage is set.
This is where...
I whoop you!
I Evolved Into an Evil Dragon
Illusia!
Mr. Gregory!
Where'd the Rock Dragon go?
Aurus, you're okay?!
Where are the others?
What's happened to Gregory?
Gregory...
What in the world happened?
It was the black dragon!
It killed Gregory!
Black dragon?
You mean the Plague Dragon
Myria brought here?!
He couldn't have...
I saw it with my own eyes!
The black dragon cut Gregory's head off!
Then it suddenly got bigger...
It grew?
You mean it evolved?!
I-I don't know.
It moved east
while fighting the Rock Dragon.
Damn those nasty monsters!
Illusia killed Mr. Gregory?
It can't... It can't be true!
Calm down, Myria.
We have more important things
to do right now.
Come on.
We need to hurry and treat the injured.
R-right!
Aurus, get a move on!
Okay!
A Rock Dragon and a Plague Dragon, huh?
The village is doomed
if they come back here.
Using Tremor again?
Is that all you've got?!
It's my turn now!
Whirlwind Slash
Whirlwind Slash!
So this is my newly gained skill,
Whirlwind Slash, huh?
How useful.
Bellow
Meteorite
Nutcracker
Human Transformation
Whirlwind Smash
Neckbreaker
I've got one called Neckbreaker too.
Bet that hits hard.
That was close!
I'd have been cooked
if that attack hit me!
None of the hits I landed
made a good dent in its HP.
It's sturdy as hell.
Doesn't it have a weak spot somewhere?!
The Divine Voice cannot provide
explanations of that nature at level four.
Yep, I knew you'd say that!
Considering its body is hard as rock,
maybe its weak spot is... the head!
There's nothing I can do but try!
Dragon Punch!
Onto the next one!
Dragon Tail!
Try this on for size!
Hell yeah! I crushed its eyes!
This should be easy pickings
if it can't see.
I can just beat it into submission now!
Wait, not that way!
You're not going any further!
Okay.
Aurus, take those who can move
and evacuate them west of the village.
You got it!
Myria, we're going to search
around here...
Myria?
She better not have gone after it!
Stop!
Dragon Scale Powder!
Is my poison working on it?!
Its neck...
You know, the neck
seems slimmer than the rest of it.
Did I just find its weak spot?
It's working!
Don't stop! I gotta pummel it!
Almost there!
I'll snap the damn thing!
Neckbreaker
There it is!
Take this!
Neckbreaker!
You have received 384 experience points.
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
you have earned an additional
384 experience points.
Plague Dragon
has gone from level 1 to level 19.
All right.
I beat it.
Illusia?
Myria!
You are... Illusia, right?
You still recognize me?
You beat the Rock Dragon for us, huh?
And you've gotten so big...
Did you evolve again?
Evolve?
Oh, right.
I killed Gregory
and turned into this monstrosity...
Light Sphere!
Myria, get away from it!
What the?!
There's no time to waste, run away!
Please stop, Miss Marielle!
Myria?!
What are you doing?!
Miss Marielle!
This is Illusia,
the dragon I told you about!
He's bigger now,
but I'm positive this is him!
Gregory was killed by this monster!
Really, Illusia?
Get away from it!
There must be some misunderstanding!
Illusia would not do that!
Myria...
You believe in me?
Oh yeah, the Dragon Scale Powder!
Miss Marielle, I...
I've turned into a monstrosity
who can't be near her anymore...
Myria!
Light Sphere!
You must've been hit by
the Plague Dragon's poison.
No...
No... Illusia...
Farewell, Myria.
So awesome! I'm built like a tank now!
I bet I can kick so much ass!
My whole body feels stiff.
Aren't I supposed to have
automatic recovery?
You know, I never really cared
about flowers until today...
Illusia, Value D+.
Illusia
That's... my name.
A beautiful red and white flower.
It is said this flower only blooms
where monsters live.
For that reason,
these flowers are difficult to gather,
and they make excellent gifts.
In flower language,
it symbolizes courage, bravery,
and heroism.
You're a hero.
How about... Illusia?
It's the name of a flower I like.
Erase it!
Get rid of this name!
Once your name is confirmed,
it cannot be changed.
Bravery? A hero?!
You really think I can use this name?!
Delete it! Get rid of it this instant!
Once your name is confirmed,
it cannot be changed.
I'm an idiot.
A huge idiot!
What was it I wanted to become?
What did I want to do?
Why was I even brought to this world?
What's that sound?
Ah, whatever, I don't care anymore...
Can you tell me? Shinjita kotoba
Never ending kawareru bokura
Always remember yakusoku nakutashita page
Owaranai monogatari o
Don't let nobody bring you down
Tokihanate break of dawn
Kirei na mama no omoide nara
Oitakita through the rain
Tesaguri demo mae ni susumu emotion
Tsune ni mune ni daite
Atomodori wa nashi
Kokoro ni oshita rakuin
Shoki shoudou no mama ni
Attouteki na made ni
Hisometa ketsui hyoumei wa
Kakumei no makuake sa
Hajimeyou ka 3, 2, 1 GO!!
Can you tell me? Shinjita kotoba
Never ending kawareru bokura
Always remember yakusoku nakushita page
Owaranai monogatari o
Shukumei wa ima da mikansei
Shimesu sono kanousei
We fly together koko de wa nai dokoka e
Yoru ga akeru made
Hane hiroge
Itsuka sora ni kieru made
I Caught Sight of the Mastermind
"I Caught Sight of the Mastermind".