Episode 9
"Judge's Problem"
Oh, he's closed.
Even he goes out sometimes.
Mr. Lizel!
I'm so sorry. I'll open
the shop right away.
It's all right. We just arrived.
Could you appraise something for me?
Yes, come in.
Judge?
Y-Yes?
Did something happen?
Well, um...
It's nothing.
Um, thank you.
I'll be back.
It wasn't those bandits.
I can't. I'm leaving.
He wouldn't pull something after
being terrified that badly.
He did cry until his eyelids were puffy.
Are you going to help?
For now, I'll wait and see.
He didn't complain, so he probably
doesn't want to be cheered up.
Something must've happened to his shop.
That's not something we can butt into.
Is that right?
That's what it means
to be a professional.
Welcome back.
I wasn't expecting you to come
today after yesterday's events.
Really? Nice.
Has your wrist healed already?
It's totally fine.
I've got healing potions.
Mr. Lizel, you're not being bothered
by nasty men again, are you?
You're not far from the mark.
Hey, wait!
See? You shouldn't lie
about knowing Mr. Lizel.
Gil, do you mind if I
take a shower first?
Go ahead.
You're leaving me here?
Wait, seriously?
Let me join your party...
He's actually leaving!
Come on, don't squat there.
Your hair's brushing the floor.
You think he hates me?
Mr. Lizel wouldn't bother hating
someone who doesn't matter.
I don't matter?!
Okay, I'm staying here, too.
Got any rooms?
We're full.
Can't you do something about that?
No!
So you're finally willing to talk to me.
The innkeeper seemed put out.
Anyway, you had something
to discuss, didn't you?
I came to ask to join your party.
Is the answer still no?
Yes.
He's not responding like before, so...
I promise I won't hurt you again.
It's all right. I don't think you will.
Then what am I supposed to do?
I'd like to see you sell yourself
in a way only you can.
Okay, then a bribe.
The item shop you're friendly with fought
with the merchant's guild today.
That's a good bribe.
One that doesn't leave evidence.
Right?
But how did you learn that?
I'd been investigating you
recently, so as part of that.
Oh, I see. Gil seemed annoyed
about someone watching us.
Seriously? I actually used
decent guys this time.
You're not mad?
Were you watching me, too?
You couldn't tell?
Not at all.
It's not as though you did
anything to me. I'm not mad.
That's good.
So, about Judge...
Oh, right.
A few of his labyrinth items were
stolen by an employee he hired.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Merchant's Guild
Merchant
At a registered merchant's request,
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
I'd like to leave my
shop for a while, but
I have no one to
watch the store…
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Submit
Request
the guild dispatches staff,
like shopkeepers.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Dispatch Staff
The employee was a high-ranking staff
member dispatched by the guild,
so the fight got really nasty.
I see. The staff denied
they stole anything.
Not wanting to admit their mistake,
the guild believed their staff
and is treating Judge like a liar.
Exactly.
The guild's higher-ups would know
that Judge is Mr. Insigh's grandson.
Perhaps he's dealing with
lower-level members.
It's not my place to talk to the
merchant's guild, so what should I do?
Pretty useful, right?
Aren't you a bandit leader?
I'd like to avoid having
you join my party.
Then I'll quit being a bandit.
A bandit gang without a
leader would sow chaos.
Oh. Should I kill them all, then?
It would be disastrous if you failed.
Poisoning them might work.
As a snake beastman,
you'd be the prime suspect.
If a bandit gang as large as yours
were wiped out, it'd be big news.
Are you actually worried about me?
Of course.
By the way, you can poison people?
Huh? Yeah, it's easy.
You secrete poison from glands
inside your mouth, was it?
I'd rather not say, but...
Open your mouth.
If you want to know that badly, go ahead.
In exchange, let me join your party.
The glands are behind your fangs, so...
A slit at the base.
Is this the gland?
'eah.
Could you secrete something now?
What are you doing?!
I was curious what kind of poison it was.
My mouth and fingertip feel a bit numb.
Well, yeah! It's an anesthetic poison!
Aw, man.
Drink this.
Why do potions have to taste like
they make everything worse?
I don't believe you.
What if it killed you instantly?
I'm fine now.
Seriously?
Were you worried about me?
I mean—
Didn't you promise to
never hurt me again?
Did he actually believe that?
Hey, Blade! Hey!
Stop knocking. It's loud.
What did you teach that guy?
Nobody tastes something
they know is poison.
Don't yell at me to hide
your embarrassment.
What? I'm not embarrassed.
Don't close the door!
Let's talk about what
you're teaching him!
Hey, open up! Open this
door! Open the door!
I might get in trouble with Gil later.
All the stolen items are labyrinth goods,
all worth around one gold.
Where'd you learn that?
Total coincidence.
I was looking for something juicy to
bring you and happened to stumble upon it.
How kind of you.
I've always been this way.
Anyway, do you want to spar sometime?
If you can last five minutes.
Five minutes, huh?
Judge's shop handles more
valuable goods, doesn't it?
Perhaps they avoided those because
it would've been too obvious.
They'd also get caught when
they tried to sell them.
I'm having my gang search
the black market,
and I haven't heard about any
labyrinth goods on the market.
I doubt they'll show up there.
I thought you were staying out of this.
I haven't done anything
yet, so I'm still okay.
Apparently he goes to the
guild every day to complain.
He's got more guts than I expected.
Perhaps I'll take a job tomorrow.
What?
I'm going with you!
You're taking that one?
What do you think?
Might be tough for you.
Acquire white golem cores?
Aren't golems resistant to magic?
That'd be dangerous for you.
But I've never seen a golem before.
Suit yourself.
Then I'll get this taken care of.
Don't you think you're too soft on him?
If he's going somewhere dangerous,
that means you'll have to protect him.
I don't think that's a good
way for a party to operate.
How is that any of your business?
It'll be my problem
when I join the party.
Sorry.
If he wanted me to protect him, he
wouldn't take the job in the first place.
But they're resistant to magic.
He's serious about being an adventurer.
Thank you for waiting.
Did something happen?
I had a little request.
What labyrinth are we going to?
The closest labyrinth with white
golems is... the Box Cavern?
Yeah.
Adventurers generally
stand out, don't they?
It's their weapons that stand out.
And some of their armor looks awesome.
They're unique. I enjoy looking at them.
People who really care about their
appearance get them custom made.
With materials they've
desperately gathered.
Then they break what
they ordered in a day.
What a tough world we live in.
But you guys wear practically
only cloth armor.
You must use a ton of nice materials.
You're lightly armored as well.
I just don't like heavy stuff.
I still take a lot of
damage when I get hit.
All the way back, please.
A little more.
You're really packing us in there.
Sorry. The inside's already full.
This is surprisingly unstable.
Well, yeah.
Doesn't your butt hurt?
A little. Oh, right.
Here, Gil.
And for you as well.
Is this an illusion wolf pelt?
And you used it to make a cushion?
I don't like hard seats.
I had it made.
What a waste.
It's so fluffy!
Isn't it?
We'll be at the first labyrinth soon.
We're going to the third, right?
Yeah.
Gil?
I'm impressed you noticed
when you're not a beastman.
Birds that run incredibly
quickly along the ground.
They have a mysterious intensity.
They hardly fly even though they can.
Maybe they run faster.
Gil, catch me if I seem like I'll fall.
Just don't.
Oh, it's the noble.
Be careful. We nearly
attacked you by accident.
I'm sorry.
So, are there monsters?
Yes. Three forest runners.
Yikes.
Their beaks really hurt.
If there aren't any materials
you'd like, I'll defeat them now.
What? Uh, thanks.
Do you want any materials?
No, I'm good.
Oh, one got away. They really are fast.
There.
Why's it floating?
To combat the recoil.
Let me see that again.
No.
What's wrong?
I feel sick.
You're motion sick?
You were fine during the escort job.
The wagon didn't shake
this much last time.
Are you okay?
Chocolate? Thank you.
Whoa.
Sweets are good for motion sickness.
I think I feel a bit better.
Then give me your hand.
There's a pressure point here
to stop motion sickness.
I feel thoroughly pampered.
Well? Pretty useful, right?
Yes, you're a very good boy.
The construction is rather
precise. I like it.
I know.
It's exactly like I imagined.
There's a trap there.
You mean this?
What?!
Why'd you step on it?!
Didn't I tell you? I did, didn't I?
I was curious what kind of trap
it was and couldn't help it.
Control yourself!
Anyway, how did you
know there was a trap?
Instinct, I guess. More importantly...
Mind if I handle this?
Go ahead.
He's unique, isn't he?
Only the truly eccentric dual wield.
Impressive.
Am I underwhelming after
seeing the Blade?
No. To be honest, your flashy movements
looked more impressive to me.
Yeah, they'd seem flashy when
you're dodging that much.
I just don't like getting hurt.
And I like my style.
I can't help watching since
dual wielders are unusual.
It's far more normal than your weapons.
They're big.
They're on the bigger side
for a non-boss monster.
They're slow, but they're resistant
to magic and blades, too.
Let me try something.
I told you, magic won't—
How'd that pierce it?
I read in the encyclopedia that golems
are resistant to magic because their cores
absorb the mana of magical attacks.
An encyclopedia? How diligent.
But my rifle...
The mana's end point isn't the monster.
It passes through instead, so I
thought it might not be absorbed.
Was your experiment successful?
Yes.
Then you've had your fun.
I'm killing them.
How'd you finish it off so quickly?!
These guys are unbelievable.
Here.
Is this the core?
What kind of freak stomps on
a golem to break it down?
Do mine, too.
Do it yourself.
I'll do it.
Just wait there.
Whatever. Let's head to the next place.
It's our job. Should we let him?
Let him do what he wants.
We got so many.
Too many.
The next wagon's in... thirty minutes.
It must be past noon. I'm hungry.
Then you can have these.
Thank you.
Hey, Blade.
We've got time. What do you say?
You'd better last five minutes.
Nice.
Give us a signal.
Begin.
How are you so quick
with such a big sword?
Don't aim for the neck.
It makes it hard to hold back.
They're too fast for me to follow.
We couldn't find our last marionette.
Whoa, what is that?
They're sparring.
Excuse us for taking up space.
It's fine. Wait, is that the Blade?
This adventurer sure seems like a noble!
You must be tired. Have some.
Uh, thanks.
That was dangerous.
But I gave those to you!
As you can see, he's been scolded.
Please forgive him.
Here, to make up for it.
We gathered plenty.
What? These are the marionette
ribbons we're looking for.
I hope you'll forgive him now.
Uh, sure.
I'm not in your party. You
don't have to protect me.
It's my fault.
It was rude of me to share
when you gave them to me.
We'll eat them together, okay?
He lasted five minutes.
And could apparently afford
to pay attention to you.
Oh, the wagon is here.
Come on, let's go.
Yeah, yeah.
Next Time
"Eleven's Request"
Next time: "Eleven's Request."
Illustration by: Inu