We totally...
hit the jackpot!
I knew this was
a lesser-known spot, but still!
We only had to take one bus!
It's beach time!
I have three childhood friends...
I'll show you my graceful butterfly today!
I'll follow you with my breaststrokes.
You two are so full of energy.
Visiting the beach
with your childhood friends...
is a classic rom-com setup...
Hey, hey, Eiyu! What are you doing?
No sulking on the beach!
What should we do?
How about we
split the watermelon?
Or make shaved ice?
Huh?
It's all set up now.
Go for it.
Seriously? You're such a downer!
Are you digging for clams?
Are you actually stupid?
See? You can't be in a rom-com
with your childhood friends.
See? You can't be in a rom-com with your childhood friends.
Eiyu
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
What's your problem?!
We finally made it to the beach!
Don't mind me.
Have fun, just the three of you.
Ooh, that's a pretty shell.
Seriously? You're like a grumpy old man!
Just forget about him.
Let's go swimming!
Aw, come on. Let's go have some fun!
Yeah! Let's have some fun!
Huh?
Come on, let's go swim!
Yeah, the more the merrier, right?
Ugh... Stop that.
Come on, Eiyu!
Hey! Stop that!
Onii-chan!
My mind's set on making it
a special summer with Eiyu this year!
It's my first time at the beach
with Onii-chan in five years!
Huh?
Childhood friends!
Childhood friends! Childhood friends!
sting
This is devastating!
This is way more intense than expected!
I-I can't look directly at them!
I know I told Shio...
Things will stay the same.
Childhood friends are childhood friends.
No, no, no!
You're taking the clam digging
that seriously?
Oh no!
I forgot to put sunscreen on my back.
Eiyu... Can you help?
Come on, please?
Eiyu.
Then I'll put some
on your back, Onii-chan.
Hey! Stop that.
Aw, come on.
You don't have to be shy.
Aren't you going to take responsibility?
Promise you'll take responsibility
for today at some point, okay?
Kidding!
E-Eiyu, let me put some on you, too!
Hey! I'm already doing it!
Wh-What's going on?
Everyone's being so assertive.
Am I... falling behind?!
Come on, Onii-chan.
Hey! S-Stop it!
Ready?
Onii-chan.
Come on, let's go in the water.
Let go! Don't push me.
Come, let's go!
Hey, you two!
Let's go!
Go, go!
It's the beach!
Endure it... I have to endure it!
We gotta go in the water!
Junior High School
Entrance
Ceremony
From the day...
I started noticing my feelings
for my childhood friends...
until today...
What do you wanna do?
You have no idea...
Steel Your Heart
You have no idea how much
training I've gone through!
Extinguish It
My stoic face...
H-Hey, Eiyu...
D-Do you wanna...
Um, do you wanna play...
beach volleyball... with me?
My stoic face is an impenetrable wall!
What's your problem?!
Acting all bored!
I was really excited to have
fun with you, too... Eiyu...
Wha?
That's not what I meant!
Me too...
I was excited for today too!
But...
You're all too cute!
Are you okay?!
Eiyu!
Onii-chan...
Your nose is bleeding!
Sorry! Did you hit your head?
No!
I-I wasn't embarrassed or anything!
What?
You were embarrassed?
Aw, you were embarrassed?
No, no!
I swear I wasn't!
You're totally embarrassed!
Don't lose to the embarrassed one!
All right!
I'm not embarrassed!
Say, ah!
Aw, you're so embarrassed!
Stop that!
Stop!
Eiyu, take that!
In the end... I got completely roasted!
Dang it.
This is why you can't be in a rom-com
with your childhood friends...
Hey, c'mon slowpoke!
If you miss the bus,
you're camping here tonight.
I know!
Don't tell me you're so embarrassed
you can't even walk next to us.
Huh? Full of yourself, much?
I mean, if you have the time to mock me,
you could at least help me out, yeah?
Why should I?! You're the one
who lost rock-paper-scissors!
What's your problem?!
I swear, if you had cried and begged,
maybe I would've helped you!
Whoa! Such a brat! So petty!
Forget it, I don't need your help!
You're ridiculous!
You're way more of a brat—
Huh?
No!
ZZZ...
Wh-What are we gonna do?!
The bus left without us!
S-Seriously?
Gosh!
There's no signal out here...
I don't really know this area...
Who would've thought going to a secluded
beach would cause so much trouble?
Are you saying this is my fault?
Th-That's not what I meant!
Jeez, this really sucks!
Akari's really tense right now...
Well, I guess it makes sense
since she doesn't like me...
That's true...
It probably wouldn't feel that bad...
Now's not the time!
Hey, what's taking you so long?
We have to walk along the bus route.
There's no other option!
It probably wouldn't feel that bad...
Hello?! Earth to Eiyu!
Let's go!
Stop! It's not like that!
Don't get the wrong idea, stupid me!
Good grief, this sucks.
I'm stuck, it's just the two of us,
I'm with this useless idiot...
J-J-J-Just the two of us?!
How the heck did we end up
getting stuck together like this?!
W-Wait... could this be my chance?!
My chance to be like Shio and Runako...
I mean, what am I thinking?!
Come on, keep walking!
Huh?
A cat...
Don't start getting clingy
just because we're alone!
That's rich!
Are we gonna be okay?
It feels like we're going
towards the mountain.
It's all dark now, too...
I'm pretty sure
we're going the right way,
but I don't know how long
I'm gonna last with all this stuff...
I guess we've got no choice
but to hitchhike.
N-No way!
I've heard stories where
hitchhikers get murdered!
What? Seriously?
Then, maybe I should
just run and get help?
You're gonna leave me alone?!
You know people start disappearing
when they're left alone!
Understand our predicament?!
In the mountains at night,
you're more likely to be targeted
hey...
by yamanoke or ghosts
trying to kidnap you!
For being a scaredy-cat,
you sure know a lot about
scary stories from all over.
Who are you calling—
caw
A-A scaredy-cat...?
Yeah, exactly.
Come on, let's get going.
Shoot. I'm really freaked out.
Wh-Where are we? I wanna go home!
It's okay, Akari.
I'm here with you.
No... I can't muster the courage...
Huh?!
H-Hey! Are you okay?!
Y-Yeah! I'm t-totally fine!
Well...
You definitely don't look it.
Just leave me alone!
Gosh!
Can you stand?
Don't patronize me.
Of course I—
See? You can't even stand straight.
W-Wait!
What're you doing?!
All right, let's go.
Put me down. You're so annoying.
You're already carrying too much.
Give me a break.
You weren't this stubborn before.
So not fair...
Come on, we don't need
to walk home together anymore.
You're the one who changed.
Just stop.
Put me down!
I'm such a pain, right?!
Wh-What?
Because...
Ever since then...
You've looked tense the whole time...
And you won't look at me anymore.
Oh... tense, huh?
Well, yeah...
I'm on edge because I'm
focused on protecting you.
I'm here with you.
So you haven't changed...
You haven't... changed!
Look, Akari!
We're out of the woods!
We're gonna be okay!
Akari?
It finally went through!
Where are you? Are you okay?!
Onii-chan! Akari-chan!
Yeah, okay. Will do.
Bye.
Mom said we should stay the night.
She already booked us a place.
Let's go.
Okay.
What's going on?
Akari's been dead silent this whole time.
She's mad at me, right?
Wait, it's a shared room?!
And we're sleeping next to each other?!
What the heck are our moms thinking?!
I'll ask if I can get a different room.
It's fine.
I want to stay with you.
Y-You want to stay with me?
You mean...
I see, you're still scared
of ghosts and stuff, right?
Thanks for today.
It... well, it took me back.
What? Took you back?
I'll go take a bath now.
O-Okay...
What?!
What was that about?
Usually, she'd be like...
Staying in the same room as you?!
I'd rather stay in a pigpen!
That's not even an exaggeration.
It's like she doesn't
have her usual disdain...
This is...
Men's
eerie.
It's called the calm before the storm!
menacing
She's gotta be up to something.
Hey, were you waiting for me?
Women's
Men's
Yeah.
Women's
That's a surprise...
You usually hate having to wait.
Whatever.
This is definitely eerie!
Wow! This looks delicious!
Looks like we were lucky
to be left behind!
Damn it, I can't read her at all!
Here, have my shrimp.
How's the heat level?
DANGER
It's like I'm tap-dancing on a minefield!
A-Akari, how about some tea?
Wah! That's hot!
No! Th-This is bad!
Sorry, Akari!
Is your finger okay?
I'll clean this up,
go cool your finger off.
Th-Thanks...
I'm so confused!
What's going on with her?!
She's never been this cooperative...
Well...
Let's go to sleep then, huh?
snug
Good night.
Stop! Don't get your hopes up!
Don't get your hopes up no matter what!
We're just childhood friends!
Which is why...
What...?
Don't be so mean.
I don't like it when
you're so bratty and cold, Eiyu.
triggered
Then why are you lying next to me?
So...
look at me like you used to.
Okay, fine.
Yeah...
He makes me feel at ease.
I love you.
Did she just say...
"I-I love you"?
What?
What?!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
heh
That was a rom-com situation.
Sleep Deprived
heh
That was totally a rom-com situation!
Sleep Deprived
I didn't expect to be in one with Akari!
Jeez, she really is so stubborn.
Wow!
Hey, Akari.
M-Morning.
So listen, about last night...
Huh?
Gross, what are you talking about?
Forget that! Stop peeking
at a girl getting ready!
Well, I'm going home!
Hey!
Abandoned
Then what the...
What the heck was last night about?!
I knew it.
You can't be in a rom-com
with your childhood friend.
Did I say that?
I love you.
Did I? Did I?
Did I really say that?!
Oh no...
I really said it!
What do I do?! What do I do?!
Episode 6
Summer Beach? Looking Away?
Spent the Night? Still Won't Start a Rom-Com
What do I do?!