Episode 9
It's almost done.
As long as the vital
acupoints are destroyed,
these stripes will no longer function.
Since the Sect Leader never
truly approved of this valley,
I'll destroy it myself.
This whole ordeal is finally over.
Who said it's over?
Huh?
Why do you think I gave
Zhang Chulan my phone number?
Even if that kid doesn't contact me,
I'll contact him myself.
Contact him? For what?
Who are you?
Who are your parents?
Who is your master?
My master forbade me to speak of it.
Ah, right. I always felt that
Feng Baobao seemed familiar,
but I shouldn't have met her before.
You really haven't met her before.
There are no treasures in
the "What Is Human" cave.
It only contains things that
the Sect Leader values.
Many of us in the Quan Xing Sect have
seen some of those things before.
Zhang Chulan...
What are you doing, San?
You took Baobao and Xia Liuqing of
Quan Xing on a mission behind our backs,
and got involved with
someone like Wang Zhenqiu.
Do you have any idea how much
danger you've put Baobao in?
Have you considered the consequences?
What do you think you're doing?
San...
It was indeed dangerous.
Open it and take a look.
This is...
Wu Gensheng's treasure.
I managed to get my hands on it.
This is...
Baobao?
I was the first one to rush in back then,
and in front of me was this painting.
At the time, there was
no way for me to take it,
so I could only take
a photo with my phone.
The lighter's flame was too weak.
I had to ensure the entire painting,
including the canvas, was destroyed.
I had to force myself to shatter it
with the Thunder Palm technique.
I knew the black ash on the
ground might raise suspicion,
but I simply didn't have the strength
or time to deal with it back then.
As soon as I got to the city,
I printed the photo and deleted it.
With someone like Erzhuang around,
I had to be careful.
But... why did you say that
even we couldn't be trusted?
I'd feel the same way.
There really is no one left to trust.
Sorry, my suspicion of you
two is purely based on logic.
Emotionally, you two are more worthy
of Baobao's trust than I am.
San, don't you get it?
The thing Father always cared about has...
Wu Gensheng's treasure was taken long ago,
yet this painting was left behind.
If the person in this
painting really is Bao'er,
then the person Grandpa Xu
has been searching for,
someone who knew Bao'er,
has finally appeared.
If this painting was deliberately
left for me and Bao'er,
then how did they know we'd go there?
Lu Jin? Didn't you say Lu Jin
mentioned Granny Jinfeng to you?
Yes, but the one who first introduced
me to Granny Jinfeng wasn't Master Lu.
It was...
back then...
in Biyou Village.
Chen Duo herself said she was suddenly
tasked with capturing Jinfeng.
The timing coincided exactly
with our capture of Chen Duo.
After that, capturing Chen Duo inevitably
brought Jinfeng into the picture.
And the information Jinfeng provided
led us to the "What is Human" cave.
Then, they made arrangements for
those foreigners ahead of time,
and among them, one woman was clearly
prepared to deal with Bao'er.
What's the goal?
Not clear yet.
If my guess is correct,
then none of this is a coincidence.
Now do you understand?
To have orchestrated all this,
they must meet two conditions.
First, knowing Baobao
and Chulan's movements.
Second, understanding
the Company very well.
Both of us meet these conditions.
The only ones capable of doing this
are the bigwigs who could
deploy Part Timers back then.
The suspects are among them.
Is this a convenient time?
If possible, I'd like to meet
with you to discuss this.
Okay.
What's wrong, Sister?
Interesting...
The Chairman of the Company,
Zhao Fangxu, wants to see me.
You don't need to worry about this.
How's the Furnace?
I've got experience now,
so it'll be quick.
It's just...
Come with me.
Back when you founded Biyou Village,
wasn't it to gather Outcasts who could
provide samples for the Furnace?
I'm not opposed to what you're doing.
It's just that you've
never been careful enough.
Remember the 12 Shanggenqi Mutants?
In the end, the Company still
found out about them, right?
These 15 people cover various
types of Outcast powers.
They should be sufficient for your needs.
No one knows about their connection to us,
so they won't raise any suspicions.
I always felt that if you
had been the one, Sister,
maybe the perfect Furnace would
have been built long ago.
Forget it.
I can't master ordinary techniques,
let alone Divine Craftsmanship.
All I can do is fully support you.
Xianhong, trust me.
As long as you can build the
perfect Cultivation Furnace,
you'll definitely recover
your fragmented memories.
Let's not speculate about Baobao's
relationship with Wu Gensheng for now.
As things stand,
it seems the person behind the scenes
knows far more about Baobao than we do.
If we find them, then
everything will be clear.
It's not that simple.
If they had to go through all this trouble
just to convey a bit of information,
then they must have some reservations.
Reservations?
Reservations about what?
I don't know.
Baobao, seeing this painting really
doesn't jog any memories at all?
Nope!
I don't care what their reservations are,
but the existence of such a person
makes me extremely nervous!
Me too.
So there's something else
we need to talk about.
Do you know Zhang Lingyu?
Ah, Chairman Zhao mentioned him to us.
He wants you to recruit
him into the Company.
What? Let Zhang Lingyu
work alongside Baobao?
No way! Absolutely not!
Why should we put an outsider
like Zhang Lingyu next to Baobao?
San, I've discussed this
with Bao'er, and she agreed.
What do you mean "she agreed"?
Does she have the judgment to decide this?
Baobao, do you know how dangerous this is?
Zhang Chulan said it'd be fine.
The longer Zhang Lingyu spends with me,
the less likely he is to harm me.
And what if something does happen?
Zhang Chulan, are you treating
Baobao's safety as a joke?
San, I've thought about this.
Baobao needs strength around her
and time to prepare for any eventuality!
Si and I are the strength behind Baobao!
That's not enough.
Still no!
Zhang Lingyu is worth the risk.
Why do we have to take the risk...?
That's enough, San.
Calm down.
Why do we have to take risks?
Because the situation is already dire!
Our biggest advantage has
always been staying hidden.
No one knows what we're doing,
or what our goal is.
But now this painting has exposed us.
Hiding carefully is
meaningless at this point.
At this point,
what's wrong with taking a risk
to develop a potential "ally"?
San, if it weren't for Father's request,
would you still protect Baobao?
Of course!
Why?
Wh-Why?
It's because that's the
kind of people we are.
Are all the good people
in the world in our family?
Are you sure Zhang Lingyu
isn't that kind of person?
There could be other candidates.
I'm still concerned about that
hand reaching out to Bao'er.
San, Si, do you know what
happened with the Lyu Clan?
Lyu Clan?
They're a really troublesome clan.
What about the Lyu Clan?
Come to think of it, it is strange.
A group of them did come out,
but they all quickly went
back to their village.
Father, Lyu Liang still isn't talking.
What do you think?
What he did was preposterous,
but he's still got backbone.
As expected of a member of the Lyu Clan.
Of all the Outcast clans
that I've come across,
the Lyu Clan is the most perverse.
They have an abnormal
obsession with bloodline.
It's understandable, though, given their
ability to manipulate others' minds.
It's an exceptionally isolated village,
where your status is
determined by your powers.
The Lyu Clan passes down two skills:
the acquired Ruyi Jin,
and the innate Bright Soul Skill.
Those who can't cultivate qi
manage the clan's businesses,
but they have absolutely
no say in clan matters.
Even if a clan member without
powers leaves the village,
they can't cut ties with the clan.
All their actions are monitored by
the village, especially marriage.
It's quite inhumane, isn't it?
I don't know if any Lyu
Clan members ever rebelled.
Most people in the village
have the Lyu surname.
As for the few outsiders, they're all men.
The Lyu Clan only accepts son-in-law.
They treat these sons-in-law
well materially,
but their status is probably
the lowest in the village.
Ruyi Jin is only passed to males
and not females.
By controlling these sons-in-law,
they ensure all awakened users of the
Bright Soul Skill have the Lyu surname.
Through these methods, they maintain
control over their Outcast powers,
standing above others.
The one who now controls the entire clan
is the current clan leader, Lyu Chi.
Bro, you're amazing, seriously amazing!
You're getting better and better!
I'll never catch up to your
Ruyi Jin in this lifetime.
What use is that?
How can I compare to you?
You win by default.
Hey, don't be like that!
With innate talent, who
knows when it might awaken!
Cut the crap. Anyway, I've never
heard of anyone awakening after 30.
Fine, so what?
Does that mean you're doomed?
Look, beneath Great-Grandfather,
Chi
Zhong - Xiao - Ping - Yi
there's Grandfather Zhong,
Second Great-Uncle Xiao,
Third Great-Aunt Ping,
and Fourth Great-Uncle Yi.
Grandfather and Third Great-Aunt awakened.
Second and Fourth Great-Uncle didn't.
But Second Great-Uncle's Ruyi Jin was
passed down from Great-Grandfather.
Fourth Great-Uncle simply wasn't
cut out for cultivating qi.
Great-Grandfather never favored him.
So back then, it's said that the one
who truly won Great-Grandfather's favor
was Grandfather, who had both
Ruyi Jin and Bright Soul Skill!
But by the third generation, the uncles'
generation, things got awkward.
The entire generation produced quite
a few promising qi cultivators,
but very few awakened!
And their level was nowhere near
Grandfather and Third Great-Aunt.
But you have to admit, when it
comes to acquired cultivation,
there's hardly anyone in the clan
that Great-Grandfather acknowledges.
Even including our own father, would he
really give these uncles a second glance?
But who would have thought,
in our generation,
so many would awaken Bright Soul Skill!
Children from many families have awakened,
and their levels aren't bad.
Naturally, Great-Grandfather is happy.
But if we're talking about the
strongest in this generation,
it has to be the children of
Second Great-Uncle's son and daughter,
the children of Uncle Ping and Aunt Feng.
Uncle Ping had two children,
the brothers Lyu Gong and Lyu Liang.
But the most extraordinary one
has to be Aunt Feng's daughter, Lyu Huan.
She was the strongest user of
Bright Soul Skill in the entire clan,
and her talent for acquired
cultivation was also extremely high.
Great-Grandfather even made an
exception and taught her Ruyi Jin!
Just like that, the previously
unremarkable Second Great-Uncle,
along with his entire branch,
saw their status skyrocket!
Uncle Ping! Who's he? He's simply not
cut out for cultivating qi at all!
But now, even he can say a few words
in front of Great-Grandfather.
Second Great-Uncle became highest-ranked
in the clan after Great-Grandfather!
But now?
Everything has changed!
The killer is Lyu Liang,
and he's completely finished.
As his biological brother, Lyu Gong can't
hold his head up in the clan either.
Second Great-Uncle has no other
outstanding descendants left.
Among the younger generation,
who can still compete with us,
the descendants of Grandfather?
So you see, now we just need to sit
back and laugh at Second Great-Uncle.
We're all brothers.
Why create conflict between us?
But tell me, do you really think
Lyu Liang accidentally killed Huan?
He's never admitted it.
If I were him, I'd have confessed long
ago with this kind of interrogation!
I was also asked to interrogate
that Lyu Liang kid once.
His memories were all
jumbled up. Weird, right?
He actually used his power on himself!
U-Used it on himself?
Yeah, you can do all sorts of things
with Bright Soul Skill.
It's not just about testing or peeking
into other people's memories.
Lyu Liang has already reached a
level beyond my understanding.
And Lyu Huan is said to
be far above Lyu Liang.
Stop thinking about it.
Lyu Liang killed Lyu Huan.
It was him!
Eat.
Are you playing dead or what? Eat!
You think just because you act
tough, I'll respect you, right?
You think you're safe just
because you can take a beating?
You think that by denying it,
this matter will just go away?
Say something!
Father! Grandfather!
Because of you, they can't hold their
heads up in the village anymore!
It can't get any worse!
The only way you can atone
for your sins now
is to tell everyone exactly
what happened that day!
At least let the clan know
how Huan really died!
Haven't I already told you all...
about what happened that day?
I told you.
I told you from the very beginning.
You're also one of the awakened ones.
You should at least be able
to tell if I'm lying, right?
You copied my memories, didn't you?
So... this is what's kept
you going all this time.
After Lyu Huan died, you became the
strongest user of Bright Soul Skill.
You know very well that when it comes to
thoroughly examining someone's memories,
apart from you, only I can do it,
and barely at that.
But I have no idea how long it would take.
Then at least you can
confirm my current state!
I've been sealed now, so I can't use
Bright Soul Skill to resist you!
Come on! See if I'm lying!
Come on!
Huan once said to me...
Huan! Isn't your brother
Lyu Gong a handsome guy?
Yes.
Hey, it's the truth!
And you said you could lie to me!
Not only is my brother
Lyu Gong a handsome guy,
he also has three heads,
six hands, eight feet,
twelve noses, twenty eyes, thirty...
Hey, wait!
What's going on?
How... How did you do that?
From your perspective just now,
there wasn't any sign of lying.
And I couldn't feel you using
Bright Soul Skill to resist me either.
I didn't resist, and I didn't lie to you.
From my perspective, everything
I just said was the truth.
How can that be?
You know what, Brother, I'm starting
to realize that extracting memories
and detecting lies through
mental fluctuations
are just the basics of what
Bright Soul Skill can do.
These blue hands are getting
stronger and more agile.
Previously unreachable places within the
mind can now be easily touched.
Recently, I've even found
a way to modify emotions.
TRUTH
Just now, while I was lying,
LIE
I adjusted my mind to a
state of truthfulness.
I call this "passive emotion."
You... can do something like that?
That's amazing!
No, this isn't enough.
Passively giving emotions
isn't perfect yet.
This basically means I deceived myself
when the situation required it.
Once the situation requiring
a lie disappears,
the lie is still a lie.
If I could find this place,
if I could even manipulate
people's perceptions,
TRUTH
then I could create reality
within subjective consciousness.
That would be the most perfect deception.
Creating real perceptions within
someone's consciousness.
So this is what's been bothering
you these past few days?
Don't worry! You'll definitely
be able to do it!
No one in the village is
more capable than you!
Ah... it's not about that.
Huh? Then what is it?
Brother, if I really did it,
wouldn't you find me terrifying?
How should I put it...
I can't quite explain it.
I really want to understand
how that would work,
but I'm a bit afraid.
What's there to agonize over?
It's not like I can do it.
If I could, I'd be laughing in my sleep!
You're worried that you'd use
such incredible power for evil?
Impossible!
If it were that idiot
Lyu Liang, I'd worry.
But you're Huan!
Powers are just powers.
Powers don't change who you are!
Really? Am I overthinking it?
Lyu Liang, purely in terms
of ability, I admire you.
Truly, I admire you.
You've also been able to reach this level,
the ability to modify your perception.
Have you gone mad, Lyu Gong?
Is there anything else in your
head besides Bright Soul Skill?
I'm a person, not a machine that
solves everything with powers!
What do you want from me
to make you believe me?!
Great-Grandfather.
Leave.
Great-Uncle, Grandfather,
Third Great-Aunt...
Has Great-Grandfather already decided...
how to deal with Lyu Liang?
Great-Grandfather, you...
Agree to my three conditions,
and you can leave.