Don't retreat!
Protect the villagers!
Beyond Journey's End
Episode 34: A Demon-Slaying Request
30 years after the death of Himmel the Hero,
in the Rufen region, located on the Northern Plateau
Please.
I have a son. He's still a child.
Silence.
I've heard those words
more times than I can count.
So, where is this son of yours?
At least try telling half-truths.
I received a demon-slaying request
directly from Ms. Serie.
I didn't know what I'd find,
but it seems to be my hometown
in ruins after a demon attack.
I bear no attachment to this place,
but it's still sad seeing it like this.
Is that you, Genau?
Yes.
Genau. Demons destroyed the village...
I know. I've already taken care of them.
I killed them all.
What about the others?
They're safe. All of them.
You'll be okay, too.
A newly qualified
first-class mage came with me.
She's a mage, but she can
use the Goddess's magic.
Unusual, right?
She'll heal your wounds right away.
You'll be able to reopen your shop soon.
Have you finally learned
to bake decent bread?
I've only been able to eat
cold, hard bread recently.
I'd love to have something freshly baked.
In truth, it doesn't
even have to be fresh.
I'd gladly take unsold leftovers
or loaves like your old failures.
I'm not picky.
Mr. Genau.
Bring the injured over here.
"Injured"? You don't need
to spare my feelings, Methode.
He's already dead.
He was beyond saving
when I found him.
The stench is dreadful, isn't it?
His stomach wound was
already starting to rot.
Someone like that can't be saved.
But he still clung to me.
He was a baker's son.
We often played together as children.
He took over the shop
after his father passed,
but his bread wasn't very good.
I won't get to eat it anymore.
Everyone's together now,
so he won't be lonely.
Why does it have to be them
instead of us?
Unlike us, the people of this village
didn't choose to fight.
If anyone has to die,
it should be the first-class mages
like us who chose this path.
Mr. Genau.
By the time the request from
the Chivalric Order of Norm
stationed here reached
the northern branch,
this village had already been destroyed.
You're not responsible for what happened.
I'm going to look around
the village again.
Perhaps you should rest a bit.
Why?
Why? Because...
Quiet.
One of my eyes was just put out.
One warrior and one hidden mage—
no, two mages?
Two.
They're quite skilled.
Do you think they're enemies?
No, they're probably...
Oh, it's you, Frieren.
Which means the other one I detected
was Fern the first-class mage.
Who do we have here?
Methode, and one of the proctors
from the first-class mage exam...
Genau, right?
Honestly, there was so much bloodlust in
that spell, I thought you were a demon.
Was there? My apologies for the confusion.
She's right. I was worried to death.
Fern, it's okay. They're on our side.
Let Stark know.
Okay.
I see.
So Ms. Fern also received
a demon-slaying request.
We were on the Northern Plateau anyway.
So, what's the situation?
Are you praying?
Is that a problem?
No, I don't think so.
My village was destroyed by demons, too.
I see.
Hey.
Demons eat humans, right?
So why are the bodies still here?
It was the same at my village.
Who knows? Not me, at least.
They kill humans even when they're full.
I wonder why.
I see. The two of you defeated
the demons in the village.
We were a bit too late.
We even hurried here.
There's still one loose end
that Mr. Genau wishes to tie up.
These are what remains of the Chivalric
Order of Norm that was stationed here.
The Chivalric Order of Norm?
We saw them in Norm Company
territory, remember?
They're the trading company's
military force.
There are so few of them.
This is the standard amount
to station in a village this size.
Even then, they were far better
soldiers than the village deserved.
This was their captain.
He was a great man who defended
the village for years.
I'm surprised.
He was far stronger than Stark.
That's not a high bar to clear.
What was the cause of death?
An autopsy spell revealed
that they were killed by blades.
They all died instantly.
The demons in the village were weaklings
who'd have stood no chance against them.
The one who attacked the village
is probably still alive.
Good news. You didn't come here in vain.
I see. Looks like there's still
something we can do to help.
Let's show it how terrifying
humanity can be.
Like this, this, this...
and then this, perhaps?
Those are pretty unrealistic movements.
But based on the knights' wounds...
Maybe...
it fought with two swords.
In that case...
Typically, demons only conceal
their mana for short periods of time,
so we can assume it's currently
outside mana detection range.
So the immediate area
around this village is safe.
Genau told me where demons are likely
to establish bases around here,
so we'll focus our search there.
Okay.
But first, we should have dinner.
You can't fight on an empty stomach.
This bread again?
We'll just have to be patient until the
logistics network is reestablished.
Where is Genau?
Still at the church, I believe.
I'll bring his share of the bread to him.
Actually, could you tell me
your analysis of the enemy?
I'd like to know their composition first.
I'll deliver the bread, then.
Thank you.
So, what's your analysis?
It will take some more time to accurately
determine their composition,
but there's something I know already.
I see. Then let's hold a strategy...
Actually, maybe we should eat first.
What? Are we heading out already?
No. It's time for dinner.
It's hard.
Sure is. What were you doing?
The demon attack destroyed
the church's barrier.
I replaced it with a stronger one.
The villagers' bodies
are inside, after all.
Hey, why are you just leaving them there?
I'll help you bury them.
I'm good at manual labor.
I see.
I suppose someone not from the
Northern Plateau wouldn't understand.
In general, villages on the Northern
Plateau don't have graveyards.
If they do, they're tucked into
corners of sturdy fortress cities,
or they're nobles' graves
protected by barriers.
Everyone else is buried
in common graveyards
at the Plateau's southern edge,
where there are fewer monsters.
They go to the trouble
of transporting them there
with a Chivalric Order of Norm escort.
Do you know why?
No.
Because if they're not careful,
the smell of decay attracts monsters.
It's a hellish sight.
Not even the bones are left behind.
For a while now, the Norm Company has
been insisting people cremate their dead.
It's the kind of rational thinking
you'd expect from merchants.
I agree with them.
But the clergy have voiced
their opposition.
I understand how they feel. Painfully so.
It's inhumane to suggest burning people
who already suffered painful deaths.
But it's something we'll
eventually have to accept.
Soon enough, no one will be able
to rest in their homeland either way.
This really isn't how
eating bread should sound.
It feels somehow strange
to be sharing a meal like this.
Honestly, I never expected us
to meet again here.
Neither did we.
We received the demon-slaying request
while we were camping on the
other side of the mountains.
It really took me by surprise.
Who's this little guy?
He's holding a letter.
What are you and Genau doing here?
I find it hard to believe two other first-
class mages just happened to be nearby.
Ms. Serie instructed me
to come to the Northern Plateau
and slay demons with Mr. Genau.
So I'm here on her orders.
I didn't know first-class mages
had those kinds of obligations.
I'm glad I didn't become one.
It's actually something
I'm doing as her student.
Her student?
Yes. Typically, first-class mages
become Ms. Serie's students.
Come to think of it,
I heard something about that.
I turned her down.
You're a good girl, Fern.
So that's why the two of you gave in
to Serie's unreasonable demands.
She must be running you ragged.
I wouldn't say that.
If anything, I only wish
I could be more useful to her.
She's so small and cute, you know?
Is she?
Of course, you're just
as cute, Ms. Frieren.
Thanks...
And Mr. Genau has been a perfect
example of how not to behave.
Don't end up like me.
Well, now that we've eaten,
let's hold that strategy meeting.
How's the analysis of
the enemy coming along?
Well...
Have you learned anything?
Yeah. She's still figuring out
exactly how many there are,
but we did learn one thing.
Didn't you say the enemy
fought with two swords?
Actually...
That was our initial theory,
but it didn't quite add up.
What do you mean?
As far as I know,
most dual-wielding styles
emphasize a balance between
attacking and defending.
Typically, one blade is a longsword
for inflicting fatal blows,
while the other is a more
maneuverable shortsword.
In other words, there should naturally
be a difference in the cuts inflicted.
Could it be an incredibly strong demon
who wields two large swords?
We did consider that assumption
and attempted to recreate the
same cuts based on the marks
left on the dead and the
field of battle, but...
A dual-wielding style still resulted
in unrealistic movements.
What comes next is still
only speculation, but...
Just tell us.
Oh, sorry.
Excuse me.
The enemy wields...
four blades.
I see.
Apparently, it was the natural
conclusion based on the cut marks
on the knights' bodies
and surrounding buildings.
Four blades...
Translation
Sho Stifler
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Edgar Cruz
Quality Check
Alicia Ashby
Translation Check
Elizabeth Ellis
He's better than me.
We can handle that many.
You can't run away, though.
You'd be abandoning the village.
Shall we begin?
You seem to know who I am.
She should be fun.
It's likely that it has
a far-from-human appearance.
One of them was a demon general.
Episode 35
The Divine Revolte
The Divine Revolte.