You...
It hurts...
Damn it!
Again with this?!
Levy, it's him!
He's the strongest!
Run!
SCUM OF THE BRAVE
DEATH OF A BRAVE
Hey! Let me go!
Enough!
I-It's not what you think! I just...
Don't make this harder. Get going.
I said go, damn it!
Of course they followed us.
They might be close still.
I'll find them.
That one has an ether perception
that lets her track targets.
That badge...
Where's that mark from?
A dragon?
She's actually trying to kill me!
Come on, let's call this off.
You don't wanna deal with
security guards, right?
Considering where we are.
You respond quickly.
Enhancement powers, I take it?
Well, I'd say...
Now the tables are turned.
The difference is...
I won't be negotiating.
Seriously?
Is this kid actually insane?
Master!
Your beautiful apprentice
has come to your rescue!
Perhaps you could look more pleased?!
I told you to run, damn it.
Where's Indo?
Not to worry!
She should have safely escaped by now.
Not what I meant!
If you guys weren't gonna listen,
the useful one could've
come back at least.
Maybe you should've
read my mind to figure it out!
Well, I've got a teenaged hindrance now,
and that woman is physically
stronger than me at the moment.
If I had a sword, I'd just
lop her hands off.
But with these toys?
Maybe if I knew what her ether
perception was tracking...
It's scent, Master.
She appears to track scents.
Or more like, she has a remarkable
ability to distinguish smells.
Think of a well-polished mirror...
No, more like, the way watercolor paint
would look on damp, sandy ground.
Jogamine.
Good work!
I'll kill you later.
R-Right!
It would be an honor!
It seems my wordplay
has yielded unexpected—
I didn't say all that.
And when you try to explain something,
keep it as short as possible.
You talk too damn much.
It's a special occasion,
so let me show you what
a super move looks like.
When you've got two swords clashing,
and they're bound up together,
pushing or pulling at the wrong
time can cost you your life.
You shift offense and defense quickly.
In other words...
It's right up my alley.
B-Brilliantly done, Master!
I busted her nose,
which she used to track us.
But seriously, who are these people?
Because I'm pretty sure
they're not security guards.
Should I kill them?
Getting rid of the bodies
would be a pain, but...
Master!
Oh, I wouldn't if I were you.
If the two of us fight,
I think one will have to die.
You're pretty strong.
I get that a lot.
So, what's her deal?
I'm pretty sure you're
not after me, right?
Are you two just wild dogs?
Sorry, sorry.
I think your group getting the
drop on us must've irked her.
She's a proud soul.
I guess. And you?
Hardly.
Why don't we both avoid further trouble?
I'm going to pretend
I didn't see anything.
If you recant your actions,
then we shall forgive you!
But never attempt to trespass again!
Master and I will catch you every time!
Well, thanks for the lecture.
What do you think, "Master"?
– Let's go.
– Yes, sir!
Bye!
My own master...
He called that move the "Draw."
When you're bound up,
you push just for a second.
The other person will
push back instinctively.
Which is when you pull back,
and their stance collapses.
And if the other person pulls back—
Since the bind is undone,
you take that opportunity to strike.
And it's not as easy as it sounds.
It takes practice, and experience.
Master!
Should I interpret your explanation as
an exclusive lesson for yours truly?
Don't make me laugh, stupid.
What the hell made you so goofy, anyway?
An E3 overdose?
No, sir. It's...
It's the same as you.
My father would, from time
to time, tell me about you.
I was so moved that night
I encountered you,
I'm not sure how to describe it.
You're gonna wanna hit the hospital.
See ya.
At first, I was shocked by the contrast.
"Really? This failure of a person who
looks like a petty thug?" I thought.
But the deeper I read your thoughts...
Hang on.
Your dad...
What was his name?
Takamiya Kiyohito, sir.
That is to say, your master, Master!
Did you not realize?
I would have thought Ishino-san told you.
When my parents divorced,
my mother got custody,
and I was only able to see
my father once a month.
When I did see him, he would describe
how wonderful being a Brave was.
Master said that?
That being a Brave is wonderful?
I look up to my father, Master.
But why did you decide
to become a Brave?
Seven years ago...
I had to drop out of high school
for personal reasons,
and I got kicked out by my parents.
I ended up running errands for some
two-bit Dark Lord in Ikebukuro.
Some neophyte Dark Lords were warring over
the west half of the Yamanote Line.
The perfect hunting grounds for Braves.
And who waltzed in
to render me unemployed?
"Nine Fingers" Takamiya Kiyohito.
With my boss dead,
I didn't know what to do.
With no other options, I sort of forced
my way into becoming his assistant,
under the premise of
being his "apprentice."
I believe my father understood what
life was like for the less fortunate.
That's why he had such lofty ideals.
He had the will to pursue
the greater good,
even as his work would sometimes
force him to do questionable things.
He spoke of his apprentice—of your
exploits—very happily, Master.
That you had incredible talent,
and a promising future as a Brave.
The battle against the Radiant Snake
Count, the battle of Shinjuku 6-17...
Something's not adding up here.
This sounds nothing like
the Master I know.
He was a cowardly guy, weak-willed, and
always seemed to be afraid of something,
which led him to be cautious,
cold-blooded, and even ruthless.
"Being a Brave is a job for
the lowest kind of scum."
He used to say that all the time.
That it wasn't a job you
should work for a long time.
That you're better off moving to
Hawaii and becoming a fisherman
once you've saved up enough money.
I think this gig is shit, too.
And it's been years since he died...
I think he must've been lying to you.
The ideal Brave is someone who
is good at, and enjoys, killing.
But you helped us, Master.
What you're saying seems at
odds with your own beliefs.
You think so?
But it's what your old man taught me.
No, Master, you—
Go home.
My head hurts.
Must be the E3...
No, it's because of Jogamine.
I should get over to Ed's, quick.
Beer...
Pizza...
Card games.
Where all the best things
in the world wait for me.
SCUM OF THE BRAVE
What kept you?
Seriously, what was the holdup?
I was eating a hamburger.
Quit lying.
It's true.
Where's Ed, the owner?
Said he was gonna get something
to eat and left all of a sudden.
With some guy named Malta.
How the hell does this
place stay in business?
You could've just gone home, y'know.
It's late.
What're you, a delinquent?
I was worried, considering how I left you.
I wanted to make sure you were okay.
You...
are incredibly normal.
Are you making fun of me?!
Nah, it's a compliment.
I'm trying to say you have
a normal set of values.
In other words, you're
a good, considerate person.
Shut up.
Your ether perception lets you
detect where enemies are...
Or, more specifically,
how strong they are.
Not visually, or with a numerical rating.
It's more intuitive...
like a sixth sense, right?
That's right.
Someone's strength...
My dad described it as being able
to sense their "threat level."
It feels like heat, or maybe pressure...
Dangerous, in any case.
Well, considering you didn't seem fazed
by that monster from the other day,
but you freaked out
over that tiny woman,
there's no other explanation.
You're right. I did chicken out.
You probably think I'm not
cut out to be a Brave, right?
Yep.
You're a good person, so you
should quit being a Brave.
What do you know? Damn.
My master once told me...
there's nothing wrong with
being afraid of an opponent.
The issue is controlling your
fear before it kills you.
The only way to get used to
it is through experience.
People like Jogamine are
the exception, truly.
That girl...
I mean, I gotta ask...
What the hell is her deal?
She sure doesn't seem like a mind reader!
I'm amazed you put up with her.
Well, Aki apparently
doesn't read our minds.
She usually mentions if she uses
her power to read someone's mind.
When she meets someone new,
it's hard to tune them out.
So she hears them
unintentionally at first.
I don't think she's reading your mind,
either, unless she needs to.
Did something happen?
Not really.
I've only teamed up with
her since the exercise.
I don't know her that well...
But she seems nice.
You call someone "nice" when you don't
have anything nice to say about them.
I'll admit, she's definitely weird.
She's always butting into
other people's business,
and she shows up to help even
when she has nothing to offer.
But the fact that she does all
this stuff out of stubbornness...
I kind of like that about her.
Jogamine, I mean.
Well, I sure don't.
Since you're a good person, you tell her!
That kind of...
Hey, Joe.
Ed Cyrus isn't around.
I thought you had work?
– Did you botch the job already?
– Shut up.
Oh, I know.
Malta of all people apparently came by.
Seems like he and Ed went out.
You think we should grab some
food while they're gone?
Joe?
Look, Yashiro, what are you gonna do?
Do about what?
I saw tonight's news.
Then I asked someone
who knows what's what.
This morning, a dippy-looking corpse was
found in a back alley over in Shin-Okubo.
And it was...
You'll probably laugh.
When I saw the picture...
He was stabbed all over, with the
finishing blow right across the throat.
You should've seen the hole in his neck.
Dude could come back as a ghost,
but he wouldn't be able to talk.
I see. That's...
Then there's this.
The body was holding on to it, apparently.
Pretty wild, right?
When are we gonna throw
the mourning party?
Well, I'd say after we
take care of business.
What is it? What happened?
You two look miserable.
You're imagining things.
TRANSLATION: LEE FRANCIS
TIMING: HENRY LIN
EDITING: GABRIELLA ALABANZA
QUALITY CONTROL: RILEY DALTON
FINAL QUALITY CONTROL: SHO STIFLER
NEXT TIME
– We're gonna find whoever got Ishino
and put them through
suffering worse than hell.
That's the only thing that
scum like us can really do.
NEXT TIME
A BRAVE'S SINS