Shall we go, then?
Beyond Journey's End
It's unusually warm today.
Yeah, but...
we sure could use some cold, hard cash.
We'll have to look for work
in the next town.
You're already thinking about that, Fern?
It's important.
Mr. Stark,
unless we think two steps ahead,
our journey will come to a premature end.
I suppose that's true.
Work, huh?
I hope we can find something suitable.
Huh?
This feels familiar.
Thank you for the ride.
Don't mention it. It was most reassuring
to have a first-class mage along.
Anyway, you're headed to Ende?
To those of us who never
travel far from home,
that sounds like an
unimaginably long journey.
Maybe it is.
Beyond Journey's End
29 years after the death of Himmel the Hero,
in the Saum Marshes, located in the northern lands
I caught a fish.
I'll add it to our breakfast.
I'll catch a big one next time.
That's odd. It should be around here.
Frieren's not usually up this early.
Apparently she woke up because
she was curious about something.
Huh.
Did you praise her?
Of course.
Found it.
Now this is a big one.
That's a pretty stone. What is it?
Here.
Huh?
I can't conjure fire.
It's called a magic-nullifying crystal.
It's a mineral that neutralizes
magical effects.
A crystal of this purity has an
effective radius of three meters.
Stark, try stepping away a bit.
Huh? Okay.
There it goes.
They're extremely rare.
Even a pebble-sized crystal
is worth several gold pieces.
You could buy a mansion
with one this large.
Wow.
But if it stops us from using magic,
we can't bring it with us.
It'd endanger us on our journey.
That's the problem.
Get rid of that stone right away.
If a monster attacked us right now,
we'd be wiped out.
Before that, I want to show you
an unusual property of this stone.
It's really interesting.
When you imbue these stones
with lots of mana...
they glow really brightly.
It's blinding.
Please just throw it away already.
It's still glowing.
We'll probably reach
the next village today.
By the way, are we near
the Northern Plateau?
That's still a ways away.
It's beyond a vast forest
and volcanic area.
A volcanic area, huh? Sounds dangerous.
It really isn't.
There hasn't been an
eruption in centuries.
These days, it's a relatively safe
hot spring region.
Hot springs?
A warm bath sounds pretty appealing.
It sure has been a while.
Huh? Hold on.
The ground here...
I knew it. It's an underground cave.
I hate how unstable the
ground is in marshland.
Huh? Ms. Frieren...
Oh...
We might be in trouble.
Huh? What?!
No wonder we found that
magic-nullifying crystal on the surface.
I've never seen a deposit
this large before.
Please get off.
Almost the entire cave is filled
with magic-nullifying crystals.
If we brought it all back with us,
we'd be billionaires.
I doubt that's possible.
Huh?
Magic-nullifying crystal is one of
the hardest materials in existence.
And unlike other materials, it can't
be cut or processed using magic.
Some things are simply
out of humanity's reach.
In any case, we're not
climbing our way out of here.
Let's look for another exit.
What is it?
We're counting on you, Stark.
Since we can't use magic,
we're just ordinary girls in here.
Girls?
I haven't forgotten that you
called me an old hag, Stark.
Sorry about that.
You still haven't let that go?
I never thought we'd end up
camping in a place like this.
This cave complex is unbelievably vast.
We found lots of animal bones, too.
Ms. Frieren said this might be
the den of a large monster.
I'm amazed she can sleep so soundly.
She sure is carefree.
Ms. Frieren still seems to be
having fun, even here.
But it scares me too much.
I can't even detect mana.
I've never experienced
anything like this.
It's like I've been plunged
into total darkness.
Fern...
A monster!
Frieren, wake up! Run—
It's a venomous apex dragon.
Venomous?
It's a bad matchup for you.
You'll die from poison again.
I didn't die the first time!
But what are we supposed to do, then?
I can't believe you were sleeping
so comfortably, either.
How can you be so—
I trust you with my life.
I have ever since I recruited you
to be our front-liner.
Parties don't function otherwise.
I'm a man who flees
during critical moments.
I'm desperate to run away right now.
Are you?
Shall we run away together, then?
Stark, Fern.
Close your eyes.
Himmel, how can you
trust me with your life?
That's not something you
should say so readily.
I abandoned my village and fled.
Is that right?
Then if you feel like running,
let's run away together.
After all, we're a party.
Shall we run, then?
I'm a priest! Why do I have
to carry the heavy one?
Because the light one
says you stink of liquor!
That was scary.
But running away together
isn't so bad, is it?
Yeah.
Shall we go, then?
Frieren.
What?
My legs gave out. I can't walk.
Episode 29: Shall We Go, Then?
29 years after the death of Himmel the Hero,
in the Great Sanft Forest, located in the northern lands
Is this enough for lunch?
Huh? They're not here.
Maybe I came back too early.
Okay, I'll go fishing.
I'll catch a big one today.
So cold...
It's just until we reach the hot springs.
Good. It's clean now.
Didn't Stark give you that
mirrored-lotus bracelet?
The hairpin you gave me
is also clean now.
You keep your staff in good shape, too.
You seem to really enjoy maintaining
your equipment, Fern.
Do I?
You're smiling right now.
Maybe it's because they were gifts.
I lost everything, including
my home, to war.
Perhaps I'm glad to gain more things
that are important to me.
It was worth the effort
picking that out for you.
You did put a lot of thought into it.
How do you know that?
Oh.
Pervert.
I'm really sorry!
I didn't know you were bathing!
I'm not mad.
Okay, all done.
Stark, I've been thinking...
What?
Are things a bit awkward right now?
They might be.
So you're starting to pick up
on stuff like this, too.
I'm kind of impressed.
This seems to happen from time to time.
Maybe you two aren't a good match.
I wouldn't say that.
Stark.
If you're uncomfortable, say so.
I'm the one who forced you
to join the party.
Listen, Frieren, I—
It's a crossroads.
The Northern Plateau is this way.
Neutral Harbor is that way.
Frieren, is that an inn?
Well, this is a major highway.
We won't have to camp out tonight.
Oh?
Well, if it isn't Frieren.
Our reunion was sooner than expected.
Stark, thanks for your help
with the Fresser.
Wirbel, you seem well.
I ended up traveling home by sea.
The demons are acting up
in the far north again.
I have to rush back.
I'm traveling with these guys
to the imperial capital.
He's been whining about how
much he hates being seasick.
Aren't you a grown man?
What are you doing?
Just so you know, I'm not that old yet.
I was still in my twenties
until just recently.
Another old man used
to say the same thing.
Anyway, Stark, have you
considered my offer?
What offer?
The situation in the far north
has gotten pretty bad.
There's a severe shortage
of front-liners.
I can't force you into it,
but I'd like your support for two or
three years until the front stabilizes.
Like I told you before, Wirbel,
I'm this party's front-liner.
I see. Well, I don't give up easily.
I'll do anything to protect the far north.
Frieren, mind if I persuade him a little?
Excuse me—
Suit yourself.
Ms. Frieren...
Cheers!
Seriously, Stark. Join our party.
He seems to be having fun.
I really can't.
Maybe Stark does find our
party a bit restrictive.
Um, Mr. Stark.
I turned down Wirbel's offer.
Are you sure you want
to do that, Mr. Stark?
Fern, why do you think I'm in this party?
When I first met you guys,
I was at the end of my rope.
I was ready to abandon
the village and run away.
I suck, right?
Frieren said she forced me to join the
party, but that's not what happened.
I don't think you'll run.
Because you encouraged me that night,
I wanted to travel with you
and joined your party.
You may not realize it,
but Frieren isn't the only one who
dragged my cowardly butt this far.
I'm not going anywhere.
So be nicer to me.
Very well.
Come here. I'll pet you.
What are you plotting?! I'm scared!
What a pain in the rear.
I couldn't convince you after all, huh?
By the way, you're not traveling by boat?
Ocean travel is expensive.
Besides...
My master's party traveled
through the Northern Plateau.
We're always accepting weird jobs,
getting caught up in trouble,
and taking detours, though.
You've got your own adventure
to follow, huh?
No matter. You'll reach the
far north eventually, right?
I'll see you then.
Shall we go, then?
Translation
Sho Stifler
Editing & Typesetting
Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing
Edgar Cruz
Quality Check
Alicia Ashby
Translation Check
Elizabeth Ellis
That seems a bit extreme.
Talk about tyrannical.
You just like taking on difficult jobs.
Straight to the point. I appreciate that.
She looks really unhappy.
I will die without achieving my goal.
Will you offer a prayer?
But we got to defeat a demon.
Episode 30
The Hero of the South
That's the Hero of the South.