JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES, PARTY OF NONE
Sophia, Logan, Caroline...
They all have pretty heavy pasts.
Especially...
EPISODE 10: THE JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES
MAKES THEM TRAIN HARD
Selma-cchi, new lieutenant,
morning!
Good morning.
Good morning...
Your desk...
...is as messy as ever.
It's cleaner than usual today.
It is?
You're scaring
the new lieutenant, Estella.
Well, I do my job right at least.
I'm Carla with the Adventure
Management Division.
Nice to meet you.
Carla's looking after the new members.
She's like their caretaker.
I see.
Nice to meet you.
I heard from Estella that you'll
be helping train Group 10.
Yes.
Did you read their files?
I did.
Only then did I make my decision.
Then there's no need
for me to say anything.
Please take care of them.
I will.
We were pretty worried about them.
I'm glad you're looking
out for them, Or-cchi.
Um... "Or-cchi?"
Oh? You don't want me calling
you that in my head?
No, it doesn't bother me, but...
So, what's the policy for training them?
None.
You're in charge of everything.
Just teach them what you've
learned from your experiences.
Teach them what they need to know.
What they need...
It's fine for him
to come up with the plan,
but you could at least give him a goal.
Yeah...
I guess it'd be nice to have them able to
handle the middle floors on
their own after six months.
That's a pretty high bar.
We do have high expectations for them.
They grew up a lot during
the teaching expedition.
Well, it's certainly possible, but...
We're counting on you, new lieutenant.
Orhun.
If you read the files...
You know about me
and Sophia already, right?
Yes. I was surprised, honestly.
Her mother was a maid in my household.
She died right after giving birth to her.
After that, my family,
the Claudels, took her in,
but as the child of a mistress,
she had no real place in the household.
Life was hard for her at a young age.
I did everything I could for her, but...
Things got even worse
for her after you left.
Yes.
When I came home for the
first time after leaving...
I asked her...
"Why don't you come with me?"
And that's why I want Sophia
to become a great adventurer.
Maybe you think it's wrong to give
her special treatment, but...
It's only natural to feel the way you do.
I'll do everything I can.
I'm glad to hear that.
Take care of my sister, Orhun.
Yeah. Got it.
Mister!
Orhun!
Hello.
Hey...
I kept you all waiting, huh?
Do you know why I'm here?
Yes. You're taking us on
as students, right?
This is officially part
of my work at the clan...
But I suppose you're right.
Yay!
I'm so happy you'll be teaching us again.
You know all kinds of stuff
and you're super-strong!
No, I've still got a lot
to do to get stronger.
That's not true!
You totally beat up that Black Dragon!
Totally beat it up, huh?
From my perspective, it was a close thing.
Thank you.
But someday, you'll have to fight
the Black Dragon yourselves.
If you're going to try and
clear the Great Dungeon.
We'll have to fight the Black Dragon...?
I know it would be hard for you right now,
but I think you could do it someday.
You've all got a lot of potential.
With hard work, you can
become great adventurers.
I'll do my best!
Me too, of course!
Th-Thank you for teaching us!
There're two important things I
want to talk about at the start.
First,
you need to be thinking at all times.
There're lots of different
ways to solve any problem.
Don't just stick to the
standard script. Be flexible.
And secondly...
Don't think what I'm saying
is always right.
Don't think you're always right?
What does that mean?
I don't know everything.
I've made lots of mistakes and
messed up a lot of things.
Don't think that just because I'm your
teacher, I'm automatically right.
Don't just automatically do what I say.
Think about it and make it part of
your own knowledge and experiences.
If you're not sure, you can always ask.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
All right, before we begin,
I want to hear why you decided
to become adventurers.
Let's start with Sophia.
O-Okay!
I want to be like my sister,
Selma Claudel.
I want to decide for myself
what it is I want to do...
Like her...
She really looks up to
Selma as a sister, huh?
But I haven't really
decided what I want to do.
That's why I became an adventurer,
so I could find my own goals and dreams.
I think that's great.
I'll help too.
So let's search for your dream together.
Th-Thank you, sir!
Was I showing off a little too much?
Now it's your turn, Logan.
Okay!
The reason I want to be an adventurer
is that you can make a lot of money.
I've never heard that before.
It's fine. Keep going.
The village I grew up in doesn't
have good soil for growing.
There's barely enough food
to eat each day.
But the villagers said it
wasn't right for me to stay.
They gathered up all the money
they had and sent me here.
So I want to become a successful
adventurer and pay them back.
That's my goal.
I see. That's a wonderful reason.
To be honest, I thought I was as
strong as a high-ranked adventurer.
But when I saw how strong you were,
and how scary the
Black Dragon was, I realized...
I'm still weak.
I need more power for my goals.
So please!
Teach me everything I need
to know to be an adventurer!
All right.
I'll teach you all I know.
But it's up to you to put
in the effort to master it.
Okay, thanks!
My turn, next!
Yeah.
Why did you become
an adventurer, Caroline?
Well, I...
I guess I don't have a real reason.
I guess because I can kill monsters?
And that will make everybody happy!
Really? There's no other reason?
That's all, really!
I just want everyone to smile!
You really like people's smiles, huh?
I sure do, yeah!
'Cause smiling people don't hit me!
Everybody's smiles disappear
when monsters are around!
So I kill them!
I want everyone to be smiling...
Her darkness seems pretty deep.
You're right.
It's best that everyone smiles.
Thanks for telling me.
You're welcome!
I understand why everyone
decided to become adventurers.
I want you all to keep those
reasons in your head at all times.
Got it?
Yes, sir!
Um, do you have a dream or a goal too?
Of course.
I want to make sure that no matter
what horrible things happen,
I don't lose anything...
I want to be strong enough that I
can protect what matters to me
no matter what happens.
That was why I became an adventurer.
You can't protect anything if you're weak.
I plan on getting stronger too.
I promise you again.
I won't be treating you like children.
So I want you to give me your all.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, Caroline, do you not like
being called by a nickname?
I don't really care. Why?
The name "Caroline"
is pretty long, isn't it?
It seems hard to say in an emergency.
I see.
Then give me a wonderful name!
Me?
Yes, I want you to name me, Mister.
O-Okay...
"Carol," maybe?
Carol! I love it!
From now on, my name is Carol!
No, it's a nickname, not a name.
I want a nickname, too!
"Logan" isn't that long, right?
Please!
Okay...
"Log"?
"Log"...
The name Orhun gave me...
I'm so happy!
Is it that moving?
And I guess you could be Sophie?
Is it too obvious?
No, I really like it.
Sophie, huh?
From now on, we're Carol and Sophie, huh?
Yup!
Then can I call you "Teacher" from now on?
I don't mind... I guess.
I will too, then.
I'll keep calling you "Orhun."
That's totally fine.
Okay, let's get to work.
Right!
Okay!
That fighting style is bad news.
A Defender shouldn't be
trying to defeat an enemy.
Their job is to just draw attention
so the Attacker can finish the enemy.
And the Attacker's job
is the other way around.
But right now, she's neither.
Her fighting style has a very
high risk of getting her killed.
Carol!
That's enough, I think.
Reflective Wall.
Agility Up!
Triple!
He's fast!
Carol.
When you're fighting, you need to
keep an eye on your surroundings.
I knew he'd come from the rear.
That's why I was making sure
I was defenseless, right?
What does that mean?
I don't understand.
You could've been badly hurt there.
Why didn't you dodge?
Oh, right. I never told you, Teacher.
Wh-What are you doing?
Is this her special ability?
I don't die!
No matter how hurt I get,
I heal instantly.
And I'm used to the pain, too!
So you don't have to worry!
Caroline Inglot...
She was captured and held by
the Cyclamen Church for years.
Their goal is to revive the most powerful
and terrifying of all monsters,
the "Evil God."
They attack villages and towns,
conduct human experiments
and human trafficking.
They're one of the largest
criminal organizations.
And two years ago, one of
their bases was destroyed.
Albert from Unit 1 rescued her then.
But the Church had done
a lot of horrible things to her
because of her self-healing ability.
She was extremely
mentally unstable, at the time.
But after treatment,
she recovered, to a degree.
She became an adventurer
of her own volition.
But the death of Albert, the man
who saved her, came later...
The wounds in her heart
are too deep to imagine.
But I promised...
that I wouldn't treat them like children.
Carol, look at your comrades' faces.
Why? Why aren't they all smiling?
Because you're hurt.
But my wounds...
Yes, they'll heal quickly.
But it still hurts, doesn't it?
When you feel pain, me, Sophie,
and Log all feel pain too.
Because we care about our comrade.
So when you get hurt, we get
hurt too, and lose our smiles.
Is that okay with you?
No! No it's not!
What should I do?!
I knew it.
The scariest thing to her is
to not see people smiling.
So just don't do the things
that cause you pain.
I'll never do it again,
so smile, everyone!
Please!
Carol...
Please don't hit me!
Carol.
Don't worry.
Nobody here is going to hit you.
If anybody tried, I'd knock them out.
So it's fine.
Don't worry. It's fine.
Teacher...
Ow!
Your movements still aren't right!
They keep coming out of nowhere!
It's hard to dodge them!
Carol, you want everyone to smile, right?
Yes, of course!
So first you need to practice
protecting yourself!
No whining! Get to work!
Teacher, you meanie!
Your basics are getting better, Log.
Yes, I didn't understand why I was using
a spear instead of a sword at first.
You can keep your distance
from an enemy with a spear,
so you can do double-duty
as an Enchanter, right?
Right! Smart thinking, teacher!
Wil's better with a spear than I am.
Let's have him come teach you.
Thank you!
472, 465, 458...
Red!
Fire Arrow!
451, 444.
Blue!
A-Aqua Arrow!
I've got Sophia counting
down from 500 by sevens,
while keeping two magic circles up
and casting spells at a target
when random spells appear.
It's practice for parallel construction.
Keep counting.
S-Sorry!
If you stop moving or panic and mess up,
you'll put your comrades in danger.
R-Right!
Two at once?!
Um...
What's wrong?
I reached out my hand without
thinking and felt something strange.
Strange?
Yes.
And then the target fell over even
though I didn't cast a spell.
It feels like if I do this I can
affect the things in front of me...
Am I imagining things?
I felt the same thing once,
when my special ability appeared.
So it's a special ability?
Like yours and my sister's?
But it couldn't be...
Everyone's ability is different,
and there's a lot we don't understand.
So let's take our time and find
out what that feeling really is.
O-Okay.
445.... 437...
If she's Selma's little
sister, it's possible.
Okay, two more sets before we wrap up!
Okay!
Monster!
Orhun sure trained us hard.
Training's the one time
he seems like a monster.
Oh, if it isn't Sophia and Caroline.
Carla! Estella!
Hey there.
You two seem to have really grown up, huh?
We're cheering you on!
Yay! Thanks!
I-I'll do my best.
Growing up, huh?
But I still haven't...
What's wrong, Sophie?
You guys are all so big...
We're still growing!
You'll get bigger!
Traitor.
Hey, don't say that, Sophie!
My, my...
Forget it!
353, 346, 339...
Fire Arrow! Aqua Arrow!
They're both doing a lot better.
Looking good. You're getting better.
Thank you.
Yesterday, you defeated
the floor boss on the 20th floor,
the Orc Lord, on your own.
You've passed the first stage.
We're going to aim higher from now on.
Hooray!
Orhun!
Your sword's ready.
That's the one made from
the Black Dragon's scale?
Wow!
The way it fits in my hand perfectly...
And it's weighted just right.
This is my new sword...
What do you think?
It's perfect. I'm impressed!
I swear on this sword...
that I'll protect my comrades
no matter what!