The Samurai Code and Carnage
An additional expedition?
Indeed.
It's been two days, and
no one's returned with the Elixir.
Two days?
The next group's incredible.
Four Yamada Asaemons,
including the Shugen,
four Iwagakure ninjas,
and over 50 subordinates to serve them.
They'll be a real boon
to the first expedition.
That idiot.
What reason is there to send
this many forces for this job?
The ninja leader must have other plans.
Aoki-dono.
Does something concern you?
We'll be there to handle
any possible threats.
But can you control this many people?
Also...
Those two are unranked, aren't they?
You needn't worry.
That youngster is
Yamada Asaemon Kiyomaru.
He's unranked due to his age,
but his skills make him
one of the top two students.
Yamada Asaemon Isuzu.
Though she is a woman, she's a
powerful and magnificent fighter.
She served the shogunate
as a martial arts instructor.
They are what's known as "urayurushi."
The rules prevent them from being ranked,
but they are as strong
as any certified "okuyurushi."
We also have Jikka-dono,
who is skilled, if nothing else.
That's me. Skilled, if nothing else.
We do not intend to merely supervise.
We will do everything we can
for our fellow clan members.
I see.
If you're worried, shall I
demonstrate my skills, you old fart?
Wha—Kiyo-chan!
He underestimates us
because we're unranked.
It pisses me off.
I'm definitely stronger than him.
Still, you shouldn't do that.
In that case, I could
kill everyone here for you.
As you wish.
Huh? I struck the guy
next to him on purpose.
They really don't move. Boring.
Don't be rude to the ninjas.
Put your sword away, Kiyo-chan.
You, too, giantess.
Are these guys going to be okay?
Please.
Samurai mustn't argue
over such a trifling matter.
Don't trouble yourselves with us.
I-I'm sorry you had to see that.
Forgive us.
Not at all. A ninja's life
belongs to his master.
On this mission,
the Yamadas are our masters.
If you doubt us, select anyone here.
They will be thrown overboard
or executed to demonstrate our loyalty.
Oh, yeah?
Okay, you.
Show me a ninja's loyalty.
Very well.
The rest is up to you.
You may go in, you may enter.
Whose narrow path is this?
This is the narrow pathway
of the Tenjin shrine...
Shinobi do not have wills
or minds of their own.
Our greatest desire is
to be merely a tool.
We ask that you trust us.
E-Enough. Return to your positions.
Your resolve is powerful. I'm impressed.
I don't really get ninjas.
Join the mission and kill Gabimaru.
I didn't expect him
to be sent on that mission
before he could be
assassinated at his execution.
Surely you won't be satisfied
unless you kill him, too.
Gabimaru must be killed.
Use your lives for solely that purpose.
Are you sure we can
trust them, Shugen-san?
I haven't trusted them from the start.
Those ruffians are
no different from criminals.
We'll search for the Elixir ourselves.
Just us Asaemons.
What about the criminals on the island?
Execute every criminal you find.
I will bring back every last Asaemon.
Eizen-dono, everyone...
Please be safe.
Being a manager sure is tough, huh?
Managing all these rogues
must hinder your work.
It can't be helped.
The shogun is hoping
to complete the mission quickly.
He said we'd make good allies
for the first expedition.
You must be joking.
I mean, this ship
isn't transporting allies.
We're bringing more death and chaos.
We're the ship of dreams
bearing nightmares and disaster.
So, so many more will die.
No one will make it back alive.
An additional expedition?
Yes. It could be Shugen's group.
Eizen-san was ordered by the shogunate
to select a reserve group of Asaemons.
Shu-kun could probably lead a group
of condemned criminals, too.
Will Shugen be our ally?
Yes, surely.
He's the most skilled of the Yamadas.
His combat experience is first class, too.
That's not enough
to survive on this island.
You need to master the tricks of tao.
Not a trick!
Shugen can probably perceive tao.
When we practiced together,
he seemed aware of my sixth sense.
He's a serious man through and through.
He fervently tried to learn from me.
He's the one who named them waves.
Isuzu. Hold this.
What? How are you going to
fight that without a weapon?
You'll be eaten.
That masterwork was
a gift from the shogun.
It is my pride as an executioner.
I won't use it to hunt a boar.
Fuchi-kun taught me.
The structure and tension of muscles
can be estimated from the outside.
You can use that
to easily dissect or destroy.
Shion-dono taught me as well.
If you observe the waves, you can
estimate the structure of a life.
If he's that strong, it'll be great
to have him on our side!
Is something wrong, Sensei?
I think I know Yamada Asaemon Shugen.
He was involved
in that incident, wasn't he?
Incident? Did he cause a problem?
No, I wouldn't call it a problem.
He can be a bit too harsh.
What kind of incident?
I've only heard about it.
When the boss of the Silver Serpent clan,
a famous Edo yakuza, was captured,
he refused to give the locations of his
underlings hidden throughout the region.
He caused the officials
quite a bit of trouble.
Then Shugen-dono was summoned.
He beheaded his already
captured underlings
before his eyes to make him talk
and slaughtered all
20 members of the clan,
including the underlings they found.
The shogun was delighted,
gave him special attire and the
famous blade Fuributsu Kaneaki,
and Shugen-dono gained influence
within the shogunate as well.
So he kills all evil-doers.
Sounds like a pretty cool guy.
He's a good person at heart.
He's kind to all the students.
And he's Sagi's first love.
Oh? Tell me more.
You want to marry him?
No, I...
I was a child.
I suppose I did admire him.
Shugen-dono was the reason
I became ranked in the Yamada clan.
Please grant Sagiri a rank as well.
If you refuse to acknowledge
her marvelous skill,
then I cannot proudly bear my own rank.
He's rigid, but he's kind.
Shugen-san, are you hurt?
If you'd said something,
we would've helped.
Our orders are to supervise and execute.
You needn't dirty your blades
for anything else.
I'm your elder. Allow me
to handle such trivial matters.
Your eyes are scary
even when you're smiling.
Are they?
You sure are dependable, though.
Jikka-dono, you're older than me.
Let's hurry.
Once he learns of the situation,
he'll surely help us.
No, I don't think so.
You're a bit mistaken
about that story you told.
After all, it's not something
the Yamadas like to discuss.
What?
Shugen executed 20 yakuza
and their entire clan.
Yes, like I said, 20...
No.
Twenty Silver Serpents
and their entire clan.
Their families, their elderly parents,
even young children.
In total, over 100 of them.
H-How could you?
Yataro... He's just a baby...
Do you have to kill him, too?
It is painful but unavoidable.
If I'd executed only you, your family
would've inherited your business.
Evil is born not just from people's hearts
but the environment
in which they're raised, too.
I pray you're at least reborn
as a good person in your next life.
You're inhuman... You're inhuman...
You're inhuman...
I like him as a samurai,
and he's a friend.
But I don't think Shugen will let
a single criminal off the hook,
no matter the circumstances.
In fact, he probably wouldn't forgive any
Asaemons who protect criminals either.
That's the kind of man he is.
Especially if he learns what's
happening on this island.
So your name is Shugen.
Your parents were slain
when you were young,
and by some fate, we took you in.
Being an executioner
will be difficult for you.
You'll be faced with all kinds of crimes.
My parents' murderer
still hasn't been caught.
Perhaps I'll get to behead them someday.
I hear the Yamada Asaemons consider
a single painless and
emotionless strike ideal.
That's correct.
I don't understand.
It's better to do it poorly.
Strike multiple times to sever the head.
It's a more painful death.
What about damaging
the blade to make it jagged?
That would be pointless.
Because I'll sharpen it.
It will be difficult to erase
your hatred right away,
but through learning and teaching here,
you will learn how to face it.
If you still wish
to damage it then, you may.
I'll sharpen it again and again.
Someday your blade will have
a beautiful pattern.
I look forward to it.
Eizen-dono!
I... I still need you.
I still need you!
Shugen-san.
I know it's hard, but we must proceed.
I'm concerned about the others.
You're right.
At least let us put him to rest.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
They're a strange group.
He chants sutras at his leisure
on an island of monsters,
and the other two are strange
for going along with it.
I suppose he's just that powerful a man.
No, this man is odd as well.
I can't get a read on him at all.
I want to go home...
But this dangerous island is the perfect
place to outwit the Asaemons.
We'll look for an opportunity
to complete our mission.
This island wouldn't
be enough to kill him.
Wow, look at the size of those.
Capture as many alive as possible.
It speaks.
Is it different from the others?
If you can speak, let's talk this out.
I do not have the right to do that.
You must speak with the Tensen.
Hey! Shugen-san is mourning!
She threw it off balance.
Whoa.
There are plenty more, Kiyo-chan.
Oh, shut up. I know.
Their skills are incredible.
Right?
Let us demonstrate ours.
Arakagi, kill that one.
As you wish.
Bakuro Squad, Ishifudo Squad, go.
Individually, our strength
is no match for the Yamadas,
but ninjas operate in groups.
The strength of one bows
to the strength of many.
Even the greatest hero
cannot withstand such numbers.
This is how the individually
inferior genin fight.
Genin, huh?
Rest in peace.
Shugen-san!
Wow!
What?!
Monsters.
No, all creatures on this island.
I'll kill you all
as painfully as possible.
Very well.
I shall kill you and
present you as a gift...
so that I may be promoted to chisen.
So there's a limit to your regeneration.
Each time you do not answer
the questions I'm about to ask,
or I don't like your answer,
I'll cut off more.
First, your allies.
If you have some kind of group
structure, describe it in detail.
But...
Speak quickly. You're wasting time.
Now, now, Shugen.
We discovered a new type of monster.
What do you say we return
to the mainland to report our findings?
No! You simply wish
to go home, Jikka-dono.
You didn't even draw your blade.
I can't. You know that.
I'm saying you can. I know it.
Calm down, Shugen-san.
Arguing won't help anything.
You're right.
Forgive me.
I got over-excited
and was rude to my elder.
It's fine. It doesn't bother me.
Forgive me, both of you.
This side of him is cute...
Aw, man. That looked fun.
Kiyo-chan!
But if we return empty-handed,
our clan's name and Eizen-dono's
honor will be tarnished.
We'll kill every living thing
on the island.
We must teach them what happens
when you harm a Yamada student.
And for that, we need information.
Shugen-sama, please allow us to
handle the torture and interrogation.
What looks like mist
is dense tao particles.
You can use it to detect
changes on the island,
but you can't identify
the people who landed.
Sorry.
The Tensen and the newcomers...
Things keep getting more complicated.
I think we should split into two groups.
Two groups?
One group to acquire the Elixir, and
one group to secure an escape route.
What? Then I'm on Team Escape.
It's Team Secure an Escape Route.
Mei told me we'll have to
pass through Horai either way.
What? But we can leave from the shore.
There are monsters in the sea, too.
Do you have a plan
for fighting the Tensen?
I had her confirm my speculation.
Yes.
Tao has attributes,
which have compatibilities.
Wood
Metal
Fire
Water
There are strong and weak matchups.
These can be used to weaken an
enemy's tao or strengthen an ally's.
Earth
They may be beyond human understanding,
but if tao is the source
of their strength,
they cannot escape this principle.
I know it will work against them.
That's not good enough.
How effective will it be?
Can you guarantee we won't die?
It's too dangerous to enter
the enemy's base like that.
Isn't it more realistic
to leave the island and hide?
In that case, we should act alone.
You're right, Yuzuriha.
This group ended up together
by coincidence.
We have no obligation or bonds
compelling us to work together.
There are too many uncertainties.
Who are the newcomers?
Aside from that...
there could be something else unexpected.
We can't predict what
will happen or who will die.
So you should decide for yourselves
what you want to do.
If you'll come with me,
join me in the cave.
If you choose to go
your own way, that's fine.
I'll ignore your standing, too.
Wait, uh...
Shouldn't you think about it more?
That felt too quick.
At this point,
we're in it together. Right?
I don't care as long
as I make it back home,
but it's better to have more shields.
I don't really get it, but we can
kill at least one Tensen, right?
It was pointless to ask.
Working together is
the most logical choice
for anyone who wants to go home.
I'm simply performing my duties.
I'll see this through.
Were you planning to say
goodbye to me, Sensei?
No, nothing like that, but...
I know, but still!
Even if we get the Elixir,
only one of us gets a pardon.
We can fight over it on the boat back.
Honestly, I'm relieved.
It's better to have more allies.
Let's escape together.
This chaotic situation
is our greatest and final chance.