Fushi and Yuki attempt convey to Mizuha
the records that Izumi had kept.
My daughter's already moved on.
Fushi and his friends traverse the
vast undergrounds in search of Mizuha.
I remember this.
All of it.
I remember.
Invisible Battle
I'm not expecting anything of you.
But... what am I supposed to do?
Oh, pardon me, but I smell
stagnant water here.
Furthermore, the cake
looks utterly disgusting.
I recommend that you leave before you
become stinky yourself, Mizuha-senpai.
Who's with me?!
You're all awful!
How could you be so rude?
You ought to kick them out immediately!
I don't think you should do that right now.
Why?
Your dream is to grant everyone's
dreams, right, Fushi?
And for that to happen,
the world has to be peaceful.
I figured out what peace is.
Have you done something?
Huh? Fushi-kun, did you just get here?
It's already lunch.
You dyed your hair back?
Man, you look pale.
You all right?
Huh, he's here.
We are holding a special assembly.
All students,
please gather at the gymnasium immediately.
What am I doing here?
Fushi-kun?
Fushi-kun.
What are you doing up there?
There's an assembly about to start.
Hey, Fushi-kun.
Why'd you dye your hair back?
Fushi-kun?
Fushi, you have no idea
what we've been through.
Are you done with Yuki's thing?
What's wrong?
Come.
Wha... Tonari-san?
Hey, wait!
Move.
What, got a problem?
Come on, let's not do this anymore.
Hey, you're the last ones here!
Okay, we'll be right there.
That's cold!
What the?!
Water?!
Perhaps the sprinklers are malfunctioning.
Everyone, get outside!
What the hell?
My feet are soaked!
Do you have a towel?
Tonari-san?
Hit him!
Fushi-kun!
Move! You there!
I'm firing again!
What do you think you're doing, Tonari-san?!
Stop it!
That isn't him!
That isn't Fushi!
Hurry up and run!
Tanasen!
Tanacchi!
What's happening?
What is this?
Fushi...
What have you done?
You must have realized by now.
Humanity doesn't need the
Nokkers to be unhappy.
That's the curse of having flesh.
We've been making up for
the imperfectness of flesh.
So far, we've only worked on those
who were suffering misfortune.
But I just realized...
The environment is a problem, too.
Remember what you said?
That you wanted to make a place of happiness?
That's the same thing.
We can't have a better world
unless the surroundings change.
So I figured I'd try it out.
First, at school.
And?
Has something happened at school?!
Did you do something?!
I'm assuming you need this.
I can't let you have it, though.
So many Nokkers!
Cages?
We're trapped!
Wow...
It's like they're real enemies.
Vice Principal, it's all slimy!
Mizuha-senpai!
How could you do this?!
Excuse me! May I post this online later?
My smartphone!
They'll die if I'm not
careful with how I act.
Is that... school?
Pardon me! I'd like to get online.
What's the Wi-Fi pass—
My laptop!
No!
What is that?
It looks just like Fushi!
Tonari-san?!
Oh, dear.
Looks like there's a straggler.
Oh, no! Oh, no! What do we do?
The police? Ambulance?
What's this stagnant water smell?
Hey, I just noticed something...
We're the only ones who
never got hit by that water.
That's it! The water!
Don't touch the water!
I already touched Tanasen!
We haven't changed yet. I think we're safe.
Everyone, this way!
Now, go!
Wait, what about you?
I'll be a decoy.
Seriously? You're going to fight it?
Yeah. We can't let that thing
get out into the town!
I'm taking it down at school!
Go, Ligard!
You're in trouble now.
You aren't allowed to bring
weapons to school, you know.
What is that thing that looks just like me?
I raised Nokkers inside your corpse.
Really small ones.
But there's a problem.
They aren't very mobile,
so they can't get around
very quickly unless they're inside liquid.
Oh, I just came up with a fun idea.
That doll will keep going until it
turns all the students into its pawns.
For each student it gets,
I'll let one of you free.
So you're going to kill everyone?
I don't know what everyone
meant to you until now, Mizuha,
but if you don't value life...
No...
There's no way you really want to do this.
When you're enjoying good crêpes,
when you smile when your mom praises you...
That's when you're the real Mizuha!
Did you think I might
let you go if you cried?
May I ask something?
We'll all be free if Ms. Tonari
defeats that Fushi doll, correct?
What if the others manage
to flee from school?
That won't be possible.
I can't let it hit me!
I gotta regroup.
This way! Follow me!
What the hell are those things?
I have to hurry!
Where are you going?
I'm going to the staff's office to
call for help and then to Tonari-san.
I'll leave it to you to
decide what to do here.
Bye.
Please, what are we supposed to do?
Hey, look at this.
Fushi-kun?!
And a bunch of swords and
stuff for some reason.
Come on, Fushi-kun, get up!
What is going on?
Help us out!
I'm going over there.
Over there? Where?
You don't mean...
That Tonari girl's fighting all on her own.
I get the sense we should be helping her.
W-Wait, I can't!
I'm going home.
Yeah, we should call our
families and evacuate.
I think I'll stay, too.
Why?! Let's go home!
No, I'm not going.
This is what I want.
That's reckless!
You won't stand a chance!
We're just helpless bystanders.
We need to run!
I'll take you home kicking
and screaming if I have to!
It's so heavy.
Maybe we can use these.
Tanasen...
Fighting already?
Screwed whether they stay or flee.
Screwed without the Nokkers
having to do anything.
It feels great making
your ideals come to life.
I'm so happy right now.
You ought to be more selfish, too.
You didn't have to try to look
cool around your friends.
You should have just made them spoil you.
You could have taken out
that meat doll that way.
All you can do now is
watch them get taken down.
Right, Fushi?
No fair, Dad!
How could you go back to Paradise without us?
Right, Mom?
Itsuki-san...
Mom?
Everyone, get in, now!
President, this way!
Okay!
Itsuki-san!
Hey!
Why, Mom?!
I love him!
We aren't running.
Now, hold our hands.
One, two,
three, four,
five,
six.
Six seconds for it to recover.
I don't have many more Janandan arrows left.
There's no point in just slowing him down.
What do I do?
I can't dodge his attacks
in this straight hallway!
Aiko-chan?!
I brought arrows and a raincoat!
How did you know I was here?
I made a guess based on what's
on the security cameras.
But what do we do?
It doesn't look like we can
defeat it with your arrows.
Yeah, they aren't doing anything.
We need to keep it burning.
This way!
Run, run!
Jump!
Have a taste...
...of this!
Run!
Yes!
Teamwork wins the day!
Fire. Fire.
Looks like we aren't done yet.
Okay...
We can defeat it again.
No more!
We should have just run!
We don't have time for this!
Just tell me how we won't have to die!
Six arrows will work better than one.
Now, give me your right hand!
Let's go home together, Mizuha-senpai!
No!
Now, let's return home, Mizuha.
Welcome home.
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Mizuha.
You did well.
Do you want to stay here?
Let's be friends in your next life.
Fushi!
Mizuha!
Leave that body behind.
Hey. You must be the
Nokker inside her father.
This human was weak of spirit.
He couldn't tolerate the sight
of his daughter changing.
It seems Izumi-san's Nokker will be
waiting for her blood to dry and wither.
What will you do?
Why don't we all go home first?
Fushi!
How could you?!
Mizuha!
I guess that won't work.
Chami, ammo!
Sir!
Yuki...
I'll trust you.
Take Mizuha to the hospital, quick!
Fushi, we'll take care of her.
Move.
Fushi!
The Guardians need the body.
Enough!
Do not point a gun at a child!
Go!
Everyone, run!
Don't let them escape!
Stop them, Chami!
Stay back!
Allow the team's muscle to handle it!
Nice, Fushi!
The rope!
Cut the rope!
Thanks!
Go.
The elevator won't move!
It's a big one!
Open the door, Fushi!
It's open!
Stop!
Out of my way.
Get in! Quick!
Vice President, we need to deal with this!
Fushi-kun, can you move the elevator?
Hang in there!
How about this?!
You weakened it!
What did you throw at it?
I'd prepared Holy Salt for
this kind of occasion.
That's odd...
It said in the books that the
Nokkers were in sea water.
Does that mean holy power
really worked on it?
Perhaps the sodium in the water wasn't of
a high enough concentration to hurt it.
Thanks, Fushi!
All right! It worked!
I don't remember the way.
No problem. Fushi will tell us.
Look at all those creepy flowers...
We can't get out anymore!
We need to defeat that thing first.
But how?!
The fires get put out right away.
Fire... Water...
This way, guys!
Fushi...
Are you doing something somewhere?
Eyes ahead and run!
Whatever.
No matter what's happening elsewhere,
our task here is the same.
We defeat it!
Preview
The enemy's assault
robs Fushi of his vessels one after another.
Tonari and her schoolmates can't
continue fighting much longer, either.
The situation is dire.
But there is still hope.
A Willingness to Believe