Episode 7
You fool!
Now isn't the time to hold me back!
Zhang Chulan!
What a cunning move!
Get out of the way!
No one can stop us!
Fine, Zhang Chulan.
You win.
You'd betray the Company
to achieve your goal!
I underestimated you!
Charge!
Where is it?
Tell me! Where's the treasure?
Where is it?!
There's nothing here.
Where's the treasure?
Where is it?
Give me...
my treasure!
You still don't get it.
This is a game of elimination!
Ultimately, I am the chosen one!
You seem pretty familiar with this place.
Tell me! Where's the treasure?
What on earth is this mysterious power?
Judy, don't run off. It's dangerous!
Chanon!
So fast!
Mine!
It's mine!
Give it to me...
Something's wrong...
For a while now,
I haven't heard anything.
It's too quiet.
Bao'er?
Bao'er, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Are you really giving up?
Yeah, we have no reason
to stay here anymore.
Given the current situation,
we can't tell if the mission
succeeded or failed.
We were tricked by Liu from the beginning.
No, we fulfilled our duty.
We don't care about Liu's objectives...
It doesn't matter.
Let's go!
Are we just letting them leave like this?
What else can we do?
These people were just hired.
The one who's actually
in the know is Baldy Liu.
But Baldy Liu escaped.
Zhang Chulan!
Don't you owe us an explanation?
Bao'er!
Wang Zhenqiu! Xia! Baron!
If any of these three
touches me, beat them up!
Now's not the time for you guys to
settle scores with me, right, Granny?
Is this the place, Jinfeng?
There's nothing here...
It's gone. It's all gone.
Well, it's not exactly unexpected.
We had considered this possibility before.
Granny!
I know I've wronged you by
coming here alone ahead of the others!
But I really had no other choice!
I had to get here before anyone else
to confirm something!
What... did you need to confirm?
Qi Genesis...
Qi Genesis?
I only learned about Qi Genesis
when you Quan Xing came to me.
I've always pretended to be repulsed
by the Eight Secret Arts, but...
This was something my grandfather,
Zhang Huaiyi, discovered.
It rightfully belongs to the Zhang clan!
I must find out where it is
before anyone else!
Later, I discovered that
it was created after
your sect leader, Wu Gensheng,
had initiated the sworn brotherhood.
I thought this matter must be
deeply connected to this godfather!
In Biyou Village, I found out that
you were the closest person to him.
That's why I wanted to help save you!
I believe the collection might hold
the secrets of the sworn brotherhood!
It might even have clues
to the Eight Secret Arts!
Oh? If it contains
such an important secret,
how come I never found it?
Maybe you're feigning ignorance,
but I believe you simply
wouldn't have noticed!
Because anything left behind
by Wu Gensheng
was already precious enough to you!
You wouldn't care about
the Eight Secret Arts or the 36 Thieves.
The only thing you care about
is Wu Gensheng himself, right?
I wanted to have an open
and honest discussion with you.
But then that troublemaker Wang Zhenqiu
suddenly barged in!
Hey, what did I do?
This guy's had it in for me
since Biyou Village!
He saw through my plan
to get to the collection,
so he's been making life difficult for me.
I had no choice, Granny.
I trust you, but I don't trust
Wang Zhenqiu and his lot.
I had to sneak in before everyone else!
Granny, I'm sorry!
I trespassed into
your and Wu Gensheng's domain.
Never mind. It wasn't you
who trespassed here.
It was those guys who kidnapped me.
It was the ones who came here to
steal the Sect Leader's collection!
Let me tell you, Jinfeng! That bastard Wang is exactly that kind of person!
Stop having a go at me! Fine, Zhang!
You're coming for me, tough guy!
Now I'm the bad guy!
Granny, now that things have come to this,
please tell me: what exactly was
the Sect Leader's collection?
Clay Figure Zhang, a cicada shell,
a conch shell, and a stone.
A stone?
Yes, a stone.
A stone from the riverbank.
Look, Jinfeng!
Don't you think it's beautiful?
It's so refreshing and relaxing!
Refreshing and relaxing?
Is it that beautiful?
Aren't there many like this?
That's true.
It's beautiful by my standards,
but not by the world's standards.
Maybe a few of them are valuable,
but to Outcasts,
they're all totally meaningless.
Did you say there were books too?
They're just random books
you can find anywhere.
He even had The Golden Lotus,
and he said the illustrations in it
were quite good.
Maybe there's some secret hidden inside,
but I don't know what it might be.
Interesting. The people behind Ma Xianhong
took the collection beforehand,
yet hired a group to wait here.
Did they want to see us fight?
Or did they want to observe
how those people changed?
Zhang, what's with all this
black ash on the ground?
It was like this when I got here.
Huh?
Hey, Jinfeng! Jinfeng!
This...
Hmm, these footprints?
They've always been here...
Oh?
You think I haven't tried
doing that all these years?
Everyone, since we haven't
found anything, let's leave.
Bao'er really is a treasure.
She's strong, stubborn, and obedient.
Zhang, don't you feel even
the slightest bit of guilt,
being in control of such
a single-minded creature?
Why would I feel guilty?
She does whatever I ask
because she trusts me completely.
Are you jealous?
Is there someone who trusts you like that?
You're angry!
I'm not angry.
You're angry! It's the first time
I've seen you looking like that!
I apologize!
I'm not angry! Why are you apologizing?
Why would I get angry at a moron like you?
Why bother? You set me up
this time, but I'll get you back!
Kids these days are so hard to understand.
Stay away! Stop bothering me!
Just ignore me.
What Ma Xianhong worked
so hard to achieve,
this valley can also accomplish.
Indeed, the changes in those
people were truly astonishing.
The most amazing thing
about this place is that
it causes people to unconsciously
practice Zhou Tian cultivation.
As it's not being consciously controlled,
starting and stopping cultivation
is also beyond their control.
No wonder they all died like this.
After channeling their energy,
these guys were like engines
that never stopped running,
until they all ended up
exceeding their limits!
The master of this valley shouldn't
just teach people to start cultivation
without showing them how to stop!
It's the Sect Leader.
The Sect Leader altered
the patterns on this stone wall,
which must be what prevents the
natural stopping of cultivation.
But why aren't they affected
by the altered patterns?
It's those two again.
Only the Sect Leader knows why.
But these monkeys are quite interesting.
When the strongest monkey
takes over this place,
it drives the others out of the valley.
These two are probably the strongest
descendants of the previous generation.
The offspring sometimes fight to
the death over control of the valley.
Outside monkeys storm into the valley at
times, taking advantage of their numbers.
If they succeed, a new strongest
monkey will emerge from their ranks,
and the cycle begins anew.
These monkeys are learning how to
be like humans in this valley!
Whoa. These guys got taken out
by the valley monkeys, right?
If it's not at the site of the collection,
then it's very likely it's here!
Qiu, I've looked into every
suspicious location over the years.
Anything you think of,
I've already considered...
That's true.
You haven't found it in all these years.
It would be outrageous if I
found it on my first visit!
Huh? Zhang?
Huh? Has this kid lost his mind?
Zhang Huaiyi.
Since you share my grandfather's name,
I'll give you some advice today.
You must have experienced
that weird feeling
to be so obsessed with that place, right?
Going through there once is enough.
That valley teaches you only one thing:
it teaches you how to be human.
You can learn to be human in the valley,
or you can be out here in the wild.
There's no need to linger.
It's just a matter of
the easy or the hard way.
Remember what being human
was like in that valley?
Straighten your spine,
vertebra by vertebra!
Experience it again!
Although lying down is more comfortable,
and moving on all fours is faster,
there's a group of weirdos
who insist on standing upright.
What is a human?
A strange beast that
stands tall and upright!
It's difficult,
but it brings satisfaction.
That's what it's like to be human.
If one only goes
after wonderful sensations,
reverting to an animalistic
state is inevitable.
Whoa, so you've already figured it out?
The answer to
"What is human?" isn't difficult.
Looking at this valley,
the definition is clear.
One who doesn't cultivate
can't be called a complete human.
My grandfather taught me
that the first step was to
achieve an upright state in
posture, spirit, and flesh,
otherwise known as standing
tall and upright,
with a straight backbone.
Only then can qi flow smoothly.
This valley and cave clearly
symbolize the spine and skull.
The corresponding acupoints within likely
hold the secret Wu Gensheng spoke of.
You examined the area symbolizing
Baihui in the cave earlier, right?
So, the entrance to this valley
should represent the perineum.
But there's nothing significant here.
Looks like we can't
find this place's secret
without figuring out
what "sincerity" means.
Sincerity...
I have no idea about that one...
Granny, is there absolutely nothing here
related to the character for "sincerity"?
No.
"Sincerity"? Like "honesty,"
"genuine," and "integrity"?
Are you referring to attitude?
Attitude? Attitude towards what?
Forget it. If Granny couldn't
solve it all these years,
no one else here has a chance.
Wang Zhenqiu is a pain in the neck.
I need to beat him to it.
So you guys were saying earlier that
the answer to "What is human?"
is "standing tall and upright"?
Yeah. What's wrong?
Why?
Huh?
Miss, have a look!
These valleys are called
the 24 Heavenly Valleys.
When you connect them to
the cave at the end,
doesn't it look like
a human spine and skull?
I know that.
Don't humans stand tall and upright?
That's what sets us apart from animals!
I know that.
Even if some animals walk on two legs,
they don't have an
upright spine and skull.
I know that.
So, if the question is "What is human?",
the answer is "standing tall..."
You're wrong.
This valley doesn't match your answer.
Bao'er!
Humans stand tall and upright,
but this valley isn't
"standing tall and upright."
This would be "standing tall and upright!"
Translation & Timing: Henry Lin
Editing: Alicia Ashby
QC: William Haggard
FQC: Sriram Gurunathan