Okay, perfect!
I haven't made one in ages,
but it turned out pretty well.
Maybe I'm a genius!
Wonder if my Hitoman account still works.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
[OtoMAD] Saikyo Bento
Hitoman
5613 channel followers
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Edit Video
Oh, I didn't realize
I have more followers now.
Okay, time to upload.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Upload has finished
[OtoMAD] Turns Out Kaisendonman Won a Chicken Dinner
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Hitoman
5613 channel followers
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Edit Video
And press play.
Episode 5
The Misanthrope and Tobari's Hymn
Teachers' Office
There, all done!
That should do it
for the midterm questions.
This should help my students
when they enter human society,
so I'll need to keep
updating this material.
Mr. Hoshino's stuff again?
I wish he'd keep his desk more organized.
How does he keep track
of where anything is?
Man, I'm hungry.
With all this work,
I had no time to eat lunch.
Oh, no!
I forgot I bought sushi for lunch today!
Wasshoi!
Sushi, sushi!
You've gotta treat yourself sometimes.
Since I just got my paycheck,
I splurged a bit with the premium sushi!
Huh? I can't open it.
You can't be serious.
Hey, c'mon!
There!
Aw man, I spilled it.
This is why I don't trust
these tear-anywhere packets.
There, all clean.
Wait, huh?
Is this Mr. Hoshino's handkerchief?!
Advanced Class
Nope, it's not coming off.
I'm a goner for sure!
This sucks.
What have I done?
Mr. Hitoma, what's up?
Haneda?!
Wh-What are you doing here so late?!
Hey, what'd you just hide from me?
Huh?
Ah! There's an alien up in the sky!
Huh? Who would fall for that trick?
I wasn't trying to trick you...
I saw everything.
What are you talking about?
The fancy-looking handkerchief
with that awful stain.
So you really did see?!
F-From where?
From "There, all done! That should do it
for the midterm questions."
All the way back then?!
I might have messed up a little.
Isn't that Mr. Hoshino's?
I knew it.
You should apologize
to him sooner rather than later.
I agree, but I wanted to do what I could
before returning it to him.
I don't think you'll get anywhere
by stressing yourself out.
Yeah...
I'll go get Mr. Hoshino, then.
Wait, Haneda!
I need time to sort out my emotions!
Here he is.
That was fast!
I'd already asked him to come here.
Now that's being prepared!
Huh, what?
What's this about?
Well, Mr. Hoshino...
You see...
Oh, that's the handkerchief I got
as a birthday present from my wife.
Y-Y-Your wife?!
As a birthday present?!
Hold on, you're married?!
I was stumped since I couldn't find it.
Thank you.
Where was it?
I think it turned up when
that pile of paper on your desk collapsed.
Oh, so that's where it was?
Sorry for all the trouble.
I've never been very organized.
Um, Mr. Hoshino.
Actually, I used this to wipe
up some soy sauce by mistake.
I'm so sorry!
Soy sauce?
Oh, a stain like that's no big deal.
It's still perfectly usable
as a handkerchief.
You don't need to feel bad about it
at all, Mr. Hitoma.
I'm so glad you managed to find it.
I was looking for it over the past week.
My wife was about to be very angry at me.
Miss Haneda, is this
why you called me here?
That's right.
I see.
Miss Haneda. Mr. Hitoma. Thank you both.
Not at all.
I'll be going now.
I'm glad he didn't get mad at you.
Yeah.
Thanks a lot, Haneda.
Guess I'll be going, too!
Tobari Haneda.
Her true form is a bird,
the bull-headed shrike.
She's always been top of the class.
However, her school records
are sealed away for some reason,
so I don't know how long
she's spent at the advanced level.
She wants to become
a human so she can make music.
Advanced Class
Mr. Hitoma.
What is it, Haneda?
My stomach hurts a little.
May I go to the nurse's office?
Yeah. Who's willing to tag along?
No, I'll be fine.
I can make it there by myself.
No, we can't have you
passing out in the hallway.
Can one of you please take her?
I'll do it!
Sure, Usami.
Please accompany her.
Got it.
No, I'm really fine by myself.
You don't look it, so shut your trap.
What? This isn't the Usami I know.
Don't classes come first?
You sure can run your mouth
for someone who's sick.
Hurry up and rest in the nurse's office.
Will Tobari be all right?
We rarely even catch colds in this form,
so I can't help but worry.
Huh, really?
Our current bodies are that
of a model healthy human teenager.
We enjoy full bodily function,
which includes fitness and immune systems.
In turn, we don't get sick very easily.
Nurse's Office
Yes, come in.
Excuse me.
'Sup, Mr. Hitoma.
Doing good?
Hello there, Ms. Karasuma.
How's Haneda doing?
Feeling a lot better after a nap.
I see, that's good to hear.
Mr. Hitoma, you should have
a talk with her, too.
Tobari Haneda always comes to the
nurse's office at the very last minute.
Always?
She gets sick at this time every year,
so tell her to drop by a little earlier.
And to get some proper rest, too.
Every year?
Does she have some kind of condition?
Huh? Oops.
Well, I guess you could call it that...
Mr. Hitoma?
You came just to see me?
How are you feeling, Haneda?
I'm doing a lot better now.
What about class?
Come ask in the teachers' office or the
social studies prep room once you recover.
What about the math prep room?
That's Mr. Hoshino's
hideout, so no can do.
The least he could do is share!
I haven't had a chance to talk
with her alone, so let's keep going.
Oh yeah, you said you
were interested in music.
That's right.
Any music you're really into lately?
What?
I know what this reminds me of!
You sound like a dad worried
about his teenage daughter!
What?!
What music I'm into?
I've been digging otoMAD videos lately.
OtoMADs?
You never know what you're gonna get.
I watch everything from old uploads
to the latest popular stuff.
The one I'm into right now...
Probably this one.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
[OtoMAD] Turns Out Kaisendonman Won a Chicken Dinner
87K views
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Hitoman
5613 channel followers
"Turns Out Kaisendonman Won
a Chicken Dinner."
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
[OtoMAD] Turns Out Kaisendonman Won a Chicken Dinner
87K views
It was created by this guy named Hitoman.
Funny how it kinda sounds like your name.
Uh-oh.
I need to do something
to keep my alter ego under wraps!
H-Haneda, have you ever tried
to make your own music?
I've messed around
with making music here and there.
Just like Mr. Hitoman.
What?!
Hey...
If you feel all better now,
I'd prefer it if you booked it outta here.
Oh, sure...
Nurse's Office
You'll be fine heading home?
Yeah, I'm all good now!
Not very considerate though, are you?
Why not?
At times like these, wouldn't you usually
bring my stuff to the nurse's office?
You think I'm brave enough
to touch my female students' belongings?
I guess you're right.
One wrong move, and it could
be considered sexual harassment.
Right?
I've thought all this through.
Well, it's true that
I was being inconsiderate.
That's right.
Nothing good ever comes from meddling.
Advanced Class
I wish I could go home, too.
You're really gonna say
that in front of a student?
What's wrong with being honest
when you want to go home?
I've still got lots
of work I need to get done.
Must be nice being able to leave.
It's not like you can
just ignore your work.
Well, work hard, but too hard.
Sure.
Don't work yourself too hard, either.
I know you were helping
Usami study the other day.
How do you know that?!
I can tell as your teacher.
I spoke with the other teachers.
Usami's been getting better
grades on her quizzes overall.
I can't help but cheer
on someone who's trying so hard.
You really keep an eye on us, though, huh?
Pretty much.
That's my job as a teacher.
I've been keeping
a good eye on you as well.
That's true.
She knew about how I got
Mr. Hoshino's handkerchief dirty,
and how I make MADs to upload online.
Mr. Hitoma.
You're usually easygoing and careless,
but you can look real sad sometimes.
What?
With a faraway look in your eyes.
Really?
Yeah.
Like when I said you
were inconsiderate back in the hallway.
Oh, did I touch a sore spot?
No, that's not it.
If I did, I'm sorry.
Wait, it really was that?
If something's bothering you,
I'm here to listen.
Or well, if you tell me,
then I can avoid it in the future.
No, it's fine.
Sorry to bother you like that.
Besides, it's all in the past.
You still think about it
because you can't leave it in the past.
Am I wrong when I say that?
Talking about it might
be a weight off your mind.
There you go, looking sad again.
Oh, sorry.
It's all right.
No matter what, you always have me here.
Is it okay to stop bearing this weight?
Why not?
I think that's how it becomes
a thing of the past.
To tell the truth...
Yeah?
At my old school, one of my
students asked me for help.
She was fighting with a friend of hers.
As her homeroom teacher,
I wanted to do what I could.
Yeah.
But that was a mistake.
In the end, because of me...
Because I stepped in,
things got even more out of hand.
That student ended up
leaving school altogether.
And then, right before she did,
she said I physically punished her,
even though I never laid a finger.
The administration wouldn't listen
to a word I said on the matter.
Which is why I ended up
having to leave as well.
On my last day, that student
came up to me and said...
This is all your fault!
And she was right.
I was in the wrong.
That's why...
Mr. Hitoma.
Time doesn't stand still.
What?
Your past self may never leave you,
but the present you is the one I see now.
You may make mistakes,
but you can always start over.
Don't worry.
I'm right here, seeing you as you are now.
Thanks.
I could say the same.
Thanks for coming to this school.
What?
Mr. Hitoma.
You said you want to leave for the day?
M-Miss Haneda?
Mr. Hitoma.
How about the two
of us run away somewhere?
Are we allowed to be up here?
And wait, they don't lock
the door to the rooftop?
Usually, they do.
Regular students
are prohibited from entering.
So you're breaking school rules?!
Then how come it was unlocked?
It's easy to get up here
if you use this to pick the lock.
You know you shouldn't do that!
Doesn't it feel good
up here on the rooftop?
I come up here all the time.
Well?
Did this clear your head a little?
Huh?
Yeah, maybe it did.
You're so funny.
Haneda.
Sorry, but you're losing points for
sneaking onto the roof against regulation.
Yeah, I don't mind.
Then since I'm losing points
anyway, how about this?
Mr. Hitoma, turn around for me.
T-Turn around?
Just trust me!
Is this what I think it is?!
Aren't you coming
on a little too strong, Miss Haneda?!
So it's true that they feel soft!
Wait no, I shouldn't be enjoying this!
I'm starting to feel lightheaded now.
Like my body is floating in midair...
Wait...
M-M-Miss Haneda, we're floating!
Sure, since we're flying.
I can deduct points
for unhuman-like behavior!
Keep squirming and you'll fall.
Don't worry.
Just act normal and I won't drop you.
You know how scary this is?!
My safety instinct is sounding its alarms!
That's a weird way to put it.
In that case, put your
arms around my neck.
What?
Feel a little better now?
Yeah, I do feel safer...
Although it has me nervous in another way.
Hey, are you thinking something dirty?
No, not at all.
Good.
Go on, take a look.
When you see the sky from up above,
it looks so much bigger
and more beautiful than from below.
I wanted to show you what it looks like.
Mr. Hitoma.
I want to be like this sky,
and accept you for everything you are.
Are you confessing to me?
Don't get too full of yourself.
I'm sorry...
Thanks.
Did you have fun, Mr. Hitoma?
I sure did.
But you broke way too many
rules in front of a teacher.
Don't blame me if you can't become human.
That's fine by me.
In fact, it makes me happy
to see you treat me fairly.
Don't you want to become human?
Yeah, I do.
But I don't have to just yet.
What does that mean?
It's a secret for now.
What she did today will lose her points.
All for bringing me here to try
and cheer me up.
Even so, I'm a teacher.
Outside of academic exams,
all I can do is take points away.
Then why don't I...
Hey, Haneda.
You like music, don't you?
Yeah, that's right.
Both listening to music and singing.
Then can I ask you to sing
for me right now?
Here?!
You watched my MAD video
in the nurse's office.
Think of it as a fair trade.
What?
Flying in the air doesn't count?
That was a flagrant
rule violation, so nope.
You said it was fun, too.
Well, if you'd rather not,
then that's fine.
What?
Are you okay even if
it doesn't sound very good?
Let me hear it.
Just this once, then.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
November 23rd
Could Tobari not be feeling well?
I'm slightly worri...
Next Episode:
The Misanthrope and the Light of Dawn