THREE DAYS AFTER THE RETURN
OF THE PURIFICATION EXPEDITION
Kondou-san!
Shiraishi-san.
Thank you for all you've done on
all three purification expeditions.
You're so welcome!
My humblest gratitude for purifying
the miasma, Your Holiness.
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Er, Shiraishi-san...
I'd like to hear about the expedition.
Then why don't we have lunch together?
I'd like to hear about the progress
on the cram school, as well.
Would you care to join us, Siegvold-san?
Indeed.
We need to make sure
the disciple eats his meals.
Please stop calling me that.
My name is Kondou Seiichirou.
But you are the disciple...
It attracts too much attention.
You leave me little choice.
I shall compromise.
Master Seiichiro.
Very good, Reverend.
I conceded first. Please call me
by my first name, as well.
Understood, Siegvold-sama.
ISEKAI OFFICE WORKER: THE OTHER WORLD'S
BOOKS DEPEND ON THE BEAN COUNTER
EPISODE 10: I INVESTIGATED
What a beautiful place!
The holy maiden of two generations
ago created this flower garden.
I had no idea this was here!
You didn't need a lunch?
That's right.
Kondou-san has to be mindful of
what he eats or he'll overdose.
Huh?
Master Seiichiro has no
resistance to magicules.
So he must be careful with
his diet and lifestyle.
Magicules give you strength so
long as you don't absorb too much,
and they're everywhere! Like air!
He came from a world unlike ours.
The air and food there
must have been different.
Wh-What about Your Holiness?
I seem to be blessed with divine
protection, so I'm unaffected.
Master Seiichiro has been
suffering this tribulation,
yet he still works hard for our kingdom.
Please treat him with care.
Don't paint a weird image of me.
Don't worry, Selio-san.
I've been slowly gaining some resistance,
and I won't die unless I absorb
a large amount of magicules.
You could die?!
Shiraishi-san, could you tell me
about the purification expedition?
Yes.
There were no changes during
the first and second expeditions,
but once the miasma was gone,
light poured onto the tree,
and buds sprouted on part of it.
They're apparently proof that
the purification is complete.
I heard that the sorcerers
are now recording
below-normal levels of magicules there.
But when they investigated
the surrounding area,
they found the footprints
of a beast called a nepolic.
Aresh-san wanted to dispatch it at once.
It takes three days to reach the
demon forest from the royal capital.
Staying out was more efficient
than returning.
I would've done the same thing.
But...
Kondu-sama, you have
a letter from Aresh-sama.
Nepolics have rather large territories,
so our hunt is taking some time.
You have nothing to worry about.
Just take care of your own health.
He's smart and talented.
Though he's a cold beauty with a way
of speaking that makes him seem mature,
he's surprisingly childish at home and
sulks if you don't pay attention to him.
He always wears a guilty expression
when Valtom-san scolds him.
When he has work he doesn't want to do,
he ends up clinging to me even more,
as if smothering his reluctance to go.
That's why he took on this
sudden subjugation mission.
He wants me to praise him.
Apart, I cannot help but
marvel at our past unmet.
Now that we're apart,
I can't help wondering how I managed
to live before meeting you...
How about some fish?
Bro! Long time no see!
Sigma-kun. How have things been?
Oh, well, my boss hurt his hand,
so I can't train under him right now.
He's looking for a new place that'll
take me, but since I'm just a kid...
I keep getting brushed off.
Perfect timing, then.
I want you to make more
of those calculators for me.
Really?!
You pay real well, so that's great!
How many?
Thirty of them.
Thirty?!
Also, Sigma-kun...
Have you ever thought
about going to school?
Oh, it's Kondu.
Huh? Something's different.
Different?
Your magical energy's
different from normal...
Oh, right.
The third order isn't around right now.
That's right, Kondu!
Did you bring me a sacred relic?
You have a good memory
for such things.
I bid you also remember that
I told you that'd be impossible.
Why do you want one so badly?
Huh?
Because those things have so much
magical energy stored in them.
I'd be able to do all the research
I wanted with that.
They store magical energy?
Doesn't that make them magic tools?
Ist-san, have you seen
a sacred relic before?
I have.
You pray to them when you turn six.
Plus, I have loads of magical energy.
According to the prime minister,
kids train to reduce their magical energy.
Now the church has a sacred relic
to collect said magical energy.
Where exactly is that energy going?
Something feels off. Where should
I start investigating first?
Sei-san, did you finish up
with the sorcery department?
Nor, perfect timing. There's
something I want to ask you...
Kondu.
Your Highness.
There's something I wish
to ask you. Come with me.
Then I'll just be on my way...
It's fine. Join us.
Huh?
I heard you spoke at great length
with Yua the other day.
Yes. We were discussing
Her Holiness's work.
Tell me the details!
Then please take a look
at this document here.
I shall!
A private school for
the almshouse children and
the poor children of the city...
Did Her Holiness really
come up with this?
This kind of flawless, pragmatic plan
feels like something you would—
I'd expect no less from Yua!
What a brilliant idea!
But why didn't she mention it to me?
She was probably planning to share it
with you once her plan came together.
However, for Your Highness in all your
wisdom to catch on ahead of time
and fulfill her wishes
by supporting her cause...
That's exactly what I wanted.
That's right! You're absolutely right!
I was actually thinking the same thing!
Me and Yua are totally on the same page!
He's so excited, he started
talking casually.
I agree.
Now, should you support her with your own
funds instead of the national treasury,
it would further emphasize
your stance on the matter
and make you dependable in her eyes.
That's how things work in our world.
Oh, is that so?!
Well, I was thinking of doing just that!
I shall go speak with Yua at once!
Sei-san, are you planning to make this
happen with His Highness's personal funds?
The kingdom's budget is tight right now.
Besides, it's true that my
country values self-sacrifice.
That must be how they raise
workaholics like you, Sei-san.
Kondu, enjoy these with the rest
of the accounting department.
Is His Highness aware of this?
His Highness gave me the order.
You don't believe me, do you?
His Highness may greatly
admire Her Holiness,
but he is also a worthy heir as
the first in line for the throne.
Yurius and Nor, the illegitimate
son who was adopted out,
are both children of the current
king and biological brothers.
Treats from His Highness?
I really loved these as a kid.
I see.
So he's aware of his
little brother's likes?
Come to think of it, wasn't there
something you wanted to ask me?
Oh, yes.
You've seen a sacred
relic before, haven't you?
A sacred relic? Yeah, I have.
Those statues with magic
crystals in them, right?
And as for magical energy...
They absorb it, right?
Is that common knowledge?
Only the royal family and
the bishop know about it.
It's actually a secret,
but I figure it's fine if you know.
That makes it a state secret.
No wonder different people say
different things about it.
What happens to the magical
energy once it's collected?
It's used for the barrier that protects
the royal capital from magic beasts.
The barrier around the royal
capital is kinda special.
It can even repel magic attacks
from other countries.
Who would've thought
not only the prime minister,
but even Aresh-sama was unaware of this?
The barrier around the
royal capital must be
constantly replenished
with magical energy.
That's where the Church comes in.
Their sacred relic has a magic tool
embedded in it to convert
the prayers of the people
into offerings of magical energy.
Just as I suspected...
There's an unnatural bump.
I've learned three things.
First, the church is collecting
the magical energy
of people's prayers and
storing it in a sacred relic.
Second, that magical energy is being used
for the barrier defending the capital.
Third, the kingdom gives
financial support to the Church,
including a provision for magical energy.
Furthermore, it seems some of this magical
energy was used to summon the holy maiden.
However, there's no record of the
exact amount spent in the process.
Even though it's kept secret,
it's a recognized source of energy.
Since it's generating money,
I need more detailed information on it.
Master Seiichiro, you don't
look well. Are you all right?
I'm fine.
But your face looks pale...
Oh, Siegvold-san! And Kondou-san!
Good morning!
Shira— Your Holiness and...
Your Highness?
No need to stand on ceremony.
I shall allow you to call me "Yuri"
when I am dressed like this.
Kondou-san!
Yuri-sama says he'll help
support the cram school!
He was thinking of doing
the same thing I wanted to
and decided to come check out
the almshouse incognito today!
As expected. Men in love move fast.
Kondu! Give us the rundown and a tour!
Yes, yes.
Will you be all right?
Y-Yes.
Your Holiness!
Good morning, Selio-kun.
Huh? Who's that?
Bro! Thank goodness you're here.
Sigma-kun? What are you doing here?
When I told my mom
about the private school,
she told me to hurry up and get in on it
before the nobility changes their mind.
Perfect timing.
With both children of the almshouse
and common folk here,
we can better explain
things to our sponsor.
Sponsor?
It's another term for an investor.
I mean that man over there.
I'm no noble myself, but he's very
important, so tread carefully.
What's your relationship with this kid?
I recruited Sigma-kun here
from a street stall downtown.
He's an amazing boy who's
smart, creative, and proactive.
Hey, Bro...
Didn't I tell you, Selio?
That's the kind of man the
disciple—Master Seiichiro is.
Don't be swayed by the talk and
preconceptions of those around you.
Look with your own eyes
and decide things for yourself.
With my own eyes...
Here I am.
Ist-san? Why are you here?
Huh?
You dropped by yesterday and looked
at all sorts of documents,
so I thought you'd be here
checking out the sacred relic.
Did you guys already pray today?
No.
Not yet.
I see. In that case,
can I tag along with all of you?
Sure!
He's here for prayer...
In other words, to observe the supply
of magical energy to the sacred relic.
Master Seiichiro, might this man be...
That's Ist-san, the assistant director
of the royal sorcery department.
Master Ist, welcome
to the Church of Abran.
A handshake! He wants to shake your hand!
Hello!
I can imagine how difficult
Director Zoltan has it.
Are you going to pray? I'll come too, then.
Shiraishi-san...
Have you been to pray before?
Yes.
I usually attend prayer when
helping at the almshouse.
Yua, you...
Huh?
Yuri-sama?
Outside of practice,
everyone makes sure she uses as
little magical energy as possible,
yet the church is extracting
magical energy from her
when her top priority is the purification.
This very well may
affect the purification.
It would seem the royal palace
was in the dark on this.
Ist-san and I will attend the prayer.
If you would, hang back
and show Yuri-sama around.
Oh, okay...
Yua, please be my guide.
Of course!
Well, let's go.
Go? Go where?
To the sacred relic.
Huh?
Outsiders must obtain permission
from the bishop before entering.
I see...
Then could you please ask for permission?
But this is so sudden...
Never mind me. That guy from the
sorcery department came here alone,
without an appointment,
just to see the sacred relic.
You understand where this is going, right?
He won't listen even if you tell him no.
We have no idea what he may do.
Get permission quickly.
I won't be able to stall
him for very long.
Master Kondu, I'm very sorry for the delay
on the income and expenses report.
I should be able to give
it to you by tomorrow...
No, that's fine, Brother Cipriano.
I'm sorry for causing you more
trouble when you're so busy.
I'll be done with the church tomorrow...
That means I have to wrap things up today.
This is the special prayer room.
As beautiful as I remember it...
Bro?
Aresh! You've returned
from the expedition.
Yes, Your Highness.
The third royal order has returned
safely, without a single knight missing.
Very good. Excellent work.
Aresh-san, welcome back.
Where is that guy?
"That guy"? Oh, Kondu?
He went to the prayer room
with the almshouse children.
That can't be...
You mean where the sacred relic is housed?
When I was little, I couldn't
control my magical energy,
and I began to believe
that I was a devil's child.
Then I was brought to this prayer room,
where I prayed to Abran
and regained control.
In that moment, I swore to serve
him for the rest of my life.
Didn't his condition just calm down
because the extra magical energy
flowing out of him was absorbed?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Um... I was just thinking the way
they're praying is different from before.
Oh, you've prayed before?
Five years ago at my baptism.
Maybe things have changed since then?
You're right.
It wasn't like this before.
This method absorbs too
much magical energy,
which could disrupt the
body's magical circulation
and make the children lose control.
Huh?
Isn't this a ritual to express
gratitude for God's blessing?
Looks like that priest can
sense magical energy.
I wonder if they absorb
this much every time now.
You can tell how much
magical energy there is?
Yup. The sorcery department tends
to collect those of us sensitive to it.
Bro, are you a sorcerer?!
That's right.
That's awesome! I can't believe
you can see magical energy!
Must be nice...
I can't tell at all.
It'd be cool if there was a tool
to measure magical energy.
It'd be even better if it could
measure magical energy
in a way that even someone with
no sense for it, like me, could see.
What shape would it take?
A device worn over the eye?
Do you look through it like glasses?
Uh, that would be fine if it
were for a single person,
but if you're making it...
Making what?
It'd be better to have something that
lots of people could see at a glance.
How would you measure the
amount? In numbers? Words?
What about people who can't read?
Maybe use colors?
Colors? Would the color change depending
on the amount of magical energy?
Um, not exactly...
Well, is there a material that responds
to levels of magical energy?
There is. It's poisonous,
but there's kelsil,
which expands when exposed.
It can be extracted from an ore
that's often used in magical research.
In that case, if we put it in a
rectangular mold and let it expand...
What if we make it so magical energy
can only contact the bottom?
Then it'd be forced to expand upward!
Right! And if we can make it so the color
changes with the pressure from that...
We have a color guide for magical energy!
That's it!
No, it's still just a concept...
I think I can make it with
the materials in the lab!
Not good. It's going to overflow.
Huh?
Oh, it's no use. Here it comes.
Bro! Watch out!
EPISODE 11
I GOT HOSPITALIZED