Infirmary
You coming over to my place today?
I think I'll pass.
Why, though?
Doctor!
Because an annoying nuisance has arrived.
What is it this time?
The infirmary is closed.
Oh, you had a visitor?
I'm so sorry.
Whatever.
Come on in.
Sorry, Misaki.
I'll call you.
Sure thing.
Better not lay a hand
on such a little guy, Hokuto!
As if!
Was that your boyfriend just now?
Nope.
More like a lover, I guess.
Adults...
So, let me get this straight.
You're here because you want me,
a man about to turn 27 this year,
to lend you an outfit for a young lady?
Right!
Why would you think I have that?
You reap what you sow.
Figure it out yourself.
I know this is a big ask.
But you're the only person
I can depend on...
You're ignoring me?
I'm sorry.
I'll go home now.
Hang on.
What's up with him?
He's been sneaking around since yesterday.
Wow, it's been so long
since I wore a skirt!
I even got a headband.
This is my little sister, Rio.
Oh, good! Looks like it fits you.
I-I'm really sorry.
Don't be.
My brother explained the situation to me.
I wonder exactly how he did that.
Good luck!
Thank you, Rio-chan!
Ah, I'm late!
Dressed like that,
she really looks like a girl.
My Big Brother's Coming!
Thank you.
Onii-chan!
Mizuki!
It's good to see you, Shizuki.
Still a tomboy, I see.
You have no idea how surprised
I was when Dad told me
you were studying abroad in Japan.
I'm sorry.
It's all good.
As long as you're fine.
Here, let me have a good look at you.
You can look all you want, but...
put me down.
My bad, my bad! Sorry!
What the hell am I doing?
By the way, what happened to your hair?
I cut it when I came to Japan.
But why?!
I loved your hair!
How long will you be in Japan?
I'm here on an exchange program
between our office
and Japanese medical schools.
So about two weeks, I guess.
Two weeks, huh?
I have to make sure he doesn't find out
I go to a boys' school in that time.
How are things?
Already used to high school here in Japan?
Um, yeah! It's tons of fun.
Wh-What?
Nothing. I was just thinking that
you've reached the age where
you can make your own decisions.
Onii-chan...
But of course.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
have decided all this so swiftly
while I was away on my internship!
So, were you able to meet him?
That high jumper?
H-Here we go!
Yeah!
I'm really glad I came to Japan.
W-Well, I need to be getting back.
Next time, I'll show you around Tokyo.
He's always had a thing against Sano.
I'll just keep my mouth shut.
Osaka High School, eh?
So, yeah...
Listen, Ashiya...
Oh, totally...
Right?
What the hell?
Since when are they buddies?
Who knows?
We were surprised too.
He's so curt with me.
I mustered all of my courage
to tell him good morning,
and in response, he just says,
"Oh, morning."
It's got me so down.
I know what you mean.
It's, like, if your crush is curt with you,
it just throws you off
for the whole rest of the day.
It's not like I'm usually
attracted to guys.
I only fell for him because
he's Nanba-senpai.
We're the only ones who understand
what this feels like!
Sorry.
I don't know what that feels like either.
What's goin' on here?
What're you whispering
so secretively about?
Nakatsu.
Let me in on it.
I'm saved!
No way.
This is a meeting for cute boys only.
Go away.
What part of me isn't cute?!
You have, like, zero sense of aesthetics.
How dare you?!
I'm running away.
Screw you, Nakao!
Where've you been, Sano?
Talking to the team supervisor.
I see.
So Sano plans on competing
in the preliminaries?
Later.
Good luck!
I'm sure he'll be able to jump by then.
Yeah, I'm totally sure of it! For certain!
Mizuki!
Onii-chan!
What's the meaning of this?
This is a boys' school!
Just let me explain.
That won't be necessary.
We're leaving, and you're coming with me.
Onii-chan!
Th-That hurts!
Stop that, Mizuki!
I think it's time you let go.
You're making this uncomfortable.
And who are you supposed to be?
Sano!
Sano, eh?
So you're the one!
The Sano Izumi who seduced Mizuki!
There was no seducing!
Same mannerisms.
They really are siblings.
Then why don't you show
me your jump right now?
Onii-chan...
Didn't you come to Japan just
to see his heroic performance?
So let's see it and be done with it.
He can't!
Sano's still suffering from
the aftermath of an accident!
Aftermath?
What do you mean?
All right, I understand the situation now.
So let's do it this way.
If Izumi-kun can clear the bar
before I leave Japan,
Mizuki can stay here.
Wh-What?!
You got that?
Don't forget!
Ashiya.
Please take care of walking Yujiro
for the time being.
I'm going to pick up my training
before preliminaries.
Okay.
There's nothing I can do.
I can't offer any help...
Mizuki?
Nakatsu? You just get out of practice?
Yeah.
You all right?
You look down.
What? O-Oh, it's nothing.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Say, wanna hang a bit when
you're done walking Yujiro?
There! It's done!
Maido
This is my first time eating okonomiyaki.
It's pipin' hot!
Today's my treat. Eat all you want.
Sure.
Hey, that's really good!
Right?
This place has my seal of approval.
Do you come here a lot?
Now and then.
First time I've brought anyone, though.
Guess you could say I kinda get homesick.
When I first came to Tokyo,
I was the only one from Osaka.
So I felt really alone, ya know?
So when I'm feelin' that way,
I come here.
And I tell myself, "Get it together.
You're not alone."
Okonomiyaki's just a little taste of home.
Nakatsu...
Yeah?
Thank you.
Easy does it. Don't want to wake him.
Smells like food.
Oh, Sano! You're awake?
I brought you back some
okonomiyaki. Want it?
Yeah.
L-Listen, um...
It probably isn't my place to say, but...
What?
Good luck!
I did it!
I feel like saying that one little
thing took so much thought and energy!
Well, that's the least
you should be saying
to make this jump worth it for me.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm doing this because
Kagurazaka won't shut up.
Your thing is secondary.
Got it?
So stop endlessly worrying
about nothing and chin up!
So Sano noticed...
Now that I've had a snack,
I'm really hungry.
Wanna go have dinner?
But you just ate.
Doofus. That wasn't nearly enough.
You think that'd fill me up?
I need more energy.
Oh?
We've got another someone
with striking hair wandering around.
What could be more useless than
a high jumper who can't jump?
I'm sure he'll choke when the day comes,
meaning he won't meet my challenge,
and it's game over.
On the off chance he pulls it off,
I'll convince Mizuki she's met her
objective in seeing said jump,
then take her back home.
My strategy is foolproof!
Observe!
Clothing darker than the floor!
And an item to disguise my identity!
None can stand in my way!
Now, let's begin our reconnaissance.
But where is Sano Izumi?
May I help you?
Yes! A family member of mine
attends this school.
Today, I'm here for recon—
I mean, to observe.
So this is Ashiya's older brother?
Is that so?
Please, come on in.
Oh, really?
Well then...
That saved me.
Have some tea.
Thank you very much.
So, what is your impression
of our school here?
Well, you see...
While I can't say I've seen anything bad,
I haven't seen anything great either.
Oh, that was rude.
It's fine.
Our school has a relatively
unrestricted atmosphere.
And lately, we've had an unusual
sort of student transfer.
It would seem they're here
specifically to chase
a high jumper they admire.
W-Wow, that is rather bold.
In fact, you'd think
this student was a girl
based on how sweet he is.
A-Apologies.
I must be going now.
Almost there!
That was super close,
but you did have the height.
The rest is in...
Probably my last stride.
Right!
I just remembered...
What's wrong?
My first kiss was...
Ashiya?
With you.
Are you sick or something?
I'm fine!
Ow, that freakin' hurt.
Next one, Sano! Let's go!
You're so close to being able to jum—
What's this?
Sano, you're...
Kagurazaka.
You're still dragging
that baggage around?!
F-Found him!
I got lost.
I should've just asked
where the field was.
Sano!
You're delusional if you think you
can get on my level like this!
Your old injury?
Yeah, I'll bet it hurt!
I mean, you tore ligaments
in your dominant leg.
But you still recovered.
That was admirable, but afterward?
I won't mince words! You ran!
You threw the high jump away!
And now you say you're coming back?
When you can't even jump?!
I don't care what you say or think.
I'm doing things my way.
Besides, I already made a
promise to not run away anymore.
To him.
Sano...
Which is why I'm going to jump again.
I'm jumping for me.
Preliminaries is the
first step in that direction.
Yeah? Then I'll be waiting
for you to make good on that.
Listen up.
You'd better not run.
I won't let you get away with
quitting while you were ahead!
Kagurazaka, he's...
No, no way. That can't be.
Shall we head home too?
Yeah.
Here.
Hey... What are you going
to do if I can't jump?
Guess my brother
will just drag me back home.
What about you?
What do you want to do?
I... I want to stay in Japan,
here at Osaka.
As long as I'm not bugging you, that is.
Then stay.
If you want to be here,
then follow your heart.
Sano...
I'm afraid that's not for you to say.
Onii-chan!
If you don't want me to take
Mizuki back, you had better jump.
But you've got less
than a week before I leave.
So it's ultimately impossible.
Sano is doing his best!
He's giving it all he's got.
I've been watching all this time.
And nothing you say changes that!
A high jumper who can't jump
is nothing but pathetic.
Hey, Sano!
Coach was calling for you.
Got it. I'll be right there.
Sano...
Look at that. No backbone.
I said that to his face,
and he didn't even get angry.
You... You...
Huh?
I hate you!
Why? How?
My adorable baby sister has started
going to this filthy boys' school,
and me trying to rectify that
is somehow a crime now?!
Is God dead?!
Wh-Whoa, why are you sitting out here?
What are you doing?
Sano.
You'll catch cold if you don't get inside.
U-Um, listen, I really told
my big brother off.
I'm so sorry about earlier.
What's for dinner tonight?
Um...
Fried shrimp.
I'll forget about it if you give
me one of yours.
So you should forget about it too.
That's it. Case closed.
Seriously...
How much more do you want me to love you?!
Let's hurry up and get dinner.
Yeah!
Public Track and Field Stadium
A Few Days Later
It's so sunny.
Damn, why couldn't we
wear our normal clothes?
Well, it's not a practice
match or anything.
Yay! There's quite a lot of girls!
Huh, I didn't expect this many spectators.
Onii-chan.
Wow, a foreigner in the flesh.
Hello.
I'm Mizuki's older brother,
Shizuki Claude Ashiya.
Thanks for coming.
Hey, where's Mizuki?
Said he was going to say hi
to Sano and Sekime.
He's so diligent.
Here. It's a charm.
We're in Japan,
so I figured the support of
a Japanese god might be good.
You know...
This is a love and marriage charm.
Love and marriage
What?! No way!
I asked Nakao-kun for help and everything!
I... You've gotta be kidding!
I'm so sorry!
God, I'm such an idiot!
It's fine. I'll take it.
You're Nakatsu-kun, right?
Er, yeah.
What's this Sano Izumi like?
Izumi, huh?
Not to be rude,
but you're gonna have to watch him
and make that call for yourself.
Now, on to the high jump!
Number 8 is Sano Izumi-kun,
a first-year from Osaka High School.
Did they say Sano Izumi?!
Didn't he quit?
And here I thought you had
your tail between your legs.
Kagurazaka...
Please, God!
Mister?
Sano...
You did it...
You could jump!
What a relief!
I'm so happy!
Congratulations!
I could jump...
I could do it!
Save it for later, kids.
As far as high jumps go,
Sano's was still pretty low.
Let's head back to the bench?
But his form was better than anyone's.
You don't need to make all that noise
just 'cause you finally cleared a jump.
Kagurazaka.
Sano, stop spacing out
and get on my level already.
Rise up and prove
you can be on par with me.
Or what?
Are you too scared to do that?
You must be joking.
I really can't stand to lose.
Then you'd better give it your all.
Would it kill him
to be more straightforward?
Sano, you did it!
Good job!
My brother?
What's up?
From my brother.
He says good luck.
Thank you, Onii-chan.
Mizuki...
What?
I don't know.
Unfortunately, Sano didn't make
it past the preliminaries.
Nevertheless, for him, it was a huge step.
Hurry up.
Wanna be late for the first day
of the new term?
Hey! Wait up, wait up!
And as of today, I, Ashiya Mizuki,
am now a second-year student
of Osaka Private High School.
Listen here, Mizuki.
Make sure you eat a balanced diet,
drink warm water...
Oh, and stay out of boys' rooms!
Wash your hands and gargle!
Dry your clothes in your own room!
Put the dryer on cold toward the end!
Don't stay up late!
And then...
Onii-chan!
You're going to miss your plane!
Next Time
Because I'm a Guy!