Episode 10
"Eleven's Request"
This is your payment for the job.
Also...
I looked into that matter for you.
Impressive as always,
Stud. You work quickly.
Shall I tell you here?
If it won't cause trouble for you.
In that case...
You had a long talk with
him again this morning.
I'd asked him for a small favor.
Here.
It's your third of the reward.
What?! I wasn't planning on getting paid.
You worked the hardest. It's only proper.
Are you okay with that, Blade?
It's our leader's decision.
Then don't mind if I do.
Welcome.
Hello.
The usual?
Yes, please.
May I discuss something private?
Do you need the room?
No, I'd like to speak with you.
Merchant's guild staff and adventurers
have met in that room, yes?
Please.
There are a few groups.
They meet roughly once a
month, carrying luggage.
I can't be sure, but a group matching
that description has been here.
When did they last come?
About a month ago.
Then they'll come again soon.
What time do they arrive?
Always around this time.
Welcome.
Two glasses of that whisky.
I thought they'd come today or
tomorrow. What good timing.
Don't do anything crazy.
I won't.
I'm meeting someone.
He's already here.
Nice night, isn't it?
How long do they normally stay?
Thirty minutes at most.
They don't stay long.
Perhaps I should've
brought someone with me.
It's hard to pass the time
at a bar when I can't drink.
Thank you.
If I'm to tail one...
it should be this one.
Adventurers tend to stay in the same
area, so I won't seem unnatural.
He turned? I don't think
there are any inns that way.
He could be luring me into a trap.
How did he know?
Perhaps I shouldn't today.
I knew it. You're tailing me.
You're the Blade's...
If you were tailing me,
does that mean you know?
Are you doing something you
don't want me to know about?
Screw you!
You're just the Blade's toady.
Don't get fresh with me!
People still think I'm a toady, do they?
Don't kill him.
That's how you're begging for your life?
Die!
No, you die.
Will he be okay?
He'll be fine.
Thank you. You saved me.
I heard you were tailing some
weird guy and came running.
Oh, are you still having me watched?
Then you probably haven't
noticed this either.
At least act a little flustered.
I knew it was you.
You didn't notice at first, did you?
I never would've noticed if you
were serious about tailing me.
I wasn't trying to avoid detection.
I noticed him.
Well, I'm not like you two.
So, who is this guy?
Do you recall how the
merchant guild's staff
stole labyrinth goods from Judge's shop?
But he's an adventurer.
Yes, an adventurer connected
to that staff member.
He'd get caught if he simply
sold the stolen goods,
so he gave them to an adventurer
to sell to the guild.
That's why nothing turned
up on the black market.
So I had Stud look into it.
I found exactly what you described.
Recently, this party has been bringing
in labyrinth goods above their rank.
He belongs to that party.
I have one request.
First thing tomorrow, could you confess
what you've done to the merchant's guild?
Listen...
No.
They have to go there themselves.
I don't want to rouse
suspicion by hurting them.
Want me to do it, then?
What?
You can do that?
You want it done tomorrow morning, right?
Don't worry. I won't
leave any visible marks.
In that case, perhaps
I'll have you do that.
I've got this.
This is your last chance.
Will you confess your crimes to
the merchant's guild tomorrow?
I will. I will, so please—
That's a shame.
It's really such a shame.
Don't hurt him too much.
I know.
His party's in on it, too.
Please get all of their names.
Got it.
Make sure he won't say we
threatened him for information.
And don't give him a
reason to hold a grudge.
Yeah, I know.
Move him.
Take him to base number
two. It's soundproof.
Was one of them watching me, too?
D-Don't!
We'll have this resolved
by tomorrow morning.
It's a bit late now, but should I
have asked him to do that for free?
Why not? Think of it as his
way of making it up to you.
I see.
And don't go places
like that by yourself.
Oh, please. I assumed
you'd be coming with me.
I wonder if they won't
take me seriously again.
But Mr. Lizel might want
the stolen goods someday.
The merchant's guild has
really gone downhill.
I heard the damage was pretty severe.
They say someone went
to complain every day.
I can't believe it was a
high-ranking staff member.
Could it be?
Hey! What's the meaning of this?
How are you going to take
responsibility for this?
We demand a guarantee!
An apology won't cut it!
Excuse me...
One moment, plea—
We're terribly sorry for the
inconvenience caused by our incompetence!
What?!
All the stolen items have been recovered.
This way, please.
These are those items.
Once again, we're terribly
sorry for what happened.
Please raise your head.
Thank you for recovering the goods.
Again, we're terribly sorry.
So, may I ask what happened?
Of course.
This morning, a group of
adventurers came to the guild.
They confessed to working with
guild staff to sell stolen goods.
Because they named their accomplice,
rumors spread instantly.
What happened to the staff member?
He noticed the commotion
and attempted to flee.
He was arrested by some officers
who found him suspicious.
We'll work with the police to ensure
the staff member is justly punished.
We'll let you know as soon
as a decision's been made.
Th-That's all right. I'm just
glad I got my goods back.
If you'll excuse me.
Thank you for stopping by.
So that's what happened.
I was worried since you'd
seemed down recently.
I'm sorry.
So, um...
Oh, me?
I'm Eleven, and I'm currently convincing
them to let me join their party.
Nice to meet you!
What?!
Why are you so surprised?
B-But...
Mr. Lizel, um...
are you really going to
let him join your party?
That doesn't seem like a good idea.
Spoken like a true appraiser.
Do you disapprove?
I just think if you're letting
someone join your party,
they should be more, well...
It's all right. He hasn't joined us yet.
R-Really? Never mind, then.
If you really don't want him
to join us, I won't let him.
Hey, wait!
Judge, right?
Are you really against me
joining their party? Why?
M-Mr. Lizel, help—
What do you think about this?
C'mon, why?
A-Ask Stud!
Huh?
He actually left.
He must be stupid.
By the way, there's no merchant's
guild in Marcade, is there?
No.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Typical Situation
Merchant's Guild
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Meet Conditions
& Register
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Inspect &
Provide Services
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Shop
They're basically self-governed.
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Marcade
Local Lord
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
No restrictions
on starting businesses
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Man      age
May join guild
if desired
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Shop
The lord manages everything directly.
Is Mr. Insigh registered with the guild?
Yes.
Trading merchants frequently deal with
other nations, so it's necessary.
Then I'm sure he'll hear about this.
I actually sent him a letter
saying you seemed down recently.
What?
I said I wanted to give
you something to cheer you up
and asked about your preferences.
I'm sure he'll be able
to connect the dots.
What?
He might think I'm a pathetic shopkeeper.
Should I not have done that?
Oh, no.
Your concern for me is, um...
very much appreciated.
If that doting grandfather hears about
this, worst case, he could quit the guild.
The guild is screwed if they
lose someone that big.
Does this guy know that?
Shall we get something to eat to
celebrate the situation being resolved?
It'll be my treat.
I-I'd love to go.
Oh, but let me pay for it.
Even if he does, he
probably doesn't care.
Sit with me.
Nah. The boss would kill me.
Are you my shadow today?
Something like that.
Thank you for last night.
Did you get enough sleep?
That's what you're worried
about? I'm fine.
Anyway, did you need something from me?
I was pleased to have spotted my shadow
for the first time and called you over.
Are you serious?
Also, since you're here, maybe you
could tell me about your boss.
Like what?
Anything. Perhaps his behavior
has improved recently.
It hasn't.
If my answers determine whether he joins
their party or not, I could lose my head.
It's okay. You can tell me
exactly what he's like.
Well, his attitude towards you
guys changed a few days ago.
We're not so much watching
you as guarding you.
Guarding me?
He doesn't want you to have any problems.
How did yesterday go?
I may have been too casual
about asking him to do that.
If anything, he seemed happy about it.
He felt like you were counting on him.
You seem to have known
him for a long time.
I've known him since he joined the gang.
So are some subordinates just
fodder, while others aren't?
I have another question.
How would you feel if I killed
many of the gang's underlings
aside from elite members like you?
We're all disposable.
If anything, us underlings should
be honored to be killed by you.
Then... tell him
to come see me tomorrow morning.
You probably meant what you said.
But I would never kill you.
You two have gotten really friendly.
Did I say you could talk to him?
He called me over.
He did? Really? And you
let him see your face?
You got to meet him last night, but
don't let that get to your head.
This guy's about to kill me.
When you return, if you don't report
every word that was said, I'll kill you.
Morning!
You're back?
He invited me today.
Is he still asleep?
He usually is at this hour unless
he's got something to do.
Excuse me.
Oh, it's you. Did you come to
complain to Mr. Lizel again?
No, I'm here on an errand today.
Unfortunately, he's still asleep.
Well, that's no good.
There's someone who'd
like to see him today.
Shall I wake him?
Yes, plea—
Hey! What if you broke it?!
Sorry.
I'm sure you heard, but
he's still asleep.
So?
Wait until he wakes up.
I'm here on behalf of a busy man.
Yeah, so wait until he wakes up so you
can take him with you right away.
Get that through your stupid head, loser.
Do you realize I'm a police officer,
and you're obstructing my duties?
Of course I do. I hate the police.
Stop right there!
I'm not letting you kill
each other on my doorstep!
Forgive me.
Ah, Captain. You're here as well.
Morning.
My apologies for keeping you waiting.
Not at all.
So, you've got something to do, right?
Yes.
He has time for me today, does he?
Shall we go?
There's no time. Let's hurry.
While I still have the
chance, let me ask you.
Do you still want to join my party?
Yes, obviously.
Why?
Why? Because...
At first I was just curious,
but since then...
Hey.
Some huge shopkeeper hates my guts.
I'm sure he does.
What?
Why do you serve that guy, anyway?
I want nothing from him.
My only and greatest joy is
to grant him his desires.
You sound like a fanatic.
Don't compare me to those who
seek something in return.
Oh...
So that's how it is.
I want to be with you.
Let me be with you.
Then let's do what has to be done.
Next Time
"Welcome to the Party"
Next time: "Welcome to the Party."
Illustration by: Ugonba