SCHOOL FESTIVAL REPS
BOYS:
GIRLS:
I feel so bad for the girls!
Talk about rotten luck.
SCHOOL FESTIVAL REPS
BOYS: MAEHARA MAKI
GIRLS:
Whoever wins has to babysit Maehara.
Please... Please no.
All right! I struck out!
Yay, struck out!
Yes! Safe!
Do you all hate Maehara-kun or something?
Why are you acting like this?
Why do you have to shun
and exclude him so much?
He hasn't done anything wrong.
So tell me why!
Sensei, can I volunteer for the position?
Huh?
I'd like to work with Maehara-kun.
I mean...
I'd prefer to pick someone
who actually wants to do it, too.
Are you okay with that, Maehara-kun?
If Amami-san says so,
I have no complaints.
Wait, Sensei.
I won.
What?
But Asanagi-san...
Whoever draws the winning lot gets
the job. That's how it works, right?
I have the time, so I'll do it.
But I said I'd do it—
Owwie.
You need to calm down, Yuu.
I get that the way they were treating
Maehara-kun ticked you off.
But you took it a little too far.
Just take a look around.
Oh, s-sorry, Umi. I...
Come on. I'm not the one
you need to apologize to.
Sorry for acting out like that, everyone.
Maehara-kun, I'm sorry for
putting you on the spot, too.
Oh, I'm not bothered by it at all.
Anyway, as per the results of the lottery,
our class reps for the festival will be
Maehara Maki and me, Asanagi Umi.
We look forward to your support, guys.
A/V ROOM
Man, you're amazing, Asanagi.
Aren't I? Feel free to praise me more.
Okay, now you're getting carried away.
Though I guess I have to
hand it to you this time.
Yuu's the one who's actually
amazing, though.
She went at them straight up,
not caring about ruining the vibes.
It's so cool that she can get angry
on somebody's behalf like that.
I mean, it must've felt good
when she yelled at the class, right?
Meanwhile,
I prioritize positive vibes over all else,
so I could never do something like that.
Is everybody here?
I'm Seki, the student council president.
Let's get right down to business.
This is the first meeting of this year's
school festival executive committee.
Why did Asanagi sound a little down?
I guess homeroom did turn
into a mess over me.
I gotta do this and show everyone!
Umi!
You waited for us? You didn't have to.
No, but...
Thanks for today. Thanks so much.
You waited for me just to say that?
Yeah.
If you hadn't stopped me, I...
I would've said much nastier things.
I figured.
Thank you, actually.
Huh?
Why?
WINNER
Who wants to see infighting when
we're supposed to work as a team?
I know, right?
You were my knight
in shining armor back there.
It's been ages since
you've called me that.
DECOR
There you have it.
Our class has been put
in charge of the decor.
What?
Stop that.
Quit complaining just because
we couldn't do a maid café.
If you can be proactive and
come up with decor ideas,
some cosplay on the day might not be
out of the realm of possibility.
Whoa!
For Yuu and Nina, that is.
Wha?!
Why just Ninacchi and me? What about you?
I'm the producer this time.
It's imperative that we exploit you two
to secure #1 on the popularity ranking.
Isn't that right, Maehara-kun?
Don't ask me.
So, anybody got any decor ideas?
Um...
I do have an idea.
Go for it, Maehara-kun.
Mosaic art using cans, huh?
DECOR
EMPTY CAN MOSAIC ART
Nice going, Maehara.
You actually thought this out.
Th-That wore me out.
What? That was only the first discussion.
I'm so glad I'm working with you.
If this were Amami-san or someone else,
my nerves would've given out midway.
Right? You should be
thanking my lucky stars...
is what I'd like to say...
Here, a gift for you.
That's the lot I drew the other day.
Sorry. I actually didn't win.
What? You came up with that idea
in the middle of that disaster?
You're really amazing.
Aren't you gonna tell me off?
I cheated, you know?
If you'd cheated people out of
something they wanted, sure.
WINNER
So...
I'm glad you drew the winner.
I see.
Thanks, Maehara.
Color Sorting Minister Amami here!
Red ones go there!
And yellow ones over here!
Ugh, I'm not happy with this.
I ended up just copying the original.
This is plenty impressive.
So we paint this in, pixelate it,
and decide on a color scheme.
After that, we'll just have to punch holes
in tons of cans and connect them.
Umi!
What's the matter, Color Sorting Minister?
Reporting in!
We have too many dirty cans with
stuff like cigarette butts in them!
Let's put those aside and wash them later.
We should probably wash out
the sugary drink cans, too.
Oh, hey, a manga.
Hey, can I try drawing this?
Done!
What do you think?
I just drew a pose I came up with.
Amami-san... are you actually
a pro illustrator in secret?
Oh, please! But I'm glad I drew something
I'm happy with. It's been a while.
Asanagi-san?
I-If she's this good,
we should leave the art to Yuu.
Are you sure? But who'll be
the Color Sorting Minister?
We can have Nina take over.
Roger that!
Umi, Maki-kun! Let's do this!
Sure.
Whoa, this is crazy good!
Yuu drew that.
Seriously?
She really can do it all.
Other than study.
Thanks for cleaning up that mess
during homeroom, Asanagi-chan.
We were too mean to Maehara-kun.
We got carried away.
Of course Yuu-chan would get angry.
If you hadn't stopped it there,
we might've...
Maehara's working his butt off,
so help him out, okay?
Yep.
See ya.
GOOD WORK, ASANAGI
PRAISE ME MORE
ATTAGIRL
DON'T FEEL PRESSURED TO COME OVER ON
FRIDAY. YOU CAN GO HOME AND REST UP.
This feels like a rarity these days.
Oh, for the love of...
KARAOKE CAN
What is it? What's up?
Oh, sorry, are you out?
I just felt like it wouldn't be right
to make adjustments on my own.
Okay, and?
And, uh... if you feel like it...
Uh-huh?
Wanna come over for some food and games
while we go over the design?
Or something?
I see. So you're lonely without me around.
That's not what I'm saying.
Don't lie to me. I see right through you.
Come on, just spit it out.
"I, Maehara Maki, am currently
missing Asanagi Umi to death!"
W-Wrong!
Fine, I'll just do this by myself!
Bye!
Wait, wait.
On second thought, can I come over?
I kind of miss you, too.
Umi? Is something the matter?
Sorry, something came up at home.
I'm gonna head out.
O-Okay.
Heya.
Heya. Come on in.
Hey, Maehara.
What?
Just felt like saying it.
What the heck?
Hey, you've made a lot of progress.
I'm really sorry for summoning you
out of the blue.
Can I lie down for a bit?
Sure. You can take a nap if you want, too.
You want me to take a nap? Here?
Someone's being quite daring.
Hey, you slept just fine the other day!
I guess it's okay.
Masaki-san's given me permission to
kick your ass if you try anything funny.
Sheesh, that mother of mine.
Hey, Maehara.
What?
You see, I think I...
Huh?!
Amami-san?
Good evening, Maki-kun.
Sorry for showing up so late.
Umi? I know you're there.
Come in first.
It's okay. I won't stay long.
I don't want to intrude
on your alone time.
Listen, Yuu. I wasn't trying to...
Amami-san.
When did you figure us out?
She'd been making a lot of excuses lately,
and she seemed oddly comfortable here.
Umi, why didn't you tell me
you were hanging out with Maki-kun?
Well...
Sorry, it's my fault.
I asked her to keep it a secret.
Umi.
Is that true?
Why won't you say anything?
Do you not trust me?
Am I the only one who thinks of us
as best friends?
Do you not see me as that?
That's not it!
Then why?
I...
Umi!
I'm so glad we're in the same class again!
She's so pretty.
Like a model or something.
You could brag about being friends
with someone like that.
Oh, are you free next weekend?
Oh, sorry. I have plans.
Me, too.
Sorry, Umi-chan.
All good.
Over here, Yuu-chan!
Sorry! Did you wait long?
Took you long enough.
That's the one thing I can't tell you.
I don't want to.
Maehara, sorry I got you mixed up in this.
I'll be heading out now.
Wait, Umi! I'll go with you!
Please let me go by myself.
Sorry, Yuu. I'm such a jerk.
What do I do, Maki-kun?
I've never seen Umi like that.
AMAMI-SAN LEFT
HELLO?
ASANAGI?
She read them, but she didn't respond.
She's not going to skip school, right?
Morning.
Morning, Maki-kun.
Morning, Amami-san.
And Asanagi-san, too.
Hey.
She seems the same as usual.
TODAY
MAKI-KUN, SORRY ABOUT THIS
Amami-san?
Um, so it's about Umi.
Have you talked to her since?
No, I haven't. How about you?
Me neither, actually.
I felt too awkward to reach out to her.
But she came to pick me up on Monday
morning like nothing happened,
so I thought maybe you'd
smoothed things over with her.
Did she say anything?
"Sorry about Friday. Forget about it."
That's it.
I had my hands full just keeping Asanagi
and my secret under wraps.
That's the one thing I can't tell you.
I don't want to.
What if Asanagi had to deal with
all that and a secret of her own?
What if she had to bear
that burden all by herself?
Ninacchi, no problems with squad B?
Hmm, I think we're a bit short on reds.
Should we get everybody
together to drink Core Cola?
A... Asanagi-san.
Do you have a sec?
What is it?
I've got something
important to say to you.
Uh, I need to stay here
to give out instructions.
We'll be fine. We're checking
the design as we work.
You can go, Umi.
Squad B will be fine
without you reps around, too.
Come with me, Asanagi.
You idiot! You stupid idiot!
It's supposed to be a secret
that we're friends!
But you tied my hands
by asking in front of everybody!
It's your fault for leaving me on read.
W-Well, I mean, I...
Anyway, let's get the work
out of the way first.
That goes in black.
Hey, Maehara.
What?
Aren't you gonna ask?
About what?
Why I've been avoiding you,
and all that other stuff.
Do you wanna talk about it?
I don't...
but I know this can't go on forever.
The thing with Yuu, too.
Frankly, I do wanna ask, and I do
wanna know what you're thinking.
But I'm not going to force it out of you.
Are you sure? I might not ever tell you.
That's fine, too.
I'll wait until you're ready.
Maehara, you dumbass.
Wait, what?
You stupid idiot!
I like how nice you are, but when you
take that too far, you're just a softie!
And some nasty person might
take advantage of you someday.
A nasty coward like me, for example.
U-Uh...
Don't! You're not allowed to turn around!
Say, Maehara.
If I said I wanted to fess up,
would you hear me out?
I would.
Also, could I ask you to wait
until after the school festival?
It's up to you.
Thanks.
I'll hash it out with Yuu, too.
So just give me some time.
Sure.
JOUTOU HIGH SCHOOL FESTIVAL
Yeah!
Even I could pull it off, huh?
Yeah.
Asanagi, can I ask you for something?
If you don't want to, that's fine.
But can we hold hands?
Oh, it's just...
It seemed like you were cold.
Are you trying to lift my spirits?
You? Looking out for me?
Your hand's so warm.
Gee, thanks.
Thanks. That helped me relax some.
You're late, Yuu.
Sorry, Umi. I got too into
talking to some friends.
Hey!
Over here, you two!
Oh, we need to introduce them to Maki-kun.
Umi and I have been friends
with them since elementary school.
Wrong, Yuu.
That may be true for you,
but it's not for me.
After all, you two don't really
see me as a friend, do you?
Asanagi...
This is sooner than I planned,
but hear me out, Maehara and Yuu.
Let me tell you about my petty
little inferiority complex.
Translation: Sriram Gurunathan
Subtitle Editing: Geoff Mazzolini
Subtitle Timing: Krzysztof Kunc
Quality Check: Ashley Barboza
Translation Check: David Saylor
"From Now On, and Then On."