Bring Despair to the Earth, and…
Hey, does this mean...?
The backstage has been restored?
Not just that. It's calling for us.
That means XENOS hasn't given up.
Lord Apollo?!
It can't be...
Lord Apollo didn't trust us to do our job?
It's you he doesn't trust.
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
It's Show Time
The price of living in the time of freedom
"So, what do you want to do?"
Just standing there with my empty body
Like a calling to protect the world
I craved an unequaled gift
Lost in night's darkness
Until a voice called out to me
Like the light that declares the dawn
I'll take you with me at
any cost (I pray and wish)
Beyond the Echo-verse (To the future)
Just being with you makes me strong
It's not an exaggeration
That encounter was a supernova
(Our eyes were locked)
In an instant, everything that I am
(In an instant)
Will be changed forever (Just to be)
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
Destiny is Calling us now
Just to be who we are
Just to be by your side
The Mirage has exuded!
The coordinates are...
Right above us?!
Since they know the headquarters
of SI-VIS, it was just a matter of...
We should probably
think about moving, President.
The stage has been set
on the rooftop of Harmonia!
Connecting to the backstage!
All members are on standby!
Don't you try to start without us.
You're gonna pay for that later, okay?
Why? Why did you come?
You physically left the home world?
Lord Archon is watching over
Lady Eden. No need to worry.
You don't trust me?
I finally understand
your thought process.
I can now see from the bottom
of my heart that they're pests.
I've finally made up
my mind to crush them.
You'll continue to deal with Earth.
But there's one thing...
I need to assess it myself...
Whether that girl
is the heir to the Diva or not.
Idea is rising above the expected value.
Twelve thousand, thirteen thousand!
Go for it, everyone!
The hell?! Is that guy messing with us?
Or he has complete confidence
against SI-VIS.
On his own?
Who is that?
It's not the pervy old man
or the quibbling old hag.
So you are SI-VIS.
You raise Idea by singing and
protect your planet from your enemies.
Are you the guardians of the
planet or simply drones?
Now we've got a senile
armchair philosopher.
Wait, I saw him earlier.
Yosuke's old friend.
No, he attacked Nagi and Yosuke
when they came to Earth. An enemy!
Yosuke-kun knew him?
XENOS attacked Yosuke and Nagi?
Holy crap!
They found out at the worst possible time!
What are you going to do, President?
If they get upset...
Listen, everyone.
Yosuke and Nagi are...
Um, sorry to interrupt,
but is this gonna take long?
What?
We don't have time for that.
Or more like...
We don't actually care.
Who Yosuke-kun and Nagi-chan really are?
We know who they are.
They're the members of SI-VIS.
Everyone.
And that's not all.
About Kyoya and Nagi...
Huh? Hold on. That I need to hear!
Oh, Kyoya. After you hear this, you'll
know you're forever in Nagi's debt.
Well, it's... um...
So Nagi-chan has dirt on Kyoya-kun.
Dirt on Kyoya?!
I can't let that go.
μ, give me a hint!
You wanna hear? I'm not gonna tell you!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I see. I will retract my earlier
statement of calling you drones.
You connect with your teammates
and improve one another.
And the five of you are able to release
Idea equal to tens of thousands of people.
It wasn't a mistake to say
you are the biggest threat we face.
You come at us alone, knowing that?
I can use my power
to the fullest if I'm alone.
That way, I won't have to drag anyone in.
I get it. You care for your friends.
And you're the strongest.
You're the last boss, aren't you?
The ranking of strength
is a matter of opinion,
but it is true that I carry the wishes of
XENOS on my shoulders.
Which means if we can handle you,
we can protect the Earth, right?
I am called Apollo.
I am Kyoya of SI-VIS.
I'll carry on Yosuke-kun's wishes
and protect the Earth.
I'll make sure everyone survives!
Nagi!
I don't care who you are
or where you're from.
For now, I want you
to sing... for me, for us!
Yes! Listen, Kyoya!
Playing music!
Go beyond time to the Destination of Life
The stage is set!
The members are going up on the stage!
Idea has exceeded 30,000!
What?! We just got started!
Like the light that
drives away the darkness
But it's true.
This is crazy.
I embrace our united wish
and look straight ahead
The enemy is ascending
to the stage as well!
He's breaking through
the outer wall of the stage!
Believing in a different future
I could see salvation beyond the darkness
Because you noticed the presence of light
The reason the light feels so bright
Is because you understand the darkness
Go across time and space
to the Destination of Life
Everyone's moving so well
as the Idea increases!
The best performance we could ask for!
Like a prayer that dispels the haze
That man.
I'll simply sing this wish by your side
He's doing the same thing as me.
One hundred twenty thousand.
One hundred twenty-six...
What's going on here?!
Seeking a different future
Idea is higher than ever before,
so how are we neck and neck with him?!
Can I see the details
of the Idea's scatter diagram?
I've been trying to,
but they're too close to each other.
Don't tell me he's...!
We can't reach him?!
Damn it, his defense is tight.
Don't give up, guys!
If we keep on attacking, then surely...!
The shouts filled with desire
as my spirit burns
Surely what?
Link together to give me strength
Just try to end this battle
before I unleash Helios on you.
Hurry up, everyone!
Nagi?
Idea... It's gathering toward him.
The Idea of an unbelievable
number of people!
You could see the pain in my profile
Because you didn't look away
and kept your gaze
Lord Apollo. You've finally chosen to...
You are able to keep your gaze
It's not just SI-VIS's Idea that's rising?
Because you've conquered
and overcame your weakness
Idea analysis is going up on screen!
I've never seen this before.
Neither XENOS nor the Mirage had a way
to raise their Idea on their own.
That's why SI-VIS could fight against
them since we can raise our Idea.
Does it mean they have
a monster like Nagi on their side?
What?!
That bastard!
Your wishes will never reach me.
Because... the wishes of all XENOS...
Their Idea...
It's all on my shoulders!
Kyoya?
μ?
Soji?
June-san?
This... can't be happening!
I was going to take down June and SI-VIS!
No. No!
What was it that I wished for?!
Do I smile? Do I raise a cry of victory?
Should I be relieved
that the pests were crushed?
I... Did I...
Did I really want something so pointless?
Everyone! Please respond!
Kyoya! μ! Please! Say someth—
Please stand by
Kyoya! μ! Please! Say something!
So you're supposed
to be the heir to the Diva?
The hope of salvation for us XENOS?
Everything about you is inadequate!
Because you have no power,
my comrades have fallen.
Me?
If you could control Idea at will,
then even I would've found it
difficult to defeat you.
But that wasn't the case.
Samael and Medea were mistaken.
I fail to see the value they saw in you.
Therefore, as SI-VIS,
as a human being, you shall perish.
Labyrinth, huh?
What do you plan to do,
trapping me in here...
Medea?
It is too early to turn our backs on Nagi.
But she was unable to do anything.
If she couldn't drive me away
or protect her friends,
there's no way she could save XENOS.
She grew up on Earth.
It will take time for her to gain
XENOS's, the Diva's, power.
Not everyone is strong, almighty,
and perfect like you.
Of course, neither am I.
Yes, Medea. You're inadequate.
Your loyalty to XENOS,
your devotion to your duty.
I devote my life to righteous duty.
But does your decision
fall under that category?
You doubt my judgment?
If she disappears, so does
the hope for Earth.
This is a battle for survival
to begin with.
Erasing the hope of Earth has been our—
And what we gain by that
is temporary Idea to be used up.
It is not the Idea of blessing
our Diva Lady Eden has produced
that has supported us for years.
And you think this immature girl
is capable of singing that blessing?
The tainted Diva who grew up
on the tainted Earth?
It is true that Earth may
not have the order we do.
They're cumbersome,
disorganized, and incohesive.
They're animals who release
Idea uncontrollably.
No, they would look like
pests in your eyes.
But still, they produce
Idea and improve each other.
They're doing something we can't.
You want to protect the blood of
the Diva and the fate of Earth?
You sound like Orphe.
Orphe was right.
Haven't you come to realize
he was right, too?
If she becomes Lady Eden's heir,
XENOS will find its true salvation.
It may take a long time, but both XENOS
and the earthlings can be saved.
The future Orphe dreamed of
can be achieved, do you not agree?!
Orphe this, Orphe that.
You also fell for that imbecile.
You were right, Samael.
The secondary?!
Man, you just had to step
on a landmine, didn't you?
Samael, did you not find
the earthlings amusing?
Did you not see hope in them?
That's a different interpretation, Medea.
I found hope...
in the Earth as a mighty foe.
Medea-san?
Medea, you said there was a way
to save both XENOS and the earthlings
even if it'd take a long time.
But the road to salvation
must not be any longer, not even a step.
If there's even the slightest
possibility of a detour,
then I will not hesitate
to save XENOS alone!
Before you kill her,
shouldn't we check in with Archon?
She is kin to the Diva, after all.
Do as you wish.
Well then, now that that's over with...
Why don't you come with me, Miss Diva?
I kindly gave you a chance for survival.
You'd be better off doing exactly
what you're told, you know?
A chance for survival?
Yeah, because you're Eden the Diva's—
Is there a chance for Kyoya to survive?
Huh?
A chance for μ, Soji, June-san...
everyone at Harmonia, everyone
Kyoya holds dear, to survive?
Look at that.
She's shamefully begging for their lives!
Tell me!
If you stay here until the Mirage closes,
then you disappear along with SI-VIS.
You, SI-VIS, Harmonia, they all disappear
from the memories of the world.
And we'll take this world
without any resistance.
It's the exact outcome Apollo had in mind.
But if you agree to my condition,
you can hold on to a glimmer of hope.
Although that choice may be
a double-edged sword for Earth.
Your condition?
Don't do it, Nagi.
Don't listen to what they tell you.
Kyoya!
Here we go.
Don't you want to say goodbye?
I'm fine.
I know I'll be seeing him again very soon.
Bring Pandora to Earth, and give
the one-and-only Elpis to SI-VIS.
Medea, you take this one.
It's getting exciting.
With our convictions at stake,
why don't we destroy each other?
Huh?
What's that? Is it floating?
No, it's falling down!
G-Get out of here!
Nagi! Nagi!
Move! Move!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Tomoko Takedani Sater
Krzysztof Kunc
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Michelle Tymon
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Tomoko Takedani Sater
Krzysztof Kunc
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Michelle Tymon
In the musical stave
WOW, I let my feelings play
My bright future
WOW, started to shine
Unparalleled
With a smile on my face
I feel like I can even change
the world with you
(3, 2, 1, Singing over)
Intertwining harmony (Harmony)
I wouldn't have believed in miracles alone
This breathless heartbeat (Heart Beat)
I'll let it resonate in
the night sky with my voice
Our dream at full blast
Singing over, forever
Lan lan la la la