Aresh-sama scolded me severely,
but the ultimate goal of this expedition
is the holy maiden's purification.
If her mental state becomes such
that we achieve no results,
this is a huge financial loss.
Besides, in the end, I can't rest easy
unless I verify things with my own eyes.
ISEKAI OFFICE WORKER: THE OTHER WORLD'S
BOOKS DEPEND ON THE BEAN COUNTER
EPISODE 6: I MADE A PROPOSAL
Yua, do you think you can do it?
I can.
Yua!
Ist-san, what's the progress
of the purification?
Huh?
The purification.
Oh, let me see.
About 30% or so?
In that case, we'll need to organize
at least three more expeditions.
The cost of each expedition is hefty,
so I was hoping to do this in one go...
Yua, you did well.
Was I of any help?
Of course! You truly are our holy maiden.
Looks like she's at her limit.
Hey, I told you not to leave
my side. What are you doing?
I asked Ist-san and the royal sorcery
department for a small favor.
Why did you go to the
royal sorcery department?
My third royal order has more
experience when it comes to magic.
In that case, Aresh-sama,
I have work for you.
Work?
Since civil officials couldn't come,
I'm short on manpower.
We'll be all set with the third
royal order's help, right, Ist-san?
Hold it! I wasn't informed of this!
What is it you're planning?!
Huh?
I discussed everything with
Assistant Director Ist beforehand.
Is that true, Ist?!
Um, perhaps?
Ist!
This again?
Figures.
Now, now. Doesn't it all work out?
As we need people highly practiced
with magical energy and in magic studies,
this could only be handled by
the royal sorcery department.
Accordingly, we'll grant special
compensation for the job.
Can a mere assistant director of
accounting decide something like that?
Please, rest assured.
Both my director and His Excellency
have already signed off on it.
Indeed...
That should be enough
for their department.
I'll have Director Zoltan,
who's always eager to be in charge,
instruct the others while Ist-san selects
members more resistant to magicules.
Now, I'd like everyone
of the third royal order...
Halt.
On whose authority are you
doing whatever you please?
His Excellency the Prime Minister.
I have a letter here entrusting
this matter to me.
I'm in charge of this
purification expedition!
Yes, which is why this was entrusted
to me as a separate affair.
A separate affair?
Your Highness,
you should see to reassuring
Her Holiness and getting her
somewhere to rest.
I-I'd like to stay behind
with you, Kondou-san!
Yua?
Has she only now realized
the dangers of this world
and the precariousness
of her own position?
Still, there's nothing I can
do for her right now.
You seem quite tired, Your Holiness.
Please return to the town we set out
from this morning and get some rest.
So, what is it you intend to do?
Huh?
As I said, I'm in charge here.
The damage from the miasma is
the most pressing issue in our kingdom.
I can't leave matters to an
otherworlder who knows nothing.
Oh?
As a prince of this kingdom,
it at least appears he's strongly
motivated regarding the miasma.
Then, Your Highness, please stand back
with your guard to observe at a distance.
Seiichirou, what should the knights do?
Please protect the members
of the royal sorcery department
and record the details
of the barrier they cast.
Barrier? What are you going to protect?
We're going to protect this kingdom.
What nonsense are you spouting?
Barrier spells are a complex form of magic
that only a select few can use.
A barrier large enough
to cover the entire kingdom
would require far more
sorcerers than we have.
Isn't that right, Zoltan?
Yes, Your Highness. We only have eight
here capable of casting the spell.
You need only think of it
the other way around.
We know the root of the miasma,
so we just need to shift our perspective.
We can simply seal the source.
Let's begin.
So we cast a barrier approximately three
meters in radius around the tree
and determine the concentration
of miasma inside...
Then we plant various flora
around the area
to document how long it takes
for the barrier to weaken, huh?
Yes.
It's not a permanent spell, after all.
In the end, once Shiraishi-san
finishes the purification,
we'll cast the barrier again,
station guards around the forest,
and have the spell reinforced regularly
to prevent any miasma leakage.
Meanwhile, if we find a way to eliminate
the source of the miasma itself...
I'd never even considered something
like this before you suggested it.
Probably because of the holy maiden.
Few bother to consider other
more time-consuming solutions
when an easy one is available to them.
It's intellectual laziness.
But, well, there won't be a need
to summon holy maidens from
another world with this method.
Basically, I'm telling the kingdom
it should wipe its own ass.
Granted, the holy maiden is
a symbol of hope to the people
and an ace up the kingdom's sleeve.
Convincing the king that one is no longer
necessary will take more work...
Aresh-sama, I still have
a lot of work to do.
Save it for later.
You were exposed to miasma today.
We need to reinforce your barrier.
True. Even the knights with high magicule
resistance were feeling unwell,
yet I was fine thanks to the barrier.
I can't thank him enough,
but...
I wonder when it started.
I've grown aware of his feelings,
but right now...
Aresh-sama, do we need to go this far?
We do.
W-We really don't, do we?
We need physical contact to familiarize me
with his magic, not acts of pleasure.
Wait, Aresh-sama...
Kondu, you here?
We're in the middle of something. Leave.
I sensed the commander's magical
energy from Kondu at the banquet.
It's odd for someone
with no magical resistance
to emit another's energy...
Hey, don't run away.
So this is how it happened.
This is a perfectly normal reaction.
Let's do this another time, Aresh-sama.
No. You'll just use your glib tongue
to gloss things over and escape.
Um...
Can I stay here and watch?
I'm fine now that we're
somewhere with less miasma.
I have documents to submit upon
our return that still need organizing.
Also, starting tomorrow, I'll be riding
in a royal sorcery department carriage.
Ist-san, we can discuss what you
wanted to talk about as we ride.
Got it.
And so, the only ones who lack resistance
to magical energy are usually newborns.
But since you have zero
resistance as an adult,
It's already been over two hours...
Why are researchers so single-minded when
they find something that interests them?
Commander Indolark cast an
advanced barrier spell on you
and he's acclimating you
to magical energy himself.
This is most unusual!
Assistant Director Ist of the
royal sorcery department...
Your body is permeated with the
commander's magical energy waves,
Apparently, he's from a merchant
family rather than a noble one.
allowing magic to circulate within you,
He's incredibly dedicated
to his pursuit of magic
which acts as the organ thought
to be the core of magical energy...
and highly skilled in
a wide range of spells.
He's gifted in a different way
from Aresh-sama.
The magical circulation system
consists of an organ to move
magical energy throughout you.
The topic is very interesting,
but I still have countless things to do.
Since you don't have this organ,
I suspect another organ has activated
in its place. I think it's probably...
I need to report to Prime Minister Camile,
make arrangements with
our collaborators, and...
This is a crucial time.
I sent swift notice to Viscount Blanc
and prepared the documents
in case of an emergency.
Now, all that's left is...
You're still awake?
It would seem the people of this kingdom
don't knock before entering.
I knocked, but you didn't respond.
Aresh-sama, we return to
the royal capital tomorrow.
I still have some accounting
work I need to finish.
If things are going to be
even busier tomorrow,
then all the more reason for a
protective barrier. Am I wrong?
No...
I really appreciate it.
It's true that I can't afford
to collapse right now.
He's thinking about me
more than I expected.
Without him, I'd already be dead by now.
There are still things I need
to prioritize at the moment,
so I can't properly address
his feelings yet.
I'll need to think about them seriously
once everything is over...
Hey.
Yes?
I don't plan on letting anyone
else take care of you. Got it?
No...
Hang on. Are you seriously
saying that now?
What's wrong with saying it right now?
Well, whether or not you
say something like that,
my life still depends on your help
familiarizing me with magical energy.
True.
That's why you can't leave me, right?
I mean, it's simply the humane thing to...
That's what makes this the most efficient.
That's true...
Y-You have a point there.
It's better to make our intentions clear.
Actions based on clear intentions
are easier to understand.
But have you never considered
that I might feel awkward
toward you and develop negative feelings?
No.
You're a man who always
prioritizes efficiency,
so you value outcomes more than
the words and actions of others.
He knows me so well
that I can't even argue.
No matter how things turn out, Seiichirou,
I know you can't give
me an answer right now.
Which is why...
I'm going to take advantage of that.
After all, it's the most efficient method.
Raise your head.
This man is Nor's biological father,
as well as the king of the Romany Kingdom.
It's my first time seeing him up close.
First of all, thank you for your
hard work during the expedition.
I heard that,
in addition to the purification, you took
additional measures against the miasma.
I received a report from Viscount Blanc.
What?!
What report?
May I speak, sire?
You may.
I became acquainted with
Viscount Blanc through his son,
who works with me in the
accounting department.
For the sake of the kingdom,
and by extension,
the royal family,
the viscount commissioned me
to conduct experiments regarding the
long-term effects of miasma damage.
Even if Norbert's illegitimate,
the king still entrusted
his own son to the viscount.
It's clear how much the king trusts him.
And I was merely helping the viscount...
At least, that's the story.
After consulting with
His Excellency the Prime Minister,
we concluded that we ought not
unnecessarily worry Your Majesty.
I offer my sincerest apologies for failing
to report until after I had results.
The spread of the miasma has currently
been halted temporarily.
Though how long the
barrier lasts is a factor,
as long as we periodically send
sorcerers to recast the spell,
the blight of the miasma
can be considered resolved.
What nonsense!
Our kingdom already has the holy maiden!
There's no need for such unnecessary acts!
Silence! You are in the
presence of the king!
Comparing the cost of
summoning the holy maiden
and all of her estimated expenses
for the next fifty years
to casting and maintaining a barrier
for the same amount of time...
The difference in price is fivefold.
As for maintaining the barrier seal...
We are still in the experimental stage,
but even after three days, we have not
yet received any report of failure.
How dare you belittle the holy maiden
with such financial scheming?
Her Holiness is a national treasure!
Have some shame!
He's right! What do you think
you know about Her Holiness?!
Our kingdom stands because
of the holy maiden!
You're just a weakling from another
world trying to tarnish her prestige!
I...
I want to go home!
I'll do my best as the holy maiden...
But there's nothing left for me
once that's over, right?!
Please send me back to my own world!
What are you saying, Yua?
You're our one and only holy maiden.
Even after the purification is complete,
our kingdom will cherish you dearly.
Wh-Why?
Wasn't I summoned to
perform the purification?
You won't need me after that's done.
That's not true.
The very presence of the holy maiden
guides our kingdom to prosperity.
K-Kondou-san!
As I mentioned earlier, I believe
the role of holy maiden
will no longer be necessary
in the future.
However, at present, there is no way
for us to return to our original world.
No way... No...
Yua!
No way... No!
Mom! Dad! Big Brother! I miss them...
Your Holiness, the holy maiden
is vital to our world!
I want to see them! Send me back!
Let me go back home!
Now, allow me to distribute
the next document.
What the hell are you saying?!
Because of you, the holy
maiden is in distress!
You're the ones who dragged
her here against her will
with nothing but the clothes on her back.
Please excuse me for standing.
As I just said,
we have no way to get home after
the parallel world summoning spell.
However, we were summoned here via
methods developed by
studying magical technology.
Therefore, with further research,
there may be a way to send us back.
Wh-What are you...
Y-You stand before the king!
The parallel world summoning spell
uses the magic of the royal family,
who can connect to parallel
worlds through divine revelation,
allowing us to accurately
summon the holy maiden.
BLABBER BLABBER BLABBER BLABBER BLABBER
However, as for sending her back,
though we have the original coordinates,
the possibility of dimensional warping
may send her to a totally different world.
I told you so many times
to watch your words!
I will distribute simplified
documents I have prepared.
To stop that, we'd need a pool of
magical energy not currently possible.
A proposal to expand the
royal sorcery department?
In summary,
we have decided to start a research
project under the royal sorcery department
that aims to return two people, including
Her Holiness, to their original world.
Additionally, the proposal I've prepared
factors in the personnel required
for monitoring the miasma.
H-How dare you try to interfere
with palace personnel?!
Oh. Regarding that, I reviewed and
approved the proposal in advance.
I-If it's magic, the third
royal order would be more—
Our order focuses on
practical applications
such as dealing with magic
beasts, not research.
We are knights, not scholars.
We have various expeditions and cannot
allocate troops to monitor the miasma.
DENIED.
His expression says, "Aren't I useful?"
You're just a normal person who followed
the holy maiden of your own accord!
We're already providing your livelihood,
yet you still demand more?!
With all due respect,
I am not demanding you return us safely
using a vast amount of national funds.
Instead, I'm proposing a new system that
doesn't involve summoning a holy maiden
while also promoting new magic research
within the originally allocated budget.
Such research should benefit
other research projects, as well.
Isn't that right, Director Zoltan?
Y-Yes.
If we can establish a method
for stabilizing dimensions
and ensuring safe warping
to target coordinates,
it will greatly advance the
research of relocation magic...
That's right! Relocation magic!
BLABBER BLABBER BLABBER BLABBER BLABBER
Until now, it's required a magic circle
and sorcerer on both ends,
and it couldn't be used
for living creatures.
Director Zoltan. Please take away Ist-san.
If we can implement a return spell,
that'd be possible!
Meaning we could use it for rescue and...
Yes.
In other words, with your proposal,
we trade the legend of the holy maiden
for advanced magical technology.
That is exactly right.
Technological innovation
and breakthroughs,
along with the development of skilled
personnel, will spearhead progress.
Furthermore, the budget for this
is all covered by the funds
previously allocated to combating miasma,
so there's no additional
financial burden to the kingdom.
U-Um, Kondou-san!
What... What should I do until then?
I believe it would be best for you to stay
here until you finish the purification.
It's the best option when considering
expedition preparations, her well-being,
and the exhaustion of the purification.
And after that...
What should I do after I
finish purifying the miasma?
What do you wish to do, Shiraishi-san?
I want to leave the royal palace.
But I can't accept money
if I don't do anything...
I'd like to work at the same
place you do, Kondou-san!
Give me a break.
Huh?
Nothing...
It would be better to use your
powers as the holy maiden.
In other words, why not find a place
that can utilize your special skills?
Perhaps a clinic or a church.
Yua.
Why do you want to leave the palace?
You are the holy maiden.
Even if you return to your world,
it won't diminish your great
achievements as our holy maiden.
Safeguarding and caring for you is
a matter of course for our kingdom.
Why not stay here in the royal palace?
Yurius-sama...
I would like to leave the royal palace
once I'm finished with the purification
and think things over.
Allow me to return all the accessories
and dresses you've given me.
Thank you so much
for treating me so kindly.
It'd be better if she sold
them to cover living expenses
or to donate the money
to the national treasury.
That's probably what he's thinking.
Prime Minister.
Yes.
So, next is the miasma
observation project?
There's still a lot to do.
That's true.
Don't push yourself too hard.
I know.
EPISODE 7
I WENT ON A TEMPORARY ASSIGNMENT