Kamen Rider does not retreat!
Tojima-san!
All done fighting?
So, he's running?
It's the police!
Why?!
Hey, I didn't...
Aniki!
"Aniki"?
It's us!
What do you think of the outfits?
It's just you guys?!
Dammit, don't scare me like that.
Sorry about that.
They're our security guard uniforms.
We've got a gig coming up.
You do?
We're gonna be security guards
for an idol concert!
This way we'll have multiple
income streams to help you out!
Let's work hard to rebuild the gang!
Wh-What are you guys, my wives?
You'd be pretty lucky
to have three wives, Aniki!
No, no, none of that!
All right, we're off to work!
We're off!
R-Right.
This isn't like you and your little mask.
This is the real thing.
Listen up.
An imposter can't beat the real deal.
You'd better remember that.
I said all that, but...
Am I as real as I made it sound?
IDOL HODGEPODGE FESTIVAL
An idol music festival's such a nice gig!
Yeah. Especially compared
to the guy idol shows...
Last time was a real nightmare.
I don't even wanna remember it.
We love you all!
You're in the way! I can't see!
Absolute hell.
For real.
But today's heaven!
Basically paradise.
We might be facing away from them,
but we'll still feel the Combat Girls
closer than anyone else!
Y'know how they say
"a sight for sore eyes?"
I bet they're a "feeling for sore backs!"
What does "a sight for sore eyes" mean?
Good morning.
Good morning!
Hey.
You boys better run a tight ship.
That's the Combat Girls'
new manager, right?
Who does he think he is?
I mean, he's functionally the head
of their agency at this point.
But I don't like him.
I-I've always been a fan!
I wish you luck on your—
Time's up.
He didn't need to toss me like trash.
True.
That older guy who used to be their
manager and head of the agency
disappeared, apparently.
And ever since this new guy took over...
Their act has really started taking off.
Yeah, the agency moved into a
much bigger office
and started hiring a bunch more staff...
They switched to a major record label
and started appearing in commercials too!
I'm not gonna say the
dude's not good at his job...
But he's still kind of a creep.
I miss the old manager.
Tell me about it.
Hey, you guys.
It's almost time for the show.
Could you move into position?
Yes, sir! Right away!
That'll be 345 yen.
Right...
Here.
Th-Thank you.
That was good of you.
A hero's always gotta help
people in trouble, Dad!
And I wanna be a hero someday!
Sounds good to me.
I wanna be Kamen Rider!
Would you like me
to heat up your food, sir?
Sir?
I'm already fired up.
Die, Kamen Rider!
Snowman! Feel the power of my Rider Kick!
Rider Kick!
I don't stand a chance like this.
Rider...
You're getting a little full of
yourself, you puny human.
Transform!
Another Kamen Rider?!
Rider Kick!
Rewatching Kamen Rider just now
has made me realize something...
I see how, after being beaten
to the point his transformation
breaks, Takeshi Hongo...
worked together with Hayato Ichimonji
to defeat the Snowman monster.
This entire time, I've been on my own,
focusing on getting stronger
and learning how to fight.
What I need to figure out....
is how to believe in my friends.
And how to fight alongside them.
Because I can't defeat Shocker otherwise!
Thank you, Kamen Rider!
IDOL HODGEPODGE FESTIVAL
Everyone! Are you enjoying the show?!
We are!
That's great!
It feels like we've
really come a long way.
I was never sure we'd make it...
Lunlun, are you crying?
Sorry.
It's way too early for that!
We've still got a long way to go, right?
That's right!
Listen, everyone!
The truth is that we, the Combat Girls,
are finally... at long last...
COMBAT GIRLS DOME SHOW CONFIRMED!
going to perform at the Dome!
We're only here today...
because of the fans
who cheered us on so, so much!
It's all thanks to you!
We wanna make sure we fill up the Dome,
so you better come see us!
And to wrap things up...
It's this song!
Thank you for your supervision!
You boys did a good job,
so I hope you'll be back.
Yessir!
I've been meaning to point out...
that's a little formal.
Nice.
Who's that?
Isn't that the head
of the Combat Girls' agency?
E-Excuse me, but we're changing.
Might as well start with you, then.
Time for a drink!
What's that about?!
Rejoice!
I'm making you all members of Shocker!
What the hell?!
No way...
Is this real?
The Combat Girls!
We better hurry and save them!
You can scream, cry, and piss yourselves,
but nobody's gonna come to—
You three, get outta here while you can!
In the meantime, we'll—
We'll what, exactly?!
We'll figure something out!
I'm so glad.
You came to save us, didn't you?
But...
That's unnecessaryee!
The Combat Girls are Shocker combatants?!
Run for it!
Hey.
Kill them.
Now, then...
That just leaves...
A bit of propagation.
By turning all these idols
into my slaves,
soon everyone in Japan...
No.
EVERYONE IN THE WORLD WILL JOIN SHOCKER
Everyone in the world will join Shocker!
What the hell is going on?!
The Combat girls...
even Junko and the others...
This isn't happening, right?!
I'm dreaming, right?
It's gotta be a dream!
They might come back this way.
We better move.
Aw, crap! Run for it!
They're catching up to us!
Faster!
Dammit all!
For some reason, humans tend to
become fixated on these so-called idols.
I can use that.
Thanks for coming by today!
WE’LL BE WAITING
I hope you'll come
see our next show, too!
Master Bat Man.
You want a part-time job?
We're not really hiring, though...
I mean, we're kind of a small operation,
and our only act is the Combat Girls.
Do it.
What is this?
You serve no further purpose.
The Combat Girls, huh...
I've gone over your material.
The singing's not remarkable,
and there's just no real unique appeal.
Sorry, but I don't think we'll be...
Wait, what?
You understand your jobs?
Do whatever it takes to
make them number one!
We of Shocker are superior
to humans in every way.
Becoming a Shocker combatant could
very well be supreme bliss for any human.
Don't you agree?
Yes, Master Bat Man.
Funny you can get so hungry
when you're not even doing anything.
I wonder if the boys are
done with their shift.
Are they gonna eat before coming back?
If they come back hungry,
I oughta make something for them.
That's good.
We're gonna die!
Wh-What the—?!
NEXT EPISODE
I'LL FIGHT
SHOCKER
TOO
I'LL FIGHT SHOCKER TOO
ILLUSTRATION BY: HITOTSU YOKOSHIMA