CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
You're sure you're okay?
I'm fine!
Jett-senpai is here!
Yeah, but...
He's always holed up in his laboratory.
RESEARCH IN PROGRESS
NO ENTRY!
And Pochitan's here!
She's been doing that since yesterday.
She's having fun putting things in.
The Makoto Jewels are helping her grow.
Anyway, you have to hurry
or you'll be late for school!
If anything happens,
call me on the Voice Memo.
Okay!
See you later!
Have a good day!
It's so quiet.
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
rinto hirameku
A brilliant inspiration
kitto mitsukeru
datte Precure
I'm sure we'll find it
We're Precure, after all
watashitachi wo yondeiru
It's calling to us
shinjitsu wa doko?
hakken wa nani?
Where's the truth?
What will we discover?
nazo ga nazo wo yondeiru
One mystery after another
Puzzle wo atsume
genzai kara kako, mirai e
Gather the pieces
From now to the past and future
shouko mitai ni
toki wo koe kagayaku mono
Like evidence
Something shining across time
nande? nande? Trick kana?
How? How? Is it a trick?
naze? naze? tachimukau
Why? Why? We'll face it
mitsumete kanjite
himitsu wo tokiakasu no
Look and feel
Figure out the secret
yuuki no ippo ga kiseki made michibiku
One brave step will lead to a miracle
kotae!?
Kizuitenai mono ni kizuita toki
The answer?!
Found when you notice the unnoticed
unmei ne tte daisuki yo tte
chicchana koe
It's destiny, it's love
Whispered in a tiny voice
issho ni aruite ikou!
Let's walk that road together!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
rinto hirameku
A brilliant inspiration
Jewel no kagi ga tsunagaru
tsugi e no kizuna hiraku yo
The jewel key connects us
Opening the link moving forward
nee umareta koto
meguri aeta koto no shinpi
Hey, us being born and having met
Is a wonderful mystery
susume! Meitantei Precure!
Go on! Star Detective Precure!
Star Detectives in Trouble?
What about the Makoto Jewels?
Why don't you go steal them?
Yes. I'm carefully devising
a meticulous plan to obtain
the Makoto Jewels
described in the Tome of Mirages.
You keep failing, Nijee.
If you don't get some,
there won't be a next time.
Lie lie, sir!
I hope Mikuru is okay.
She's now a second year
junior high student.
I wonder if she's nervous
in her new class?
Whoa!
You tried to stuff too much in!
It looks like rain.
Let's bring Mikuru an umbrella!
They're ready!
Legendary Pre-Kit charms from an old book!
Legendary?
I don't know the details, but they'll
save Star Detective Precures in a crisis!
Wow!
Going out?
Yeah! I'm bringing Mikuru an umbrella.
Give Mikuru one of these then.
Got it! Thanks!
We'll be matching!
Even a Star Detective like Mikuru
can't predict the weather.
I only brought one for Mikuru.
Let's bring it before it starts raining
and hurry home!
This is Mikuru's school.
There's Mikuru!
-Miku--
-Mikuru!
Hey, Rie!
We're in the same class again!
I'm so happy!
Let's have a good year!
It looks like rain.
I forgot my umbrella.
I have one. Let's go home together!
Thanks!
You mustn't forget it, Mikuru!
I didn't think it would rain!
Oh!
I'm sorry!
It's okay.
I'm sorry I wasn't paying attention.
Pochi.
Pochi?
Uh, this photo, is so p-peachy!
I want one like it too...
Thank you. It's my little sister.
You seem close.
Keiko is a second year high school
student here, on exchange in London.
Did something happen?
Lately, strange things are happening.
People keep telling me
they saw Keiko in town.
But she's in London!
Must be someone who looks like her.
That's what I thought.
But then I saw her.
This morning, on my way to university,
by the station.
I was surprised, and I followed her here.
I asked the school
and they said Keiko's not here.
I phoned her in London
and she didn't pick up.
I'm just so worried.
Could you let me help?
Open!
Pre-Kit Book!
Huh?
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
I'm Anna Akechi from
the CUREtto Detective Agency!
I-I'm Mariko Kitamura.
UNIVERSITY STUDENT
MARIKO KITAMURA
Mariko, leave it to this Star Detective!
I'll make sure this case
is gold-star case closed!
When you put it that way!
Could I borrow that photograph?
Yes!
Thank you very much!
It looks like rain, so here!
Take this!
Mariko needed help,
so I impulsively took the case.
I have to tell Mikuru.
I shouldn't bother her.
Mikuru?
The student council president!
The Chairwoman wants you.
Sorry.
CHAIRWOMAN'S OFFICE
Sorry for calling you over.
I heard you left your dorm
to start a detective agency.
You're one step closer to your dream.
Yes, thank you.
Speaking of which, I have a favor to ask.
There's a case I need you to solve.
The ghost issue.
Huh?
G-Ghost?!
The junior high and high school
are on the same grounds.
I feel like I stick out.
I know!
Open!
Pre-Kit Gloss!
What do you think of
high schooler Anna Akechi?
Alright! Time to investigate!
Excuse me!
I'm looking for this girl.
Oh, Keiko? She's in my class.
Oh! My Pre-Kit Voice Memo!
A mobile phone?
They'll take it if they find out.
Oh, uh, no!
Why?
Sorry for the interruption! About Keiko...
She sent me a message
from London just last night.
A message...
I'll just investigate by myself.
Sir, I heard from the Chairwoman
that you saw a ghost.
Could you tell me more?
Yes.
In the courtyard of the high school,
I saw a strange figure so I went closer...
She disappeared.
It has happened more than once or twice.
You asked, but you're not listening!
I hate ghosts! I can't stand spirits!
In the end, I learned nothing.
What rotten weather.
W-Who's there?
W-What?
Mikuru! It's me!
Anna!
You took on a case by yourself?
Why didn't you ask me?
You were at school.
I didn't want to bother you.
You know school and sleuthing
are both important to me, right?
If you try to do it alone and mess up,
you'll cause trouble for the client!
Speak for yourself! You took on
a case by yourself too!
I called you on the Voice Memo,
but you didn't pick up.
I was investigating.
If I fail my investigation,
Mariko will be sad.
Who's Mariko?
My client.
She's looking for her sister, Keiko.
Mikuru?
Sorry, I have to go!
Mikuru!
We weren't done talking!
Hey!
-You're not a ghost... are you?
-What?
Never mind. Have you seen
anything strange around here?
Not especially.
It looks like rain.
Don't they say when swallows
fly low it will rain?
I hadn't thought of that...
It's nothing. Thanks for your help!
Is it a Makoto Jewel?
Mikuru!
Mikuru! A Makoto Jewel is in danger!
What?
-Whoa, Keiko!
-Huh?
She's who I've been searching for!
You were looking for her?
She's on exchange in London.
Her sister called her
this morning, but she didn't answer.
I'm not Keiko.
Nijee!
You said Keiko was in London.
She might've been asleep!
What do you mean?
If it was 8 a.m. here, it would be
midnight in London in April!
I see!
If only you told me,
we could've solved it faster!
I tried to tell you, but you left!
I had to! I'm working on a case, too!
Grrrr!
Er-herm! I wish you wouldn't get so
heated-up without me.
Why disguise yourself as Keiko?
I used a student who's away on exchange.
She's across the sea.
I don't have to worry about
running into her, right?
I was able to case
this place day and night.
What were you doing?
Working out how to carry this statue.
How to carry a big statue using
tools available in this city.
I just kept researching and thinking.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COOPERATION
DURING THE CONSTRUCTION WORK
Hey, watch out!
In the city?
Mariko and the others saw you.
I still hadn't figured out
how to carry it.
But then you helped me!
Swallows.
Lies, envelop!
Come forth, Hanninda!
Hanninda!
I can carry it as swallows!
I'll turn it into swallows,
and transport it easily!
Mikuru!
Okay!
Open!
Jewel Cure Watch!
Precure! Wake-up Time!
3! Discover!
6! And face one another!
9! We are the miraculous duo!
Spin around!
And finish off cutely!
Gold-star closing the case on any mystery!
Star Detective Cure Answer!
Jumping towards smiles
with layered reasoning!
Star Detective Cure Mystique!
Star Detective Precure!
I'll show you my answer!
Two Makoto Jewels at once,
I'm killing two birds with one stone!
You can't have them! Swallows carrying joy
are the school symbol!
That statue is full of
students' and teachers' wishes!
It looks like they're carrying
joy for me too!
Hanninda!
Han! Nin!
Magnificent, aren't they?
A Hanninda attack in perfect sync.
Compared to them, you're pitiful.
You two are out of step.
-Han!
-Nin!
Da!
You're no match for us.
The way you're acting,
it would be easier to just run away.
But if I defeat
the Star Detective Precures,
I know Maestro Usonoir would be pleased!
Are you watching?
Maestro Usonoir!
Hmm.
Stay tuned for a splendid show!
Maestro Usonoir!
Hanninda!
I'll get the statue back!
I'll get the Makoto Jewels back!
This is our answer!
Don't make me say it again.
You're out of step.
Han! Nin! Da!
You've got to get off the stage.
They'll save Star Detective Precures
in a crisis!
What's that?
Open!
Huh? Open! Open!
But... why?
Hanninda!
You're not qualified to go on stage!
Star Detective Precures!
Ha! Hanninda!
Pochitan?
W-What?
Da!
Ha-Hanninda...
At this rate...
Hanninda!
Tsk! I got two Makoto Jewels.
Good enough!
Farewell, my fair Star Detectives!
A Fairy of Time and Space...
Pochitan!
Pochitan.
(NaNaNaNa naze? naze? WHY?
NaNaNaNa nazo? nazo! ANSWER?!)
(NaNaNaNa why? Why? WHY?
NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER?!)
ten to ten musundara ara? ara!
Connect the dots, oh? Oh my!
"hanamaru kaiketsu!" kana? kana?
Could it be a "gold-star case closed!"?
Could it?
suiri to nazo wa uragaeshi
niten santen gyakuten
Reasoning turns around riddles
Twists and turns, reverse
kotoba ya shigusa sae wana? wana!
unomi ni shite wa dame! dame!
Even words and behavior are traps? Traps!
Don't just believe them! No!
yoku mite, kangaete, sorekara
fumidasu no yo ippo!
Pay attention, think and then
Take the first step!
komatteiru hito mitara
sugu ni tasuketai
When I see someone in trouble
I immediately want to help
datte nantoka nantoka nantoka shitakute
kakedashiteiru
Cause I wanna, wanna do something
So I go running off
Na Na Na nazo! nazo!
Na Na Na mystery! Mystery!
nazo wo toku no ga meitantei
Solving mysteries
Is what a Star Detective does
uso ka makoto ka mikiwamete
egao no kotae mitsukeru
See through lies and find truth
Find the answer for a smile
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 100 bai
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 100
chikara awasete norikoeru
tomo wa kiseki no katamari
Working together, we can figure it out
Friends are a true miracle
iku yo! Meitantei
Let's go! Star Detective
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 1,000 bai
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 1,000
tomodachi to te ni te wo totte
banjikaiketsu suru made!
Hand in hand with my friends
Until everything's solved!
DATTE Precure
(NaNaNaNa naze? nazo! ANSWER!)
We're Precure, after all
(NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER!)
Pochitan is...
Pochi!
We couldn't protect the Makoto Jewels
or the swallow statue.
Even so...
We can do it if we stick together!
Star Detective Precure!
"Miraculous Pre-Kit Mirror Loupe!"
That mystery! CUREtto Case Closed!