It's been five days
since the Peninsula race,
and the rainy season has ended
for the Kanto, Tokai, and Koshin regions.
Summer has come to Shonan.
MF Ghost
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Grandma's Kei Truck
Please let something good
happen to Kanata.
I'm really glad I was
finally able to tell Kanata
the secret I'd been keeping from him.
Between "coming out" to him
like that and our first kiss,
I feel like when he looks at me now,
his gaze is even gentler than before.
Let's go.
Maybe I'm being a tad optimistic here,
but it could be Kanata's feeling
some kind of camaraderie with me
as someone else who is
involved in the MFG series.
Doesn't that make
our relationship really special?
Like some kind of invisible connection
between the two of us.
The costume might still
be embarrassing to wear,
but I'm really glad I pushed myself into
going to that MFG Angels audition now.
Good grief. It's hard to find motivation
for work when it's this hot.
Ogata Automotive
Ogata-kun, sorry to ask,
but could I get something cold to drink?
Sure thing.
The upcoming Seaside Double Lane
has some of the highest average speeds
out of all five courses, right?
Yeah.
Do you think power differentials
will be a big factor?
I've been wondering about that.
I'm sure our rivals will use the
summer break to add their own upgrades.
As a result, we can't afford
to sit on our hands.
Since we have time, I might pull out
the engine, take it apart, and rebuild it.
I can re-balance and replace parts with
ones more resilient to higher output.
Wait, does that mean...
You're saying you intend to boost it
even more and give it more power?
You could see it that way,
but not necessarily.
We'll need the driver's opinion first.
Looking at the data,
Katagiri-kun spends more time on
the accelerator than any other driver.
Which means more stress on the engine.
I feel like he might be holding back
to some degree for the car's sake.
So I want to build an engine
that can keep up with this prodigy,
no matter how hard he pushes it.
I've got two ideas in mind
for the Double Lane race:
make the engine more resilient,
and take control of the invisible element.
An invisible element?
The airflow.
I can't believe it's nearly five
and the heat is still this bad.
It's that late already?
I'm getting hungry.
I'm really looking forward to dinner.
I feel like my attitude towards eating
has changed since I came to Japan.
In England, except for
on special occasions,
eating was just something
I did to satisfy my hunger.
But now, every meal
every day is a big event.
I love the rice Mama Mayuko serves.
Oh, really?
My grandma in Niigata
actually sends us that rice.
I've never eaten anything else,
so I figured all rice tasted like that.
It's a type called "Koshihikari"
from Minami-Uonuma.
Whoa, really?
Minami-Uonuma farms?
They say the best-tasting rice
in Japan comes from there.
I had no idea I was eating
such a fancy brand on a daily basis.
That explains why it's so good.
Hey, Kanata.
When it comes to Japanese rice, how would
you like to try the best of the best?
Kana-chan said that?
What's up?
He's joining Ren on her trip to Niigata.
Oh, sounds wonderful.
And we'll rest easier
knowing he's with her.
We sure will.
Aw, c'mon, Mom and Dad.
It sounds weird when you put it like that.
Like you'd be worried if I was on my own.
I'm the one who's taking
Kanata with me, okay?
I mean, he's a foreigner.
He wouldn't know left from right.
Well, that's true, but...
It's just such a relief
that he's going with you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Now, now. Let's not fuss over semantics.
Mom will also be glad to meet him.
Give her my regards, Kanata-kun.
Sure.
Don't get carried away, Kanata.
I'm the leader on this trip, okay?
Do you understand?
Yes, I get it.
Imagine fussing over something
like that. What an odd girl.
Looking at the map,
the route from Kanagawa to Niigata
takes us across the width of Japan.
Bravo. We're going over
some tall, rugged mountains.
It feels a bit like we're driving
across the Swiss Alps.
This tunnel is super long.
When I was little, I used to
get afraid going through it.
I'd close my eyes in the back of
Dad's car. This really takes me back.
It drives home that we're on the way to
Grandma's house, passing through here.
And being with Kanata is so awesome,
I don't know what I'm gonna do!
Grandma, are you here? It's Ren!
Oh, Ren-chan. You've grown
so much since I last saw you.
Let me introduce you, Grandma.
This is Kanata.
My, my, he's as tall and slender
as a beech tree.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Katagiri Kanata.
Thank you for coming all this way.
I don't have much,
but make yourself at home.
Ren-chan, could you light
some incense at the altar?
I'm sure Grandpa would like that.
Sure.
You should join me, Kanata.
For the incense and the bell.
This is an altar for the gods?
It's called a "butsudan."
Our ancestors are enshrined there.
So every day, we put our hands together
and express our gratitude.
And in exchange,
our ancestors look out for us.
So for Japanese people,
ancestors are a bit like God for Christians.
Wow, amazing!
Pretty, isn't it?
This place is called Bijin Bayashi.
Bijin Bayashi?
It's a forest of beech trees.
What are you doing, Ren?
Beech trees are supposed to
have lots of water in their trunks.
So if you put your ear to them,
you can hear the water flowing.
What's with that face?
Are you making fun of me?
I've just never heard anything
like that before. It seems ridiculous.
The trunk of a tree
shouldn't make a noise.
If you don't believe me,
try it for yourself.
Grandma told me about it.
I have my doubts.
Wow. I can hear it.
I've never experienced
something like this before.
A tree trunk that makes a noise.
Beech trees are pretty amazing, right?
We're back.
Grandma, let me help with the cooking.
Oh, Ren-chan, you're a sweet girl.
And so mature now.
Of course. I'm already
a junior in high school.
Is there anything I can help with?
No, I won't have that.
Can't have a young fella making
a nuisance of himself in the kitchen.
She's right, Kanata. Just watch some TV.
I'm sorry. I just feel guilty
getting fed without helping out.
If you need any heavy lifting
done later, let me know.
He's a sweet one, that Kanata-san.
He is. Mom and Dad
are head over heels for him.
Your grandma's never seen such a fine man.
Not even over in Tokamachi or Joetsu.
You think so?
Is he one of them celebrities off the TV?
Well, Kanata is a racing driver.
Well, ain't that something?
Would you like more, Kanata-san?
Yes, much more, please.
That's weird. You usually
don't eat this much.
Your grandmother's
cooking smells fantastic.
Makes sense.
It's the way she seasons the eggplant
with miso and shishito peppers.
Here you are.
Thank you so much.
Amazing.
Glad you like it, Kanata.
MF Ghost.
Did they drive to Niigata in the 86?
Yeah. In the same red car
I always see on the broadcasts.
It had the number on
the door and everything.
Unbelievable. My daughter
has no idea how good she has it.
Getting to navigate for the 86 car
with Kanata-kun behind the wheel...
She'd faint if she realized how much
that experience is worth.
I wonder if I might ever get the chance...
Hey, Grandma.
Let's go for a ride on your kei truck!
Oh, well, I guess we can
take it for a spin.
You should come, too, Kanata.
Grandma owns this whole place.
But it's only a two-seater.
We ride in the back.
That's the best part
of riding a kei truck.
You hold on like this.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
* This is actually dangerous, so don't try it at home
Is that safe?
Hurry it up, Kanata.
All ready? Off we go.
It's so fun!
Wow, this is thrilling!
It's like being on a cabin cruiser!
Feels good, doesn't it?
This is great, Grandma!
You're one funky driver!
Grandma, go faster!
Sure thing!
That was so much fun!
I love riding on Grandma's kei truck.
That truck...
It has three pedals
and an H-pattern shifter.
Hello, Saionji residence.
Oh, Mayuko-san? No, no trouble at all.
They're both good kids.
I've been having a real good time myself.
We just finished eating lunch.
Okay, okay. Don't you worry now.
I'm going to take a nap.
You two should get some rest, too.
A nap?
Go on and open the window.
Should get a nice breeze going.
It'll feel sweet as all get out
laying out underneath it.
What did all of that mean?
That it'll feel good.
Wow, he's already asleep.
Kanata must be fully relaxed.
Oh, boy. How is he so cute?
He's supposed to be a guy.
I've never seen my own sleeping face,
but I'm 100% sure he's got me beat.
Since he's looking so cute,
I'll grab a pic and send it to Wakana.
Actually, maybe I wanna
keep this one for myself?
Well, there's nothing else to do,
so guess I'll nap, too.
What should I do?
If Grandma wakes up and sees us,
she'll think we're a couple!
But I can't bring myself
to pull away from his hand.
What am I gonna do?
But, y'know, I can't deny
that I'm kinda happy.
Why do I feel so comfy?
I wouldn't care if the world
ended right now.
Huh? Where'd Kanata go?
It's so quiet and cool.
It's like a different world from Shonan.
Ren! Emergency! Wake up!
What is it?
There's a giant dragonfly!
It has yellow and black bands,
and it looks really aggressive.
It's been circling the house.
I think that's an oniyanma dragonfly.
There's lots of them in Niigata.
You don't get them in England?
It's new to me!
Ren, I really want to catch it.
Huh? Are you a kid?
Besides, you can't. Not without a net.
What's going on?
Hey, Grandma, do you know where
we can get a net for catching dragonflies?
Hard to say. Kids these days
don't do that sorta thing.
Maybe down at the hardware store?
Off we go! Full speed ahead!
Komari
I really don't think
they'll have a net here.
Got one!
No way! Seriously?
Next, we catch it.
Hold up a second.
Let me show you how it's done.
Dad and I used to catch
these bugs when I was little.
Aw, but I wanna do it.
Well, too bad. These guys are
the bosses of the dragonfly world,
and you're too slow to pull it off.
I'm not slow.
All right, bring it on, yanma!
Ren-chan, aim for a female oniyanma.
She's bigger than the male,
and flashier-looking.
That one's male, honey.
Huh!
That's weird.
This is hard.
It's coming back this way.
You can do it, Ren.
Ouch!
You did that on purpose, Ren.
How else could you miss that bad?
That's weird. I wonder if they've evolved
to be faster over time.
Please let me try.
If I can't do it with all my experience,
there's no way a slowpoke like you can.
You're the slow one, Ren.
What'd you say?
They get along like real siblings.
Since you hold the net like this,
the dragonfly's on alert and avoids you,
thinking you're an obstacle.
You should be more like this.
Then it can't see how long the tool is.
I'm gonna catch a huge,
impressive-looking female.
That one's female, Kanata-san.
Yes! This is my chance!
Why are the females
only showing up for Kanata?
The species doesn't matter to you,
does it? You womanizer.
Come on.
Don't underestimate the reflexes
of a racing driver.
Got one!
Seriously?
Wow, it's so cool-looking.
And very striking up close.
It's like one of those kaiju
in a Godzilla movie.
It's gonna eat you up, Ren. Roar!
He really does act like a grade-schooler.
And now that I'm satisfied,
let's return this dragonfly to the sky.
Goodbye, oniyanma girl.
Here's hoping you find a wonderful
summer romance and lay a ton of eggs.
Grandma, where are you going?
Just to tidy up the grave.
It's almost Obon, after all.
I'll come with you.
There's boots in the storage room,
so put those on.
What's Obon?
Obon is the one time every year
when our ancestors come home.
We make sure their graves are clean,
so they can be at ease when they visit.
Where are your ancestors normally?
Ancestral
Grave
Most of the time, they go wherever
they want, free as a bird.
Really?
My mum died last year.
I see. I'm sorry to hear that.
I'd like to think that
instead of staying put in heaven,
she's staying active
and enjoying herself.
I don't doubt it.
I'm sure your mother is worried about you,
and always watching out for you.
And if something happens and
you need help, I bet she'll be there.
My mum will be there to help me?
That's what parents do.
Doesn't matter if
you're Japanese or English.
I'm really glad I got
to meet you, Grandma.
Aren't you lonely out here by yourself?
Not at all! This is a great place
that's rich in nature.
As for the winters...
It can be rough when the snow piles up,
but my husband and I worked
hard to manage this land.
I've gotta keep it that way, so our kids
and grandkids can stop by anytime.
You can come by whenever
you like, too, Kanata-san.
The colors are quite a sight in the fall.
You don't mind me visiting?
Of course not! I already consider you
one of the grandkids, Kanata-san.
You're always welcome here.
Don't start crying now. We've got
some tasty watermelon on the cool.
It's hard to believe.
It's like something out of a dream.
This place has such kindness within it.
Watch yourselves out on
those roads. And come again.
We had a great time, Grandma.
Thanks for everything.
I'm touched by your kindness.
This will be a summer I never forget.
Oh, enough with all that.
Grandma had herself a good time, too.
Love you, Grandma.
Oh, my.
Bye-bye, Grandma. Take care.
I've never seen Kanata
give someone a hug before.
I guess even he couldn't resist
Grandma's charms.
Honey, our granddaughter has
turned into quite the young lady.
She's old enough to fall in love now.
And while it might be beyond
our ability to help her with that,
I don't want her
to experience any heartache,
so I hope you'll be rooting for her.
Bye-bye, Niigata.
Next time, Turn 30: The 1:09PM Miracle.