What was that?
Come on, Erik. What's wrong?
Please open the door!
What's the matter?
THE CASE OF THE MUSICIAN
AND THE LOCKED-ROOM MURDER
I heard a crash and my boyfriend
won't open the door.
Wait right here.
Mr. Bernhardt, I'm coming in.
THE CASEBOOK OF ARNE
PART 10: DIFFERENT COUNTRIES,
DIFFERENT CUSTOMS
So the doppelgänger of a culprit
will also become a culprit?
They're identical inside and out,
so it's the obvious conclusion.
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh! But you know what
that means, Lord Arne?
I was right when I deduced
they were both guilty.
Huh?
My reward. I'd like my reward now.
What are you talking about?
You promised me one!
You said if I worked out if the original
or the doppelgänger was the killer,
you'd give me a reward!
I said nothing of the sort.
You so did!
Huh? What's going on over there?
Who knows?
A tenant was murdered?
Yeah, and it sounds like
it's a locked-room mystery.
A locked-room mystery? How horrible.
What? Lord Arne?
Okay now, move along.
Nothing to see here.
You, too. You're in the way, pal.
Move along.
Was this really a locked-room murder?
Huh?
Well, yes. But you're not authorized to—
Oh, wait. Aren't you that
renowned master detective, sir?
Yeah. I came to help
with the investigation.
Huh? D-Did he spread that rumor
in that instant?
I wonder what's gotten into him.
Th-Thank you for coming.
This way. Allow me to show you in.
Hey, out of our way! Make a path!
It's just to kill some time.
You can go on home.
Of course Lord Arne would be all like,
"Might as well finish this crossword,"
as he strolls off to solve
a locked-room mystery!
He's the very model of a detective!
They sure are unique creatures,
these detectives.
What a pain.
Let's go with him.
Please wait for us, Lord Arne!
The victim was a tenant here:
Erik Bernhardt.
He died from a stab wound to the back of
the neck made by a thin, knifelike object.
According to the police,
when his body was discovered,
the door and all of
the windows were locked.
The witnesses used a spare key to get in,
from what I'm told.
You're really starting
to sound the part, Lynn.
Th-Thank you for saying so.
And these are the two witnesses
who discovered the body.
Yes, I'd promised to meet him here today.
When I arrived, I kept calling his name
but he just wouldn't answer.
I heard her voice and a strange noise,
so I came to see what had happened.
Then I used my spare key to get in.
A strange noise?
Yes. I heard a loud crash,
like something had shattered.
Probably these plates.
It looks like he kept them
on this cabinet.
Maybe they fell off
as he struggled with his killer.
No, seems unlikely.
Huh?
If they'd bumped it, the items inside
the cabinet would also have been disturbed.
And these fragments landed on top of his leg.
It'd be more logical to assume
the plates fell for another reason
after the man had been murdered.
Th-That makes sense.
His body also bears few injuries
and his clothes look fine.
It's unlikely he struggled with his killer.
What's this?
Looks like some kind of pet food.
Pet food? Did he have a pet?
Oh, that is strange.
Pets aren't allowed in the building.
No, he didn't have a pet.
He didn't like animals, period.
He didn't, huh?
Mr. Erik was a musician, wasn't he?
Yes, he was a trumpet player.
His playing was always so wonderful.
Lord Arne, I was just thinking...
What a strange painting.
I'm not sure why, but the style
reminds me of something.
What were you about to say?
Oh, that's right.
Actually, I overheard the police
saying something.
The victim, Mr. Erik, had fallen behind
on his rent not long ago.
And since the room was locked,
wouldn't that cast suspicion on the landlady,
since she had a spare key?
You said the room was locked, right?
Huh? Uh, yes.
The door and all the windows
were apparently locked.
But it seems the room
wasn't entirely sealed.
Huh?
An air vent?
Well, we'll have to investigate.
Go on, Lynn Reinweiß.
Go and enjoy your "paradise."
What?! I don't actually like dust, you know!
On top of that,
that's way too small for me to fit!
It is? Then, Amy, remove your head.
Don't be absurd.
But luckily, I have a stuffed animal
that should fit perfectly.
What? What was that?!
Thanks so much for helping, Nach.
W-Wait, you moron. Stop! Don't!
There.
How dare you jerks do this to me!
Find out where it goes. Get on with it.
Tch. Gimme a stinkin' break.
It looks like it leads out back.
Let's go take a look.
You actually made yourself
useful for a change.
Shut up. Never make me do that again.
I see. So this is the back of the building.
Lord Arne?
Wh-What's that?
It's an ice pick. You use it
to break ice into pieces.
It smells just like the corpse.
Oh! That must mean
it's the murder weapon!
I've got it.
The killer tied a string to the ice pick,
shot it through the air vent,
murdered the victim,
then reeled the ice pick back in,
before discarding it here.
The mystery of the
locked-room murder is solved!
Of course.
The killer aimed at the man's neck
through the vent from outside the building.
Right!
What a brilliant pile of nonsense,
Dimwit Reinweiß.
Not even a centaur could pull that off.
Guess you're right.
But I still think the suspicious ones
are the landlady with her spare key,
and the girlfriend who said she was
with the victim last night... Hmm?
Huh? Wow! When did
all these kitties show up?
There are more over there.
I wonder if this is where
the local cats always gather.
Aw, so cute.
Here, kitty. Aw! Yes, dat's wight!
Don't do it. No!
Stop biting me! Stop kicking me!
Bleh, fur! I got fur in my mouth!
Hmm? What's this?
It's filthy with dust. Just like Nach.
Ouch! Don't scratch me!
That means the ice pick must have
been dragged through the air vent.
I said ouch! Stop! Someone save me!
Hey, don't ignore me!
It appears so.
Look, Lord Arne. Isn't it cute?
What?
They all left.
Man, could you please not
scare them away like that?
I didn't do a thing.
Naturally cautious animals
are instinctively afraid of me.
Oh, they are?
We might be able to find something else.
Let's look around here a little longer.
Be careful.
Try not to scratch it. Just go slowly.
Huh? Is that Heinz?
Miss Lynn?
It is you, Miss Lynn.
Wow! It's been so long, Heinz!
Yes, it has. I'm glad to
see you looking so well.
Hey! I said be careful, okay?
Sure! Sorry 'bout that!
Come on, guys.
I never thought I'd run into you here.
Are you moving?
Oh, no. I actually just found
a truly wonderful refrigerator.
It's glossy, pure white,
and it makes the most wonderful ice.
And it finally arrived today.
So you're still cooking, Heinz?
Of course. After I parted ways
with the Reinweiß estate staff,
I traveled the world to study cooking.
Right now, I work as a chef
at a nearby hotel.
Wow!
This city has so many delicious restaurants.
Like the pizza place on the main street
or the ice cream parlor near the park.
Oh, but enough about me.
Are you still with...
Yes, it appears you did stick with him.
Yes! Right now, I'm working as one
of Lord Arne's assistant detectives.
You are?
Oh, if you're detectives, are you
investigating that murder case?
Yes, we are.
I see. That man unfortunately
did seem to have some issues.
Huh? Was he a friend of yours, Heinz?
Well, no, I wouldn't say we were friends.
You're talking about
the murdered trumpet player, right?
There's this bar down the street...
They're actually famous
for their delicious potatoes.
But um, anyway, I used
to see him play there often.
He was very talented, but...
Hmm?
One time, I saw him
and the owner arguing.
It seemed to have something
to do with money.
Ice pick.
Huh?
Hmm? Did something happen
with an ice pick?
Uh, never mind.
Thank you very much for
the useful information, Heinz.
I'll go investigate right away!
Uh, sure. I'm glad I was able to help.
I'll come and see you again.
I'd love to eat your cooking again.
Sure. It'd be my pleasure.
Excuse me!
I need to get your signature for this.
Oh, sure!
See you later, okay?
Excuse me!
Do you work at this bar?
Yes, I do.
Um, is the owner in right now?
I would like to speak to him if possible.
The owner? The owner is actually
on vacation at the moment.
Oh. He's on vacation?
Yes. He left last week.
He should be back in two days, though.
I see.
If that's true, he can't be the killer.
A-Actually, we're investigating
the murder of Erik Bernhardt.
Oh, so that's what this is about.
He could be a little high-strung,
but he really was an excellent player.
Many young women would come here
just to see him perform.
It really is unfortunate.
I see.
Did Mr. Erik ever get into
any trouble with the owner here?
Huh? Hmm, I wonder.
A while back, he got upset
about his pay being late,
but they resolved that.
Please tell me all about it!
Oh, well, I don't know
all the details myself,
but it seems the owner made
some mistake and didn't pay him fully.
But he paid him later on, and even gave him
a little extra, so they made up.
On the day of the trouble,
the owner had been drinking
and Erik hadn't been sleeping well,
so it turned into a full-blown argument.
I guess that's no surprise.
But those two had known
each other for years,
and there were no grudges between them
that would lead to something like murder.
That gives me a clearer picture.
Thank you very much.
Can I ask something?
Yes. What is it?
Did this come from your bar?
Huh? No, that isn't ours.
Okay. Thanks for your time.
Thank you very much.
Oh, not at all.
Well, that was a dead end,
but at least we got a few more clues.
The late rent must have been
because he hadn't been paid.
I guess the next question is if he'd had
any disagreements with the landlady.
I suppose so.
He did say one other
interesting thing, though.
About many female customers
being interested in him.
Yes. He may have had
girlfriend problems.
That's another possibility.
Either way, we need to keep
gathering information!
Oh, perfect timing.
Excuse me!
Oh, it's the detectives.
Well? Have you learned anything?
No, we're still trying
to gather information.
Actually, there's something
I'd like to ask you.
What might that be?
Well, um...
We were told there was a time recently
when Mr. Erik was unable to pay his rent.
Oh, that? I already told
the police all about that.
He said he was waiting to get paid
and asked me for some extra time.
Since he explained his reasons to me
and paid everything he owed later on,
it was never really a problem.
Oh. I-It wasn't?
I hope that doesn't disappoint you.
Were you starting to suspect me, maybe?
Oh, no! Definitely not!
Oh, more kitties.
Shoo! Shoo! Get out of here!
Those darned cats.
I don't know when they started
coming around here,
but they're always such a nuisance.
A nuisance?
Oh, yes. They dig through
the trash and leave a mess,
and worst of all, they growl
and make noise every night.
Oh, I see.
What is it, Lynn?
The pet food in the room.
Maybe Mr. Erik actually
really loved pets,
but since he wasn't allowed to keep one,
he went out every night
to feed the cats?
What? I certainly hope not.
I see.
No, I don't think that adds up.
Huh? Why not?
Let's go look into it right now.
Back to the victim's room.
Huh? Oh, okay!
That stuffed animal
of yours sure is cute.
Are you serious?
Huh?!
Lord Arne, did you figure something out?
Take a look.
I made my blood stick to any dust
from the air vent.
Aren't those footprints?
That settles it.
Lord Arne, what does this mean?
Lynn Reinweiß, check inside
that pet food bag.
Huh? Oh, okay.
There's something in here.
What is this?
Let me see.
It's poison.
P-P-P-P-P-P-Poison?
Wash up when we're done.
Uh, yes, I will!
But are you okay, Lord Arne?
Poison doesn't work on vampires.
Oh, of course not!
Only things like silver
and garlic work on vampires!
Now I understand.
The man wasn't trying to feed the cats.
He was trying to kill them.
Huh?
A high-strung musician who hates animals.
It's not hard to imagine the noisy cats
driving him crazy every night,
so he tried to kill them.
So the room wasn't
completely sealed after all.
The killer pranced right in and killed
the man before it could be killed itself.
Isn't that right?
That cat has been following us
the whole time.
It never got close, so I thought
it was just being cautious.
Yes, but I told you there's no way
any normal cat would follow me around.
Th-The cat is...
That's a cat-sìth, a kind of cat fairy.
A cat-sìth?
Like the detective says,
I killed him before
he could kill all of us, meow.
If I could've gotten the humans
to suspect each other more,
I would've loved to have killed
that female they call the landlady, too.
Too bad, meow.
Hey! Cut it out! I won't let you forget this!
Quit tickling me! That tickles!
It's so cold! But so good!
How dare you treat me like this!
You should've gotten some
gelato, too, Lord Arne.
Nope.
What if it were made from blood?
Who would eat that?
I wonder if we shouldn't have
let the cat-sìth get away.
From a human point of view,
it's nothing but a murderer.
But from a feline point of view,
that cat-sìth is a hero who saved
many of its kind from slaughter.
A feline point of view?
Do you want cats menacing you
night after night?
Huh?
You can all relax.
We have no interest in your cat hero.
Yeah. I'm not interested in cats.
What I am interested in is...
Lord Arne?
Let's go home, Lynn Reinweiß.
I have a feeling
we're about to get very busy.
Yup! A beer after work
sure hits the spot.
How long are you gonna
keep drinking anyway?
Well, it's still "after five"
until the next day's shift begins.
Excuse me! I'll have another!
Sure.
Well, I guess it worked out
since I was hoping to eat this again.
Do you remember what we were
delivering here the last time?
Uh, what was it?
Oh, right. Wasn't it some kind
of weird painting?
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
TIMING: HENRY LIN
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: ELISABETH CRIST
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS