A quest from the merchants' guild?
Yeah. Cargo keeps getting stolen
from merchant ships over in
the port town of Frimeille.
The quest is to investigate the thefts,
and if possible, to capture the
thieves and find the stolen cargo.
Hmm... A port town, huh?
The ocean!
Yoki!
That quest is mine!
I'm here.
Hey.
What?! You can't go?!
I have important work to do.
I really can't leave Minerva for
several days straight right now.
Stupid.
I know, okay?!
Failing to check Cecilia's schedule
in advance was my mistake!
What's that at your waist?
Weapon.
Wait, are those your feathers?
Yes.
My body.
Cut it out! You'll give
people the wrong idea!
Roger.
You're unusually obedient today.
Sorry for keeping you.
Happiness? Why are you here?
Morning.
Th-That... hair accessory...
Now departing for Frimeille.
Roger.
Why is Happiness here? This
isn't a pleasure trip.
I asked her to come because she
could be valuable in battle.
She's pretty skilled with magic.
Really?
I didn't even know that about her.
Of course not. You pretty
much just met her.
You have plenty of time
to get to know her.
C'mon, let's go.
Dude, you should be sitting
next to Happiness!
We're finally here.
I'm gonna go meet the client.
You guys start asking around.
Got it.
I-I...
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Since they're both here,
I'll give them time alone.
Information.
Huh?
You need something, miss?
Quest.
Quest? What does that mean?
"We're here to do a quest
for the merchants' guild.
We'd like you to tell us what you
know about the thefts on the ships.
Do you have any idea who
might have done it?"
If I knew that, I wouldn't be
having such a hard time here.
Even when I post guards,
stuff still gets stolen.
Mysterious.
I guess so.
And the guys upstairs treat us
sailors like we're the thieves.
Innocent?
Of course! Men of the sea never steal!
We'll investigate.
You believe me?
Thanks.
Men of the sea don't keep secrets.
You can ask me anything.
Hey, boys! Gather up!
You wanna know about the thefts?
We're innocent, ya know!
Want some candy, miss?
What a sausage fest.
Hey, hard at work, huh? How's it going?
No one has any information
about the thief at all.
All the ships have had
guards posted at all times,
but no one remembers the
moment the thefts happen.
That sounds weird.
Yes, it's weird.
If the sailors were behind it, I'd
think they'd come up with a better lie.
So you think it was someone else?
Some said that right before
their memories cut off,
they could hear a beautiful singing voice.
Singing?
I suspect demons are involved.
Probably mermaids.
Mermaids...
I'd love to meet one.
Hey, Happiness! I hear there's
a mermaid around here?
Don't!
So it really was a mermaid?
Masa, this is real bad!
We're all gonna get eaten!
Hey, you guys are adventurers, aren't you?
So get rid of that mermaid!
Yeah, that's right!
Please!
Huh? Are mermaids that scary?
You really don't know?
Tons of sailors
have ended up shipwrecked
or even killed by mermaids.
And the sea around here was so safe...
Now we're too scared to get on our boats!
"I am Raven, captain of
the knights of Clariness.
It is a knight's duty
to protect the people.
I will defeat the mermaid without fail."
You're the knight captain
from the hero's party?!
I'm so glad you're here!
You gotta take out those demons for us!
I guess, from the humans' perspective,
demons and monsters are
things to be feared, huh?
Recluse.
Where'd that come from?!
Truth. Demon King's army. Conquer humans.
I know. I just forgot for a second.
Sorry to keep you.
Done with what you needed to do?
Yeah.
I got more paper and pens.
Good work.
Th-Thank you.
Eat.
Right...
It's sweet.
What's sweet here is the
mood you guys are setting.
Yoki, I found someone who
claims he saw a mermaid.
Huh?
When I was shopping, a man
came up and talked to me.
Um... Captain?
WHAT?
Y-Yes, sir! The thing is...
I saw those sailors hiding the
cargo in a cove just outside town.
And there was...
a mermaid in there!
That sounds kinda shady.
But I think we need to make sure.
Happiness, you can wait here.
No.
Fighting demons is dangerous.
Why?
There was once a village
where demons ran rampant.
At the time...
there were so many lives
I failed to protect.
I'm a knight. It's my job
to protect the people.
I'll be sure to defeat the mermaid.
So don't worry. I'll be back.
Absolutely not.
Huh?
Come on.
H-Happiness?!
Hey, she'll be fine.
She's a hundred times
stronger than she looks.
Er... but...
This must be it.
Wooden box.
Yep, no doubt about it.
It all matches the descriptions
of the stolen cargo.
Ocean.
This cove's too small to dock a boat in.
Raven?
Something's there.
Oh, no!
Cover your ears!
If I let my guard down, I'll
be asleep in a heartbeat.
Happiness!
What are you doing?!
Happiness is using her own song
to cancel out the mermaid's?
Yoki!
Right!
You're not getting away!
I don't care if I die.
But, please, I need your help.
My friend has been captured by the humans.
She hasn't done anything.
Please, just make sure she survives!
Quiet.
I won't be deceived by
the words of a demon.
Dislike.
Happiness?
Move, Happiness.
No.
Why are you protecting a demon?
Don't.
Hey, Raven, just put the
sword down for now. Okay?
You're siding with the demon, too?
No. If she attacked humans,
she ought to be taken out.
I wouldn't show mercy to anyone
who hurt me or my friends, either.
Then why?
Because it sounds like she has a reason.
It can't hurt to hear her out first.
Please.
All right.
You okay?
Fine.
Yeah? You've gotten stronger.
U-Um...
Oh, sorry. Forgot about you.
Well, if something's going
on, tell us about it.
You all believe me?
I do.
Really?
Really.
This is so awkward!
Okay, then! Time for introductions!
I'm Yoki the adventurer. Nice to meet ya!
Did you hit your head?
I'm perfectly sane, you dolt!
I'm trying to lighten up the mood here!
This rude one here is Happiness,
and the sulking guy who refuses
to look at you is Raven.
Um... my name is Shike.
Okay, Shike, why did you
try to put us to sleep?
A human ordered me to.
We normally try to avoid
getting close to humans,
but one day...
I was playing with my friend, Misaki,
when we were caught up in a sudden storm.
Next thing I knew, we'd
been captured by humans.
If you want your friend to
live, you'll do as I say!
then I just followed that
human's orders and sang
to put the people on the boats to sleep.
Well, it doesn't seem like she's lying.
Yoki, don't be fooled by appearances.
You can't trust her?
Of course I could never trust a demon.
Then... trust me as I trust her.
I...
All right.
I'll start a new investigation
based on what the mermaid said.
Empty.
Yeah, these are just
fakes left here for show.
So the thief leaked information
to lure his pursuers here,
where he'd have the mermaid put
them to sleep to silence them.
What?! We were about to be killed?!
It's a pretty roundabout
method for a demon.
Hey, Shike, do you know where
the thief's hideout is?
I'm sorry. He blindfolded me
during transit, so I don't know.
What to do?
If my hunch is correct,
the thieves should show up here soon.
We can make them tell us.
Let me be the one to make sure.
Never thought we'd catch the
eye of the knight captain!
Maybe it's about time we
moved to another island.
Ah, Captain! I'm glad to see you're safe.
We were worried, so we
wanted to check on you...
Are you the thieves?
Huh? What?
Dude, what's with your voice?
It sounds so weird!
Fools.
Both you and I are beneath that mermaid.
At least she cares for her friend.
I won't kill you, but I will
have you judged under the law.
Tsk. Damn that mermaid.
I'll have to punish her good later.
Get him, boys!
Damn it!
You ruffians had the nerve
to use an innocent mermaid.
I will put an end to your story—
Move.
I can fight with you.
H-Hang on! You've got it all wrong!
That mermaid had us under her control!
Where is the mermaid's friend?
That's... probably Shike's friend, right?
They packed her up like cargo.
Emergency.
You're the mermaid called Misaki, right?
Yeah.
Oh, we can change our fins into feet.
We can't use our powers
when we do, though.
Perv.
I wasn't looking, okay?!
Report.
Wait! What are you gonna
report, and to who?!
Misaki! I was so worried!
There, there. You think I'd
kick the bucket that easily?
Man, you guys saved my skin!
I really appreciate it!
You're taking this lightly.
Thank you so much for saving Misaki.
We owe you our lives.
I'm really grateful, too.
Hey, let me sing a special song
for you to show my gratitude!
A song?!
Don't worry.
It won't put you to sleep.
It's called "Thank You for Saving Us."
Not the most creative title...
I won't lose.
Whoo! Not bad!
Goodness, what is even going on?
Yeah, baby! It's getting good now!
Wow...
Well, see ya.
Thank you so much for your help.
Don't get caught by any
more bad people, okay?
You were without sin,
and I tried to kill you.
I'm sorry.
G-Goodbye!
Bye! Hope to see you again!
Dislike.
Eh?
First... apology.
Huh? What are you—
Damn it, what the hell was—
Uh, wait. What did you guys just do?
What?!