It's rolling.
My name is Yuki, written with
the characters for ghost and oni.
This was my 27th cleared game.
I'm closing in on 30.
Why did you start playing?
At first, I wanted money.
I was chronically broke.
When I was scouted by management,
I decided to participate.
Yes. After a few times, I had enough money.
But I didn't quit playing.
Why?
I thought that maybe I could keep doing this.
Since I'm risking my life,
it pays decently well.
I figured I could make a living doing this.
I'll probably die eventually
if I keep playing,
but then I'll just become an actual ghost.
That was fine with me.
What about now?
Thank you for waiting.
Susuki grass for a ghost?
Don't you think that's simplistic?
I haven't told you the name
of the next game yet.
Apparently, it's Ghost House.
This is a story about a deranged world.
You think I'll let my guard down?
That around 30 games, veterans let
their experience get to their head?
It's possible.
It's also possible that you'll perform worse
because I drew your attention
to the "Wall of 30."
But based on my experience,
it was nothing so ambiguous.
Everything works against you.
You'll feel like you're under attack
from the whole world.
How can I overcome that wall?
It would be so much easier if we knew.
She still felt a little dazed.
Her body felt heavy.
They were the effects of the sedative
given at the start and end of a game.
After completing her post-game custom,
Yuki went outside.
She went for a walk.
At some point, it had become her hobby.
Place the right foot forward, then the left.
Simply repeating that action.
However, not even that walk
raised Yuki's spirits.
28th, Ghost House.
29th, Dangerous Lab.
She knew her play had been
shameful in both games.
Something had to change.
Her next game would be her 30th.
Sixty-nine more games.
What has been essential?
Well...
Luck and meeting my mentor.
Oh, yes. I mean Hakushi-san.
Then there's...
Actually, before I could
even think about survival,
there was the question of
whether or not I could continue.
If I could put food on the table
playing deadly games.
In my case, well...
My mentor...
She...
No, wait.
Actually...
Why?
I guess I thought that this was fine.
I thought that this was fine.
Who is it?
My name is Kaneko.
I owe you much for what you did
for my daughter the other day.
Your daughter?
I believe she called herself
Kinko in the game.
How did you find out about me?
I used our network.
Are you aware of your
daughter's final moments?
We are planning to destroy that game.
We'd like you to help.
Naturally, once it's destroyed, we'll provide
you with all the support you need to live.
If you'd like, we can even
find new employment for you.
We don't seem to be on the same page.
Kaneko-san, do you think
I'm participating reluctantly?
You're not?
I'm not.
Look under the phone.
Huh?
It's a transmitter.
Swallow it before you head to your next game.
What are you—
We would appreciate your cooperation.
Is this a new sedative?
Yes. Unfortunately,
we're out of our regular one.
The effects are mostly
the same, so don't worry.
That's fine, then.
Your next game is your 30th.
You should start getting ready.
It was harder to swallow than usual.
That was not good.
Starting the game like this would not be good.
It could not be helped.
After swallowing it, Yuki realized
the additional mistake she had made.
After swallowing it, she realized
She could simply say she
didn't feel well and turn back.
She could have simply
said she changed her mind.
She attempted to resist,
Yuki attempted to resist,
but out of 29 times, she had not once
successfully fought off this drowsiness.
Ow.
Hey! I thought you'd all escaped already!
I'm Mikan.
If you'd like, we can look
for the exit... together...
Who's she?
Who knows?
Hey, where'd you find that?
Huh?
That tag. Where'd you find it?
In the shower at the start.
Let me see it.
I'll give it right back.
Hello? Can you hear me?
Come on, let's team up.
Okay?
Tsubaki!
Wait, damn it!
Hey! Don't get carried away!
Grab her!
Stop trying to run!
Let go! Let go of me!
Stop—
Okay! You can have the damn tag!
Hold her legs!
You'll get it now!
Sister.
Bye-bye.
It's time to end this.