This is a world where things like killing
and torture have been legalized.
Hey!
You there.
You wouldn't happen to be
interested in torture, would you?
What, this?
Oh, it's fine! It happens all the time!
What's up with this creep?
I think you'd be quite suited to it.
What do you think?
How about some torture?
You're a high school student, right?
I'm a freelance torturer.
Why do you think I'd be right for torture?
Because you have an overabundance
of free time and violence.
I was wandering around and some idiot
picked a fight with me, that's all.
Then it was legitimate self-defense!
There's also...
your face, I suppose.
"The beautiful is nothing other than
the origin of the fearsome."
Apparently, beautiful people
are suited to torture.
Here.
You can have this.
I didn't say I'd do—
This is a whip I used to use.
It should be perfect to start with.
Very nice. It looks good on you.
Oh, that reminds me.
I never asked your name, did I?
I'm Hera.
Siu.
For your first time,
that's very well done.
How was it?
How was it? Exhausting.
What a lackluster reaction.
Isn't there anything else?
Dragging out the answers he had in him
with my own two hands
felt... fun, I think.
You've got a good sense for this.
I knew you were suited for it.
All right! Now to contact the cleaner.
Yes, hello?
It got messier than usual.
No, not me. A new guy.
Take care of it, will you?
He's a weird guy.
Thanks for helping out again.
Having clean torturers like
you two around is a huge help.
Thank you.
Is the boy back there a new hire?
Yes.
He's recently started working with me.
I see.
You were lucky to meet
a good torturer like him.
I'm the one who was lucky,
meeting a good, talented kid like him.
Hey.
That guy earlier mentioned
"clean torturers." What does that mean?
Well, in this business,
there are many torturers who'll torture
people who aren't torture targets,
or who don't maintain
proper confidentiality.
It's unbelievable, really.
I want to produce results
using honest methods.
Otherwise, no one will
trust the kids of today
who become torturers in the future.
Hmm? What's wrong?
Why did you start doing this work?
I tagged along with a torturer
that I just happened to meet,
and the rest is history.
I guess it was just chance.
But...
it suited me as a person.
It felt like the truths I extracted
filled the cracks I had in me.
I'm the one who dragged you into this,
but whether you continue or not
is for you to decide.
Comfortable everyday life...
If I close my eyes, it's all wonderful.
If I go with him...
I'll lose these kinds of days.
Who'd regret losing this everyday life?
What?
What's that bandage for?
Ink.
And I quit school.
Well, that was sudden.
I'm not gonna quit.
You dragged a young person
with a promising future into this.
Take responsibility.
Well, of course. I'll do my very best.
What do you think? Do you feel
like spilling what you know?
He's a stubborn one.
Sorry!
My last job ran long.
You're late!
That's Von. He's in
the same business as us.
Nice to meet you.
Good work today.
Thank you for coming. It was a huge help.
You're quite welcome.
Well, I'll go and call the cleaner.
Thanks!
Siu-kun, was it?
I hear you quit school.
Yeah.
I'm sure you've already realized this,
but this is an odd industry.
Wouldn't it be better to get back
to a normal life as quick as you can?
Normal is a pretty good thing, you know.
Though, I guess since it was Hera-san
who caught you, it'd be hard to do.
What happened?
He coughed up foam and collapsed!
Don't worry.
He isn't dead.
Thank you, Izua.
If there's a patient,
of course I'll come.
You're so dependable!
Ramen
As you can see, I'm a doctor
that these guys work to the bone.
A doctor?
Even the kind of trash that gets tortured
needs medical treatment sometimes.
But when it's guys like that,
and we're treating them when
they're gonna get injured anyway...
Not many doctors would do that willingly.
So I do it because
I figure it's necessary.
I do look after regular
patients, too, though.
When you do this kind of work,
you end up attracting
all kinds of weirdos.
Like this guy, who seems unmotivated,
but has a set of personal
policies in his work.
Yeah, yeah.
Or guys who appear detached and aimless,
but are unexpectedly sensitive.
It's because this work isn't easy.
There's also...
punk kids with empty bellies...
and police officers
who treat them to ramen.
There's all sorts of people here.
Yeah.
Given where I am now,
I wonder if I'd be able to help
a kid who's like I was back then.
Why are you getting all sentimental?
Want me to do a consult?
What? It's not like that.
It's just... you know.
Pull yourself together.
Okay, let's give it our
best tomorrow, too!
I've got myself a good
partner now, after all.
Right?
I'll try my best to live up
to your expectations.
You're so dependable!
3 Years Later
Oh, this is the best!
Siu-san, thank you for
doing this all the time.
Don't you get sick of having
omelet rice all the time, Noe?
Nope! Your omelet rice is just so good!
He seems like he'll make
a good papa one day!
As if.
Well, I'll go and check your job requests.
If you would, please.
Come back safely!
Be careful out there today, too!
Noe has grown up into
a good boy, hasn't he?
Has it already been three years?
Yeah.
I'm so glad Noe and I
became family that day.
Thanks to you and Noe, every day is fun.
Glad to hear it.
I want to stay like this forever.
But, well...
Von quit being a torturer...
and I'm sure people don't normally
last too long in this job, but...
Siu, do you think you'll be
able to continue doing this?
I can't imagine myself not
being a torturer anymore.
Probably.
How do I put it? I feel like this job
has become the place where I belong.
There's something I've been
thinking for a while now.
It'd be nice if I could create a place
in this world where torturers could stay.
A place...
Hera!
Damn punks, running wild
all over our turf like that...
Stupid brats!
We won't let you off so easily next time.
You understand now, don't you?
Get out of the torturing
business while you can.
Please...
Please save him.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault someone so important
to you is in that condition.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
It's because Hera protected me.
Morning... Siu.
I seem... to have
overslept... quite a bit.
What are you talking about?
You moron.
Ow, ow, ow!
Sorry.
That's enough of that.
It's my responsibility, after all.
Besides...
the truth is, I've taken
a bit of a liking to it.
The old scar I've had
since I was a child...
This new scar has swallowed it up.
It's proof that I made these
choices of my own free will.
And that's why there's no
need to make that face.
Everything is better this way.
Are you stupid?
Hey, Siu, do you remember?
I was talking about wanting
to make a place...
Contract Complete
I'll make it so that
everyone can feel safer.
Contract Complete
Just wait. Okay?
Independent Torture Contractor
Spirytus (Co.)
You seem very comfortable
with that appearance of yours now.
Right?
You're beautiful once again today.
Noe, you're such a good, honest boy!
Noe, I finished up all
the work allotted for today.
If you've got anything else, send it over.
Oh. I will!
Siu-san seems very eager
to work, doesn't he?
Hera-san, it's time
to apply your medicine.
Oh. So it is.
Thanks for always helping.
It's nothing.
Come on!
I told you! You have it all wrong!
I'm just a journalist!
I've been made to pose as
a torture target, that's all!
Darn it...
Seriously, how did I get into this?
Why all the fuss?
Hey! Untie me!
It's the truth! I'm telling you,
I'm just a reporter!
Are you really a torture target?
I just said I'm not!
I'm sorry we treated you so roughly.
I should say you have!
But I'm used to it.
It happens a lot in my line of work.
I do hear a lot of information that would
be inconvenient for various organizations.
And that's why they sent you here, huh?
Exactly. They're merciless, you know?
But never mind all that.
Thank you for earlier!
You untied my ropes so quickly.
Right.
As thanks, if there's any info
you need, just let me know!
Despite how it looks,
I'm good at what I do!
Well, this is my contact information.
I'm Sowa. Looking forward
to working with you!
Oh! That reminds me...
That girl from before, um...
Sowa.
Yes, that's right.
I've asked her to do some
simple digging for me.
Yeah?
She was very cheerful, wasn't she?
What is it?
I just thought the two of you
might get along surprisingly well!
Say...
haven't you been smoking
a little too much?
You should take a break
every once in a while.
It's good to be passionate
about your work, but...
What a pain.
Hello!
You're here again?
Yes! And I've brought provisions!
No one asked you to.
Wow, looks like this
week will be rough, too.
Don't look at that without permission!
Siu, the color of your
hair here is just like mine!
Why'd you drop the honorifics?
Well, I am older than you, after all!
Stop that.
Hey, look at that!
It's beautiful!
This kind of thing is nice
every once in a while.
I'm glad.
I got to see you enjoying yourself.
That scar.
Isn't it exhausting
covering it up all the time?
Even if it is...
it was all my fault, so...
You don't have to hide it
from me, though.
I want to know more about that scar...
and about you.
Even though she didn't
have anyone in this world,
she was ridiculously sunny and bright.
She could find a way into
people's hearts in a flash.
That said, she knew
loneliness all too well.
When we were together, it felt like all
the empty cracks inside me were filled.
I thought it was the same for her.
Thank you.
Take care of yourself, okay?
But she suddenly disappeared.
I wondered vaguely if that
was all there was to her.
I was reunited with
her three years later...
in a hospital.
Why... are you in a place like this?
Sorry to contact you out of the blue!
You should apologize for
disappearing out of the blue.
Yes, you're right.
Mama! Who's that?
Who's that?
Who could it be?
Are those my kids?
Oh. You can tell?
They're adorable,
aren't they? They're twins.
Is this why you disappeared on me?
Yes, it is.
Because you couldn't depend on me?
That wasn't it.
I just selfishly ran away. That's all.
When I thought that you
might start to see me as a burden...
It terrified me.
You were the first connection I'd
made that meant so much to me.
You're a moron.
Yes, you're right.
You know...
They say... I only have
half a year left to live.
Do they?
Sowa...
want to get married?
Did you always have this much compassion?
It would be better if we did.
After you're gone,
you won't be able to look
after them, right?
I see.
Is that cold of me?
No.
It was that kindness of yours
that I fell in love with.
Thank you.
Over here! No, over here!
Hey, you two. It's ready.
Okay!
Papa, it's amazing!
You're so good at this!
Hurry up and eat. The bus is coming.
Okay!
The cats are so cute!
I love omelet rice!
Me, too!
I thought you quit smoking.
Every once in a while is fine.
It's been a little while since
Sowa-chan passed away.
How are things after all that?
Things are... not bad.
I see.
I wish Sowa had relied on me more.
But she did call you, didn't she?
She entrusted her
precious children to you.
She definitely relied on you,
and you're living up to it just fine.
All of it... is what
Sowa-chan chose for herself.
Even this thing about my scars...
You took responsibility for
them like no one else could.
You're the best partner
I could ever have.
Thanks.
My, this is unusual.
Back then, you called out to me.
I've only been able to walk
this far without losing my way
because you were there for me.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
Hey. When are we gonna get more workers?
Oh, come on. At least wash
your face before you come in.
Just how many cases do you think
I'm handling by myself here?
Now, now.
We have some new help coming tomorrow.
Yeah, someone useless again, I bet.
Well, it's rare for people
to stick with this job.
How many have we had quit this year?
Sixty-eight.
What kind of kid are you hoping for?
Whoever comes, it's always the same.
I hope someone you'll like shows up.
Yeah...
I won't get my hopes up.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Elanor Sakamato
John Chandanais
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Becky Cottrill