Yelenetta's attacking!
Evacuate!
I don't believe it.
Lady Arte's homeland...
N-No way.
M-Mother!
EASYGOING TERRITORY DEFENSE
BY THE OPTIMISTIC LORD
EPISODE 12: EASYGOING TERRITORY
DEFENSE BY THE OPTIMISTIC LORD
In short, their commander says Yelenetta
Kingdom's plan was a three-pronged attack.
Seatoh and Scudet
were two of those prongs.
And the last one is...
Ferdinatto County.
Arte's homeland.
Lord Van.
Please let me go there.
Then, I'll go, too.
No.
I can't rely on you
for everything, Lord Van.
But you're talking about
going off to war.
This is a family matter.
I've never seen Arte
this stubborn before.
I'm sorry.
I know you're genuinely worried
about me, Lord Van. But I...
Oh, I see. If I were to save
Ferdinatto County from danger...
You're the lord of
a small, remote village.
If someone like you saved them...
Mm-hmm. Count Ferdinatto
would lose his standing
and maybe even his land as well.
Guess that's all there is to say. But can
I at least provide you with an escort?
Yes. Thank you for your consideration.
Please leave that to us.
She'll definitely be safe
with us guarding her.
We'll protect your future wife.
Ortho? And you, too, Kusala and Pluriel?
It's fine. We just want
to help you out, Lord Van.
Besides, adventurers like us getting
involved won't create any issues.
All right. Please take care
of Arte, you guys.
M-Mother!
Oh, young lady!
Drop the black balls!
Lady Arte.
If we join the battle now,
we might be able to turn the tide.
Please let me command this squad.
You can't.
It must be someone from House Ferdinatto
who drives out Yelenetta Kingdom.
But how will you handle that army?
Hurry and evacuate!
Save me!
How can this be?
I can't believe Yelenetta's army
is attacking us.
M-Mother.
You must not cry.
SHARON TORA FERDINATTO
I'll make sure it looks like you
committed suicide at the very end.
Later generations must see
the eldest daughter ended her life cleanly
like a noble should.
Don't fret.
Mother.
Arte?
Ferdinatto County is no match
for the Yelenetta army.
Now, let's conquer it!
Yeah!
Victory is already ours.
Wh-What just happened?
A silver knight is attacking the wyverns!
A silver knight?
Th-That's impossible.
They took out all of
those wyverns in a flash!
What the hell is that thing?
Commander, this is bad!
House Ferdinatto's flag
has been spotted on the hill!
Damn it. Curse the Scuderian army.
They sent reinforcements, huh?
Change target to the forces on the hill.
We'll attack with our full might!
But what about the silver knight?
Won't be worth fearing
if we crush their main force.
Now, go annihilate them!
Yeah!
The enemy's coming to crush us first.
I knew it wouldn't go as easily
as it did for Lord Van.
I don't know enough about battle.
And I can't stop my hands from shaking.
But I have to do all I can.
Ortho.
What is it?
I'm sorry, but could I
ask you for support?
Yes, of course.
Everyone...
Please lend me your strength.
Please help me save my homeland.
Everyone...
Please lend me your strength.
Please help me save my homeland.
What are you planning to do, Lady Arte?
I'm...
I'm going to the front line.
Lady Arte?
Automaton! Uno!
Get them!
Damn it. How are they
so overwhelmingly strong?
All right. We're going, too.
Yeah!
Settle down!
What? I can't move!
Looks like it's my turn.
Piece of cake.
How dare you hurt my brother-in-arms!
Kusala!
Prepare yourself!
Its arm...
What? You can still move?
Huh?
Y-You saved me there.
Thank you, Lady Arte.
Good.
Looks like we've taken
control of this area.
Is it finally over?
We had quite a tough time of it.
Not yet!
What?
No way.
They have that many wyverns?
There's roughly 50 of them.
It always pays to be cautious.
I requested reinforcements.
Now, wyverns!
Take down that silver knight!
No! We're in trouble!
Look out!
Th-That's...
Another of Lady Arte's marionettes?
No way... She can move two at once?
My mana won't last long like this.
Keep the pressure on!
There's just too many of them.
Decimate our enemies...
Aventador!
I've always believed I was a failure.
Even though I was a noble,
my aptitude was for marionette magic.
A type of magic loathed by all.
I swore I would never use it
in front of others again.
But then, Lord Van saved me.
Because I met Lord Van,
I was able to gain confidence.
What power...
She took out more than half
in the blink of an eye.
Incredible.
What are you doing?
Crush them!
I...
I will save those precious to me
with this magic!
Last one!
Th-That's impossible.
Yelenetta's army...
I'm getting outta here!
They're too strong!
We can't win!
We did it!
We won!
Yeah!
We did it!
We were able to win thanks
to these girls Lord Van gave me.
I'm sorry for making you fight
until you got so battered.
I'm truly grateful to you
for saving my home.
Who in the world saved us?
So this is where you were.
Darling.
I'm sorry I was late.
I'm glad you're safe.
Father.
Do you know anything
about those reinforcements?
Yes.
All I know now is that the Yelenetta army
was driven off by just two marionettes.
Huh?
The other thing I know is a young girl
with white hair was standing at the head,
commanding those reinforcements.
You don't mean...
Yes.
No... It can't be!
How ironic.
Especially after we drove her
from our home.
We treated that girl poorly.
Are you sure you aren't going home?
Your parents are right there.
I would only cause them trouble
if I went home.
But the city was saved
thanks to your marionettes.
The people will be overjoyed when they
hear you were the one controlling them.
Even your parents—
I wouldn't be so sure.
My mother loathed
my marionette magic.
Let's go home. Lord Van is waiting for us.
Lady Arte has returned!
Arte, are you hurt?
What's the matter?
I'm no good.
Why do you think that?
Well...
I couldn't issue commands to everyone
with confidence like you do.
I think you're doing just fine.
If anything, I can't understand why
you're lacking confidence.
I mean, it's incredible how you move
your marionettes so freely.
But...
Lady Panamera said it before.
She hardly recognized you as the girl
she brought here from that county.
That's because you're very kind, Lord Van.
Arte.
You did very well.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
TRANSLATION: JOHN PICKETT
TIMING: ANDY ELLIS
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: RILEY DALTON
TRANSLATION CHECK: REI MIYASAKA
Ta-da!
I've created new shops and
a new inn in the center of town.
Wow, they're lovely.
Yup. I want all of the villagers
to enjoy a pleasant life, after all.
I was honestly worried about living here
when I first arrived, but...
Can you believe it?
This once-impoverished place has
transformed into such a lovely village.
Welcome!
Welcome to all.
We have the latest goods
from the royal capital!
Please stop in and take a look.
Don't go fallin' off now, grannies!
I see they haven't changed.
We have all ages, races,
and personality types in this village,
but everyone gets along oddly well,
and they're all having fun.
Cheers!
This meat is really good!
Hey, Kusala! That was my meat!
That's your fifteenth drink.
Impressive, Lady Panamera.
I was born a noble,
but my aptitude for production magic
got me kicked out of my home by my father,
and I became the lord
of a remote village.
However, thanks to him,
I've met many entertaining friends,
and I was able to develop
this remote village.
I thought I'd lost my home,
but I found myself enjoying life,
and this village became precious
to me before I knew it.
Thank you, everyone.
Lord Van.
It is nearly time for your studies.
I'll ensure you get a thorough education.
Lord Van!
This is the era of swordsmanship!
I'm going to train you to become
this kingdom's greatest swordsman!
No, Lord Van shall become
the kingdom's most astounding scholar.
I won't let that stand.
I don't want to be either!
Ah, hey, Lord Van!
Wait up!
It's so lively, isn't it?
You can do it, Lord Van!
You need to run faster
or they'll catch you.
Just a little further.
That's it! Go on!
Run faster, young man!
Hang in there, Lord Van!
Okay! I'm gonna continue making leisurely
progress toward a fun place for all of us to live!