Thank you for the meal.
What's wrong?
Done already?
You need to eat a proper lunch, y'know?
Or was it not to your liking?
No, it's delicious!
I just don't have much of an appetite.
I'm really sorry.
Are you sure?
Maybe it's a touch of heat exhaustion.
Oh, I'm fine.
It's also that I don't want
to gain weight...
But man, my chest feels so tight.
Sano.
I could help—
Izumi-sama!
I missed you so much.
The beach is so boring without you!
I came back on my own ahead of everyone.
Listen here.
I'm working right now.
Call me Tamami!
Come on, get off me.
No way!
You still haven't gone swimming.
Ashiya-kun.
Get off.
Oh, yeah?
Can you help me change the light
bulbs around the entrance?
Sure.
Ashiya-kun?
Hey, Ashiya-kun!
Ashi—
Sano?
Don't touch him.
Is Mizuki-kun all right?
He seems fine.
But you call me right away
if anything seems off.
Huh?
Yes, ma'am.
You back?
Oh, right.
I couldn't breathe all of a sudden.
It's because I forced myself
to wear that tight binder...
Should I call a doctor?
No, I don't need one.
I'm fine.
All right.
Then I'll get back to work.
Okay.
Sorry for troubling you.
Don't worry about it.
I've got the rest covered,
so you just rest for the day.
Okay.
Got it?
He's leaving.
S-Sorry.
What am I even doing?
Do you want me to stay?
Fine. I'll stay until you fall
asleep, so hurry up already.
Okay.
What should I do?
I'm checking on him 'cause he's unwell,
but I might just be a bother.
Yet on the other hand,
if I don't see that he's fine,
I'll be too worried to live—
Drop your one-man comedy
act and get back to work!
How about cleaning the back yard?!
Yes, ma'am.
I slept so long.
Sano?
He's not here.
Of course.
Oh wow, I sweat a ton in my sleep.
Staff Only
That feels great!
Getting out of that binder is such a relief.
I think...
I really have gained weight.
Damn, it's hot!
Nakatsu?!
I can't take being
covered in sweat anymore.
I forgot to lock the bathroom door!
Don't come in here!
Now what do I do?!
Huh?
Th-That was a surprise...
Wait, th-this is a chance for us
to be in the bath together.
What are you thinking, you idiot?
You sound like a pervert!
Dumbass.
Just be honest with yourself.
I mean, think about it.
Nothing weird about two bros
getting in the bath together.
Damn right!
We're bros.
Why am I freaking out over this?
Let's go!
It's not like I'm doing this with a girl.
Yeah, it's not like... he's a girl...
I can't!
Wh-What?!
N-Nakatsu?
Jeez!
What happened?
N-Nakatsu?!
Hey! Hey! Nakatsu!
Nakatsu, sorry!
Clothes... Clothes!
Okay, done!
Just hang in there!
I'll go get someone!
I can't believe I got a
nosebleed and passed out.
What the hell was wrong
with me last night?!
It's too early in the morning for this!
It's Not Like We Could Become Lovers
Good morning.
Getting in some training?
You could say.
I really need to be ready
for the next tournament.
He looks like he's enjoying himself.
There you are!
Really, you are so bad!
You promised you'd go to the
beach with me this morning.
I never did that.
Hey, get off of me!
Oh, morning, Mizuki-kun!
Good morning!
Listen to this, Mizuki-kun.
Izumi-sama's the worst, isn't he?
I told you to stop calling me that.
Mizuki-kun.
Makita-san?
Good morning.
How are you feeling?
Think you can have breakfast?
Yes, I'm fine.
That bastard.
Huh?
Oh yeah, I need to go buy stuff later.
Wanna come with?
Yeah, that'd be nice.
Yo.
Hey.
Kagurazaka.
Who was that with you just now?
Makita-san?
He's my coworker.
You two seem to be
hanging out a lot lately.
What happened to Sano?
I mean, it's not like he and I
are together all the time.
We have different work tasks...
Hmm, that's not like you.
I know Tamami scurrying
around is annoying,
but you're usually more of a loose cannon.
Huh?
I actually appreciate that side of you.
So stop looking so down.
Kagurazaka...
Are you trying to cheer me up?
I mean, I'm a nice guy.
Not that I give a damn about
what happens to you two.
Yeah, right.
You've got a thing for Sano too.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Beware Bears
I like women!
Women! Women!
Anyway, that Makita guy or whatever...
I don't like his vibe.
Could you grab that bag over there?
Sure.
You can leave the heavy stuff to me.
Thank you.
I think he's a nice person.
You two can take a break.
I'll go get some fresh air.
I'll get some drinks.
Izumi-sama!
Good work.
Not you again.
I'm cleaning the entrance now,
so stop getting in my way.
Izumi-sama, wait!
You look like an abandoned kitten.
Makita-san...
Don't wanna spend your break with me?
No, that's fine.
Here you go.
Thanks.
See? Someone who's kind
at a time like this...
I can't think he's a bad guy.
You like peach?
Yeah!
Nice. Great minds think alike.
I know you having to clean is a lie!
Come on!
The beach?
That's right.
We're taking a special break
between guest check-out tomorrow
and preparing for dinner.
Are you sure?
Of course I am!
You came all the way here
to the beach, and it's summer.
Besides...
I bought myself a brand-new swimsuit!
She's really something.
The beach, huh?
This'll be fun.
I guess.
Can you even get in the water?
Yeah, so, Ashiya...
Hmm?
I hope Makita hasn't done
anything weird to you.
What do you mean by that?
Pretty obvious, no?
Being overly touchy,
putting his arm around your shoulder...
What? That's just him being friendly.
I don't think you get what he's after,
which is why I'm trying to warn you.
It's normal to be friendly
like that back in the States.
And look who's talking!
You're awful happy with a big-chested
girl like Tamami hanging off you all day!
I-I'm gonna go take a bath.
H-Hey.
Damn it.
This is exactly what I meant
when I said you don't get it.
I went and said all that...
It's not like we're lovers...
It's not like we could become lovers.
Because I'm a "boy" right now.
Wait...
Could it be...
The binder wasn't so tight
because I gained weight,
but because my boobs got bigger?
I'm over the moon, but this isn't
what I need right now!
Damn it!
I can't properly enjoy this!
Whoo!
It's the ocean!
What's up, Mizuki?
Aren't you hot in that sweater?
I, uh... don't think I'm 100 percent yet.
Just playing it safe.
That's too bad.
Yeah.
But just coming out to the beach is fun.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, wow! You look great, Mayumi-san.
Lookin' real good yourself, Boss!
My, I do like an honest boy.
I mean, the sunhat does
give your age away.
It screams, "I'd rather die
than get the slightest tan."
Let's go, everyone!
Hot!
I'm so hungry I could die.
It's already lunchtime.
I'll go buy something.
We're counting on you.
Have you seen Tamami?
Nah, I haven't.
She just ran off by herself.
Babysitting ain't easy, huh?
Kyomi.
Be a good girl and wait here.
Huh?
I'm gonna go find Tamami, so keep
an eye on her while I'm gone.
Hey, wait!
Uh...
So unfair!
We haven't talked since.
Sano.
Hey, so... I'm sorry
for all that yesterday.
Ashiya.
Yesterday... was...
Gosh, what a coincidence!
I can't believe I get to
be with you at the beach!
Hey, hey, Mizuki-kun!
Got a second?
Okay, like, so does Izumi-sama
hate the color orange?
What do you think?
Oh.
I'm sure he doesn't mind
a girl in bright colors.
You're fine.
Really?
Thank goodness!
Thank you, Mizuki-kun!
Izumi-sama!
I just can't bring myself to hate her.
Io-san's not back from shopping...
Mizuki's disappeared too.
Kagurazaka dumped this on me
and then ran off.
I'm all by my lonesome.
I wonder what Sano was
trying to tell me earlier.
Shaved Ice
And where did Nakatsu and the others go?
Showers
Restaurant
Seafood
Bowls
Hey, girl!
You looking for someone?
We could help you.
Thanks, but I'm fine.
I don't need any help.
Hey, hey now!
Don't be so cold.
Icy!
Are you just going to keep following me?
But...
Knock it off and leave me alone.
Let me go!
Ashiya?
Sorry, but they're with me.
Damn, she's with someone?
Why didn't you say so?
Makita-san?
You okay?
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
Standing around here looking lost
will have guys like
that on you like flies.
Yeah, sorry...
Found you!
You just bolted out of the blue!
There you are, Mizuki.
Nakatsu!
Io-san got us some lunch.
Wanna come eat?
Yeah!
Where's everyone else?
That's just it.
Everybody ditched me.
Where are you going, Izumi-sama?
Wait, don't just leave me here!
Izumi?
Hey, Izumi!
Sano...
What's his problem?
Did he not hear me?
Well, they look like they're having fun,
so let's stay out of their way.
I know I haven't talked to Sano
since our fight last night...
Maybe he really is angry.
Whoa, watermelon!
I cut a bunch, so why don't
you call our guests over?
Yes, ma'am!
The guests eat first!
Down, boy!
Edamame and cold beer are nice,
but nothing beats watermelon
in a yukata on a summer night.
Oh, wow.
The pretty lady looks good
even in a yukata.
Oh, you charmer!
Come on now, eat up.
Io-san, can I take this?
I figured you'd be out here.
Um, so...
Uh...
She cut us some watermelon.
Want any?
Yeah.
Japanese watermelons are round, huh?
The ones in the States are oblong,
so I was pretty surprised.
And these are really sweet, too.
I've even heard there are
yellow and seedless ones.
Amazing, right?
Sorry, I'm babbling over here.
I've been thinking all this time...
About how to apologize
for what happened last night.
Us getting into a fight over him
is the dumbest thing ever.
So ridiculous.
You're right...
That's true.
This watermelon's good.
Yeah.
I'll go put this away.
Okay.
There's no point in saying anything.
She's dense, rash, stubborn,
and has zero self-preservation instinct.
I really...
I really have to look out
for her, don't I?
But what am I to her?
I should just let her be.
We're only roommates.
When did being together become so natural?
She has this soft side
but despises losing,
and she's crazy enough to come here
from the States, pretending to be a guy.
And yet here I am pretending
not to know she's a girl...
Why?
What am I trying to achieve?
Hey. So this is where you were.
What do you want?
Nothing much.
Just to talk, man to man.
Kyomi, that sour face is not cute.
Try laughing.
Why don't I show you?
Now I just feel like an idiot.
Idiot.
Next Time
Can Things Stay This Way?
What'd you say?!