Suppressing the urge to speed off,
these 15 drivers focus
on the drones in front of them,
waiting for that light to turn green.
And the 16, our final competitor,
passes through the gate!
And there's the green!
It's a picture-perfect start!
It's all orderly as the Godly Fifteen
zoom away in single file!
Sawatari in the 4 car is
pushing hard from the start,
even though his tires will still be cold.
This is likely his strategy.
He's going on the offensive
by flying out of the gate.
Living up to his reputation, Sawatari
the gambler risks it all without fear.
But will it pay off in the end
or cost him dearly?
It's no good.
I still can't stand to watch.
Honey, you could at least try.
Our children are
working hard in this race.
What does it say if we turn away?
Our children?
You're right.
I'm already so proud
of Kana-chan and Ren.
The 4 car is in the process
of eking out a lead.
How will the two cars
directly behind him respond?
They're nearly at the Hydro Trap.
The 4 car splashes through it!
And the size of the spray he's kicking up
indicates how fast he's going!
Whoa! The 4 is thrown
sharply off balance!
Did his wet tires
lose purchase on the road?
Get a grip, Sawatari,
you utter imbecile.
The 4 car is spinning out.
How do I avoid him? Right? Or left?
Right!
Mistake.
The 4 car spins out!
And with their line blocked, the 12
and the 86 spin to avoid a collision!
MF Ghost
I've never seen chaos like it!
What's happening out there, folks?
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
The Strongest
Train
The top three in qualifying
have come to a complete stop!
They managed to avoid crashing,
but the cars previously behind them
are now blasting past.
There's a gap between the Lamborghini
and the red car behind it.
You know what to do. Go, Katagiri.
The 86 and the 12 manage
to get going again!
Lightning fast as always,
the pair executed perfect spin turns!
That was quite impressive.
They recognized there was enough space
between the 3 and the 18 to squeeze in.
Even the slightest hesitation
would've made it harder to rejoin.
They ran the risk of colliding
with the next car.
They acted before race control issued
a directive, which worries me a little.
I doubt they'll get a penalty for it.
The driver of the 86 seemed
100% confident in his maneuver,
and the 12 car spun it around
pretty much in tandem.
I think both of them having three-pedal
manual transmission was key.
Being a two-pedal automatic,
the 4 couldn't pull the same trick.
And Sawatari, our polesitter,
rejoins the race in last place.
A mistake like this is hard to imagine
from a driver like Sawatari Koki.
What do you suppose happened?
I'd say he got on the power a split second
too early after exiting the trap.
The wet tires didn't grip the road
in the way the driver was expecting.
With the adrenaline pumping,
it wasn't the measured start he needed,
and the Hydro Trap was in the perfect place
to pounce on that nervous energy.
Ah, Ko-kun!
He's been acting differently
since our date yesterday.
He didn't even finish his lunch.
It's the kind of call I doubt he'd make
if he were in a calm state of mind.
And it shows the pressure of starting
on pole and trying to stay out in front.
All that pressure must've
been weighing him down.
My poor Ko-kun.
I'll make you feel better later,
so please come back to me in one piece.
Ah, what a joke.
Well, I never denied being a screwup.
Still, that's a huge weight
off my shoulders now.
Feels like someone exorcised ten specters
that were clinging to me.
All I gotta do now is pass some cars.
I already got the pole position bonus,
so it's time to add to the stack
by scoring some overtaking bonuses.
Wait for me, Sana.
Whatever you want, it's yours.
The Godly Fifteen bear down
on the hairpin where Sector 1
becomes Sector 2!
Let's take a look at the order
at this juncture.
In the lead, it's Moroboshi in the 885.
In second, it's Emma Greene in the 624.
Akaba is third in the 2 car.
Aiba is fourth in the 9.
Fifth, Yanagida in the 6.
Sixth, Ishigami in the 1 car.
Seventh, Maezono in the 13.
Eighth, Oishi in the 3 car.
And here, back in ninth place,
it's Katagiri in the 86.
Tenth belongs to Beckenbauer in the 12.
These two still have plenty of the race left
to climb up through the field.
And I have no doubts over
whether they've given up.
These red and white bullets
have explosive potential!
In 11th, it's Kitahara in the 18.
In 12th, it's Sakamoto in the 5.
13th belongs to Taylor in the 8.
In 14th, it's Yashio in the 16.
And the 4 car is already
hot on their heels!
Being able to rejoin the race without
damaging the car is paying off big-time.
That's Sawatari Koki in his blue bullet,
one of MFG's famous tricolor racers!
How far can he climb up
the field? Let's watch.
My mind's gone blank.
I've lost my pacemaker.
Booth to Sena. You're wrecking your tires.
This race has six laps, remember.
Rein it in!
I would if I could, damn it.
I don't know how to set the freaking pace.
What do you think of my pace?
Am I going too slow?
Obviously not. Stay confident.
So I'm not going slow?
Despite the fact the Aston's
breathing down my neck?
The whole world is watching me
lead the pack right now.
My Gunma pride won't let me
drive like a chump.
What's going on?
Something about the 885 makes it
easy to stick close to him.
It's like he has something in common
with Mr. Fujiwara's driving.
I think it might be the rhythm.
I could pass if I wanted,
but there's something to be said
for seeing how this plays out.
The race has only just begun,
and it's going to be a long one.
I'll be patient for now.
Because I know you'll be back.
And you're the one
I want to battle, darling.
The Godly Fifteen scythe through
the forested area of Sector 2.
And just look at those big numbers
unexpectedly occupying first and second.
Being at the head of the pack
comes with any number of stresses.
Gotta wonder if it's too much
for a rookie like Moroboshi.
This might've turned into
a stroke of luck for Kanata.
His biggest rivals are behind him,
and the top two are rookies,
lacking in experience.
This could be a real opportunity, right?
If he's able to climb up
through the field...
That's one way of looking at it,
but you're forgetting one vital thing.
Beckenbauer is the
"absolute king" for a reason,
and it remains to be seen what he'll do
now that he's right on our tail.
The sunny yellow Supra and the dark green
Aston Martin emerge from the shade.
And a bright red Ferrari
is honing in on them.
Our colorful top three are
coming up to the Jumping Spot.
This seems a good moment to ask, Sudo-san.
Jumps are a bit of a rarity
in the world of racing...
...aside from in rally, which often
takes place on mountainous courses.
As a rally driver yourself, could you give us
some insight on how to take jumps?
I understand. I can certainly try.
Since this is
a man-made jump,
it's a bit different from
the kind you find in nature.
But in general, it's about
controlling where and how
you're going to land.
The last thing you want
to do is lose speed
or hit the brakes.
If you're tipped forward
when you land,
you'll be thrown off balance.
That'll prevent you
from braking in time
for the next right turn,
and risks sending you
out of the course.
The crucial thing is to grip the wheel
and try to touch down level.
If you start rotating in the air,
you'll be all over the place when you land,
and as you struggle to regain control,
you're at risk of spinning or crashing.
So in general, grip the wheel,
don't touch the brakes,
and keep the gas pedal half down.
The more you explain it, the more
dangerous and difficult it sounds.
It's pretty tough to verbalize it.
But I imagine these 15 elite drivers
are able to handle it all intuitively.
The leaders are now
on the run-up to the jump.
The jumping-off point awaits.
This legion of supercars takes to the air!
An incredible sight! It's Double Lane's
specialty, the Jumping Spot!
You won't see a race like this
anywhere else in the world!
Here's the duo in the spotlight.
The 12 is still clinging to the 86's rear,
putting unrelenting pressure
on Katagiri Kanata!
This is what I was talking about.
With Beckenbauer on his tail,
Katagiri-kun can't make a move
even if he wants to.
His overtaking options
have been reduced.
If he tries to pull ahead, he creates
an opening for the car behind him.
Whether he goes to the inside or
the outside, he'll always leave a gap.
That's definitely bad news.
A driver like Beckenbauer
won't miss that kind of chance.
Even with their inherent speed,
if this pair are stuck in a stalemate,
it'll be hard for them to move forward.
But there's something about how
the 12 is moving that bothers me.
Would he actually try that?
MF Ghost.
Mr. Beckenbauer.
I sense no intent to pass from you.
You're maintaining the exact distance
that will maximize the tow.
With you occupying the draft
directly behind me,
the 86 is accelerating smoothly.
I can tell my top speed is above
what I'd reach if I were on my own.
Are you actually helping me?
If you are, I gratefully accept the aid.
I'll switch to pursuit mode now.
Do try to keep up.
He's stopped trying to block me.
Seems I got through to him.
He's surprisingly quick on the uptake.
This gentleman's agreement
is a win-win for both of us.
Let's see what you've got.
Eyes forward, Katagiri.
Oh, fantastic. That nightmare,
Katagiri, is right behind me.
And behind him is someone
even worse: the crazy German.
How bad can things get?
What did I do to deserve this?
It feels like my life's on the line.
Again with this?
Why am I never able to hold him at bay?
Huh. An interesting choice.
There's movement
in the middle of the pack!
The 86 is going on the attack!
Damn it. The Porsche is making
a move while I'm still all at sea.
And I'm supposed to take on these monsters
at the corner into Sector 3?
It's not worth the risk.
And here comes the 18!
A third one? Seriously?
Screw you, Kitahara.
You're not going anywhere.
Once I get my nose in there,
I don't back down from endurance tests.
This is turning into
something incredible.
A sequence of side-by-side battles.
The 3 car is under relentless attack!
Katagiri Kanata
was the first to strike,
followed by the 12 car,
and now the 18 is taking advantage!
But the 3 car is fighting back!
The bumpy road's a struggle for its tires.
It's a desperate cornering battle
as they both fight to maintain balance.
I keep hitting the biggest bumps
for some reason.
The 3 car is starting to be outdragged.
Kitahara in the 18 zooms off in front!
Oishi in the 3 car has
just lost three positions!
What a shocking display.
Could you talk us through
what we just saw, Sudo-san?
The 86 created an opening which must've
been extremely painful for Oishi-kun.
When cars go side by side,
it always slows both of them a little,
creating the perfect opening
for the cars behind.
And that's all the space they need.
When was the last time
we duked it out, Sawatari?
We never seem to get to
mix it up while racing.
We're both driving cars with
nimbleness as a selling point.
Don't expect me to just lie down.
Bring it on, Alpine.
I think it was two seasons ago now?
I recall you and your sis giving me trouble
with your barely legal blocking.
But on your own? I have nothing to fear.
Where is your talented sister, anyway?
Did she leave you in the dust?
If I remember right,
she always was better than you.
You're making a move here?
Talk about forcing the issue.
Bad choice, Yashio.
You don't look steady at all.
We're seeing movement
at the back now!
And the 4 car goes for it!
He's pulling ahead!
Sawatari in the 4 climbs up a spot!
The tricolor musketeers
are all making moves.
Was this simply fated to happen?
We're seeing the beginning of their quest
to reclaim their original spots.
Now, we go back up front.
They exit Sector 3 and
head back along the shoreline.
We're into the second lap of the race!
And now, a question for
Big Sis Kyoko and Number Seven.
Any sweet memories of summer break
to share? We'll start with Big Sis.
Mine was awful.
I got hit with norovirus
after eating some raw fish,
and I felt like I was gonna die.
I had killer runs and puked up a storm.
I was basically trapped
in the bathroom.
Big Sis Kyoko.
I know being self-effacing is kind of
your thing, but isn't that a bit overboard?
It's not a joke.
What do you want me to say?
What happened, happened.
That said, I lost 4 kg and my waist shrunk,
so I'm looking even finer than usual.
Moving on from that, uh,
scatological anecdote...
On to something hopefully a bit more
glamorous. Take it away, Number Seven.
Well, I, uh, had a lot of fun, honestly.
I went to visit my grandma in Niigata,
and it was like taking
a trip back to my childhood.
Stuff like that is so enjoyable.
I went to a fireworks display
in a yukata, too.
It was all clichéd summery stuff,
but that didn't ruin it.
I'd say it was a special one for me.
Perfect. Exactly the kind of
idealized picture I was hoping for.
I've never heard two
more contrasting answers.
Downright chaotic.
Beckenbauer and Kanata?
Talk about a scary combo.
No planning. No practice.
They're improvising this dance.
I guess crazy stuff happens
when you put a pair of geniuses together.
With my brother way at the back,
my best hope is to take advantage
of their impromptu teaming up.
Oh! And now the fight over seventh
looks ready to spark into life.
So fast. Since when has
his car been that fast?
And there he goes!
He slips through a narrow gap
like an expertly fired shot.
The red bullet moniker is
growing more and more accurate.
I get it. That's why
he's going faster than usual.
It's the slipstream with the 12 car.
The physical evidence
is pretty clear-cut.
Not that I don't have
other things to complain about.
Could you maybe stop zipping past me the
first chance you get when you're in range?
Do you never weigh up the situation?
Or hesitate? Anything like that?
It helps to be mentally prepared
when you're being passed, you know.
And what's more...
How come the usually aloof
absolute king is willing to assist you?
It's downright unfair.
Since when did you two
become best buddies?
The 86 car pulls ahead.
And the 12 follows him through.
It's another string of
side-by-side action!
They haven't given the NSX
enough space to steady itself.
I gotta make my move now.
Before the gap closes.
The 18 car follows suit!
Expertly executed! We're seeing some
intelligent and efficient racing today.
I'd have a hard time pulling ahead
of an NSX in a straight-up drag race.
But right now, my car's inside
an invisible air tunnel.
Here's hoping it pulls me along.
Let me pass him.
Is he going to fall behind?
The high-IQ driver, Maezono,
painfully loses three places!
I'm speechless at this point, Sudo-san.
This course really is
seeing incredible speeds.
Double Lane is living up
to its reputation.
The battle with air resistance is having
a bigger effect than anyone thought.
Even so...
Kitahara in the 18 is
turning into a dark horse,
pulling out a performance
no one expected.
If I had to describe it, I'd call it a twist
born out of a string of coincidences.
First, these two cars rejoined the race
right in front of the 18 after spinning.
Second, there's the fact
it's only the second lap,
so there hasn't been
much field spread yet.
Because of that, she's able to keep pace
with the cars in front of her.
And third,
Kitahara Nozomi has always specialized
in coordinated attacks.
The pair in front are executing
some high-level teamwork,
but her experience lets her join in.
I have to admit, it's strange how well
the 18 is able to follow them.
But just look at what the 86 and
12 cars are capable of together.
It's downright incredible.
Is there any driver out there capable
of outrunning this pair as allies?
They're the strongest train.
Next time, Turn 36: The Midair Feint.