Was that a kiss?
Oh, damn it! I can't concentrate at all!
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
I'm the One Who's Gonna Win
And I need to finish my summer vacation
homework by the day after tomorrow, too!
A famous morning drama actress.
Let's go out to eat, Ouri-kun!
A charismatic top model.
Are you free, Ouri-kun?
Sorry, I'm busy.
Aw...
No matter how much others came onto me,
it never resonated
with me at all, and yet...
What the hell's going on
with my emotions?! Damn it!
This place is closed, too.
There's nowhere open...
Utage Kinoshita!
What's she doing here?!
Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
Smooth as ever, I escort you
And this voice, seducing you
Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
I am your ace darlin'
Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
Please Please
Whisper just to me, call my name
You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
Hey, girl
Look this way!
I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
So take my hand and let's roll
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
It's a spell that makes your heart race
We can't go back
You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
Sweetie honey
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
I focused too much on my job and
fan activities during summer vacation
and forgot to do my homework.
I need to finish it by
the day after tomorrow...
"Supernova"!
The idol group that everyone
has their eyes on right now... F/ACE!
No way! A commercial?!
Their first on-location trip show
coming soon!
Did I use up all my luck for the day
by running into this today?!
A Documentary Program Featuring F/ACE
Coming Soon!!
Supernova
Creating a new era beyond imagination
Jeez! You're way too serious!
Their latest single is a massive hit!
Supernova
And we get to see another side of F/ACE!
It's a miracle that we
were born in the same era
So we've got to enjoy it
(Yeah, song song song)
Good morning.
I'm sure everyone wants
to see footage of us waking up.
Sing out loud (sing sing sing)
Harmonizing loud and proud
Don't worry, we made sure
the cameras were rolling.
T-Tamon-kun's naked?!
Song, song, song
Let's sleep together
for just a little longer...
Sing out loud (sing sing sing)
Shining bright as one
We shouldn't be doing things like this
first thing in the morning, Tamon-kun!
Supernova
F/ACE's
Super Exciting
Summer Vacation
F/ACE's Super Exciting Summer Vacation!
We hope you'll check it out!
I will! I will! I'll absolutely watch it!
Please stream it worldwide
at the same time!
Meaning I need to finish
my homework so I can watch.
If there was some system
where I could deposit 1,000 yen
Internet Banking
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Tamon Fukuhara's
Account
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Deposit Total yen
into Tamon-kun's account
every time I finished a problem,
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1,000 yen
Deposit 1,000 yen
Deposit 2,000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1,000 yen
Deposit 3,000 yen
Deposit 4,000 yen
I'd be much more motivated.
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1,000 yen
Deposit 5,000 yen
Deposit 6,000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1,000 yen
Deposit 7,000 yen
Deposit 8,000 yen
Utage Kinoshita, sixteen years old.
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1,000 yen
Deposit 9,000 yen
Deposit 10,000 yen
Deposit     Utage Kinoshita             1,000 yen
Deposit 11,000 yen
Deposit 12,000 yen
Fan Activities
I can draw out all my potential for fan
activities, but not really anything else.
Fan Activities
No, no!
Even Tamon-kun is working hard
to do both work and school,
Menacing
so I need to get a grip!
It'll cost some money,
but I guess I could go to a café.
If I'm so bothered by not knowing
what her relationship with Tamon is,
I'll just ask her outright.
Somewhere cheap and quiet would be best.
Oh? Gloomyhara-san?
Oh... Hello.
Hello. Today's a lovely day, isn't it?
What the hell is he doing here?!
Are you heading out somewhere?
I went to get the uniforms that
Fujita-san sent to the dry cleaners.
Right. The new school term
starts the day after tomorrow.
You have two uniforms?
One is Ouri-kun's.
I see.
Waitaminute! You go to high
school, Gloomyhara-san?!
And to the same school as Ouri-kun?!
Oh, yes. Didn't I mention that before?
Oh, right. I made him go get them.
There's a Tamon-kun that
goes to high school in real life?
Tamon-kun who's a third-year
in high school exists in this world.
How is that possible?
My brain can't process that.
I'm right here, though.
Though I mostly just do my makeup
classes at night or on my days off,
so it doesn't really feel like
a normal high-school life.
What are you up to, Kinoshita-san?
Ah, well, I hadn't finished my
summer vacation homework yet.
You take Pochi for a walk, Yamato.
I have a date, and I'm busy!
I have to study, so no.
I can't concentrate at home because
my siblings and dog are too loud.
And both the library
and community center are closed.
Closed
So I was looking for a place to study.
Hm... Somewhere you can
study quietly for free...
I know! You can come over to my place.
There's no way I can step foot into
that sanctuary other than for work.
Oh, I'm sorry!
In that case...
A table in that park was open.
And it's pretty cool today.
Between those two places,
it'd be the park.
Sure.
I have to memorize tomorrow's script,
so I'll buy some sandwiches and...
Hey.
What the hell are you two thinking?
Tachibana-san?!
Don't just casually go have a picnic.
You two need to be more
aware of your surroundings.
What are you, grade schoolers?!
Facts
Come with me.
Huh?
Where are we going?
If you have nowhere else
to go, do it here.
Frugality Is a Virtue
There's nothing distracting here,
so you should be able to concentrate.
I-I guess you're right.
Did you eat lunch yet?
Not yet.
Save Water
Once Open, Three Seconds
I have some prepped meals in the fridge,
so you can eat those if you're hungry.
Just make sure not to pull the drawer
out more than fifteen centimeters.
Once you open the door,
close it within three seconds.
Once Open, Three Seconds
Also... Tamon, you little...
A Journey of
a Thousand Miles
Begins with a Single Step
Huh?
Did you go outside without
putting on any sunscreen again?!
Please calm down, Tachibana-san! Please!
Stop that!
I'm wearing a bag over my head, so it's f—
No, it's not!
Your face is an important product
that prints money!
You need to care for it with your life.
Don't underestimate UV rays!
Drench your face with lotion!
Huh? They seem closer than before?
Also, you look pale.
Have you been sleeping?
W-Well, just thinking about
the eight billion intelligent lifeforms
wriggling about on Earth
got me really scared suddenly,
and before I knew it, it was morning...
If you have time to think about
that kind of nonsense, just go to sleep!
Good for you, Tamon-kun.
You've gotten closer to Keito-kun.
You can have this.
Huh? Dirt?
Do you mean I should go
be one with the dirt again?
No. They're used coffee grounds.
I'm so happy for you.
Are you giving me garbage
because I'm garbage?
No. They can help you sleep soundly.
But I've also been worried about him
and watching over him.
Just take it!
Thank you very much.
If I... If I were born as a guy...
Jealousy
and a F/ACE member
I could be that close to him...
Jealousy
Well, I've got a shoot, so I'm gonna go.
Save Energy
Today's Savings is
Tomorrow's Happiness
Once you're done, just lock up
and give Tamon the key.
Okay! I will.
Have a great time...
Popular segment on
their official channel
shooting Mama Keito's 30-minute Cooking.
You don't need to say the name.
U-Um, why are you doing all this for me?
You seemed to really despise fans
as if they killed your parents.
Turn off the Lights
I saw how hard you worked
during the training camp,
and I checked Tamon's apartment.
Huh?
He suddenly came over yesterday,
checked my whole apartment, and then left.
Really?
It's clear you were supporting him
by professionally handling
his household chores.
I also know in my head
that fans aren't all insane.
So I'm sorry, Kinoshita-san.
Bye.
Keito-kun has now started to complain
to me more than before the training camp.
That sounds like
your relationship is worse.
No. Rather than him suddenly getting
mad at everything that happened
Hey!
Hey, Tamon!
in the past all at once or
quietly clicking his tongue at me,
What the hell are you doing, Tamon?!
it's less scarier to have him
tell me how he feels.
Hey.
The hell are you doing?
Shut up. Don't make me
punch your glasses in.
Hmph.
I guess Tachibana-san's the type
that lets everything build up inside.
I'm going to do my best so
he doesn't keep everything in.
He is our very precious leader of F/ACE.
I'm the leader of F/ACE, after all.
Right.
If Tamon-kun says all that,
Keito-kun is a good person.
Today's Savings is
Tomorrow's Happiness
Okay, I'm going to start my homework.
Could you not summon me on my day off?
Well, I don't want to waste
any money on transportation.
Yes, yes, of course. Okay, let's go.
Is there something on my face?
Oh, I'm sorry. I've just never
seen you study before so...
It made me realize that you are
actually a high school student.
It's a bit embarrassing
when he points it out like that.
Well... I guess I am usually working
when I'm around you, Gloomyhara-san.
Oh, please just think of me as waste
that's wearing a garbage bag and
pay me no mind so you can concentrate.
Ten Million Yen
Data-Driven Management
How High Performers Reset
Condition Management for Professionals
Time Investment Strategies for Management
Flash
Tamon-kun is humanity's
greatest treasure!
Church of Tamon
Tamon-kun is humanity's
greatest treasure!
I'm done with modern lit
and world history!
That was fast. I'm impressed.
I do pretty well with literature stuff.
Oh, I figured as much.
You did?
Whenever you encourage me,
you always use so many words
in so many ways, so I figured as much.
Tamon-kun is a God
World Peace (Sexy & Wild)
Rejuvenating Eye candy
A Fallen Angel That's
Lost His Wings
Tamon-kun
Belongs to
Everyone
Er, um... though I basically use
most of them in an unofficial way...
I'm not very good with
science and math, though.
Arithmetic Drills
Tamon Fukuhara Kamioshi
Not to mention those got harder
in my second year.
I see.
At first, I thought you were someone
who could do anything, Kinoshita-san.
What? Really?
But... there's no way
someone like that exists, right?
You're just working harder than others.
That's very admirable.
Th-That's not true!
I'm just doing what I should
because I should.
But isn't that pretty hard to do?
My handwriting's so bad that I
can't even read the notes I took
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Gloomyhara Font
and then I get stuck.
Whenever I clip my nails, I bleed...
Ow...
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
I can't even do what
I'm supposed to be able to do.
Gloomyhara-san...
So the fact that you can do
all these things is admirable.
You tell me that all
I need to do is exist,
but you seem rather hard on yourself.
Well, you're special, Tamon-kun!
Being told that doing the most
trivial things is admirable...
makes me feel tingly inside.
Hm...
What's wrong?
I can't seem to figure out this problem...
Oh, a trigonometric function problem.
Um... Here, I think you... oh right.
He's acting like my senpai...
You use sine, cosine, or tangent and...
You're right.
Your complexion looks much better today.
Now I remembered that...
I don't know!
Huh?
My brain is smoother than a boiled egg,
so there was no way I could actually
remember what I learned a year ago!
Please forgive me and my ugly
vanity for being overconfident
and trying to act all senpai!
I'm sorry that I was nothing more
than a rotten boiled egg!
Tamon-kun is the embodiment
of light born from star fragments!
Yes!
Now's my chance since
I'm in the same grade as that chick...
I'll teach you everything.
You're so smart and wuvly!
Yeah, that's what'll happen.
Then I'll cheer you on as Hottiehara—
No!
But why? I have nothing left to offer
if you don't let me do that.
I keep telling you not to
waste Hottiehara-kun!
You keep saying it's a waste,
but it's not a waste to me...
You're always so strong
and cool, Kinoshita-san...
and the only time you change is
when you're around Hottiehara.
Honestly, that's a win for me.
Huh?
Do you like troubling other people?
That's not okay, even if you're Tamon-kun!
I do feel... bad about it.
Huh?
But... I'm always the one crying
and falling over...
and you're always there for me...
So... I want to be something to you, too.
Not the music video
or the photo version of me.
But the me that's
in front of you right now.
The Tamon-kun that's in front of me...
What the hell am I sneaking around for?
I just need to march in there,
ask them what I want to know,
and get it over with!
What the heck's going on with you two?
We're dating!
Am I... actually scared to ask?
My father is a leading actor
that represents Japan.
Film Awards Ceremony
Toshikazu
Sakaguchi
It goes without saying,
but he's handsome.
My mother is a singer
who defined a generation.
Of course, she's also beautiful.
Their son is currently
a new idol in the spotlight.
Ouri
Sakaguchi
Everyone would agree that his good
looks rival any national treasure.
The educational policy of the
elegant Sakaguchi Family
was a bit different from other households.
Ouri.
You inherited our superb genes
and were born into this world.
Meaning you are a winner amongst
winners just by being born.
Yeah, I know! Everything
goes ridiculously well for me!
But that's only
if you live a mediocre life.
You will never be a winner
in the entertainment industry.
Huh?!
That's because your father...
...and mother...
...will continue to be winners!
Whether you like it or not,
if you stand on the same stage as us,
you'll be compared to us
and always feel disappointed.
Having to face a giant obstacle
known as your parents
is the fate of second-generation talent.
B-But I want to be on TV, too!
Then you must be ready to surpass
your mother and father!
Always remember this, Ouri...
Family Motto
Strength Is Power
Strength is power.
I'm... gonna be the winner here!
Her relationship with Tamon
doesn't matter!
I...
Kinoshita-san, I...
Huh?!
Ouri-kun?!
I'll teach you your homework!
You kicked down the door
even though it was unlocked?
Gloom, gloom...
Tamon's in the damn way.
By the way, Gloomyhara-san, weren't
you trying to say something earlier?
U-Um...
It's not important,
so don't worry about it.
I'm talking to Gloomyhara-san.
It really isn't important,
so please don't worry about it.
Isn't this great, Kinoshita-san?
Huh?
Now, you'll be able to
get your homework done.
It's great that Ouri-kun showed up.
Yup, exactly.
I'm sure this buffoon was useless.
I'm sorry for being a meaningless
existence and occupying this space.
I can learn lyrics and choreo in three
minutes and it takes him thirty hours.
Gloom, gloom, gloom...
Sting
He just doesn't have the knack for it.
Actually, I'm surprised you were
even able to survive this long.
I'm sorry that my brain capacity
is less than an ostrich's!
Tamon-kun spends 300 times more time
on hard work than others. I love him.
Tch.
Grrr...
Thank you very much, Kinoshita-san.
But it's true that
I'm not being very useful...
so is there something else
I can do for you?
Then... please just exist.
Er... something other than that.
Then get me a shine muscat Daifuku
and terrine de marrons!
Wha—
Humanity is not ready for Tamon-kun
to be treated as an errand boy!
Well, he doesn't have
anything else to do, does he?
I'll be back soon. I'll buy some
for you, too, Kinoshita-san!
Wha—
And there he goes...
Kekeke! Now, no one's in my way.
By the way, are you actually
smart, Sakaguchi-san?
What's that supposed to mean, huh?!
I clearly look intelligent!
Er, I was just curious...
That's right. I guess you haven't
seen me get serious in person.
Academics? Of course, I'm great at it!
Work Hard and Practice Frugality
How else could I play the prince
character if I wasn't cultured?
I-I guess?
I've spent ten years in showbiz.
Co-star
Ouri-chan, you're amazing.
Screenwriter
Editor
In order to survive, I needed to be
likable rather than unapproachable.
Creator
Genius.
Popular Celebrity
You're truly amazing, Ouri-kun.
Critic
Producer
In the end, no one can run away
from what works.
Director
You're lovely.
Cameraman
Director
What a good boy.
Scriptwriter
Today, I'm gonna get her
to look my way for real!
Utage-san.
Tamon-kun's great,
but won't I suffice as well?
Ouri-kun's gone into idol mode!
Oh, I'm sorry for calling you
by your name without asking.
If you're all right with it,
may I continue calling you Utage-san?
S-Sure.
W-Wow... the background's
all see through...
I'm so transparent that people say
that there's nothing more transparent
than the beaches
at Palau or Ouri Sakaguchi!
I'll make you take this head on
and make you fall for me!
I'm just getting started!
Please, have a seat, my princess.
I'll lend you the notes I wrote up,
so please feel free to use them.
Trigonometric Formulas
You're correct! Well done!
This is how you do this part...
Oh! I'm sorry!
I'll finish you with the reliable
youngest member act.
It's a little nerve-racking being
here alone together, isn't it?
But I'll maintain the innocence!
Squee.
Got 'em!
So this is what Tamon-kun
gets to see all the time...
I'm so moved.
I get to experience being my oshi.
This hasn't gotten through
to her at all, damn it!
A normal chick would've
melted into nothing by now!
I wonder what Kinoshita-san's
favorite fruit is.
What do you like?
Tamon-kun!
Tamon-kun! Tamon-kun! Tamon-kun!
Fruits Daifuku Fair
Maybe I don't know anything
about... Kinoshita-san after all...
I'd like...
to know more about her.
I should eat soon.
Why?
What would he do right now?
Sakaguchi-san?
Huh?
U-Um...
I'm back—
G-Gloomyhara-san! This is just...
What exactly is this?!
I don't know what to do after this.
What is this aura?
Murderous intent?!
Oh, I was just giving her
a little fan service.
To show her gratitude
for always supporting F/ACE.
Ah...
Wha—
Wait, is that Darkhara-san?!
Kinoshita-san...
doesn't like that.
Not that I'm an expert, or anything...
but I've messed up before.
Tch.
What?! You bought every kind?!
I'm sorry.
Is she really not going to look my way?
Does she really not even...
Sakaguchi-san.
You probably did this because you
don't like me and you were mad...
But I can't approve
of what you did earlier.
You didn't really seem
like yourself, Ouri-kun.
What?
Tamon-kun has a lot of fans,
but you also have a lot of fans.
So please make sure you
take good care of him...
The pure and sincere idol Ouri-kun
that's loved by everyone.
I mean, you can't be
anyone but yourself, right?
I thought I only wanted to get her
to look my way because of my pride...
I thought it was because I didn't
want to lose to him as an idol.
But that's not it.
You bought so much. Thank you.
Is there anything you don't like?
I...
I'm in love with...
I love them all! I'll take all of them!
Utage Kinoshita.
Damn it.
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:
Michelle Tymon
\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
\h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
Translation Check:
Alicia Ashby
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan
Uh huh...
Na na na...
I wonder what the world
would look like without you
When I look back,
you've always been by my side
Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
A speedboat sails across the endless skies
An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
Like a wilted flower coming back to life
A light that shines
Through the impossibly dark night
(Light of your soul)
I wanted to grasp it
(I love you so)
So I strived for it
Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom