Class Monitor
Rules
A class monitor's morning starts early.
I'm heading out on patrol now.
I wonder if Poem-san is still sleeping.
She does sleep well.
As you know,
Kohinata's
Home
Sakuradaimon's
Sakuradaimon-kun's home
is really close to Poem-chan's.
Poem-san?
What?
Hmm?
Oh, sorry, wrong person.
Are you a friend of my older sister?
Huh?
I mean, the only one
with such an odd name
would be my older sister.
Po-chan!
Come down for breakfast!
Even if you are off today,
you can't just sleep forever.
A Day Off With the Klutz
It's only 8:30?
Po-chan!
Morning.
Why don't you go wash up before eating?
Huh? I'm fine. I'll do it later.
Don't blame me then.
Your mama warned you.
Confusing.
So you go jogging
every morning, Lyric-san?
That's great.
Wearing a skirt and showing off thick legs
like my sister does would be embarrassing.
That's not true.
Poem-san has nice legs.
What the hell are you doing here, Togo?!
She really is a funny person.
Poem-san!
Good morning.
Lyri! Did you let him in?!
Don't look at me. We were
chatting out front when Mama...
You must be Sakuradaimon-kun!
What are you doing? Come in, come in.
Have breakfast with us!
Mama! Jeez!
What is it?
Wait a second, Poem-san!
Please don't blame your mother!
It was originally my fault
for coming into your home
so early in the morning.
Even if we have grown close,
that was careless of me.
I'm sorry!
I'll take my leave at once.
Huh? Oh, no...
How could I ever let myself be so rude?!
Please just give me a moment!
I'll leave once I've finished this!
Hey, don't you think shoveling it
down like that is rude too?
Huh? You're leaving, Sakuradaimon-san?
Well, but you see, Lyric-chan....
Lyri! Why, you!
What's wrong? Let him stay.
Also, why don't you go get changed first?
Gonna stay in pajamas forever?
Sakuradaimon-san, you can
take your time eating, okay?
Okay. I'm sorry.
She's so difficult.
So?
I just want to make sure for now,
but you're not going out, right? You two?
Going... Wha?! Huh?! No way!
Right! We're not dating.
Huh?
For one thing, illicit relationships
are prohibited in our school's rules.
Huh?! Really?!
Okay, so that's the stage they're at.
Are you interested in dating
at all, Sakuradaimon-san?
Hey! Lyri!
What are doing asking
such personal things?!
Hardly.
What are you panicking for?
We're just chatting.
I wouldn't say I'm not
interested in romance.
Though a student's main duty is to study.
Sir, that's really a line
only smart people can use.
So you're not uninterested?
Good for you, Big Sis.
What's your problem today?!
So what's your type?
My type, you ask?
Come on, Lyric!
Type... My type, huh?
I haven't thought about it before.
What kind of woman do I view fondly?
Hmm.
Diligent, well-mannered, honest... Hmm?
No, those are certainly traits
that I desire for myself,
but it feels wrong to say
I seek them in women.
You really are proper to a fault, huh?
Wait, judging women by
my preferences seems wrong too...
You're funny.
Then how about my older sister?
She's neither diligent
nor well-mannered,
but she can be surprisingly cute.
Hey!
Hey! Hold on!
I know that.
Poem-san is a cute, kindhearted,
and all-around wonderful woman.
You hold on too!
Ow!
Huh? What was that?
Then you two should go out already.
How are you two
still not dating yet? Scary.
Lyri!
You're getting too carried away!
I'll get mad!
Huh? I just don't get it.
I was only giving you
an extra push, Big Sis.
Hey you two,
you shouldn't fight each other.
It's okay, Sakuradaimon-kun!
These two are actually
very close siblings!
Now, here's a snack. Eat up!
Today we're having Po-chan and
Lyri-chan's favorites, PreChure Pancakes!
Mama!
How many times do I have to say it?!
I'm not into things like this anymore!
This is wonderfully well done, ma'am!
Thank you, Sakuradaimon-kun!
Ah, this takes me back!
To that day when the three of us
went to the PreChure movie together.
PreChure Heartthrobbing Love Cherry Splash!
You're finished.
Foolish PreChures.
This place will be your grave!
Big Sis, what do we do?!
The PreChures are going to lose!
You can't give up, Lyri! Look!
All you good kids!
We need you to help by sharing some
of your light energy with the PreChures!
Now, everyone!
Grab your PreChure Wands!
Come on, let's go!
Come on, Lyri!
Wave your wands!
You have the magic light
they gave us when we entered, right?
Everyone, lend us your power!
Wave it to support them!
Thank you!
S-So cute!
Drive off those evil villains
with the power of light!
My daughters are so cute!
There!
You can do it! PreChure!
Drive off those evil villains
with the power of light!
Evil Villains
Jeez, Mama! Go somewhere else!
Huh? No fun. I want to chat too!
Evil Villain
You Can Do It, PreChure
Klutzy Class Monitor
What's wrong with that,
Poem-san, Lyric-san!
Go ahead, ma'am!
Please sit here with us.
Like I said!
You're so kind, Sakuradaimon-kun!
Mama, jeez!
Oh my, I didn't realize
I had stayed so long.
Thank you for the food.
Yeah, you said it.
Who would've thought I'd spend
the whole day off with you at home?
Come back again, Sakuradaimon-kun!
Shoo! Shoo!
I haven't hung out at a friend's house
since elementary school.
Thank you for letting me
have a really fun time.
Oh, well, uh...
Sorry it was so noisy.
I'm glad Pa—my father was out.
That old man's
the most annoying one of all.
It was nice and lively.
Plus, well, Lyri said all those things...
Oh, yeah.
I have a little sister
around Lyric-san's age too.
Girls around their age
love to talk about that stuff.
I didn't take it seriously.
Huh?
Oh! Right! That's right!
Now, excuse me.
Oh, yeah!
Be careful on your way home!
Even though it's close!
You could have taken it
a bit more seriously.
Dummy.
Yes?!
Did you say something?
It's nothing!
Go home, go home!
See you tomorrow!
Yeah. See you later.
Big Sis.
That one's going to
be difficult, you know?
He's all kinds of off.
Rules
Dating's against school rules, right?
He might end up just
leading you on until graduation.
He seems like the kind of guy
who's a walking embodiment of the rules.
Guy Walking Around
in a Shirt That Reads "Rules"
Lyri.
You had plenty of fun teasing me today,
so you're prepared for
the consequences, right?!
Wait. Calm down.
I did it for your sake!
Shut up!
Don't make excuses, Lyri!
Hey! Wait!
Stop running!
Hey! Lyri!
What did she mean by
take it more seriously?
Totally Heard Her
m 0 0 l 115.5 0 l 115.5 108 l 0 108
The Klutzy
Class Monitor and
the Girl with
the Short Skirt
The Klutz and the Skirt!
m 0 0 l 115.5 0 l 115.5 108 l 0 108
The Klutzy
Class Monitor and
the Girl with
the Short Skirt
The Klutz and the Skirt!
So good!
If Togo spots me in a place
like this again...
"Dining on your way
to and from school is prohibited!"
"The first time is a warning!"
"The second time,
it's a reflection essay!"
That's what he'd likely say.
What's wrong with this? Jeez.
The Klutz Gets Plunged Into Battle on the Streets
Hmm, what's the best thing I can get
to show my thanks to Poem-san's family?
Power Strip
Trust It With Them All!
This looks like something
the whole family could use!
All right. I'll get this one!
No, we don't need it!
Poem-san?!
What are you doing in a place like this?
I could ask you that!
Thank us? For having you
over the other day?
Yes.
You treated me to breakfast
and shared pancakes with me too.
So I felt like I needed
to do something in return—
We don't need that!
Especially not a power strip!
Mama just did that on her own anyways!
If you bring a gift, Mama will just get
fired up and bake cookies or something!
If she returned my thanks
with more thanks...
Then I'd have to thank her yet again!
That's why I'm saying you don't need to!
The sentiment is more than enough
for things like that!
I see.
Then allow me to visit one more time
to show my appreciation.
S-Sure.
How about today?
That's far too sudden!
True. I'm sorry.
It is already late in the day.
No, that's only part of it.
Besides, what are you doing
while on patrol?
You went on and on about how
we can't buy food on the way home,
yet now you're shopping?
Isn't that a violation of the rules too?
No, I went home first.
So I'm not on my way home anymore.
What kind of cheap logic is that?!
The trip home from school
lasts until you reach your home.
Don't talk like it's a field trip!
And if you already went home,
why are you still wearing your armband?!
Huh? I'm pretty sure I was
wearing it on our day off too.
That's right. You were!
Still, why?!
Because I'm a class monitor, of course!
That's not an answer!
More importantly, I still haven't heard
your answer to my previous question.
What are you doing here, Poem-san?
Well...
She then manages to fool him.
Your family is full of nice,
cheerful people.
I can see how you grew up
to be so kind and honest.
Shut up.
Those pancakes were amazing too.
What a wonderfully perfected PreChure!
Shut up!
Say any more and I'll punch you!
Huh?
At any rate, you all showed me
wonderful hospitality.
I'd love to meet your father next time.
My papa...
My father is rather annoying,
so it's seriously better if you don't meet him.
Oh? Annoying?
First off, he'll probably punch you
just for being a man in our home.
Yeah.
He'll give you a preemptive punch
before hearing you out.
He never listens to what people say.
Also...
Huh?!
My name is Kohinata Rhyme.
I'm 37.
I just finished work for today,
so I'm hurrying home
to my beloved family.
Believe it or not,
I was quite a handful when I was young.
But now, I'm very dedicated to my family.
I'm seen as a diligent, devoted father.
I had my first child at 21,
and she's now a 16-year-old
high schooler.
My youngest daughter is entering
her third year of middle school.
Mama, today's my bento box day.
Yes, okay. Hold on a minute!
Where's my gym uniform?
They hardly talk to me anymore,
like most girls their age.
Huh?
You're coming shopping too, Papa?
You don't have to.
Get some rest. Aren't you tired?
There's no point in you being there.
We can just go with Mama,
so you don't need to come.
But on the few occasions they do,
I can feel their appreciation
for me in their words.
I'm surprised such good daughters
managed to come from me.
I shouldn't be saying this,
but my life has all been smooth sailing.
I don't have a shred of discontent,
whether in my career or in my family life.
However...
There is one exception.
What's that?
Their music's too loud.
Hey, they're forming a cypher.
A cypher?
It's when multiple people get together
for some freestyle rapping.
There's only one exception
that stirs my heart.
When I was young,
back before I met my wife,
it was the one thing
I was passionate about.
U-Uh...
You're dumb! And ugly!
The lowest of the low.
Dissing physical looks is the same
as declaring you have nothing else to say.
I would...
No, no!
I retired from the street
over 17 years ago.
What could I even accomplish
by joining those young people?
My beloved family is
anxiously awaiting my return.
I shouldn't be loitering around here.
Hey! What's your problem?!
What do you all think
you're doing in this space
frequented by people
in front of the station?!
As a class monitor,
I can't overlook this!
Wha?! Who's that?!
Judging from his outfit, he clearly
has nothing to do with that group!
Is he barging in?!
On that cypher?!
I recognize all of you.
You're all students
at our school, aren't you?!
It's Sakuradaimon, the class monitor.
Yeah, the guy who nags people
at the school gate every morning!
You dare to just waltz right in here?!
Hey, get him!
Time to humiliate
this haughty class monitor!
Hey, yo!
Why the hell are you here?!
You rule-abiding teacher's pet.
Class spies like you can go on, get.
We've had enough of
your brown-nosing act.
You're just the man's little mutt,
so you sure ain't gonna
find friends near.
We're full-on tough thugs
Like a rabid pack of hyenas
So tuck your tail, and beat it!
Scram! See ya!
It's plain for anyone to see
that he's not versed in rap battles,
and they're planning
to publicly execute him!
How cowardly!
Hyenas?
I see.
So you made a metaphor
with animals and our positions.
The thing about hyenas is
they are nocturnal.
But we're still students
so here's a kernel.
Early to bed, early to rise.
Don't make your parents worry.
Correct that biorhythm
in a real fast hurry!
Shouting and making a fuss at the station?
I don't get this kind of sensation.
It only serves to lower
our school's stellar reputation.
The cost to your grades
is as clear as an equation!
Now go and return
to your place of habitation.
He hit him with a response?!
What was that?!
Was it a fluke?!
But his rhymes were too stiff!
The lines were stiff too!
Is he experienced at this?!
No, but...
Yeah, man!
High schoolers should be at home
doing homework!
You'll be the ones in trouble
when your grades drop!
Compared to you guys,
that class monitor looks real smart!
Klutz
We never even cared
'bout our school's reputation!
Question how we live?
It don't matter to us.
They can go eat shit
with those stupid regulations!
You say our grades'll drop,
but that ain't persuadin'!
All that waits at home
is an annoying spiel.
This time with my crew's
the only thing that's real.
Better off ditchin' homework
so I can hone my skills.
A goody-two-shoes
would never get this ideal.
On the face of it,
that sounded like a good rebuttal,
but if you ask me, it was a parade
of stock phrases I've heard before.
Though it'll still garner a good deal
of support from the delinquents here.
That's right! An honor student
will never understand us!
School can eat shit!
Now, how will he fight back?!
This determines the match!
The last eight bars!
You say you don't care about
your grades one bit,
yet here you are,
showing off plenty of wit!
Huh?!
Ba-dump...
Use that wisdom and cleverness
your parents passed down,
and you could turn
your test scores right around!
I'd love to learn a thing or two
from your language unbound.
Ba-dump-dump...
This honor student
wants advice from me?!
I don't know what "my crew"
is supposed to mean,
but I'm jealous that you're friends
with so many teens.
So why not do things nice and proper?
Found a club and make it prosper!
Ba-dump
Ba-dump...
A club?!
I never even considered that.
Still...
Outcasts like us in a club? A rap club?
I'll do everything in my power
to help you as well.
Work hard for our students.
That's the fundamental rule
for class monitors!
I'll speak to the school
on your behalf as well.
Way to go, class monitor!
Yeah. Thank you...
You guys are the best!
Sakuradaimon!
Excuse me.
You there.
Yes?
You remembered to show respect
instead of just ending with a diss.
That was very cool.
What a great rap battle!
Translation: John Pickett
Timing: Mariana Martinez
Editing: Zachary Carlysle
Quality Control: SMR
Translation Check: Rei Miyasaka
Rap? Oh, sure, thanks.
I'd love to ask for a match with you.
Would you someday...
Hey! Togo, you idiot!
What are you doing wasting time here?!
You suddenly disappeared on me!
You're in high school! You're too old
to be getting lost, you klutz!
N-No, Poem-san, you see...
P-Po-chan?
Geh?! Pa—Father?!
What is your relationship
with my daughter?!
Whoa!
We're friends!
Pa—Father, stop it!
He goes to my school!
Feast on this iron fist that'll leave
weblike cracks in the asphalt!
Listen to me!