I'm in my own room?
Does that mean I've looped again?
But...
I'm surprised... you figured it out.
Honestly, I was fooled, too... until
I realized it during today's meeting.
But didn't you investigate me
as the Engineer?
Sorry to say it,
but even humans lie...
Are you kidding me?
We put Remnan into cold sleep, I survived,
and we succeeded in
getting rid of all the Gnosia.
Knowing the truth is no simple matter.
Survive this loop.
If you manage that,
I will tell you everything.
Does this mean that I'm
supposed to go see Yuriko?
Or...
Is this still not full enough?
Oh, Yuri. You're awake already.
Comet...
We're all in the cafeteria eating
right now. Wanna join us?
EPISODE 16: TRUTH
So I've been thinking...
-About what?
-Aren't you just naked, Shigemichi?
-I'm not!
-Wait, really?
-I'm wearing clothes here!
-Ah, Yuri.
Oh, hey. Did you recover already?
You were hurt pretty badly, weren't you?
Huh? Yeah...
Yeah, there was, like, stuff sticking out.
Come on, bud. Don't talk about
gross stuff when we're eating here.
I see... So I was hurt.
That's why I got carried into the
medical pod to receive treatment.
Come to think of it,
I wasn't in the pod this time.
Every time I loop,
I always wake up in that pod.
You'd better thank Setsu, too, Yuri.
Thank Setsu?
Yeah! If it weren't for Setsu,
we wouldn't have been
able to escape Liu-An
without being infected by the Gnosia.
I'm grateful to Setsu, too.
It's just, my gratitude
kinda morphed into lust.
Y'know, maybe it was a
mistake to save Sha-ming.
You may be right.
Infected by the Gnosia...
U-Um...
Hm? What's up?
Well, um... Are we gonna have the meeting?
Meeting?
For what?
Er... Never mind.
Yuri...
Did you, like, lose your
memories, or something?
Do you know my name?
Er, yeah, I'm fine. You're SQ, right?
Oh! Well done, lovely Yuri!
Sorry. I have to use the bathroom.
There's no meeting.
They didn't even know what
I meant by "meeting."
Then...
LeVi.
How may I assist you?
Do you detect any Gnosia
on board the ship?
Negative. I do not.
Due to Setsu's quick guidance,
this vessel successfully avoided
any Gnosia infection.
I knew it.
So that's what's going on.
This is a world line where no one's
been infected by the Gnosia.
Maybe the truth is here.
Would you refrain from
making me repeat myself?
It's absolutely clear that the optimal
choice is to set course for Glyze.
Racio, please... It's okay.
I'd like to hear your opinion about this,
Setsu, since you're in the military.
What is it?
If you'll entertain a foolish old man's
idea, I think we should set course
for a nearby military base so that we can
notify the proper authorities of Liu-An.
The "foolish" part is right.
If we end up in military custody,
just think of all the reports,
inspections, and who knows what else?
I can't imagine how long they'll hold us.
Well, you heard them.
Right...
Setsu should be the one to decide.
Then no one'll have to argue.
I'll be making a report
about Liu-An myself,
so I don't think there's any need
to stop by a base.
Are you certain?
According to interstellar regulations,
if Gnosia infection occurs,
-we must immediately—
-But no one on this ship is infected.
So we don't need
to follow those regulations.
Well, this is a surprise!
Setsu, you're more cooperative
than I thought you'd be.
Hm. So be it.
We will set course for the Glyze
star system as Racio requests.
Racio...
No need to thank me. I just want
to hurry up and get back to Glyze.
No, I get it.
You knew that if we went to a base,
they'd find out that I ran away
unlawfully and capture me.
Hmph. I'm sure everyone here
thinks this already, but...
Remnan, you're rather creepy.
Huh?
Um, Jonas...
If we're heading to Glyze, could you stop
by Dr. Yoshikado's place on the way?
But of course. This, too, is fate.
I shall take you all to
your desired destinations.
Yay!
Everyone's here other than Yuriko.
There's nothing untoward going on.
So the truth I came here to find...
Yuri, is something bothering you?
Huh? No, I'm fine.
I think that's a good idea, too.
There aren't any Gnosia infectees here.
Everyone managed to safely
get on board the ship.
Is there really anything hidden about the
mystery involving the loops in this world?
In fact, this is the world
we all wanted...
So is there actually information
I need to discover here?
Kukrushka...
"Soon"?
Is something about to happen?
The universe will... end?
Soon?
What's that mean?
What's going to happen...
to this universe?
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
I repeat.
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
An anomalous lifeform...?
The sick bay...
That's where I always wake up.
Yuri!
Setsu, what's going on?
I'm not sure.
LeVi seems to have detected
a lifeform that shouldn't exist.
It could be an error
in the detection software,
or something might've snuck on board.
Let's go see.
You didn't notice anything
when you woke up?
Huh?
Apparently, the presence was detected
in the vicinity of the pod
where you were being treated.
You've been looping, right?
Huh?
Don't worry. There aren't any
Gnosia infectees in this world line.
There's no need to lie.
There's a possibility that something else
got onto the ship in place of the Gnosia.
Setsu...
I didn't wake up there.
Huh?
I didn't actually wake up
in the pod during this loop.
Then...
I'm not sure... but...
There's no way.
But...
No, it's impossible.
The Silver Key causes its host's
consciousness to loop into the past.
If it sent its host's body as well,
there'd end up being
two of the same person.
And if that happened,
the loop would break entirely.
Then what's the lifeform
that's being detected in here?
The lifeform... is being treated...
I knew it.
Then who are you...
No, who's the one being
treated inside this pod?
I don't know,
but...
Doubt not,
fear not,
and know.
Knowledge will save all.
That's what you told me long ago.
What? I told you?
I agree, though. We have to know.
Looks like the treatment is complete.
This is...
An extremely unstable world.
Setsu...
It seems we were brought here in the wake
of the universe being destroyed.
It probably won't last long.
The universe was destroyed...?
Yuri...
Fear not. Knowledge will save all.
Setsu? Setsu!
No... No! No!
Be at ease.
Nothing truly exists in this world.
Existence itself is uncertain here.
Yuriko...
Do you understand now?
This is the truth.
How the hell am I supposed
to understand?!
What's going on?
The universe has been destroyed?
Cause and effect has collapsed.
Because of you, something which
ordinarily could never exist,
the universe has been destroyed.
You are the cause of all of this.
Me?
Yes. Why are you bereft of memories?
Because... I have amnesia.
And what's the real reason?
I didn't... have any memories
to begin with.
Yes. You are...
another Yuri that came into
existence at that moment.
You are a fake that was created
separately from the real Yuri.
That's right. You are a foreign object
anomalous to this world—
to this universe.
Something that absolutely cannot exist.
You are a Bug.
Is something wrong?
Setsu...
So, where did you want to go?
Where?
You're the one who said you
wanted to go somewhere, Yuri.
Huh?
Setsu... Setsu!
Setsu!
Yuri...
No...
No!
Where...
A Bug...
Do you understand now?
You are a fabricated existence.
You are a Bug that was created
separately from the real you.
That's why...
If you run into the real Yuri,
the universe gets destroyed.
B-But it never got destroyed before!
I've been looping over and over,
and nothing like this has ever happened!
Don't you get it?
It didn't happen for a reason.
It is not that you avoided it
out of mere happenstance.
There was no way for it
to happen to begin with.
"Because... there was only one Yuri."
Just think about it.
What was different this time
compared to all the others?
You should be able to figure it out.
There weren't any Gnosia infectees...
Way to go, Yurinchy!
If you've gotten that far,
I'm sure you can figure out the rest!
If there aren't any Gnosia infectees...
the humans won't be attacked.
That's right!
Well done, Yuri.
Man, I'm exhausted. You can say the rest.
I see.
In the world lines where
Gnosia infectees exist,
the real me that was sleeping here had
already been eliminated from the start.
Correct.
The real Yuri was eliminated
by a Gnosia infectee.
Right after that, you, the Bug,
appeared within the same pod.
And you've been looping
ever since as a Bug, bud.
But in the world lines where
there are no Gnosia infectees,
the real Yuri doesn't get attacked.
So, having not been eliminated,
they remain in the pod.
So when you loop and return
like you just did...
The real Yuri and the Bug Yuri...
Both of you end up existing at once.
Basically, you're a dual existence.
That destroys the law of cause and
effect, and with it, the universe.
You understand now, don't you?
When you arrive at a world line with no
Gnosia infectees like the previous one,
you will unavoidably encounter the
other Yuri, destroying the universe.
Then...
You can only exist in world lines
where the Gnosia exist.
That's... the truth?
Indeed.
How... did this happen?
Tell me! Why did you do all this?!
Do you actually believe
I am capable of that?
The one who created you is Gnos.
The only one who can willingly
create a Bug is Gnos.
Gnos?
Gnos is a collective entity formed
from the cyberized minds of humanity.
A single consciousness
that arose out of the chaos.
Or so they say.
The shrine maidens of the
Hoshibune serve Gnos.
The technology of cyberization
was granted to us by Gnos—
in other words, by God.
God...?
A collective entity
possessing all human wisdom.
The supreme will entrusted
with all decisions.
That is the will that created you.
They may be trying to determine something.
A universe where countless individuals
struggle to communicate with each other,
or a universe ruled by a single
great will like Gnos...
Which one has more value?
What am I supposed to do...?
Who knows? That is the extent of the
knowledge that Gnos bestowed upon me.
They disappeared?
This is...
When I touched Gnos through that light...
that was when I knew.
Now all that is left
is to see this through to the end.
Oh, Yuri. You're awake already.
Comet...
We're all in the cafeteria eating
right now. Wanna join us?
No... I'll go later.
Okay.
No...
N...
No!