Generally, the Spirytus
employees work as torturers.
But just for tonight...
Thank you for choosing me.
...they transform into princes!
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Huh?
Hosts?
What?
That's right!
There's a host club we're on friendly
terms with as a source of information,
but apparently, their whole
cast is down with some bug.
They said they'd like our help.
Amateurs can't handle
something like that.
Well, they said they'd
teach us all that stuff.
We're talking about being hosts!
The place is called NOX.
Oh!
That's the place I worked at!
What?!
Oh, my! Well, that speeds
things up, doesn't it?
Oh, Sero-chan! It's been so long!
Nice to see you!
I never imagined you'd
be working at Spirytus.
I was surprised, too!
I didn't know NOX
was one of our regulars!
That's a secret!
Still...
They're absolutely wasted
as torturers, aren't they?
Owner, you're drooling.
Say, what do hosts do?
T-Talk?
I'm sure we can just play it by ear.
I see I have no choice!
Now that it's come to this,
I suppose I'll have to give a lecture.
S-Sero-san?!
No, no. It's Seroelle.
Name
Seroelle
Wasn't there some other
name you could use?
Well, you'll need to be able to do the
bare minimum of waiting on customers.
Think of me as a sweet young lady
and practice, practice!
A sweet young lady?
I'm not sure that's...
You're the only one who could...
I'm pretty cute, though!
You have no shame.
Hello? Hurry up and get over here.
R-Right.
Pleased to meet you!
I'm Mike!
My, what an adorable boy you are.
I-I'm Hugh.
Don't you have any other
answers in your repertoire?
Seroelle-san, what's your
favorite torture implement?
Hey!
What do you think about
Torture Law Article 6, clause 3?
Now, stop that!
Choose topics that are more likely
to get a conversation going!
This seems the most likely
for lively conversation!
Honestly! You silly
torture-brained idiots!
Refrain from talking about torture!
You two can stick to smiling
and nodding in conversation!
All right.
Exactly. Good. Making drinks
is part of a host's job.
Why'd you make such a strong drink?!
I thought I should take 'em down fast.
Our guests are not meant
to be taken down!
Honestly!
All of you are just terrible!
Watch how I do it, okay?!
Should've started with that.
Mike-chan, you're cute!
Really? I bet you say that to everyone.
Yes.
But out of everyone... you're the cutest.
Squee!
Hugh-chan, you said you're
a university student, right?
Yes.
I like torture studies,
so I learn about torture methods
and the basics of current law...
That's amazing.
I'm sorry. I'm boring you.
Not at all.
I don't understand all
the complicated stuff,
but learning what you like...
is fun for me.
Squee!
Sero-san is incredible.
Mind if I have one, too?
Sure.
No better way to do naughty things
than to do it with someone beautiful.
Wow...
You don't have to be so grossed out!
This level of cliché is good!
Wow...
All right, we're about to open!
All right!
And so...
And then, this is the incredible part...
the princes who had to dive
straight into their challenge...
with their handsome faces and rookie
enthusiasm, managed to do quite well.
Thanks!
Miss, I can tell you're
working really hard!
Business hours have ended for the day.
They drummed up a
considerable amount of money.
How?
How'd this happen?
Thank you for today!
You've been such a great help!
And thanks to you,
business was very good!
Packed House Bonus
All of you are well-suited to this.
We're all good at listening, so...
If it's the same sort of work,
isn't being a host better?
You'd be welcome here!
We prefer torture!
And so, the princes' night
passed like a fleeting dream.
Hera-san?
But for it to end after just
one time is such a shame.
Host Club Spirytus. That could work.
No, it wouldn't.
I'm so thirsty!
What's this? I've never seen it before!
No idea. It was just sitting here.
Maybe it was left as a snack
for us? I'll have some, too!
It's sweet and bitter.
What kind of juice is this?
What's this?
This paper...
It's awful
m 0 0 l 130 0 130 50 0 50
I made a fun
new drug.
Careful not
to drink it.
-Izua
Oh, that makes sense.
It was one of Izu-san's compounds.
What kind of weird drug is it this time?
Hey.
What?! You've gotten smaller!
How cute!
Wait, why haven't I changed
at—Oh, you're so adorable!
Calm down.
Safety First
Let's stay safe today!
But you're just
seriously so cute, though!
Ugh! Cut it out!
I'm still me on the inside.
What is this? You're so adorable!
I wonder why Sero-san is the
only one who's still the same.
It's probably because I drank
the prototype for this before.
Maybe I built up some resistance.
Izu-san!
Oh, I get it.
So that's what's going on.
You guys, too?!
All right.
For now, I went and bought
a bunch of kids' clothes.
Pick out whatever you like.
So cute!
What's wrong with him?
Sero-san really likes small,
cute creatures.
Even you're cute.
Stop it.
What should we do about
the rest of our work?
Let's see.
The optics are bad,
so let's leave it for now.
Let go! Stop it!
Makes sense.
Hey!
Now! The two of us will do our
work just like we always do!
This desk is so tall...
This turned into a real mess, didn't it?
You're acting like it's not your problem.
Since we can't work, should we go home?
Since we have time, we thought
we'd organize our paperwork.
Yeah.
You're both such good workers!
Well, if we went back to
normal on the way home...
it could be a problem.
That's true.
All this concentrating
has made me thirsty.
Mike-chan! What do you want to drink?
And I'm hungry, too.
What should I go and buy for you?
I feel like eating something, too.
Understood!
Anything you like! Just name it!
I'll go and buy it all!
You're scaring me.
What?
But it's so adorable when
someone cute is happy!
Are you okay?
Oh, come on! This love
is the purest of pure!
No.
GRIND
Infuriating.
With only a child's strength,
that doesn't hurt!
I won't forget this.
We're back!
It's such a relief.
I've had enough of
that guy's experiments.
You say that, but you'll
drink them again, right?
Wait.
Everyone's so big.
You've turned tiny.
What?!
Why is the timing only different for me?!
Maybe your resistance only delayed
the onset of the effects.
It should make it not work at all!
Guess it's my turn to
take care of you now.
No! He's abducting me!
Thanks for all your hard work!
Even if it's just your outward appearance,
it's dangerous for a kid to go home alone.
Papa, you're so nice!
What? Sero-kun?
Sero-kun, is that you?
Wow!
Hurry up. We're having dinner.
Okay!
Back to
normal
I might be happy being
a kid in Siu-san's house.
Is it okay if I stay the night?
Get out.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Speaking of which,
when they teach us something...
we pair up like this a lot, don't we?
What kind of teaching
style does Siu-san have?
He's very detailed in his instructions,
and it's easy to understand.
What about Sero-san?
He's the same! Sero-san
is really good at teaching!
He is? I might be a little curious now.
I know! In that case...
So...
can we try pairing up differently
than we usually do?
Oh! That sounds like fun!
I don't mind either way.
Okay, go ahead and give it a good whabam.
A "whabam"?
Yeah.
And after that, it's okay
to be more like, "pyaa"!
"Pyaa"?
Do you count the breaths?
Well... just a general idea.
Heart rate, pupil dilation,
angle of the head...
They're all important.
You have to check everything
at this stage.
Y-Yes, sir.
Theory-Based
Intuition-Based
He was so hard to understand.
He was so hard to teach.
Sero-san!
I was organizing the
shelves and found this.
Oh, that brings back memories!
Is this the two of you
from a long time ago?
That's right.
Your hair looks sort of
like Siu-san's back then.
The way it goes like this.
Oh, that.
It's because if I tuck my hair back
when I'm working, I get blood on my face.
It's a practical thing?!
I thought you copied him
because you look up to him.
Do you want to do it, too?
I'm okay like this.
You've got blood on your face again.
Huh? I didn't notice.
You just can't fix that habit, huh?
Maybe I'll do my hair like yours, then.
That way, my hair won't fall down.
That's creepy.
You're so mean.
Which reason was it?
Good mor...ning?
Siu-san?!
Huh?
Um, your hair is sort of... cute today.
It was them.
You're forgetting your recorders.
Okay!
Papa, I'll do your hair for you!
There. All done.
Thanks.
You're good at this. And fast.
You seem used to it.
Are you pleased with my work?
I actually really like drying hair
and braiding it and stuff.
That's...
something that'd snag the ladies, too.
The poor things.
Stop it. You make it sound
like I'm a con artist.
It's Von-san!
I'll go and say hi.
Von-san!
This really is high-quality stuff, right?
Well, of course. I prepared
first-class goods for you.
There've been adulterated
mixtures making the rounds lately.
But we've known each other
a while, so I'll trust you.
Thanks for your business.
That's what happened.
Von-san is a scary person, isn't he?
Really?
Yeah.
You're only realizing that now?
Mi-chan! Chi-chan!
I'm home!
I bought you some really good food!
Eat it all up, okay?
Siu-san.
What do you want to do
about dinner today?
Right. What should we do?
Sero-san, are you guys
having a sleepover?
Yeah. We have work that'll
go late into the night.
Oh! Can we join you, too?
Huh? Why?
You do realize that I know...
that every once in a while, you two
eat really good late-night snacks!
Did you think I hadn't noticed?
Those aromas that occasionally
linger in the kitchenette...
Lingering aroma of
delicious late-night snacks
You can't fool my nose!
We make food sometimes, that's all.
I wanna eat some! I wanna
eat some! I wanna eat some!
Hugh, you want to eat
some, too, don't you?
Yes, I'm curious.
Most of the time, we go out to eat
or make do with ready-made.
Please cook something this time.
Siu-san, what do you want to do?
It's not a bad idea for them to get
experience with how we do things at night.
In that case, I guess...
Shall we go shopping?
Yay!
What are you going to make?
Ramen and fried rice.
Wow!
Set your expectations high!
Siu-san's cooking is really good!
There are four of us today,
so I guess I'll add more
toppings than usual.
Yay!
Do you two cook at all?
I always get delivery.
My mom always makes food for me.
What about you, Sero-san?
Most of the time, I eat out
or get it ready-made,
but if I watch a video or look
at a recipe, I can usually make it.
Wow. You're so talented.
When I cook something...
it's usually because I saw something
and thought it looked good,
or someone asked me to make something.
Really?
When I want to eat home-cooked food,
I visit my parents' house...
Siu-san, I want some
of your rolled omelets!
or I go freeload at Siu-san's place.
Are you a stray dog or something?
Buy some eggs and bring them back here.
Wow!
You've already chopped all this up?
That's amazing!
I can do it, too, you know.
Wow!
Stop making it a competition.
Cooking looks difficult.
It's easy. Wanna try?
Y-Yes!
That's actually amazing!
I'm sorry.
It's fine. Don't worry about it!
It's just about ready,
so you two go sit and wait.
Okay.
We've been sent to the bench.
Siu-san, do you like cooking because
you have Leu-chan and Nero-chan?
No.
Before that,
I was always around some people
who were careless about their food.
I used to cook for them a lot.
Oh. So that's why this place
is so well-stocked, huh?
Real
Mirin
Cooking Sake
Soup Base
And we've got gluttons
like you around, too.
Much appreciated.
My, what a wonderful smell!
You're still here?
A tricky negotiation took
longer than expected.
Now I'm famished.
Want to eat here?
You don't mind?
No problem.
Thank you so much.
I'll make more noodles!
Don't just stand there.
Set the table, moron!
Why are you calling me a moron?!
Oh, no, we'll set the table!
And now...
Time to eat!
This is delicious! Like it
came from a restaurant!
I love this flavor!
Siu-san, this ramen is delicious!
Okay, moron! I'm the one
who made the ramen!
You—
Even so... it's still delicious.
It's good to be honest.
As usual, it's delicious.
We three used to eat it a lot, huh?
Yeah, we did.
It's good, huh?
I never thought we'd ever
have a day as lively as this.
Yeah!
What do you think you're doing?!
Yeah, that's true.
Let's build a fun,
cheerful workplace together!
Stop harassment!
Thanks for the meal!
I'm so full.
Hey, now.
We have work after this,
and you even had seconds.
You're going to get sleepy...
Sheesh.
These kids sure need a lot
of looking after, don't they?
They really do.
The Next Day
I'm sorry for falling asleep last night!
You guys were out cold.
I'm sorry.
I guess we can't give you
night work for a while yet.
Not until you handle yourselves better.
We really are still awful
at this, aren't we?
We'll work even harder from now on
to make sure we'll be able to do it.
All so that we can eat at
the Spirytus Diner again!
Yes, yes!
That's your reason?
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Elanor Sakamato
John Chandanais
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Becky Cottrill