Campus Store
I've got this childhood friend.
That's him, and he loves rom-coms.
I'm so curious.
I love you, Onii-chan!
I'm so curious!
So, so, so, so curious!
What does he think about her
after what she said to him?!
There better not be anything sketchy
happening between them!
Hey, if you have something
to say, just say it!
Huh? What are you talking about?
You've been staring at me
all morning, too, weren't you?
N-No I wasn't!
Why would I do that?!
Seriously?! Self-absorbed much?!
I came here to buy some bread!
Loud, much?
H-Hold up!
What now?
Are you serious?
Are you really going for that?!
EXTRA EXTRA HOT
LIMITED EDITION
3CURRY BREAD
CURRY BREAD
Huh?
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
LIMITED EDITION
EXTRA EXTRA HOT
CURRY BREAD
E-Extra extra hot curry bread?
Wait, I...
Stay calm!
It's not too late to put that down.
Why are you approaching me like that?
Like I said...
No! If I put it back, it's like I'm
admitting that I was following him!
I-I'm free to buy what I want!
I'm in the mood for something spicy!
You don't understand!
You're gonna die!
Die?!
The spiciness hits as if
you're drinking sulfuric acid!
What?!
I've had a bite before,
and it was no joke.
Everyone who tried it
has had to go home early.
EXTRA EXTRA HOT
Some say their butt swelled up
the next morning!
But you know all that, right?
Since you're here for it.
I-I'm fully aware!
Don't do it!
It's gonna mess you up!
Akari, you've always been too stubborn
to admit how you really feel.
Haunted House
I told you to wait.
Huh?!
You're gonna toss it after one bite,
so you might as well save your mo—
I'm not an idiot.
Of course I can finish it!
Thank you. Here's your change.
The spices drifting through the air
are already spicy.
Microwaved It
I can't do this.
I can't even handle level 1 heat
at restaurants...
Don't sacrifice your body for this!
Eat melon bread instead!
Be quiet!
Ugh, don't give me that
"I can't do it" look.
It's not too late to change your mind!
It's all over once you take
that first bite!
Don't underestimate me!
Oh?
It's actually... pretty—
Come on. Hand it over!
EXTRA EXTRA HOT
Not... yet...
What the heck am I doing?
I'm always choosing to be stubborn...
Not being able to say my true feelings...
Akari?
Don't force it!
Something's really off with you today.
I'll get you some water!
No, is milk better?
I'll be right back!
But...
I don't want to lose!
Watch me...
finish it!
See? I finished it.
Sorry.
I didn't think you could pull it off.
That was impressive, Akari.
Yeah... sure...
Hey... I can actually do it after all!
I like... Eiyu...
Spicy food's... not so bad!
Oh... Y-Yeah!
I'm glad you got through it.
It's really not my thing...
I feel... hot...
What?!
Akari!
Hey! Get a hold of yourself, Akari!
By the next day, the extra extra
hot curry bread was taken away.
I'll get you some milk!
Don't die, Akari!
Finals are over!
It's almost summer break!
I've noticed that I have feelings
for my childhood friends.
That was a piece of cake, huh?
I got my highest score ever!
Same here!
This means I can really
let loose this summer.
But this really isn't the time
to think about them!
Hey! Are you two free this summer break?
Eiyu?
Oh?
Where'd he go?
Onii-chan, welcome back!
Look, look!
I got perfect scores on everything!
Th-That's really impressive, Runako.
Impressive? You think so?!
Praise me more!
Sorry, I can't right now.
Huh?
This is bad.
Distracting Thought 1
Distracting Thought 2
Is it because I've been too caught up
in distracting thoughts lately?
They were acting like it was no big deal.
Yeah... This is really bad!
I can't be messing around this year!
I can't possibly be dumber than them!
I'd rather die!
That's why he's been cooped up
in his room for three days?
Yeah, so I've been really bored.
Were his grades that bad this time?
Well, it's his loss.
Let's make plans without him.
But won't you miss him, Akari-chan?
N-Not really...
You're working hard, aren't you?
Y-You must be tired!
Come on, chat with us!
Hey Shio! Give me some space! I'll fall.
I can't scoot any further, Akarin!
What are you all doing?
Y-You've been at it for a while, Eiyu.
So we thought we'd
bug you to take a break.
I'm fine.
What?!
Come on, it's only just a minute!
We wanna make summer plans!
Stop!
Are you a mountain person
or a beach person?
I said, stop!
What's with you?
Were your grades that bad?
Th-They weren't that bad...
So there's no use cramming
at this point, is there?
It's not like you're suddenly
going to get smarter.
Leave me alone!
Consistency is what matters!
Consistency?!
So you're telling me that taking one
day off would undo all of your progress?!
That's enough, you two!
Just leave me alone!
Gosh!
Come, come.
Whisper, whisper, whisper,
whisper, whisper...
Okay, Onii-chan.
Study all you want.
What?
You're the one missing out, you know!
Lame!
Enjoy your pathetic summer break.
You've got this, Onii-chan.
Pathetic?
Are you kidding me?
You don't know what it's like to be me!
I can't stand alongside you two...
unless I've got something going for me!
Poke, poke.
Ignore, ignore.
Ignore, ignore!
Poke, poke, poke, poke.
Can't you see I'm study—
Don't you wanna go to the beach?
Swim, swim!
swim
bounce
Bounce, bounce!
Yes I'd...
love to go.
Hooray!
Which beach should we go to?
Enjoy the views of the ocean
and the highlands all to yourself
I know a secret place.
You do?!
So how bad were your grades actually?
Eek!
I'm curious, too!
You better not laugh.
What?!
I couldn't get a perfect score
on any of them.
They're all really good though!
Really good?
Then, how were yours?
Eek!
W-Well...
They weren't bad... Right?
Y-Yeah! Right.
I only got, like, one failing grade...
A failing grade?
That's not good!
You both have to plan to study
during the break.
No!
And put on some clothes.
Geez. I didn't get any studying done
until Shio and Akari went home.
But... I'll be spending
summer break with them.
Akarin, did you bring your jammies?
Shoot! I fell asleep.
If you left them, you could borrow mine.
It's fine, I brought mine.
It's been a while since we
all took a bath together.
Yeah.
I'm gonna start the shower now.
Okay.
What?! I thought they went home!
Why are they using our tub?!
And why the heck did I choose to hide?!
Whoa, the shower's pretty hot!
This is... seriously bad!
How's the temperature?
It's just right.
I'm so excited for our pajama party!
I wanna hear about your
junior high school days.
Really? It was nothing special.
But hey, I wonder where Eiyu went.
Probably the store. Come on...
P-Pajama party?
That's why they're taking a bath together?
What should I do?!
Why the heck did I close the cover?
Now there's no escape!
Wow! Shio-chan!
They really are huge!
So impressive! What do you eat?
Oh come on, Runako.
Akari-chan's are...
What?
They're so cute.
What did you say?!
I-It's not about the size, you know!
Yeah.
I know you're all having fun,
but please leave!
Idiot! Don't look!
Be calm, be still...
Don't make a sound!
It's so fun to take a bath together!
If Onii-chan were a girl,
he could've joined us.
Eiyu?
A girl?
What?
Come on, Runako, don't be so weird!
bump
Runako, I'll rinse your hair for you.
Okay!
drag
N-No one saw?!
What a relief, I thought I was dead!
It's a little cramped
in here for three, huh?
Someone get in the tub first.
Oh, I just started rinsing off.
Then I'll get in first!
No...! No...!
Why don't you take off the lid?
I want to keep the water hot.
I'm gonna die! Oh God!
Okay, I'll get in, too.
No! Oh, no! Oh, no!
My life...
ends now!
I wonder how Onii-chan feels about you two.
Being around childhood friends
who are so cute,
he's bound to fall in love, right?
Wh-What are you talking about, Runako?
He doesn't have feelings like that.
Yeah! We're childhood friends!
Uh-huh.
Plus, it wouldn't make me happy
even if he did see me like that...
Really?
I'd be happy if he said he liked me.
I guess... I'd be happy, too.
Huh?!
What do you mean?
It's always nice to know
that someone likes you, right?
That's true...
I guess I wouldn't hate it...
What the heck are we talking about?!
Enough's enough!
In the end, we're only childhood friends!
I'm getting too hot. I'm getting out.
M-Me too.
Wait! Me too!
Th-That was close!
Crap, I got super lightheaded.
And I can't believe
they were talking about me.
I guess... I'd be happy, too.
It might not be the worst thing.
"It might not be the worst thing"?
I forgot something!
Huh?
Onii-chan, you're still here.
Um, Runako... I can explain...
Wait, still here?
That mole on your butt
never went away, huh?
blush
R-Runako... When did you notice...?
That's a secret.
Oh yeah! Onii-chan!
Promise you'll take responsibility
for today at some point, okay?
No, no...
No, no, no.
Summer break starts next week...
But still, there's no way...
this is the year we, childhood
friends, start a rom-com.
And now it's summer break.
Morning, Eiyu!
Hey, morning.
Runako and Akari've got something to do.
I see, then...
It's just the two of us.
Shall we?
It's the season of flirting and romance...
Even though we're just
childhood friends...
Will it start a high school rom-com?
Not a chance.
Let's study at the library this summer
when there's no other plans!
Let's finish our homework
as soon as possible
and enjoy the rest of the break!
Shio, are you sure you can concentrate?
I'll show you!
I said that, but...
I'm the one who can't concentrate!
The other day...
I'd be happy if he said he liked me.
I guess... I'd be happy, too.
It might not be the worst thing.
It's all because of that.
I'm such a fool! Don't take it seriously!
I know I'm only gonna get hurt!
I appreciate it, but... sorry.
Poke, poke, poke.
We've Got This!
I need to get over myself.
Please be quiet in the library
I'm beat!
Hey, hey, so what did you think?
I was pretty focused, right?
Yeah... Seemed like you did pretty good.
Since I was being watched,
I couldn't slack off.
And actually...
I wanted to ask you about this problem.
She's so close!
I-It's too stuffy here.
Well... could you just look at this?
"Please be quiet in the library."
Well yeah...
I guess Shio still sees me as a kid.
What will she think if she knows
it's different for me?
All right!
I'm gonna tackle all of this in one week!
You say that every year.
I'm serious this year!
English
These two are wrong, just so you know.
What?
Oh, this one, too.
English
What?!
Guess we're gonna need to do
study sessions again this year.
What?!
But what about the beach? The fireworks?!
I wanted to do something
special this summer!
Huh?
S-Since we're in high school now!
Ah.
S-So like...just the two of us...
As far as us goes...
I guess we'll always be like this, huh?
We're in high school,
but we're still doing the same things
we did in grade school.
I bet we'll be doing the same stuff
even after we graduate.
You... think so?
Wait!
Shio, are you okay?
If we go to different colleges... and
live elsewhere, will things stay the same?
I bet they will.
We're childhood friends.
Even if... you have a girlfriend?
Even if we both marry
somebody else and have kids...
Will we always...
stay childhood friends... forever?
Shio?
Things will stay the same.
Childhood friends are childhood friends.
What if...
Even if... I asked you out?
What?
If you asked me out...?
What? Could this be...?
Eiyu...
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
Eiyu...
Ice cream!
Huh?
What if I asked you out
to get ice cream with me?
Well, I knew it all along!
You really can't be in a rom-com
with your childhood friend!
Even if we're still
just childhood friends...
Episode 5
I want to make this summer...
really special!
Extra Extra Hot? Finals Done? Bath Episode?
Things Will Never Change? Still Won't Start a Rom-Com