Demon Defense Force HQ
(10th Squadron Stronghold)
With the appearance
of the Eight Thunder Gods,
the Demon Defense Force commanders
were summoned for a meeting.
These commanders' meetings
make me nervous.
Um... Can I help you?
I think she's the commander
of the 8th Squadron.
Uhh...
Does she hate me or something?
I-I should head back.
M-Miss Yakumo?!
How's it hangin'?
Lemme borrow you again, little slave!
If we need Phoenix Wings.
Otherwise, it's me and Miss Kyouka!
If we don't practice, you won't be ready
in case of an emergency!
How 'bout we fly
to a hot spring in Hokkaido?
I can show you around!
That far?!
And of course...
I'll be sure...
that you're rewarded handsomely
for your efforts!
Gotta go to the bathroom!
Catch you later!
Aw, he ran away!
Now back to the...
Hello!
Miss Tenka.
Where are you headed, Yuuki?
Back to the conference room.
Going that way takes longer.
Here, come with me!
If you walk alone, you might happen upon
some unsavory people.
I really appreciate it.
Don't worry, I've got this.
Demon Defense Force Headquarters
Conference Room
Lady Ren will be joining us remotely
from Washington.
Let's begin the commanders' meeting.
Mune ga shizunde mirai kanjirenaku nattari
Toki ga tomatte mou owatta tte kanjitari
Fusagikonde hanasenakute
Jiwari kokoro no kasa ga hiraita
Soredemo tsuyogatte ikiteta
Nagusamete nante iwanai
Tsuyoku natte mae o mitetainda
Dakedo yowasa ga oshitsubusu
Kimi ni atte sekai afurete hikari ataetekuretari
Sukoshi datte kibou nakatta boku ga waraetetanda
Nanigenai kaiwa de zutto egao ataetekuretari
Arigatou tte terete warau kara iwanai yo
Dakedo omotteru yo
Kono saki mae muite ikeru kana?
Hikari yo, boku ni
The Commander of the 2nd Squadron
Episode 8
Let me explain why
I called you here so suddenly.
Over the past few days,
Kanagawa - Serial Disappearances of Women
several women have gone missing
in the city of Yokohama.
The police were investigating it
as a crime involving abilities.
However...
the surveillance footage
revealed this person.
A Thunder God?
We've never seen one like her.
She phased through a building
and disappeared without a trace.
Phased through it?
In other words, she's utilizing
an ability to kidnap the women?
If she's a Thunder God, then it's the
Demon Defense Force's time to shine.
Up till now, when Shuuki entered
the normal world,
they just caused a bunch of mayhem.
I've said it before.
We should destroy the Shuuki
as soon as possible!
First, we deal with her.
We'll send a disposal unit
into the normal world
to coordinate with the police
and defeat her.
There's a Passage in Yokohama,
a gate connecting Mato
to the normal world.
Your team will be in charge...
Mira.
Gotcha.
The disposal unit will be made up
of a select few people.
We can't leave Mato unguarded.
If yer sendin' me...
I don't need any help kickin' their asses.
She's so cool!
Lady Mira! You're totally awesome!
We don't know how many enemies there are.
Pick one of the other commanders
and bring them with you.
Right here!
Miss Yakumo doesn't mind tagging along!
How does wreckin' the entire frickin' city
with yer Night Storm help exactly?!
Yer gonna be my dance partner...
Kyouka.
Challenge accepted.
Are you sure about losing the Kimon and
Urakimon commanders at the same time?
The others will cover for them.
We've trained for this exact scenario.
She's right. It won't be a problem.
We leave as soon as the meeting's over!
Yeah, they won't terrorize the city
any longer!
Our next battle...
is going to be in the normal world.
Looks tasty.
So she's definitely the kidnapper.
We were able to trace the victims
using our task force's abilities.
This suggests that they've survived.
We'll be able to pinpoint their location
by tomorrow night at the latest.
I suspect we'll find
the kidnapper there as well.
The enemy is a non-human.
Let the Demon Defense Force
handle combat and rescue.
Even if you find 'em, no jumpin' the gun.
Understood.
We'll contact you
once we've tracked them down.
Police Station
Damn...
Flying and phasin' through matter?
Tricky combo.
One of the humanoid Shuuki
who the Eight Thunder Gods captured
was able to do that.
And now a Thunder God is using it...
Can she steal abilities?
If so, we know the motive
behind the kidnappings.
But judgin' by the data,
none of the victims are particularly
notable ability users.
Yokohama's a big city.
They're from all over the place.
Mira, I'd like to get familiar with
the area before we engage in combat.
'Kay. In that case...
It's my first time riding one of these!
Same here.
We'll do a lap around the city.
Get a feel for it.
Here.
Thanks, Miss Kyouka.
You haven't changed a bit.
Carryin' candy in yer pocket...
Ya get that from Riu?
How long have you two known each other?
Since joinin' the Demon Defense Force.
Back in my hometown of Okinawa,
I was unbeatable.
Kinmamon
Ability or no ability,
I thought I was tougher than anyone.
But then you lost
when we went hand to hand.
The nerve of you
with that shitty ability.
We were promoted to commander
around the same time.
And we both got put in charge of hotspots,
the Kimon and the Urakimon.
Sounds like you're rivals.
Except the Supreme Commander
position belongs to me!
It's going to be me!
Ya wanna say that again?!
I'm telling you, I'm going to be
the Supreme Commander!
There they go again...
Ever heard the phrase, "Talk shit, get hit"?!
Two rivals, one mission...
I'd better give it my all!
Chinatown
It's delicious, Mira!
I thought rich food
would be right up yer alley.
By the way, kid...
Yes?
I didn't choose Kyouka for this job
to try and one-up her.
I chose her 'cause I knew
we'd crush the enemy together.
I wanna be Supreme Commander...
but I don't believe in backstabbin'.
If yer gonna try to help Kyouka win,
ya better not get overzealous.
Saving lives is the top priority!
That's the Demon Defense Force way!
Ya got that, kid?!
Yes, ma'am!
Here we go!
Yay!
Cheese!
Vibrant and trendy. It's a nice place.
Yeah. I like it here, too.
Mommy, a flower!
It's pretty, isn't it?
Damn those slimy bastards...
Sneakin' around and
snatchin' people off the street.
Mira?!
Want me to wash yer back?
What's gotten into you?
You and Tenka have been awfully secretive
about somethin' lately.
Your eyes give it away, y'know.
Ya give each other
a certain look sometimes.
Wanna tell me about it?
You're right. Something is going on.
But it's not something
I can discuss right now.
What?!
When the time is right...
I'll let you in on it, too.
If ya need a hand,
ya better not hesitate to tell me!
I know.
Let's make it happen.
Got it!
Oh, right...
We're in Yokohama.
Where's Miss Kyouka?
Oh crap!
She's gonna dump my body in the harbor!
I-I didn't realize you were awake...
I-I'm sorry!
Maybe I should sleep in another room!
It's so we can move out quickly!
Y-you can stay here.
Seriously, it's not a big deal.
Okay.
The
Next
Day
We've pinpointed the victims' location,
as well as discovered
the kidnapper's hideout.
This the place?
Pretentious, don'tcha think?
There's one now!
Oh? A lookout, huh?
It's strong!
Who d'ya think yer talkin' to?
They're finished as soon as
I whip out my ability, remember?!
Ya know how to throw punch,
but yer missin' something.
And it's...
WILLPOWER!
Yer wimpy attacks don't do jack shit.
With her bare hands?!
Does Miss Mira's ability
make her body stronger?!
Mira!
Huh?
Figured you were up to something sneaky...
but now yer playin' dirty!
Miss Mira?!
Don't worry!
Mira has that one under control!
We're going to put this one down!
Are you okay, Miss Kyouka?
It grazed me, but I'm fine.
Pieces of shit who take innocent hostages
need to be taught a lesson!
It isn't Mira's ability
that's enhancing her physical state.
Demon Defense Force
2nd Squadron Dorm
If Mira goes on the offensive,
a flag is planted
on the 2nd Squadron's roof.
Holding that flag is the 2nd Squadron's
second-in-command, Megumi Zaha.
2nd Squadron
Megumi Zaha
Megumi fell in with a bad crowd
out of a desire to seem important.
But then she met Mira the Crimson,
a peerless fighter
who looked even more beautiful
when dyed red
with her opponents' blood.
Being Mira's personal flag-bearer
gave Megumi a sense of pride
and self-confidence.
Megumi's ability, "Red Soul,"
Peerless
Mira Kamiunten
Red Hot Rod Crew
Bearing the Scarlet Flag
Red Soul
makes Mira stronger
while she's flying her flag.
It's exceedingly rare, and it can only
enhance one specific person.
On the other hand, Mira's ability...
I found all of the kidnapping victims.
They're alive.
Looks like our kidnapper's still at large.
But ensuring the victims' safety
comes first, right?
Yer trapped now, asshole!
Scarlet Regiment
All Killing
All Killing!
A cloning ability
that doesn't compromise strength...
It never gets old.
Whoa...
Whaddya expect? I'm a commander.
I don't see the kidnapper anywhere.
And not a single clue, either.
Oh well.
Let's leave the investigatin'
to the police.
I guess we've got no choice.
Go get yer injuries looked at now!
These? It's just a few scratches.
The enemy was a special type of Shuuki.
If we have time, we ought to
get it checked out just in case.
He's right!
What if ya got poisoned
or somethin', dumbass?!
Couple of nosy parkers...
Be right back.
Gonna let 'em know what happened.
No cameras, either...
Guess I can do his reward here.
Miss Kyouka, are you hurt anywhere
other than your arm?
Miss Kyouka?
Just in case...
maybe you should look me over.
Seems like that's your reward.
Yup, everything's fine!
No injuries here!
What about back here?
Nope, all's well!
We're in the normal world...
And we're in public!
Making me undress here...
You pervert!
Y-you're stunning.
You're checking for injuries, remember?!
Hey!
Let's pack our bags and-
Wh-what in God's name is Kyouka doing?!
AH!
Another woman is one thing,
but in front of a man?!
Gettin' buck naked like that...
WHAT THE-?!
What a minute, is she-
Are they engaged?!
Does that mean they've...
"taken things to the next level"?!
Oh, Miss Mira.
Kyouka will be back in a bit.
She's gettin' her injuries
checked out nearby.
Okay.
So, uh... Tell me, kid...
Are you and Kyouka dating?!
No, no! You've got it all wrong!
Wait, really?
You were so worried that I thought...
My life looks the way it does
because of Miss Kyouka.
She's a wonderful person,
and my motivation for doing what I do.
Kinda like a samurai and their master
in the olden days!
Oh, I get it! Your master!
Yeah, except... I'm a slave.
Ya got heart, kid.
Miss Mira...
Get some rest before the next battle.
Yes, ma'am!
He's clearly loyal to her...
but she gets naked in front of him
and they aren't dating?
It's a reward for her ability, sure,
but c'mon, Kyouka...
Unbelievable...
I should rest while I can.
Hiya!
The kidnapper!
I can't move.
I can't speak, either!
It's no use! I immobilized you.
Beautifully divine handiwork!
I'm Kuusetsu.
She's one of the Eight Thunder Gods!
I got back to my lair
and my lookouts were dead,
and my prey had escaped!
My plan was totally foiled!
I wanted to lose my cool and raise hell,
but Big Sis Shikoku
forbade me from fighting.
Then I saw you and followed you here!
Me?
Yuuki Wakura.
Big Sis Shikoku's favorite.
I've heard a lot about you.
So I might as well bring you back
as a souvenir from Yokohama.
My body just-
And I need you for my test.
You'll do, I guess. Barely.
"Test"?
Before I snatched one of my prey...
she was having sex with a male.
I wanna know if it feels
as good as it looked.
M-my tongue... and my arms...
They're moving on their own!
Mm, this is nice.
I wonder what happens to a human
when they have sex with a god.
Should we test it out?
Love beam!
Shiritai teka shitai furetai
Afuredasu kono omoi wa tomannai janai
Amai amai sono karada de uketomete ne darling
Kainarashite ageru gohoubi no jikan
Kasaneawasu hada to hada kara umareru netsu de
Juuden max
Ima hassha OK!
Kono te kara ima love love beam
Sono heart megake ima love love beam
Kokoro no kyori mo tobikoeteku
Zero kyori de hanate
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
Nigasanai wa mou love love beam
Sekai no hate mademo love love beam
Sou ai koso ga sekai o kaeru
Kurayami mo somero heart iro ni
A Commander's Resolve
Episode 9
Next time, Episode 9:
"A Commander's Resolve"
Here's today's bonus!
Mira Kamiunten.
She may call it a competition,
but she enjoys spending time with Kyouka.
When she sees a dog video,
she shares it with Ren.
Her parents are young
and work at a brewery making awamori.
She has one younger sister.
Nice explanation.