Unread Messages
Kukuru and Wagari are fighting near
the hot springs!
Man, Kasubata's dead meat.
Guess I'd better bail him out again.
Hey, it's Urusugawa-chan!
Hugs time!
Kusaba?!
Are you going to see Kasubata-kun?
I won't let you!
Eru Kusaba...
A self-declared "romantic"
who's actually a walking minefield.
She falls head-over-heels
for any guy who catches her eye,
then scours the net and uses sock puppets
to find out his likes and dislikes.
And once she knows everything about him,
she morphs herself into his ideal woman!
She's currently on look number twelve!
Cyber out.
Little Mine Book.
Little Mine Book
When I step on a mine, I can bring out
120% of the power of a man I've won over.
Mixed Martial Artist
Futo Ryuno
She hits fast... and hard!
Even guarding with my goo,
she throws hands like a man!
By the way, the moment he returns
my affection, I lose all interest.
Maybe I only live
for the love of the chase.
Lame
That's just the kind of girl I am!
Targeting me so I can't get to Kasubata
sounds like playing decoy for your leader.
I didn't think 1-A was into teamwork!
Oh, you've got it all wrong!
Wagari-san's just so much stronger,
Kasubata-kun's guaranteed to lose.
Which means...
Kasubata! Speak to me!
Urusugawa... You patched me up?
And then he might totally end up
falling for you, right?!
I can't let that happen! Not ever!
Can't you get your brain
out of the gutter for once?!
Sticky Love Bomb!
Sticky Love Bomb
Get lost!
Damn. I spent a ton of
spirit power cushioning my fall.
But the goo should have her pinned, so...
Her clothes?
Land Mine Connection
No need to be shy with no boys around!
Beautician
Shota Ryuha
The camera drones
can't see us indoors either!
Besides...
This is a changing room, isn't it?
Oh?
You sure you want to drop your guard?
I'll beat you down
even worse than last time
so Kasubata-kun will never
be attracted to you!
He isn't anyway!
Why do you even like him so much?!
Kasubata-kun...
Those piercing eyes! That wild masculinity
seething beneath his serious exterior!
You know, Enishiro-kun's pretty hot, too.
When they're together, it's just not fair!
You've got rotten taste!
You can't even stick to a single guy!
This is what you looked like
when you first came to school!
Did you go with the black hair
to match Kasubata?
There's not a single part of you
that's really you!
What are you into, Kusaba-san?
What about you?
I like tennis.
So do I!
I love pickled sea cucumber.
What a grandpa, right?
No, I love sea pineapple!
She's changing her interests again.
She's got a new man every day.
Like changing phone cases.
It's all me!
I was serious about all of them!
I'm just trying to be honest
to whatever moves my heart!
You're just a self-repressing
stalker, Urusugawa-chan!
Screw you!
Die!
Urusugawa-chan...
Look at this.
I did it...
With your fave, Kureha-kun.
Land Mine Connection
Sumo Wrestler
Gintakewaka
Land Mine Connection
All a bluff.
Digital Artist
Ginpei Ishiyama
Good thing I shopped that up in advance.
A twofer of physical and mental trauma.
She'll be totally demoralized now!
Your fave isn't even my type!
She thinks she's so great
just because her family's rich.
She sucks.
She gets whatever she asks for.
Even the teachers favor her.
Freak
Stay out of school
Go back to your ivory tower
Get lost
This world is shit,
but at least I have my fave.
He exists here in the same world.
That was enough to keep me going.
Kureha-kun's bass playing resonated
inside me, kept me warm.
A rope made of goo?!
How did she recover so quickly?
I knew that was a shop job!
It took me out for a second,
But did you think I wouldn't recognize
the selfie of him alone in bed
that he posted to his Insta
last year on March 2nd at 1:18 AM?!
I stared at it over and over...
imagining I was in that bed with him!
Don't underestimate a full-time fangirl!
She... She's just like me!
A total romantic!
Besides...
What the...
All of a sudden, my phone just...
What did I just do?
Hey, there!
It's not safe for a girl
to be out alone at this hour.
Can I take you home?
Buzz off. I don't do
the sugar daddy thing.
D-D-D... Daddy?!
Kiyomi Urusugawa-san.
That girl went to the hospital earlier.
I-I didn't mean to! She just kept
mouthing off, so I wished she was dead.
A-And then... it just...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What is that?
A special power only you and I can see.
You've unlocked an incredible talent.
Your classmate is fine.
There are lots of other kids like you.
You've got cyberkinesis.
Cyberkinesis?
Would you like some training
to keep it under control?
You'll be with people like you.
It's not just about my fave.
I can't afford to lose!
Neither can I!
Don't underestimate me!
Right back at you!
At this rate...
I'll run out of battery!
Damn it! Any more of this and...
I'm going to pass out!
Cyber off!
Can't move another muscle.
Me either.
Milk
You're good, Kusaba.
I take back what I said about you not
being you. And having a gutter-brain.
You're strong, too. I'm sorry
I said you were self-repressing.
Also... I've never actually d-done it.
Kiyomi Urusugawa
Eru Kusaba
Out of the fight
One win, one draw.
Class 1-B is in the lead.
Quite a turnabout
from the last A-B Battle.
Class A, under the great Wagari,
is losing ground.
Azaki-sensei, it's too early
to declare victory.
You know, Nanzo-sensei,
this really isn't about me and you.
Sheesh. And you so used
to look up to me, too.
P-Principal!
I'm picking up a ghost account
in the fake Kusatsu, yes!
A ghost account?
It's very faint, but yes!
Azaki-sensei, is this another
ridiculous "surprise" of yours?
Heck no.
Principal, we should investigate.
Contact all staff on the premises.
R-Right!
It doesn't seem like Nanzo-kun
or the school set this up.
What's going down over there?
Yeah, it's no use.
I can't stop shaking.
I suck. I really suck.
I...
What's going on?!
I'm not hitting him!
My flames aren't even grazing him!
What...
What's he been doing
these last two weeks?!
Azaki-sensei.
There's something I want you to teach me.
Well?
Teach me, Azaki-sensei...
how to use cyberkinesis without a phone!
You can't do that.
But Surugi does it!
Oh, I hear you.
That's right.
It's a bit early, but you might be ready
to move on to the next stage.
The next stage?
Listen up. Standard practice is
to cyber out directly from your phone.
However...
You can also run spirit power
through your smartphone
and back into your body
instead of outputting it.
B-Back into your body?
Then you can release the output elsewhere.
Focus on the flow of spirit power
in the pit of your stomach.
Not working...
Train hard enough,
and you won't have to hold it.
You can just have your phone
in contact with your body somewhere.
Your Onipien...
will be able to burn
more freely than before!
I had the laboratory division
make a smartphone holster for me.
My spirit power's coursing
through my body!
What's wrong?
Try harder.
Enflame: Eye!
Enflame
Eye
Thank you, Sensei!
With both hands free, you can integrate
more variety into your attacks, Aori-chan!
Thank you, Master!
Why can't I hit him?!
If I can't hit him, then...
Hit me more! More!
Harder, Enishiro...
Harder, harder, harder...
Harder, harder, harder!
Enishiro, harder!
Here we go!
Gotcha!
Letting you fry me was worth it!
Let's hear you scream!
Enflame: Shoulder!
Enflame
Shoulder
Nullify Flame Damage!
You'll need a stronger flame
than that to burn me.
Well, do you give up yet?
Th-That doesn't feel good... at all.
You're just strong now.
It just hurts!
It doesn't feel like anything!
Because it's not infused
with hatred for me!
Love and hate are the same thing.
They're both strong emotions!
Dei Surugi  To: atggldq
HOLY SHIT UR UGLY LOLOLOL GUESS THEY
LET ANYONE BE AN IDOL THESE DAYS
WHAT ARE YOU A BEHEMOTH
So many people hate me online.
Mayolar To: sO.nWpYzU
Reported
Sayaka-chan stan To: sO.nWpYzU
Who the hell is this guy?
Pretty sad to get your kicks riling people up online
My only regret is that
I can't see their faces.
Pavlov-san To: sO.nWpYzU
Nobody likes you
More... More...
Oh, shit!
Hate me more!
You're trash.
Being in a class with filth like you
goes against every righteous
fiber of my being.
But you shouldn't change.
You're better than someone
who pretends to be good.
Actually, I like you!
Getting love and hate at the same time...
I'd never felt that before!
Such ecstasy!
C'mon, Enishiro! You hate me, don't you?!
Remember when I torched
that thing you care about?!
Hit me with that anger and
sadness like you did then!
Make me come!
I don't have time for this, weirdo.
Disinterest?
Let's just end this.
Enflame: Leg!
With my enflamed super-jump,
I can go fifty meters high!
I'll show you one more
thing you're lacking!
A special move!
A flame-powered kick with
the power of gravity behind it...
Onibi Skill: Flames Falling from Heaven!
Unbelievable.
I've made it clear I'm better than him.
Why does he keep fighting?
Kukuru!
Ren!
I came to save you!
Now it's two on one!
Five Minutes Earlier
Kukuru! Please be safe!
There's a member of Class A
whose cyberkinesis you don't know?
That's right. He didn't participate
in the last A-B Battle.
He sat out to keep the numbers even.
Kiri Namekawa.
Be careful if you run into him.
You don't know what he might do.
Cyber out...
Hypnosis App.
May I introduce myself?
I'm Kiri Namekawa.
My hobbies are watching insects
and creating fake news.
There's nothing more fun than
watching low-information readers
believe lies and do what I want.
It's a lot like watching insects.
Cyberkinesis: Hypnosis App.
If a target looks at my screen,
I can make them follow my orders.
Order: Attack Kukuru Kasubata.
Order
Attack Kukuru Kasubata
I... stabbed Kukuru?
K-Kukuru...
Does that take them both
out of the battle now, Wagari?
I thought this might be you.
It's not the conclusion I wanted.
I really dislike you, Namekawa-kun.
I personally like you, Wagari.
You smell good. Like the paste
we used in kindergarten.
Well, let's clean up the rest of them.
We'll find the doll-user in hiding,
the coward, and...
It's not...
It's not over yet, Wagari.
What?
I personally find this irritating.
You should be controlled.
Don't look, Kukuru!
Don't look at it!
Order
Order: Dance to death.
Dance to death
Wahoo-hoo-hoo!
A sloppy technique
can be turned back on its user.
You caught him off guard with a roar,
forcibly canceling his cyberkinesis,
which was unstable following output.
So you still have some life left in you.
A slice of true conviction in that
warped righteousness of yours.
If I can't cut through to your mind,
this time, I'll sever your limbs
and render you physically
incapable of fighting!
I can't escape with my windows now.
Don't die, Kukuru! Just surrender instead!
Azaki-sensei, you're watching, right?!
Declare him out of the fight!
Azaki!
Azaki-sensei!
Are you trying to kill your student?
Azaki!
Azaki-sensei!
Shut up!
You're all pathetic.
If this fight ends now,
it's the end of me, too.
Kukuru... why are you so desperate?
I can't deny I thought
it was only natural I lost last time.
I'm on my last legs in terms of output.
Cyber out.
Kukuru...
Is that...