We can go home soon!
I wanna get home! I wanna get home soon!
Ah!
To Snowfield!!
This is...
definitely beyond the confines
of ordinary Magecraft.
Cavalryman... Rider?
Such thrilling music!
It was truly a wonderful experience!
All right!
First and foremost,
let's form an alliance with someone!
So, you won't be going there?
Due to the events from a
previous Holy Grail War,
a Lord is not allowed onsite.
That's what the Clock Tower decided.
You have some new information?
Yes.
I thought you should be
the first person to know.
Baleman.
S-Several hours ago,
a certain indie band uploaded this video.
First the news, now video streaming.
Look! Right here!
Sajyou?
What's wrong, Ayaka?
Nothing.
You have an uneasy look on your face.
If there's something worrying you,
don't hesitate to tell me.
I said it's fine.
Oh, perhaps you're tired?
You weren't able to sleep
at the music club, either.
Jeez!
I have nothing but uncertainties!
Isn't there another Master
hiding here or something?
Right! This Magical Energy
enveloping the entire forest
is almost like a bounded field!
What if, maybe, they attack us?
If they felt so inclined,
they would have done it long ago!
How can you have so much faith?
Huh?
I can't see Saber anymore!
Why did that weird Saber show up
instead of Altry?
What did you use as the catalyst?
They said the sheath
for the legendary sword was gone...
so I used the box that it was sealed in.
I totally thought we'd
be able to summon Altry!
Jeez!
This forest is annoying!
Hello!
What have you come to me for?
I don't know what kind of being you are...
but I wanted to make a request
to the first Servant I came across!
Huh? Servant?
Do you have any interest
in forming an alliance with us?
I don't mind...
but will my Master gain
anything from that?
I'd like to talk to your Master, as well.
Are they not here with you? Huh?
What a wonderful Master.
They're not particularly fond of humans.
But your Master seems to be an exception.
Perhaps because she's
not much like a Master.
Well, actually she's not a Master at all.
Let's get back on topic.
I saw a monster last night.
This Holy Grail War...
has either gotten roped into
some tremendous trouble,
or it's being used for something.
In either case, why don't we
eliminate them together and start clean?
The way things are going now,
if I were to lose, I can't
say Ayaka will be safe
even if she evacuates to the Church.
You seem to cherish your
Master quite a bit.
She got roped into this because of me.
If I didn't take
responsibility for that...
the people who inherited
lineage of my clan...
and...
the name of the great first king
will be tarnished.
Interesting.
You surely are a king yourself, but of
a different type than the king I know.
Especially the part that you seem to have
an exceptional number of friends.
Is that so? I'd think
you have more friends than I do.
I believe that anything
living on this earth is a friend.
Although my feelings are
often unreciprocated.
But a close friend that I can disclose
what goes on in my heart to...
That, I decided will be just one person.
Woah, come now. Is this
negotiation a failure?
Or is it...
That close friend is quite a fussy guy.
If you're weak, you'd just be killed.
I'd like to test whether or not...
you can fight against him.
I love things that are easy to understand.
I basically have to prove
my strength, right?
H-Hold on! What are you guys—
Don't worry, Ayaka.
This is just a trial to form an alliance.
Now...
let's start this battle!
Hey, Brother!
That Saber sword arrived.
This isn't a Noble Phantasm or anything.
It's just a decorated sword.
But he supposedly destroyed
the Opera House
with a single strike from that sword.
A knight with red streaks
in his blond hair...
This is most likely Lionheart.
Yeah, that Lionheart.
I see, you conclude so, as well?
Yeah. Lionheart was a
total King Arthur freak.
Some say he pretended to live
a fast life, but in reality,
went on to search around
for King Arthur's fortune.
However, isn't he a hero from an era
where the Mystics have
relatively thinned out?
Hey, Brother.
Lionheart was called the "Wandering King"
in my era, ya know.
Indeed, it's said the time
he stayed within his country
during his 10-year reign
was less than one year.
That's not what I mean!
I'm talking about the border
between mythology and history.
He's part of both eras...
and the final king from
a time when Mystics
like Elementals and Rune Magecraft
still openly endured.
Loxley!
You're quick. Is that
physical strengthening Magecraft?
It's not mine, though.
Did you...
take lessons in fistfighting?
It's a combination of techniques I saw
earlier in what they call "movies"...
along with my combat style!
Such mobility despite that. Amazing.
I'll be a bit more serious...
as a Lancer-class.
I'm Saber!
Nice to meet you!
I guess making do
with shallow knowledge won't work.
From here, as a Saber-class...
I shall use my sword!
I've always wanted to do this once.
Mimicking the Knight of
the Lake who defeated
his enemies with a branch he picked up...
saying, "A knight does
not die empty-handed."
Hey Brother, let me tell
you an interesting tale!
Just how crazy he was for King Arthur...
Things got so bad that he named everything
he owned after that sacred sword.
His sword, of course,
but also a knife, parchment,
even a stick that was lying about.
This sword is...
a road to glory, seeking a miracle!
A crystallization of
faith honoring that will!
Sadly enough, the noble dream...
leads to the ends unhindered by anyone!
Engraved once again...
this sword is the one and only...
Ex...
calibur!
Come on now.
That looks useful for cracking walnuts.
This much power with a tree branch, huh?
Do I pass the test?
It seems you haven't unleashed
even half of your strength.
You are strong.
Though I don't know...
what my friend would say.
Ayaka! We have safely formed an alliance!
Safely?
You guys were trying to kill each other.
Well, there are trials out in the world
that you risk your life for.
Give me a break!
Please don't be angry at him.
He was being reckless for your sake.
You know... do people say
you're terrible at reading the room?
The gods often said so.
Like when I defeated a bull.
Defeated a bull?
Can you tell me that story in detail?
What kind of bull? How and what did you—
Ow!
Please stop, Ayaka!
Ouch! Ouch!
It was my fault!
Why would you do something like that?
Why, you ask?
I understand that you're trying
to do something for someone like me...
but...
I didn't ask you to do that!
I told you, right?
I'm going to look after
you on my own will.
If you need Magical Energy,
you can use Magecraft or whatever
and turn me into a puppet!
But you trusted...
someone like me.
I appreciate what you did. I do. But...
I'm not worthy of something like that.
I don't deserve to be
protected by someone...
or to be trusted.
Hey, do you know about Little Red Riding
Hood of the Semina Apartments?
A married couple and a girl
moved in next to Mr. A.
The girl was being abused
and always hid her wounds with a red hood.
That girl had been asking Mr. A
at the elevator...
"Hey, can you push the button?"
One day, that family
attempted murder-suicide.
The girl sought help,
but Mr. A ignored her,
thinking it had nothing to do with him.
From the day the girl went missing,
the sound of someone knocking
on the door echoed around.
When Mr. A finally opened that door...
Hey, can you push the button?
"HEY, CAN YOU PUSH THE BUTTON?"
I heard that's based on an incident
that actually happened.
What happened in the end again?
Didn't they end up missing?
STOP
I've heard an ending
that they fled overseas.
Maybe they're still running away
from Little Red Riding Hood to this day!
You're being so kind to me like this...
but I'm sure I'll betray others again.
I might sell you to the
enemy and flee by myself!
You might sell me to the enemy?
Ayaka, you really do worry
about the little things.
Little things?
It happens often.
I was almost sold off to Rome
by my own little brother.
That... has nothing to do with me!
It does involve you!
I have lived a life where it's no longer
a surprise for anyone to betray me.
Can it be...
that you have mistaken me for a good man?
I don't know.
Besides, what you have done doesn't...
War.
That was all I could do.
People forming an alliance with us
shouldn't be making such solemn faces.
If you'd like, have some, too.
Wh-Why is she here?
You lot...
will defeat the monster?
If it harms people!
Lionheart, I have heard about you.
How you fought such monsters
together with one of our leaders. And...
what a terrifying man you used to be.
My objective differs from you.
However, I must defeat that monster first.
Then, it's a temporary ceasefire.
Actually, there is a monster
I want to rid from this city, as well.
The monster you speak of seems
even more troublesome than Dead Apostles.
That's not necessarily true.
For now, it's just a black curse
and a dark brown clump of mud.
If those two fused together
and seeped into the Holy Grail...
this planet itself might be
in a little bit of danger.
It seems my friend has found
a good partner to warm up with.
Tiné, work up plenty of
Magical Energy for now.
Even I can't imagine just how much
I will be spending from hereon out.
Please use your powers
as much as you wish.
Even if my body were to perish.
Don't speak of such nonsense.
If you are worried
that the cavalry girl made light of you...
that is called "audacity."
No matter your resolve,
when faced with a powerful opponent,
a child is still a child.
However...
I am the leader of the
guardians of this land.
I obtained my power by
sacrificing the lives
of my 12 elder brothers
and nine elder sisters...
as well as my own body.
This life exists only to regain Snowfield,
which is the earnest wish of my clan.
When opposing a proud warrior,
they will respect and fight you
regardless of age or appearance.
However, though you may
have gathered your resolve,
I can't quite say you are a proud one yet.
Those who lack self-esteem
will lack it even in old age.
Self-esteem, you say?
On that point, you are fortunate!
Even if temporary,
you are one of my subjects.
In a few days, the fact
that you were able to sear
my glory into memory will
be something to be proud of!
Yes!
There's no doubt about it.
Her hair color is different,
but that is Ayaka Sajyou.
I informed you the other day, right?
That someone who is on-site
has seen one of your apprentices, Lord.
And by that, you didn't mean Flat?
We meant her.
It's true that Sajyou was a part
of my class for about a month.
No...
it's faster to confirm
it with her directly.
Let's confirm the directive!
For now, we will form an alliance until
the three threats have been dealt with.
Is that fine?
Right.
My top priority is still
the safety of my Master,
so I can't move out of
this forest just yet.
Then I would like to find
a base with some bedding.
For that, I know of a place.
The spot where I was summoned.
Oh!
Ayaka should be able to rest here!
Phew, I'm so glad! Rest is important!
Saber... You know...
Someone's here.
What?
Ayaka! Head to a place where you can hide!
Huh? H-Hold on!
Run for it!
If you stay here—
Why do you stop me?
This guy told Ayaka to run for it.
We might be able to talk
it out with him, right?
I'm a Saber-class Servant.
Nice meeting you!
For now...
can you listen to what we have to say?
This over here is my
Master... well, not quite.
Huh?
Ayaka?
Are you going to seriously look for it?
This so-called fortune of King Arthur?
Of course!
As long as I find something,
I don't care what.
It would be the best
if that was Excalibur!
Hey there, amusing, pleasant folks!
You jumped right into the trap
I set up without any doubt!
My utmost respect for you lot
who came all the way here!
Who are you?
Thank you for asking!
My name is Saint Germain.
I am your guide, your advisor...
your prophet...
and a simple con man.
Amusing.
What kind of fantasy will
you deceive me with?
My hat's off to the great future king.
However, I am not the one
who will deceive you.
Faced with the numerous Mystics
that created King Arthur...
you will attempt to deceive yourself.
My eternal regards to the you
within the depths of your eyes, as well.
You're finally up.
Do you hurt anywhere?
Saber, do you like King Arthur?
Ayaka, are you also a fan of King Arthur?
I think King Arthur's great, too!
That's not what I meant.
Oh, I see.
It's not dawn yet. You
should rest a bit more.
You know...
sorry about earlier.
Was there something
you need to apologize for?
Well... how I yelled, pulled your hair,
shoved my selfishness at you...
all sorts of stuff.
Such trivial things.
No, I should apologize, too.
I didn't think about your feelings and
revealed my name without permission
and asked for an alliance.
You don't need to apologize about that!
Whatever you do, I won't say
it's none of your business anymore.
But, at the least, tell me
if you're doing something dangerous.
I'd like to at least try to stop you.
And I'd be troubled if you died on your
own and I couldn't tell you "Thank you."
Right. I have always troubled someone.
I don't know your "always."
And that's not what I mean.
This is me being selfish, too.
All good?
Who is it?
My husband is acting weird!
He's saying how he's not
going to leave the city!
Oh? I thought you already clocked out.
I'm sorry. I forgot something!
I see. Be careful.
All sorts of things are happening lately.
But good things have happened, too.
Tsubaki's condition is very stable today.
I'm worried about that scar on her hand
that looks like a tattoo, though.
Oh?
Mr. Jack...
This was the source of
the black fog after all.
Yes. Now I can feel it for myself.
You are a superb Mage.
But... I think we should
head back for now.
It was a fog up until now,
but that's a waterfall.
It's in a different league!
Why don't we use a bomb
on the entire hospital—
Y-You can't do something like that!
We don't even know
if that Master is friend or foe!
Right.
Let's reorganize for now.
Okay!
If I went through with it...
I would no longer be a murderer...
but something else.
Just now, someone...
no...
something visited.
EPISODE 6