In the near future, e-Pulse is
generated by human thoughts and emotions,
and used as an energy source
for AI devices called "Sapotamas,"
leading to a new development for humanity.
But from its shadows,
terrifying monsters have appeared.
Monsters that evolve by consuming e-Pulse.
They are...
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
Beyond where no one can stop me
darenimo jama wa sasenai sono saki he
I'll make my way there
As I seek the answer
mayoinagara kotae sagashi tsukisusumu
Carve your emotion
kizamitsukero Emotion
It reverberates
hibiiteiru
The tempo that synchs
tashika ni shinkurosuru Tempo wa
Is a pulse that slowly reveals
The hidden world
sukoshi zutsu
kakureta sekai abaiteiku hakudou
Record on top of the solid Baseline
yuraganai Baseline no ue de Rec
Don't mess up tempo
Normal's not enough for me
futsuu ja monotarinee
Just keep howling, howling!!!
Howling like it's all you've got
Even if what you believe begins to blur
shinjiru mono ga nijimisou ni natte mo
The reality that you grasp
Rings strong and true
nigirishimeru Riaru wa
uso janaku tsuyoku hibiku
Take away the Metronome
For this one and only JAM
Metronome topparau ichido kiri kono JAM
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
The emotional beat that rings out
kanjou no mama narasu kodou wa
Is the BPM that continues on and on
sou zutto hashiritsuzukeru BPM
(Let the beat lead the way)
The Cloudy rain swallows the city
matenrou nomikomu Cloudy Rain
Even if I link and the rhythm warps
I just make it part of my groove
rinkushite rizumu yoretatte
Groove ni shichaeba ii
Ride it like you see fit
norikonase omoidoori
(Let the beat lead the way)
Even if it hurts, I won't stop
itami daite mo tomarazu ni
Keep carving the beat
Won't back down
kizami tsudzukeru kodou
We can overcome anything
bokura nara donna koto mo norikoerareru
Drum to your emotion
tatakitsukero Emotion
Get back here!
Darn it!
Huh?
Stop, ya know!
Take this!
Let's split up!
Got it!
The target's heading for Third Street.
The Glowing Dawn's nosing around there.
Hurry up.
Paralyze...
Water Screw!
Chiropmon!
You're... from Tactics...
I guess we have the same target.
Not that I'd ever care
about your little team!
Take this!
You won't escape!
Oh no!
Looks like we won.
Your choice of targets is poor.
That's why you let it slip through your...
Thank goodness it didn't hit you.
Huh?
Sister?
You're right! It's Hotaruko!
ANTIPATHY
Please take this.
I've handed over the Sapotama.
Roger. I've secured the Owner.
Go on ahead.
I need to check up on something.
Check up on?
You better not have messed something up.
Of course not.
I won't cause any of you trouble.
See you.
It's adorable!
Is this a doll? A robot?
Uh, it's an AI robot
with the latest protection functions.
I-I am Chiropmon.
So that's why it saved us!
Thank you, Chiropmon!
You two.
Let's go home.
Aww!
We still wanna talk!
He's your coworker, isn't he?
You told us that you've got
"capable colleagues," right?
You're a "career woman" after all!
C-Career woman?
Um, I'm...
That's right! He's my capable colleague
who works with me at the World Union!
The World Union?!
His name is...
M-Makoto Kuonji.
Makoto!
I'm Kou Kanuma!
I'm Ao Kanuma!
Thank you for saving them earlier.
Here. I'll make it up to you
some other time.
Uh, r-right.
-No! Makoto's coming home with us!
-Huh?
-We're having dinner together!
Our home's an okonomiyaki shop!
It's really yummy!
What an unbelievable blunder.
OKONOMIYAKI KANUMA
So... what the heck is going on?
Wow!
Fluffy!
Why is a Tactics member
feeding us okonomiyaki?
And the stuff about a cover story?
Sorry.
Chiropmon, what's tomorrow's weather?
S-Sunny.
Hey. Doesn't this one talk?
Help me.
Both of you.
No playing during meals.
Give those back and go on upstairs.
Okay.
Makocchan's filled us in on the details.
If you want to thank us
for helping your family,
how about you stop getting in our way?
Your mochi and cheese okonomiyaki.
We're just doing our job.
Don't blame us for your lack of skill.
Enough. Stop being disagreeable
in front of your friends.
Mother...
Here's your seafood okonomiyaki.
I'm so glad.
Hotaruko's never
brought friends home before.
Mother, please!
They're not my friends, they're...
I know. They're colleagues
from the World Union, right?
You're all so very young.
Is Hotaruko getting along at work?
I know she graduated college
by skipping grades,
but she was always focused
on studying, so I worry...
Skipping grades?
She said she'd become a researcher,
but she never comes home.
That's enough about me!
Hotaruko, check it out!
Ta-da! Our new running shoes!
We won a race with them!
They look good on you two.
If you ever need anything else, just ask.
Okay!
Thank you, Hotaruko!
Thank you!
You really get along.
I'm kind of jealous.
Huh?! Hey!
Is something wrong?
N-No, I'm fine.
Tomoro's plate's already empty.
That's fast!
No, it must be the food thief!
You're right!
Food thief?
Lately, ingredients keep vanishing
from our pantry.
It's happened to all the local stores.
Maybe there's a big rat or something.
Don't talk about rats, Mother.
Man, I'm stuffed!
So she hasn't told her family
that she's a Cleaner.
She's got her reasons.
We got a load of food out of it,
so who cares?
That okomoyaki was yummy!
That's "okonomiyaki."
Keep an eye on your Digimon!
Are you three still in the downtown area?
What is it, Kyo?
I know it's sudden,
but I've got a job for you.
There's been a rash of food theft
in the homes and shops in that area.
According to investigations,
the culprit is a Digimon.
It seems to be a stray Digimon
with no Owner.
It's going after food instead of e-Pulse.
We don't know why.
Got it. We'll check it out.
What now?
Let's ask around first.
Someone stealing food...
It must be the food thief!
It's happened to all the local stores.
Makocchan?
Hey! Wait!
Sorry! I'll catch up with you later!
Hotaruko.
Mother.
I'll finish up the rest. Go on upstairs.
You're not staying the night?
A career woman has a busy life.
You don't have to send money, you know.
You worry too much, Mother.
I want to send money.
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Come home when you have time.
Sure. Thanks.
Shouldn't you tell them?
It'll just complicate things.
Getting kicked out of school because of
the accident that birthed you...
Not coming home
because of Tactics rules...
It's too much for Mother to handle.
You can't hide it forever.
Mother?
What?
Is it the food thief?
I'll check it out.
Shakomon?!
Hotaruko!
What's that?
I'm Burgamon.
Shakomon!
That food!
So that Digimon's the food thief!
Lots of e-Pulse!
This yummy food's all mine!
Get back here!
Paralyze Echo!
Green Pickles!
OKONOMIYAKI KANUMA
Thanks a bunch!
Hotaruko?
What a racket, are you okay?
Let's go!
Okay.
No trace of Burgamon.
There's nothing at all?
That's abnormally fast.
Maybe it took a vehicle or something?
Perhaps...
I thought it was strange.
How did they remain hidden
in such a crowded residential area?
If they used a boat at night
to carry all the food they stole...
Then it's headed for...
the ocean!
Yes... Yes...
I see. I understand.
Yes. Please meet up with us.
Any luck?
No traces of it nearby.
Don't worry.
Huh?
Chiropmon is looking for them.
We'll find Shakomon in no time.
You're more capable than I thought.
And you're a lot nicer than I thought.
Is that a compliment?
Of course it is.
You work hard
and send money to your family.
That's very impressive.
We're supposed to be enemies.
Why do all this for me?
You acted without asking.
That's...
I used to live in the Shangri-La Egg
until a little while ago.
What?
A lot happened and I ran away.
It was Kyo and Reina who helped me.
That's why if I ever see anyone in need
I want to help them.
I suppose I'm not
all that much help, though.
But I've got friends I can count on now.
Makoto. Found them.
Thank you, Chiropmon.
Let's go, Hotaruko!
Here!
I sense Burgamon inside.
I've brought more servings!
There!
It's Burgamon and...
What's that?
More servings!
What's that?!
A Burpmon.
Digimon with large appetites
become like that when they eat too much.
Been a while since a feast like this!
Shakomon!
Three!
Two!
One!
Supreme e-Pulse for me!
This is new.
Burpmon's e-Pulse
is flowing into Burgamon.
What?!
They have a symbiotic relationship!
So Burgamon was stealing food
to feed to Burpmon.
Chiropmon!
Here goes!
Fly!
Chiropmon Evolution!
Nightchiropmon!
Giant Rang!
Huh?!
A bone?!
More servings!
Delicious e-Pulse.
More! More! More!
Delicious Patty!
No escaping!
Nightchiropmon!
It's no good. Not with two against one.
If I can hold out
until Tomoro and Reina get here...
You need your friends to save you?
What?
There. That soft attitude.
I despise that.
Wake up, Shakomon!
W-What's going on?!
I'm sorry, Hotaruko!
I embarrassed myself as your partner!
Forget it! Make up for it
by doing your job!
Hunt them all down!
Shakomon Evolution!
Tylomon!
Delicious Patty!
Torpedo Attack!
Amazing!
Huh? Where are we?
I'll make it quick.
We're sorry! We're sorry!
Wait a minute!
They've given up!
So?!
They're bounties. We're Cleaners.
We have one job.
But deleting them...
I've had it with you!
You pity others
and you deign to lend a hand of mercy!
That sense of superiority makes me sick!
You were born with everything
and yet you strive for nothing!
You're so willing
to trust others with your life!
I won't lose to you!
The only one I trust is myself!
Torpedo Attack!
Consider my debt repaid.
I won't hold back next time.
Sorry we're late!
So? Where's the bounty?
I'm sorry. I only have
their In-Training forms.
Seriously?! Then we can't cash the bounty!
Is something wrong?
No. I'm fine.
Hotaruko?!
Makoto?
Thank you for cleaning up with me.
It's nothing.
Hotaruko was busy with work.
OKONOMIYAKI KANUMA
If you'll excuse me.
Makoto.
Look after Hotaruko for me.
Let me know if anything happens.
She always tries to do everything herself.
Makoto?
Don't let the normal be normal
atarimae wo atarimae ni shinai
Playing to the score is not enough
gakufu doori ja monotarinaindayo
Take in everything, even the noise
And make it our own session!
noizu sura mo torikonde
jibun dake no sesshon wo!
Things won't change in others' hands
Boot! Boot!
hitomakase ja kawaranaishi
Reach out your hand
te nobase
Don't be scared to mess up, go on
Boot! Boot!
machigai mo osorezu susume
With courage
yuukan ni
Go tell the rules NO
Error, error
ruuru ni tatakitsukeru NO
error, error
Scale out? Bring it on
Error, error
sukeeru auto joutou
error, error
An unexpected code
Error, error
yosoku funou no koodo
error, error
Prompts can't control these feelings
puronpto nanka ja seigyoudekinai omoide
Give it a shout
kamase shauto
BRAVE! No more fear
BRAVE! mou kowakunai
Keep my head high
utsumuitari mo shinai
I've got someone who's got my back
senaka azukeaeru kimi ga iru kara
GROOVE! We can't be stopped
GROOVE! mou tomaranai
Our beats are in unison
yunizon suru koudou ga
We're going to update the world
kitto sekaijuu wo appudeeto shiteiku
With a bang
bakuon de
A Digimon with a special skill,
and a mysterious Owner...
Who are these guys?
They are a little suspicious.
Thinking about difficult things
doesn't suit you, ya know?
True. If you're free,
then go catch some fish.
All right...
We lost our food to make stew, too...
Next time on DIGIMON BEATBREAK,
"The Price of Freedom"