Let my feelings reach her!
.44 Magnum!
Sh-She's strong.
I think we may have ended up
helping our enemy.
I-I love you...
Shut up!
I love you! I love you!
I love...
The way I feel about you...
is totally love!
Fine.
I-I'll try to keep this short, then...
Ba-bump...
You're too damn old!
It's never gonna happen! Ever!
I-I'll leave it at that for today!
N-Next time you die!
No!
Kill...
Kill me! Just freakin' kill me!
Why don't you try to kill us,
you damn Shocker combatant?!
Y-You're on!
This will be a battle royale!
Okay.
Rider...
Transform! V3!
Transformation!
Kamen Rider!
Let's go!
.44...
V3...
Rider...
Magnum!
Electric Heat Chop!
Punch!
What the hell?
Ichiyo! There's trouble!
Shocker is on the move!
What?!
SHOCKER IS ON THE MOVE
All right, let's move out!
Right!
They're all beat to hell.
Are they gonna be able to
fight Shocker like this?
FUTABA'S PUB
So, what did you mean about
Shocker being on the move?
It's just like I told you
before, Tojima-san.
The Bat Man, under
the alias of Koda Morio,
seems to have a lot of influence
in show business.
He's been hosting a variety of events,
and every time, he converts
the audience into combatants.
Yeah, he tells all the guys who attend...
"If you join Shocker right now,
you'll all get girlfriends!"
"And they'll all be idols!"
Can you believe it?
Bastard plays dirty.
Idols, though?
I'd probably be on the fence
if I didn't have Raiko!
You're already part of Shocker.
Go on.
This is the important part.
At the end of the week, there's
going to be a Combat Girls solo concert
held at the Tokyo Central Dome.
With a capacity of 55,000 people...
It has the potential to be their
biggest recruitment drive so far.
Then what should we do?!
Look at this.
What is it?
Plans for the concert that
Yukarisu and I dug up.
With it, we'll have all the intel we need
to infiltrate the venue
and thwart his plan.
Well done, Mitsuba!
Right!
Praise me, too!
Yuriko-san?!
Tackle!
What are you doing here?!
I gave her a call.
She showed up at school,
so I figured she was back on her feet.
How are your injuries?
Are you healed already?
Can't you tell?
Weren't you one of the Shocker robbers?
What are you doing here?
A lot's happened since then.
I'm here to avenge my guys.
I'll be joining you
when you take down Shocker!
Anyway, Yuriko-san,
I'm relieved that you're doing better!
Thank you.
Now, I have to ask...
Where do you get off trying to put
forward a plan without Tackle?!
Well, we didn't...
Kamen Rider Stronger, episode 35!
Who came to Stronger's rescue
as he was being brutalized
by the Delza Army's Snake Woman?
Yes, Ichiyo-kun?!
It was V3.
In the follow-up, episode 36,
Kamen Riders X and Amazon showed up.
And in episode 37, after that...
Riderman came to their rescue!
And then in episode 38!
Kamen Riders 1 and 2 made their
long-awaited return to Japan!
The assemblage of seven Riders
all worked together,
in order to confront
the giant Rock Great Leader!
Yeah!
They were roused when Stronger said
that "all Kamen Riders are brothers,"
and then joined hands,
gathering their energy,
then got the Rock Great Leader
on the ropes!
And in the end...
The seven Kamen Riders brought
an end to their long, long battle.
What have you guys been blabbing about?
Tackle wasn't there, though.
Ultra Cyclone!
But I won't let this end the same way.
I am Tackle II!
And I'll be joining you.
Of course!
You won the tournament, after all!
We'd be in real trouble
without you, Sensei!
When confronted with a powerful enemy...
What do Kamen Riders do?
Work together!
We're taking Shocker down!
It's her!
Hey—
It's on the house.
Sis...
Free stuff from you?
What in the world has gotten—
Th-Thank you.
Idiot.
Who are—
Hey.
I'm counting on you.
Right!
So, everyone, let's get to
work on the plan...
Wait, let's have a toast first! We gotta!
To celebrate Sensei feeling better,
and all of us getting together!
Good point.
FUTABA'S PUB
Cheers!
More!
All right.
What the hell is he doing?
And at such a critical time...
Who are you supposed to be?
Me? I'm Hakkyoku Hachiro.
I didn't ask your damn name!
So, what are the two of you up to?
He's been training me.
Training you?!
Did you see that?
See what?!
And why the hell did you fall over?!
He's just a human!
This man, while battling against himself,
mastered the style of Bajiquan.
He then fought as
an underground street fighter,
until he ran out of opponents,
and now he's battling with ramen in
an effort to satisfy the woman he loves.
What are you trying to—
Humans are fascinating, Bat.
As I've been fighting him,
I've come to understand something.
Humans seem to have
something like a core.
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Rider Punch!
And the humans who possess
unbreakable cores...
are capable of unleashing superhuman
potential in whatever their specialty is.
Bat.
I wouldn't underestimate humans
if I were you.
If you're serious about
doing something major...
Then you'd better not let your guard down.
Screw you...
There's no way any monster
could lose to a puny human!
Oh, are you a friend of Kumota-san's?
Would you like to join us for ramen?
You wanna die, piggy?!
I can hardly stand living around
these damn humans anymore.
You wanna talk about cores?
Then my core...
is rage!
Are we all set?
Ready!
Just you wait, Shocker!
We will defeat you.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Time to get underway.
FUTABA'S PUB
According to the schedule we found,
during the climax of the show...
when excitement reaches its peak,
the Bat Man will make his appearance.
The Combat Girls and other idols
working as backup dancers
will then convert the audience
into Shocker combatants.
Our goal is to stop that from happening.
But our real priority...
is ensuring the safety
of everyone attending the show.
Fifty-five thousand people
will be in the audience.
First, we need to figure out
a way to evacuate them all.
We can engage Shocker
in battle, afterward.
For our point of entry,
Yukarisu and Nakao-san can pretend
to be Shocker delivery people
and smuggle us in.
Once we're inside the service entrance,
we'll take our individual positions.
Ichiyo, you and Tojima-san will be
on standby on the roof.
It's likely we'll need to start fighting
as soon as the plan gets underway.
I'd like you two to wait for the signal.
We're up against Shocker.
There's no telling what kind of
unexpected trouble we'll run into.
If that happens, we'll have to use
our individual judgment to deal with it.
Hey, you two.
Stop.
What's inside those cases?
W-Well, seems to be
additional pyrotechnics
for the second half of the concert.
It's like, hey, maybe order
the right amount to start!
You hear about this?
Sure didn't.
That's suspicious.
Just to be safe, we're going to
check the contents of—
Could you guys let Master Bat Man know,
these last-second orders are real—
—Yeee—
—tough to pull off.
He's so right! But since it's for
our beloved Master Bat Man, w—
—Yeee—
—don't mind putting in extra effort!
All right, then. Go on.
Cop-yeee that!
That was a close one.
Huh? If it isn't Aniki.
It's been a while, Aniki.
Well, lately, you've
been kinda down, Aniki.
So, we were thinking about
taking you to a show!
Who's your favorite?
You'd be pretty lucky
to have three wives, Aniki!
A...
...ni...
...ki...
Y-You guys...
You're alive!
Hang on. I think they're...
How? My boys...
But... you're alive!
I'm so... so relieved!
I'm curious, though, Aniki.
What are you doing here?
This is the venue for a concert
that Master Bat Man is hosting.
Master...?
You wouldn't be trying to...
...disrupt Shocker's plan, would you?
It can't be... are you all...?
Whoa!
Aniki. We're all...
...members of Shocker now, too.
And anyone who would defy us...
...must die.
NEXT EPISODE
LET'S DO THIS,
SHOCKER!
LET'S DO THIS, SHOCKER!
ILLUSTRATED BY: MIKIHIKO TABATA