You did well, Xylo.
Allow me to praise you as well.
Xylo Forbartz.
Let's talk about what happened
after you defeated Demon Lord Iblis.
I'm not in the mood for
all that politicking crap.
No, I'd like you to hear this.
I need you to, in fact.
Bring that over here!
S'more where that came from!
Everything's fresh!
Get it moving.
As such, you and Goddess Teoritta...
have officially been allotted to
my Thirteenth Order of Holy Knights.
"Allotted to"?
What are we, equipment?
The military and the Temple
are still debating
Goddess Teoritta's
questionable standing,
but your incredible accomplishments
at the fortress have caused a sea change.
Xylo. I want you to continue
protecting Goddess Teoritta.
If you want me to protect her...
We haven't had a single day off in ages.
Take us off the front lines.
That was already the plan.
Yeah?
I'm assigning your hero unit to protect
Goddess Teoritta, here in Port City Ioff.
You're saying this city's more dangerous
than the battlefield?
Your assessment is correct.
A group of heretics
expelled from the Temple
are refusing to accept this new goddess.
They've joined with a religious order
of assassins and intend to do her—
Enough. You can fill me in later.
Xylo.
You shall protect me.
We and the heroes...
We have time off, Xylo!
I hear you've put down
a few Demon Blights, Xylo.
Oh. Hey, Jayce.
I heard about those
three Demon Lords you dealt with.
It sounded like Dotta and Norgalle
did most of the work,
but I'm willing to accept
that Iblis was all you.
I got two, though.
You're not inflating those numbers?
Rhyno was on the western front with you.
He was being insubordinate again.
He'll be in a cell for a while.
A prison cell for a penal hero, huh?
Either way, I've taken down two to your one.
That means I win, loser.
I-I beg your pardon?
Xylo is my knight.
You will not malign him so.
So you're the goddess?
I hear Dotta found you.
Must be nice to have
a kid to keep you safe.
Th-The sheer insolence!
I have never experienced
such a total lack of respect!
Don't bother. He won't change
just because you get mad with him.
And Dotta didn't find her. He stole her.
From the Holy Knights.
Same thing, if you ask me.
Like I give a damn
about human legalities.
Now, pony up. I gotta get back
before Neely starts sulking.
Give my best to Neely.
Xylo! What is wrong with that man?
That's Jayce. He's our unit's dragoon.
He's an idiot who grew and sold
illegal substances for dragons.
They made him a hero for that?
That and insurrection.
They say he went against the military
in hopes of freeing their dragons.
Normally, they would've had him
in custody in a day,
but he's from a big-name noble family,
and dragons love the guy.
It became a big enough deal
they named it: "Jayce's Revolt."
Heroes truly are an eccentric bunch.
If I may...
L-Let's keep a cool head, Xylo. Please.
W-Wait a minute. If the Mastibolt cavalry
hadn't showed up when they did,
it would've been much worse,
don't you agree?
Yup. That's why I'm only hitting you twice.
Xylo! Violence is not the answer!
I disagree. There's still something
he's not telling us.
Th-That's not true.
W-Well, Frenci may have said
she wanted to speak with you,
and that she'd kill me if I didn't
make it happen right away...
Frenci? Who might that be?
My former fiancée.
You're in an awful state, Xylo.
What's wrong with you? Sit down at once.
You haven't grown in the slightest.
You were on the level of a fly before,
but now, you're like a caterpillar.
A grave situation.
Think you could be less insulting
with your comparisons?
Oh? Do flat-landers consider
that expression insulting?
I am merely encouraging you
to behave in a way
that befits a future member
of the Mastibolt family.
I guess it's a cultural difference.
I'll revise my thinking.
I did not mean to cause offense.
So this is the goddess in question?
Don't glare at her. You'll scare her.
I-I am not afraid of her.
I am a goddess, you know.
Nor should you be. I am not glaring.
Frenci was your name, yes?
What precisely is your relationship
to my knight, Xylo?
I told you that earlier.
She's my former fiancée.
"Former" is inaccurate.
Our oath remains intact, Xylo.
Oh, come on. I'm a hero, remember?
I don't have the right to get married.
Legally, I'm not even considered human.
Frenci, was it?
This man is a hero and my knight.
He has devoted his life
to offering me reverence and praise.
Therefore, I regret to inform you...
He cannot be married!
Xylo, another curious creature
has taken to you.
I'm reminded of the time my father's
long-eared armadillo took a liking to you.
Yeah, while it scratched you.
Only because that western merchant—
W-Wait one moment! It is unfair to recount
your shared history in my presence.
And it is the height of disrespect
to compare a goddess to an animal.
Regardless, I am attempting
to arrange a pardon for you.
Wait a minute. I—
I will remain in this city for some time.
You see...
I must locate the Demon Blight.
What do you mean by that?
How it sounds.
About one month ago,
the night-gaunt chiefs and I embarked
on maneuvers to track a Demon Blight.
But a few days ago, their entire force
disappeared in the vicinity of this town.
Disappeared?
Yes. Demon Blight
Number Fifty-Nine: "Spriggan."
I believe...
it has disguised itself as a human.
A Demon Lord disguised
as a human? Spriggan?
A rare ability among Demon Lords.
Damn. That's a real headache.
It may already have infiltrated the city.
Be careful.
The creature has already laid waste
to one of our territories.
This concludes our discussion. However...
May I ask who is eavesdropping over there?
Oh, I didn't intend...
It's a rule. As their supervisor, I must
monitor interactions with the heroes.
I see. I will be leaving, then.
I advise you to come up
with a better excuse next time.
I very much wish to go.
Venetim and Dotta told me all about it.
The west and north sides of the city
are full of rare goods,
and all of the food is free.
It's only free for
that sticky-fingered Dotta.
And we're not going sightseeing.
We're trying to lure out those Temple
heretics after you and arrest them.
Yes, we are. I am well aware.
Just a bit of advice:
Don't tell anyone about that Holy Sword.
If those Galtuile bastards find out
about it, our lives will get a lot harder.
Worry not.
I am a goddess. I know just what to do.
I'll accompany you in town.
I'll be the goddess's sword and shield
should anything happen.
Now, the question is...
Who else to bring?
Venetim's no use as a bodyguard.
I can't let Dotta stroll
around town without shackles.
His Majesty will make a fuss about
how he himself needs bodyguards.
As for Tatsuya...
It's best we keep him out of the public eye.
Not a lot of options to choose from.
Those morons expect me
to keep Neely in here?
I'm at least gonna give her room
to spread her wings and tail.
You know, Jayce...
I have some important commander
work to get on with. May I go yet?
Who's the most powerful
force in this unit?
You and Neely, of course.
So do what it takes
to keep it in fighting form.
And shut your mouth, conman.
Just hold on a little longer, Neely.
I'll make you a really nice bed soon.
Oh, those other dragons?
I was just measuring them, you know.
I wasn't peeking under
their wings or anything.
I wasn't. I swear.
Have I ever lied to you, Neely?
This could go on a while.
Wait! Wait!
She asked me to do it.
I didn't have a choice.
Just one option left.
Man, lemme tell you!
Those guys are the worst!
Gwen Mohsa calls itself
a religious order, right?
But they raised me, and even I thought
those guys were pure evil.
We're talking human sacrifice,
offering kids to the goddesses...
Then there's "Holy Communion," which—
Stop now.
'Kay.
If he's going to go on like that,
why did we bother with disguises?
Speaking of...
Yours is excellent.
I wasn't expecting you to dress as a man.
It's the perfect bodyguard guise.
Look, Xylo.
Let us buy a keepsake.
To remember this day.
Remember what, exactly?
How a great goddess
and her equally great knight
toured a city's streets together
for the first time.
Oh, for that, huh?
So what do you want?
You must join me in choosing.
It is for both of us, after all.
This fabric, perhaps?
Does it not shimmer in the light?
That must've been brought
from the west, across Korio Bay.
Lots of odd knickknacks here.
And what about this bracelet?
Do you not think it would suit me?
Looks like jade. You could buy
a house for that money.
We'd better keep Dotta away from here.
I did not ask the price.
Nor does this concern Dotta.
Tsav. If you were the assassin,
what would you do here?
I'd probably mix in with the crowd.
A quick slash as I walked past.
Xylo! You must listen to me.
I wish you to choose our keepsake.
Fine.
Well, even I can judge
the quality of these.
Knives?
Maybe not. Giving weapons
to children is too dangerous.
You shall teach me to wield it.
Pick one now.
In that case...
How about this one?
Excellent. It is beautiful.
I'll take this.
This one, too.
Can I pay with scrip?
Teoritta. Use this if it comes to it.
What?
Oh, hey. Sweet gear.
Xylo, swap to the alternate route!
Right.
Let's go, Teoritta.
H-Has it begun?
Sorry. We'll do our sightseeing this way.
What's going on here? Why aren't
the Holy Knights here to meet us?
This isn't good.
Something must have happened.
Those guys back there weren't
religious order assassins.
Didn't seem like they'd had
any real training.
They could be allies of the Demon Blight.
Coexisters, huh?
One way or another, it's someone
who benefits from the goddess's death.
I didn't think they'd infiltrated
the military, but...
Freaky!
Who the hell are you?
She's got nasty tricks, bro.
This freakin' hurts.
Xylo. What should I...
Stay back. We'll deal with this quickly.
Don't!
A seal compound?
Take this.
Can you keep going?
Who do you think you're talking to?
Be quiet and focus.
That's enough, Shiji Bau.
You're fighting the penal hero
who accompanies a goddess.
Your chance of victory
is one in a thousand.
It's time to withdraw.
Did you hear me, Shiji Bau?
You rank amateur.
You're not supposed to
blurt out my name, Boojum.
Oh, I see. I didn't realize.
I don't know how things work
in this business.
I hope you'll continue instructing me
as the more experienc—
Sir, hurry! Before the Holy Knights arrive!
Quiet.
I'm talking to Shiji Bau.
It's rude to interrupt.
Did you forget being told
to avoid unnecessary killing as well?
Killing?
I didn't kill him.
That would be mean.
You still ripped off his jaw.
You're a ridiculous person,
from start to finish.
Kivia!
Niskeph!
Don't fire your lightning staves.
Getting shot in the back hurts a little.
Would you be the infamous
penal hero, Xylo Forbartz?
Your name is Boojum, huh?
Were you in a circus troupe at some point?
No.
You're an excellent
knife-thrower, though.
You'd fit in well at the circus yourself.
Yeah, I performed in one for three years.
The flying trapeze was my specialty.
Oh? That explains it, then.
I can say without exaggeration
that you're the best I've ever seen.
You have my respect.
Boojum. Watch your mouth.
Don't give them extra information.
Oh, right. That makes sense.
I'm learning a lot today.
This ain't good.
That woman, Shiji Bau,
is a famous adventurer.
I bet she's got a better kill rate
on her hits than you.
Probably. I'm such
a sweet li'l softie, after all.
Xylo. Shall I call the rain of swords?
Better not.
But I could—
I know how painful it is
for a goddess to hurt a human.
But something is wrong.
I have the strangest feeling...
Bro, we got incoming.
Yeah, just in time.
H-Help!
Hey.
We came to this cramped little place
like you asked.
You'd better show Neely some gratitude.
Right. Thanks, Neely.
Thanks a bunch, Big Sis Neely!
Neely, you're so kind.
We'll get a real day off soon.
Let's fly out over the sea tomorrow.
I see.
Dragon flames are a challenge to endure.
I don't have enough blood.
This was educational.
I'll be going now.
What was that guy made of?
After being burned by Neely's flame...
Teoritta.
What were you about to say
about that hunchbacked man?
It is difficult to describe.
But for some reason, I felt very little
hesitation over attacking him.
It is possible the man
we just saw was Spriggan.
Sentenced to Be a Hero