Thanks to support from the hero unit
and the dragoon's attack,
we were able to repel the assassins,
but the Holy Knight network
we set up was shredded,
and close to half of its members died.
A surprise attack designed to isolate
Goddess Teoritta and our team...
The execution was flawless.
Are you suggesting
there's a traitor in our midst?
If you can't trust your allies,
you're kind of hamstrung in a fight.
Nearly all of the snipers
I positioned were picked off.
We should limit Goddess Teoritta's
protective detail to only those we trust—
If we trust anyone.
"Those we trust" is
inherently untrustworthy.
Even those in this room
should be held under suspicion.
And there's no one we should
trust less than a penal hero.
At the very least,
this requires investigation.
Contact the Twelfth Order
of the Holy Knights.
They may specialize in intelligence,
but they don't show themselves in public.
We're basically hamstrung
if we don't know who we can trust.
You said it yourself.
I've taken all opinions into account.
I'd like the advisor who was brought in
to weigh in on this problem.
What do you think, High Priest Marlen?
Good question.
I've only just arrived
from the First Capital.
The question of who can be trusted is
of great importance. And I include myself.
But frankly, I don't know if the
intelligence unit can act on this.
How go the prisoner
interrogations, Patausche?
Not well at all.
Most of those we took alive were
adventurers with no real information.
If only we could have
brought in the assassins...
Don't take it so personally.
You place far too much responsibility
on your own shoulders.
Stewing in regret and tension
won't improve the situation.
I'll remember that, Uncle.
As stiff as ever.
Well, you wouldn't be
Patausche Kivia otherwise.
Your Eminence.
Xylo, quiet.
I believe my opinion is relevant.
If I didn't, I wouldn't dream of
interrupting a man of your high station.
Assertive tone, yet conciliatory words.
Patausche, you could learn from this man.
Y-Yes, Uncle.
Well then, Hero Xylo...
Let's hear what you have to say.
Yes, sir. First, we should look into
the adventurers' middleman agency:
the Guild.
Lideo Sodrick.
So he's the Adventurers Guild's
representative, huh?
They say his ancestor
founded a private army
to take down the pirates
plaguing Korio Bay,
and that's how the Guild
came into being.
It's a nice story, but...
It was probably just a turf war
between wannabe pirate crews.
Whatever the facts, Lideo Sodrick
is a big name in that town.
The history of the Sodrick's Shell region
and that of the Adventurers Guild
are one and the same.
Xylo.
Did things go well enough?
Huh? What do you mean?
Well, you know...
I figured they might have hit us
with a new punishment or something.
No, it was all pretty evenhanded.
I see.
Huh?
You weren't hoping to make a pass
at that sniper woman, were you?
Certainly not.
It's nothing like that. It's just...
No, never mind.
Oh, come on.
Come help me pick
a group for the mission.
I'll give you a few tips
while we're at it.
Oh, seriously. I don't need any tips.
It's really not about that.
It's really not about that at all.
I can't believe you failed.
The dragoon wasn't part of the plan.
The heroes were also far stronger
than intel led us to believe.
And that man there is an amateur.
You should take him off the job
or kill him right now.
Do you mean me?
I found Boojum in
a gambling house I oversee.
The whole place was soaked with blood.
Ten adventurers picked a fight with him,
and he killed them all stone dead.
If he's an amateur,
teach him how to be a pro.
He's just going to hold me back.
I'm requesting more money.
So claiming the enemy's too strong
is an excuse to beg for money, huh?
I see. You're trying to provoke me.
Big brother, she's a wild dog.
Her lack of a master
makes her dangerous.
Iri, stand down.
I'll be fine.
Shiji Bau. The Adventurers Guild isn't
like the military you were once part of.
If you drop out, you get no reward for completion.
I'll need three times this.
I'm going to hire my own people.
Experts.
You...
I'd also like a pay increase.
I'm going to buy another book.
I like this writer.
Altoyard Comette.
Such a brilliant poet.
Brother, do you think they can do it?
There's nothing you need to worry about.
Is someone out there?
Odd to see you up and about this early.
Did Neely kick you out of the stables?
Yup.
Neely's jealous.
She saw me with another dragon.
It wasn't even like that.
Hey, c'mon. Quit needling Jayce.
You guys take any excuse
to pick a fight with each other.
Not true.
It is true.
You're both simmering cauldrons
of rage and violence.
I wish they would put you on
different meal schedules at least.
They're heroes.
The shifty-eyed one
is Xylo Forbartz, right?
They say that psycho covered
his whole body in sacred seals.
Where's Teoritta? She isn't with you?
She's still asleep.
I also can't let her hear
what I'm about to say.
Oh, boy. You're gonna make me
do something, aren't you?
That's right.
And it'll be something
dangerous, won't it?
Something too dangerous
for Teoritta to tag along.
Hey, that's right.
Glad we're on the same page.
Oh, come on. Cheer up.
You get to walk around town
without shackles.
Like that's a good thing.
I hear Tsav got messed up bad.
His whole right arm got mangled.
Yeah. And he was lucky
it was just the one arm.
So what's the plan?
First, we infiltrate
the Adventurers Guild.
Wouldn't Rhyno be better for that?
He used to be an adventurer, right?
Not happening.
Rhyno's locked up at the moment.
And anyway, he's too unpredictable.
What about Venetim or whatever?
He went with His Majesty
to the repair shop.
Seems they finally found
a leg he could use.
But still...
If Dotta won't go, I'll step in.
I've got nothing better to do.
Huh? You mean it?
Then—
Dotta. I need your skills.
Fine.
You'd better not give Dotta a hard time.
Dotta fed his own arm to a hungry dragon.
He's an incredible person.
I'm not sure even I could
make that sacrifice.
You've got an unconventional admirer.
Let's not talk about it.
Well? What's the whole story?
How were you planning to infiltrate it?
Well, about that...
Is there a problem?
Are you about to say
I look like a man again?
No, it suits you extremely well.
You're the very image
of a young noblewoman.
The kind with no shortage of suitors.
C-Cease your flattery.
Do not expect to get on my good side
by paying me compliments.
Glad to hear it.
Now we need to figure out
what we're hiring them for.
For the Adventurers Guild,
faerie hunting seems the best option.
That's the military's job, isn't it?
What about wiping out some bandits?
Tone down the scale
of the violence a bit.
Bandit-hunting might work
if we were out in the sticks,
but this is Ioff City.
What kind of job do you recommend, then?
Let's say...
You're the wife of a noble.
And you're her paramour.
What?
Huh?
You're plotting to get
her husband killed.
Any nobles out there you want dead?
The defendant: Dotta Luzulas.
You have over a thousand
criminal acts on your record.
But you have been brought before us
today to address just one:
escaping the castle dungeon
in which you were confined,
and stealing that dragon in the process.
W-Wait a minute.
What is it?
What about him?
Isn't he part of my crime?
To whom do you refer?
The crown prince!
The crown prince?
What's he talking about?
What does His Highness
have to do with this?
That little boy asked me to save him.
It's true.
He said he'd been locked up in
the castle. That he'd run away.
I thought we could use
the dragon to escape—
Cease these lies at once.
The assertion that the crown prince
spoke to you is false.
So is the assertion that
he attempted to escape the castle.
Th-That can't be true.
I ran into him during my jailbreak.
He was definitely the First Prince
of the Federated Kingdom.
He was about ten years old,
and scared out of his wits.
He said the royal family
was acting strange.
The king had been out of sorts for
a long time. I think the chancellor—
Be silent, Dotta Luzulas.
N-No, there's something going on
with the royal family!
Why else would the crown prince
come to someone like me for help?
Just some two-bit
scumbag thief l-like me...
Be silent.
Even I have a conscience, you know?
Maybe I don't show it to everyone...
But when I see someone weaker than me,
like the prince was then...
I want to help them, like anyone would.
Th-This is all wrong.
If you won't let me help him,
someone else has to.
Please save that boy!
We can't continue the trial like this.
Lord Confessor, I believe death
would be a reasonable sentence.
Yes, I believe you're right.
But a more serious sentence
has already been approved for him.
By whom?
It was suggested by
the Central Noble Alliance.
The matter is final.
What's wrong with you?
I'll steal him next time for sure.
Dotta Luzulas.
You are being sentenced
to serve as a hero.
This is a pain in the butt,
but I've gotta do it, huh?
Hey, we've got the good stuff here.
Want a drag?
Tch. They're ignoring us.
Swine.
This is quite unpleasant.
"Dragon's Breath."
Its use has spread a lot
because of Jayce.
They're openly breaking the law.
I've been wondering.
Why did you join the military?
What do you mean?
You're from a Temple family
with a large domain.
Why put your neck on the line?
Well...
My mother and father are priests.
They carried out important duties
for the Temple,
and earned various benefits in return.
Benefits, huh?
"Noble priests," then,
cashing in on their influence and faith?
Yes. And not always in
aboveboard ways like donations.
I hated that about my parents.
So I joined the military,
hoping to make my own way.
What's that?
The first sword I ever got. For training.
My uncle bought it for me.
I wanted to secure my own future
with my own talents.
It was my uncle who supported me in that.
By the way, Xylo.
That f-fiancée of yours—
Xylo. I checked out the Guild.
That was fast. Nice work.
Almost too fast, I must say.
Security there seems pretty tight.
About twenty guards.
Less than I'd expect.
But I saw a bunch of weird kids
scattered around.
I think they're like little assassins.
Children? That's horrible.
I've heard they take in orphans and raise them
to ensure they have loyal soldiers.
Anyway!
I'm supposed to abscond with the
representative while you're in there, yes?
Not that stealing people has
ever gone particularly well for me.
Just do it.
Kivia, you're the daughter of
a wealthy noble. I'm your secret lover.
Th-That's right. Leave it to me!
That hurt.
It appears to be the penal hero,
Xylo Forbartz.
The woman with him
is clearly a Holy Knight.
Xylo Forbartz. That's very bad.
But depending on the circumstances,
if we could take him in alive...
I'll try to find a chance.
Contact Shiji Bau and the others.
Wake up Duhrsami too, just in case.
Don't let them leave here alive.
Yes, sir.
This is all for my family.
There's someone I want killed.
I'd like to request someone
with a lot of experience.
And who exactly are you?
My name is Madleen. I'd prefer
to keep my family name secret.
Do you have a reference?
Are you going to take the job or not?
Well?
Miss Madleen, we don't take jobs
from just anyone who walks in the door.
I'm sorry, miss.
The lady's quite sheltered.
She's not used to places like this.
We don't have a reference,
but we're truly desperate.
If nothing else, we'd like to get out
of the city without being traced.
So just hypothetically...
Who do you want killed?
A nobleman.
You familiar with the Hystead family,
the bridge-keepers of Ginai?
No.
We're having a bit of trouble with the
third son of one of their branch families.
I was married into the Hystead family,
but this man and I... well...
We pledged ourselves to each other
beneath a sacred hagra tree.
I wish to have my husband killed
so that I can be with this man.
E-Even if we have to run away together!
J-Just hold on one second.
This seems dangerous.
I think they suspect us.
We should report it to the master.
Yeah, I think you're right there.
Is she really a noblewoman?
This isn't good. What do we do?
Good question.
I'd say...
Let's raise hell.
What?
We'll start up some trouble
and cause confusion.
Like setting fire to rob the place.
Although it's Lideo Sodrick
we're here to steal.
Th-That's absurdly reckless.
Well, we're doing it.
We'll start with them—
You requested someone skilled, correct?
You—
Miss Renzari?
A noble lady and her paramour. Correct?
Could we use one of the rooms upstairs?
You're in an awful state, Xylo.
That's the reaction I expected.
Your stupidity is immeasurable.
If I hadn't stepped in, you would
have undoubtedly been arrested.
You're wrong. We were just
about to cause a commotion.
Yes, and in the meantime, our ally was to
sneak in and secure the evidence we need.
Are you with the Holy Knights?
Patausche Kivia, captain of the
Thirteenth Order of the Holy Knights.
I'd prefer it if you didn't indulge
my fiancé so much.
He's awkward, uneducated,
boorish, and thoughtless.
I don't need an outsider
encouraging him.
Outsider? You're the one
who's an outsider to this plan.
I am his fiancée. We must face
all of our trials together.
That's no excuse!
I had a feeling your personalities would
clash, but this is worse than I thought.
Huh? You thought our personalities...
...would clash?
Why is that the conclusion
you always seem to come to?
Have you no brain in your head?
No, it goes far beyond that.
His ability to evaluate others
is the poorest I've seen.
I agree. His observational skills
are on the level of a susubana mole.
I'd say your average tree
is smarter, in fact.
Could you please not bond
over insulting me?
We're in a serious situation here.
What are you even doing here?
I've disguised myself as
an adventurer to investigate.
I was on the verge of making
contact with Lideo Sodrick.
Sorry we got in your way.
Then again, we can always—
Excuse me, sir, ma'am.
The guildmaster would like to speak
with you about your request.
Frenci. Feel free to back out now.
Surely you jest.
The very suggestion disgusts me.
I knew it'd be easier
to make a commotion.
How appallingly ill-mannered.
You need disciplining.
Here you go.
There they are!
Kill them!
Don't let them leave here alive!
I'm seeing a lot of potential chaos here.
This wasn't how I foresaw
things going, but...
My goodness. You really are doing this.
Yup. We can smoke out Lideo Sodrick,
and clean up the town while we're at it.
What in the world?
Let's call it our civic duty.
This is terrible.
Sentenced to Be a Hero