Oh crud!
I release a poison powder
when I spread my wings!
View stats.
Myria
Earth Human
Status: Normal
Thank goodness, looks like she's okay.
Maybe because my skill
is such a low level?
N-no...
Stay away from me!
Sigh.
She's acting like the Demon King
just barged in while she was
getting robbed by bandits.
Definitely hurts a little.
Myria, it's me! Please recognize me!
You have gained 36 experience points.
Due to the effect
of the "Walking Egg" title,
you have earned an additional 36 experience points.
Oh, come on!
This is hardly the time!
Young Plague Dragon
has gone from level 39 to level 40.
Please, just shut up for a second! I'm begging you!
You have maxed out your level.
Huh? Eh?
You have met the requirements for evolution.
I said shut up, you damn voice!
Huh?
R-rooarr!
Roarr!
Rar. Rar. Rarr!
Could she be...
imitating what I did back then?
Raarr! Roar rarr rarr!
Roaar! Rar rarr!
Roaarr! Raarr!
I will protect you, Myria.
No matter what!
Tsuyoku nare itami yo yuuki ni nare
Nani ga umaretan darou
Te o nobashi fureta sekai wa
Kanashikute moroi kagayaki
Dakara koso no more painess
Kono basho de mirai no kodou
Kanjitara mou tomerarenai
Hikari oikakete
Gliding Claw
Dare ka no koto mamoritakunatta
Sou... dakara makenai makerarenai yo
Gliding Claw
Wakatta no wa chiisana jibun ga kawareru koto da to
Tsuyoku nare itami yo yuuki ni nare
Miss Marielle!
Oh, Gregory!
Any luck?
None at all.
We searched all through the village
and there's no sign of Myria.
I knew it!
She's such an idiot.
She must have gone into the forest.
Should I go looking for her in the forest?
No, I'll do it.
Just to make sure, will you
go looking around the village again?
There's a chance Myria
will come back here.
I'll do that.
Careful out there, Miss Marielle.
Myria, please be okay.
So that's Noah Forest, eh?
It doesn't look very dangerous to me.
It's suspicious as all get out!
Like that cave
with a jar full of Piperis we found.
On top of that,
you mentioned seeing a Plague Dragon?
Either way,
we concluded that it was too risky for the
two of us to continue investigating alone,
and that's why we called for you.
Are we going to start searching now?
No, we're headed to the village first.
We'll meet with the client
and get permission to proceed
with our full roster.
Let's go.
Damn it, they're so persistent!
And there's a lot more than before!
All right!
I won't get surrounded over here!
I can protect Myria!
Come and get me, jerks!
Time to meet your maker!
Kinda weird
how they never tried to retreat.
Why is that?
Because you have maxed out your level,
you cannot gain experience points.
I know that.
Myria?
So, what should I do?
Is it okay for me to bring Myria
to the village like this?
But I think the same thing
will happen again.
Help!
No, I'm just-
Please, listen to me!
I'm trying to help her!
What was Myria doing alone
in the forest to begin with?
There's no way that she doesn't know
how dangerous it is.
Man...
I'd understand everything
if I could just ask her directly.
Damn this language barrier!
Well, I guess I'll take her
to a safe place near the village for now.
Oh, I kinda understood her that time.
I feel it.
I think she said "thank you"!
Would you like to view the evolution tree?
There you go again, putting a damper
on the feel-good moments!
Well, whatever.
I'll give it a gander.
There are four different paths
this time around.
But like, why is there no Plague Dragon
evolution even though I'm a Plague Dragon?
The Divine Voice cannot provide
explanations of that natu-
It doesn't matter!
I'm not choosing
the Plague Dragon anyways!
Wicked
Myria would never ride on my back again if I did.
Help!
Would you like details on the evolution?
Yes, please.
Dark Drago-human.
A low ranking drago-human.
It is categorized as a demi-human.
Its body is covered in dark scales.
Uh, what's a demi-human?
Hard to know for sure,
but that's essentially a human, right?
Nah, sounds way too good to be true.
I can't believe anything
this stupid voice says.
There's gotta be a catch
in there somewhere.
Rolling Dragon.
A dragon that specializes
in speed over strength.
It is the speedster of the dragon world.
Okay, obviously just uses
the "Roll" skill.
I mean, it's in the name!
Little Arc Dragon.
A light-type dragon.
It has high intelligence,
and makes use of white magic.
A light-type!
Hard to believe a Plague Dragon
can evolve into something so righteous!
Being "little" means
less evolution options later,
but I like the sound of white magic!
Jormungand.
It has the body of a huge snake,
and its entire body is covered
with scales that contain a deadly poison.
Any soil this monster slithers over
will become barren.
Oh, hell no!
That'd make me
the number one enemy of humankind!
I'd be dooming myself!
Jormungand is completely
out of the question, obviously.
I am interested in the Roll specialization
for the Rolling Dragon.
Speed > Strength
But as much as I like that skill,
Speedster
of the Dragon World
I can't shake the feeling
I'd be turning into a circus show.
Then there's Little Arc.
It's a light-type, and seems like
I could get along well with humans.
Light-type
White Magic
High intelligence
Although, in that case,
Dark Drago-human might be better.
Low-ranking Drago-human
It's a demi-human after all.
Demi-human
That means it's in the same category
as humans, right?
Essentially a human?
How would Myria see me if I did that?
But on the other hand,
how would other monsters treat me?
Human...
Monster...
Would Black Lizard
accept me as a demi-human?
Um, I've just been giving some thought
to my future human life, I guess...
Wait, that's not quite right.
Guess it's more like a dragonic life.
Dragonic
Life
My golden, dragonic life?
Wait, what am I, a craft beer?
Anyways, I'm about to evolve into another
monster, but which do you think is best?
So like, evolving means...
Never mind.
I really wish I could ask
for Myria's advice on this.
Roar.
Does she mean... me?
I am Myria!
She's saying "I am Myria"!
I understood her!
Is it because my skill leveled up?!
Water!
The skill Greek Language
has gone from level two to level three.
I'm looking for someone.
I've come to this forest many times
by myself without Miss Marielle knowing.
Looking for someone?
Could she mean those people
who came to the cave?
Hm?
That didn't work.
Thanks to the skill, I can more or less
understand what she's saying,
but at the end of the day,
I still can't say a word to her.
Uh, well then...
Right!
Those two are adventurers from the city.
But I'm not looking for them,
I'm looking for Doz.
Doz?
But he was killed
by the Little Rock Dragon.
You know Mr. Doz?!
I knew it, you're the dragon
that saved me back then, aren't you?
I'm sorry, Black Lizard, I think
I'm gonna choose to be a demi-human...
U-um... Mr. Dragon?
Do you have a name?
I Realized I Had No Name
A name?
No, don't have one of those!
O-oh, you don't, huh?
Well then, what should I call you?
I've never thought about it.
Kinda funny.
Especially since
I'm always looking at my stats.
Shoot. I'm nameless, huh?
Well...
is it okay if I come up with a name?
But feel free to say no!
Please, do it!
Yes! Think of a name for me!
Yes!
Are you sure?
Looks like you're sure.
Okay, then.
You're a hero.
How about... Illusia?
Illusia?
It's the name of a flower I like.
The name of a flower?
Well, it sounds nice.
My name is...
Illusia!
I'll go look for that flower one day!
Confirm name as "Illusia"?
Once your name is confirmed,
it cannot be changed.
What?
The Divine Voice reacted for some reason.
Confirm name as "Illusia"?
Once your name is confirmed,
it cannot be changed.
[Yes]
[No]
I didn't know that was an option!
Once I choose a name,
I can't change it, huh?
Eh, should be fine.
After all, Myria gave me this name!
I'm Illusia!
I
llu
si
a
Illusia
Name has been confirmed as "Illusia."
Young Plague Dragon
Illusia
Young Plague
Dragon
Great!
You seem to like that name, Illusia.
I-llu-si-a...
I'm feeling... pretty happy.
Is it okay for me to be this happy?
What's that? Footsteps?
They're real heavy.
The only thing in this forest
that can make that type of footstep...
Okay!
I thought its den
was further away, though.
Well, whatever.
We'll take a detour
and head to the village.
I'll drop Myria off in a safe place,
and then go look for Doz on my own.
You guys never learn, do you?!
Magic Energy Reception
"Magic Energy Reception"?
Are they being controlled by something?
Crap, you need to lay off!
Huh? Are those...
Mahawolves?! There are more?!
Wait, what's that?
Mr. Doz!
Mr. Doz, why are you with monsters?
View stats!
Special Skills
Normal Skills
What the? His skill list is empty.
What's that mean?
Mr. Doz! Snap out of it, please!
Please, don't do this!
Fireball!
Take that!
What's the deal?
He's hugging that clump of dirt
like its a treasure.
How... how did this happen?
These jerks.
Illusia, I hear more footsteps!
Oh crap!
They're coming closer.
Could these footsteps be from that?
Wait, the thing Mr. Doz is holding...
He's going towards the village?!
Why, though?
What does he want with the village?
I don't get it!
Th-this is awful!
The thing Mr. Doz had...
It might be a Rock Dragon egg.
And if he brings it into the village...
I get it now!
That Doz guy is baiting
the Little Rock Dragon!
We have to give it back
as soon as possible!
Where'd Doz go?
Is he leading it
to the village on purpose?
Is this part of some revenge plan?
And why is he riding
on the back of those monsters?
Ah, my thoughts are all over the place!
Damn it!
I can't shake them off
with Myria on my back.
Illusia!
Leave me behind and keep going!
I'll hold the monsters at bay!
Please stop Mr. Doz in the meantime!
Are you crazy?!
There's no way you can beat those wolves!
I beg you!
Please save the village...
Illusia!
You bastard!
Get wrecked!
Myria...
Everything's okay now.
Illusia, please...
Hurry to the village...
Okay, I'll protect the village!
But...
I'm going to protect you, too!
C'mon, slow poke!
Wait up!
Hey, kids, the sun's going down.
Get home quick.
Yes, sir!
What's that sound?
I thought I heard some kind of roar...
No, I must be imagining things.
It's getting dark fast.
I have to find Myria
as quickly as possible.
I have to hurry to the village!
Can you tell me? Shinjita kotoba
Never ending kawareru bokura
Always remember yakusoku nakutashita page
Owaranai monogatari o
Don't let nobody bring you down
Tokihanate break of dawn
Kirei na mama no omoide nara
Oitakita through the rain
Tesaguri demo mae ni susumu emotion
Tsune ni mune ni daite
Atomodori wa nashi
Kokoro ni oshita rakuin
Shoki shoudou no mama ni
Attouteki na made ni
Hisometa ketsui hyoumei wa
Kakumei no makuake sa
Hajimeyou ka 3, 2, 1 GO!!
Can you tell me? Shinjita kotoba
Never ending kawareru bokura
Always remember yakusoku nakushita page
Owaranai monogatari o
Shukumei wa ima da mikansei
Shimesu sono kanousei
We fly together koko de wa nai dokoka e
Yoru ga akeru made
Hane hiroge
Itsuka sora ni kieru made
I Went to the Village and Found Carnage
"I Went to the Village and Found Carnage".
Get stronger.