You're here again? What a pest.
Good morning, Selio-san.
You look as busy as ever.
Yeah, I'm busy.
I can't get any work done because of you.
I wouldn't mind if you let me be.
Looks like he's finally planning
on monitoring me all day.
Hey, Selio!
What are you doing? Why aren't
you helping in the almshouse?
Huh? Well, I was assigned
to watch over this guy today,
so you'll need someone else to...
Just leave that guy alone.
He's merely the tagalong from
another world who can't do anything.
Don't dump your work
in the almshouse on me!
Okay...
Don't do anything inappropriate,
otherworld commoner.
And that's how you ended up here?
Yes.
Gracious, what troublesome children.
I will fetch Selio, so kindly
return to the other room.
Oh, in that case, let me
accompany you to the almshouse.
Why?
Since the almshouse is part of the church,
it's also under investigation.
Besides, if I go there instead,
Selio-san can continue watching me
while doing his part in the almshouse.
Wouldn't that be more efficient?
ISEKAI OFFICE WORKER: THE OTHER WORLD'S
BOOKS DEPEND ON THE BEAN COUNTER
EPISODE 9: I MADE A PLAN
So this is the almshouse...
You're currently caring for
28 children here, correct?
Where did you get that information?
It was in those documents.
Does your shamelessness come
from being a civil servant? Or...
It's probably due to my personality.
Do the children have to graduate
the almshouse at a certain age?
Indeed.
The almshouse only cares for
them until the age of twelve.
After that, they must either
train as monks or take civilian jobs.
I see. What kind of work do they...
Disciple, with all due respect,
you should act in a manner a little
more befitting a disciple of Abran.
I'm not a disciple.
So, where do the children
without families end up working?
Most of them apprentice with craftsmen.
Craftsmen?
They don't take jobs that make
use of their magical energy?
I don't know what you've
heard from where, but...
There are many children here
who cannot control their magical energy
and had to leave their families.
We teach them how to control their power
so that they may lead normal lives.
They're in the church's care to keep
their magical energy in check...
Aresh-sama said the same thing.
Either way, I can feel his magical
energy waves through my barrier.
It would be unwise to press him further.
You!
What did you come here for?!
I thought it would be easier
for you to watch me this way
while you're working in the almshouse.
Selio, Fredrik should have been the one
responsible for the almshouse today.
Th-That's...
Good grief. Come to me if something
like this happens again.
That's likely impossible.
I'd wager this is a common occurrence,
and snitching would only make it worse.
There's no need for a civil servant
like you to come to the almshouse!
Oh! Kondou-san, you're here!
So you really are visiting the church!
What brings you here today?
I'm on my inspection.
What are you doing here, Shiraishi-san?
Lately, I've been helping out
here in the almshouse.
Is that so?
Yes!
The holy maiden is doing other work?
Even though she's the only one
with purification magic?
I happened to meet an orphaned child
who came to the chapel and...
Oh, but this church...
U-Um, I thought the two
of you didn't get along.
Huh?
I mean, this guy is trying to destroy
the holy maiden's prestige.
Could he be talking about the plan
to eliminate the holy maiden system?
Why would that make Kondou-san
and I dislike each other?
Why? Because the importance
of the holy maiden will...
I see.
This must be the reason everyone
at the church has been so unfriendly.
That's right!
Once the holy maiden system's abolished,
I'll be able to go back to my world.
I couldn't be happier!
Um...
The children here in the almshouse
don't receive any sort of education.
Come again?
They aren't allowed to go to school,
and they spend each day here working
and doing all the housekeeping
for the communal areas.
I really don't think it's a very good
situation for these children's futures.
Um, Shiraishi-san...
I understand that not
everyone can attend school.
But it's such a shame that
they lose the opportunity
to learn just because
they don't have parents.
This is a different world.
We shouldn't compare it to modern Japan.
Still...
Losing precious talent and human resources
over their birth or upbringing
is a huge loss for any country.
Sigma, who made my abacus,
is undoubtedly talented.
Not utilizing the kids' magical
energy also seems a waste.
Above all, they have no freedom
to choose their occupations.
So I was wondering if
we could do something...
You're so kind, Your Holiness.
But it's impossible.
The almshouse doesn't have
the time or money for that.
But even you, Selio-kun...
Didn't you have a dream job
when you were a child?
That's...
The little children here
often tell me their dreams.
"When I grow up, I want to become
a sorcerer working in the castle."
"I want to become a knight."
It's wrong that they end up unable
to honestly say such things anymore
and abandon all hope.
You must have come from a very
peaceful world, Your Holiness.
The world I'm from sees war
and discrimination, too.
We even have almshouses.
But we still have the freedom
to achieve our dreams.
That's impossible...
It's not possible to change everything
at once, no, but it's worth consideration.
It's difficult to expand an education
initiative in one fell swoop,
but a potential approach is to open
something similar to a private school.
If it's at the church,
people will have easy access.
This, in turn, increases people's trust
in the church and attracts worshipers.
It may be wishful thinking on my part,
but I believe it will also attract
more and more volunteers over time.
Th-There's no way it'd go that well!
Wow, it'll be amazing!
Just like those open-air classrooms!
B-But what'll we do about study materials?
And what about our work in the almshouse?
If we organize the classes in shifts,
they can be smaller,
and study materials can be shared.
We could split the almshouse
children into three groups
and have all of them take turns working
and studying on different days.
Just learning basic reading,
writing, and arithmetic
will make you more valuable in town
and broaden your job options.
Those with talent may even be able
to pursue further education.
You...
It'd be good to include
a scholarship program.
The royal family could invest in
and subsidize gifted children.
Nurturing talent will be highly beneficial
for both the royal palace and the kingdom.
With that decided, we should confirm
the almshouse children's wishes.
Hold on a second!
No one gave you permission to...
Let's go, Selio-kun.
Come on.
I'm busy, so hurry up.
You...
I really hate you after all!
I heard the bishop and the accountant
are both currently away from the church.
Yes.
For some reason, they left despite being
notified of the inspection dates.
Luckily, that's made it easier
for me to gather documents.
I've urged them to return
by the day after tomorrow.
Tell me what you make
of the church so far.
I will include all the
details in my report,
but there appear to be discrepancies
between the titles and numbers
of nobles attending services
and their donations.
Embezzlement, eh? Any idea
where the money's going?
I'm still investigating,
but at the very least, the almshouse,
monks-in-training,
and their priest likely aren't involved.
Their priest...
Priest Siegvold?
Do you know him?
He's famous.
Not only is his family impressive,
but his abundant magical energy
and looks are also top-notch.
On the other hand, his intense
faith makes it difficult
for the nobility to get
their hands on him.
His magical energy, you say?
Yes.
It's a precious resource required for
both spellcasting and magical tools.
It's difficult to handle, demanding
special knowledge and skills.
That's why children born
with too much undergo training
at a church to learn how to
reduce their magical energy.
By the way, Seichiro...
How's your resistance to
magical energy and magicules?
Thankfully, I am slowly
gaining some resistance.
That's good to hear.
Still, you've already managed to grab
the reins of someone as famously difficult
as Priest Siegvold.
Grab the reins? You make him
sound like a wild horse.
People say he's a black beast.
So rather than his reins...
Perhaps you're his chains?
Your Excellency...
I'm not joking.
However you may feel about him,
you have become his chains.
Unlike Priest Siegvold's chains,
you're perfectly tangible.
Not to mention extremely fragile.
I plan to help you as best I can,
but it never hurts to be careful.
I am Aresh-sama's chains...
It's not just His Excellency.
Everyone is starting to notice
Aresh-sama's attachment to me.
I appreciate your consideration.
Now, I heard you want to open a private
school for commoners in the church.
Yes.
I see.
You truly are a talented individual.
You're even picking apart education now?
No.
It was Her Holiness who originally
came up with the idea.
I merely supported her proposal.
I'm presently preparing an estimate
of the project's economic impact
and will submit it to you in a few days.
Yes, that is your area
of expertise, after all.
There's one thing I'd like to ask you.
Yes?
Seichiro.
What is it that you want
to do to this kingdom?
Nothing.
I have no attachment to this kingdom.
I just want to make this place
easier for me to do my job.
The sorcery department
is sorely lacking in personnel.
This is causing delays in
miasma countermeasures
and the return spell's development.
You truly are...
Overlooking talented people
means massive losses for the land.
It's a waste not to be
cost-effective in doing business.
You're absolutely right.
Ah, what a pity.
What a pity, Seichiro.
Truly...
If it weren't for that black beast,
I would have taken such good care of you.
I appreciate the thought.
What are you doing here, Seiichirou?
Aresh-sama...
I swear...
How many times must I tell you
before you understand?
Isn't the purification expedition
the day after tomorrow?
Shouldn't you be preparing?
Milan took care of that ages ago.
You need to prepare more than I do.
Me?
I won't be by your side for some time.
You'll need a thoroughly cast barrier.
Oh, um...
I have tomorrow off in
advance of the expedition.
We have plenty of time.
I have work tomorrow,
so let's keep it brief...
Don't be ridiculous.
There's no way I'd squander
an opportunity to touch you.
You'd do well to remember that.
DAY OF THE EXPEDITION DEPARTURE
I'm off, Seiichirou.
Take care of Seiichirou
for me while I'm gone.
You can leave him to us.
Check on him regularly to make
sure he's not sacrificing sleep.
He tends to bury himself
in work when I'm not around.
Understood.
Give him a talking-to if
he doesn't finish his lunch.
Yes, Master.
Make sure he actually rests on days off.
And have him tell you where he's
going whenever he goes out.
Milord.
If he lies and goes to work
on his day off...
Young Master!
I understand your worries,
but please leave everything to us.
I never thought you would care
this deeply for another.
Even though work comes
first for Kondu-sama,
I'm sure he will be more eager
than anyone for your safe return.
I think so, too.
He'll be there to happily
welcome you home.
He will, will he?
I hope that's the case...
Aresh-sama!
Seiichirou.
Are you about to depart?
You could have stayed in bed.
I couldn't have.
You're leaving on an important mission.
The least I can do is see you off.
Aresh-sama...
What is it?
I shall await your safe return.
Take care not to get injured.
I can use recovery magic if I do.
Sorry, that was an absurd request
to ask of a knight like you...
Don't worry.
No one can see us behind my cloak.
That's not the problem here!
Today, I'll meet the bishop and
accountant, who have finally returned.
It's finally time for you
to pay your dues!
I'm the one asking for overdue payment.
You're always so picky about everything.
Come to think of it, Shiraishi...
Her Holiness said she won't be
at the church for a while.
She asked me to say hello.
Listen, you...
Even if you're a friend
of the holy maiden,
I'll never accept someone
who just tagged along with her
and acts so high and mighty all the time!
Ignorance is a road to ruin.
HEH...
Once the private school opens,
do attend, Selio-san.
What?! Did you just make fun of me?!
Aresh-sama will return in seven
days at the very latest.
I should do all I can in that time.
So you're the rumored otherworlder?
I've heard about you.
He's taking a blatantly hostile attitude
with a representative from the palace.
Hard not to see the defiance in his heart.
I am Mateus, the royal capital's bishop.
This is Cipriano, the one in
charge of the church's finances.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
I'm very sorry the income
and expenses report is late.
In truth, we were very busy supporting
the summoning of the holy maiden and...
This man seems friendly.
He lost the report and, because he was
busy, couldn't meet the deadline.
I see.
However, the deadline is the deadline.
Now you've suddenly asked us
to care for the holy maiden, too.
I believe your side is also to blame
for our hectic schedule.
No, Your Excellency.
We already knew Her Holiness
would be coming to the church.
The delay was entirely my fault.
So, are you still in the process
of preparing the report?
Yes. I'm very sorry.
In that case, I will continue
commuting here for a while longer.
We are planning to open a cram school
in the name of the holy maiden,
so this works out perfectly.
Cram school?
Yes.
It will be a place to teach
simple subjects to children
who cannot normally attend school
due to their circumstances.
That's a wonderful idea!
As expected of the holy maiden
and Abran's disciple!
In this fashion, we hope to increase
donations and elevate the church.
A favorable reaction.
People who are easy to read
are easy to handle.
I knew there was no mistake
when Abran chose you!
Please allow me to assist you, Disciple!
People like him are convenient
at times like these.
And so the days passed.
In the afternoon of the seventh
day since the expedition,
the church suddenly grew lively.
Her Holiness has successfully
purified the miasma!
Huh?
Aresh-sama hasn't returned yet?
That's right.
It seems the purification was
completed without incident,
but a herd of ferocious beasts was
spotted in the mountains nearby,
so instead of returning home,
he immediately went to subjugate them.
I see...
Kondu-sama.
I received this from a returning
member of the expedition.
It's from Aresh-sama.
"Dear Seiichirou."
"I'm sure you've already heard,
but I have decided to remain in the
area to subjugate magic beasts..."
Please take good care of
yourself while I am away.
Don't work too hard,
and get plenty of rest.
Even in letters...
But thank goodness.
It wasn't bad news.
I hope you fall to slumber with my soul.
His soul? What an odd thing to say...
Excuse me, Milan-san.
Yes?
Do you know what this sentence means?
Oh, my!
Milord is so passionate!
Huh?
For a knight, his soul is an
expression for his feelings.
In other words...
"I hope you fall asleep
thinking of me by your side."
EPISODE 10
I INVESTIGATED