September 5th, 2045
We're off.
See you later.
Take care.
Here we go.
Thanks for driving.
Go, go!
They're gone.
Um, is there anything I can do to help?
No. You'd just get in the way.
But school has started for
Saionji-san, Akari, and Riku-san.
By the way, Rui-chan,
don't you have school?
I'm already dead.
What?
You're an important part of our forces.
You should train to improve
your spirit power.
Train? How?
Ask Dad.
Dad?
No one's told you yet.
Yukihito Miyata, 47 years old,
also known as Settei the monk.
He is my father.
You're kidding, right?
Why does "music" exist in this world?
I think I've figured it out
This melody will go on living
much, much longer than us
For thousands and tens
of thousands of years
Carrying the flames of wishes past
Traveling across time
What color is your elegy?
Well? Tell me
My 1,000% pure curiosity
Can't be stopped
Let my heart sing, sing, sing,
sing and turn my life into music
I despise the word "destiny"
Ghosts still believe in pure dreams
Just as everyone's souls scream
The racing ba-dump, ba-dump, ba-dump,
ba-dump running through the present
Waltzes through the new
world with enough force
to break through the afterlife's border
Now smile and shine
I'm not kidding.
But we're not blood-related.
You're adopted?
Something like that.
Long ago, I lived on another island.
5 Years Ago, 2040
The island is a closed society.
It has no official name and isn't on maps.
The island's ancient custom
is to sacrifice a young girl to the evil
god that resides there as a pure bride.
Brides are imprisoned in
a cage at a small shrine.
In reality, there is no evil god.
It's a necessary political
practice to ensure the residents
don't lose their faith.
The practice is also used
to punish squabbling nobles and
anyone plotting rebellion.
Daughters of traitorous nobles
are sacrificed as brides.
I was purchased to take the
place of one such daughter.
I was remade to look exactly like her.
I no longer remember what
I actually look like.
That's awful.
After their sixth new moon,
girls chosen to be brides
are consumed by the evil god
and vanish without a trace.
Consumed?
They're simply killed.
It was merely a tool to control people.
How did you end up here?
I was possessed by the spirits
of the previous sacrifices.
Possessed?
Like you.
But I can't do what you do.
I couldn't control the
spirits that possessed me.
I escaped from the shrine and
rampaged through the town.
At their wit's end, the nobles hired an
esoteric Buddhist order to eliminate me.
I was nearly killed by practitioners
as part of their training.
But one of them saved me.
You mean the monk?
We've been together ever since.
He taught me to speak and helped
me figure out how to create these.
Your stitched spirit beasts.
He even gave me a name and
did my hair like this.
I believe this makes me me.
Thank you for telling me.
But why tell me something so important?
Since I was born, the only music
in this world has been MiucS'.
I felt like I'd heard real
music for the first time.
Aw, shucks.
I won't be killed if I sing.
But I can't sing like you.
I want to learn to sing like you.
I'm sure you will someday.
I meant it when I said you're a key
part of our forces, but that's not all.
I want to hear you sing more, so...
Okay. I'll get stronger
and train for you, too.
And for the monk... for your father.
Twenty-two.
Twenty-three, twenty-four.
Twenty-five.
Oh, he's back.
What is it, Seria?
Welcome back, Settei-san.
I want to become stronger.
What should I do?
You want to train?
Unfortunately, you don't need to do that.
Huh? Why not?
The spirits that possess
you are too strong.
And while an ordinary medium
would need to increase their
spiritual and physical strength,
your own spirit power is quite high.
In the Phantom Realm, spirit power
matters more than flesh and blood.
As long as you're reasonably
fit, you'll be fine.
I see...
If I had to say, it'd be ideal if you
could increase your spirit medium power,
but there's no point in letting
any old spirit possess you.
And it's not wise to carelessly venture
into the Phantom Realm
without orders from TERA.
That storehouse serves as a library.
A library?
We might run into another Great Ghost.
We've got plenty of
history books. Read them.
History books? Thank you.
Hey, it's locked.
I'll get the key from Rui-chan.
I see.
She likes history, huh? So that's why...
Wow, look at all these books.
I can read all of these?
They're too difficult for me.
This is yours to use as you please.
Thank you.
We can't read books online anymore,
and I'm getting to read paper books.
There's a note.
You seem to be having fun.
Nothing.
Yeah?
Thanks for the food.
This is a lot nicer than usual.
That's good.
Seria's salary from TERA
came in. We're celebrating.
But Seria-chan's not here.
She's eating in the library.
She said she had no time to spare.
She reads? I'm surprised.
Maybe she's possessed by
the evil spirit of Kinjiro.
Don't worry. She seems to be having fun.
Apparently she's always liked history.
Really? I'm glad, then.
Japanese History
Central Government of
the Late Edo Period
September 27th, 2045
Is that you, Yotetsu?
Yes.
What do you want?
I believe we should prioritize
installing that flagstone there.
It's not important to TERA's strategy,
but it's a shortcut to MiucS.
There's been no sign of
interference from other organizations
or dark spirits for several days.
Is that right?
We can't sacrifice them, though.
Then will you disguise yourself again?
Phantom Shift.
There. Now I can seduce Iemitsu.
Yotetsu, did you just
come here to tease me?
No, although that does sound fun.
Lady Kasuga made me a deal.
We provide a woman Lord Iemitsu
will invite into his bed.
If we do that, she'll hand over the area.
I've already secured her agreement.
But a mere invitation won't
fulfill Lady Kasuga's wish.
We just need to get him
interested in a woman to start.
They're exploring other ways
to produce an heir as spirits.
I see. So, how do you
intend to tackle this?
We'll use Seria Aiba-san.
Wouldn't her ability be useful?
What?
Edo Castle?
Using force won't work here.
Lady Kasuga has agreed to hand over
this area if we meet her conditions.
Lady Kasuga's wish is for Lord Tokugawa
Iemitsu to express interest in a woman.
B-But aren't Saionji-san or
Riku-san better suited for that?
No, you're the best fit.
Huh?
What?!
That's right. Lord Iemitsu's
spirit still prefers men.
Following history, we'll send a woman
who can disguise herself as a man.
You don't mean...
Caesar, Antonius, Okita.
Spirit-Sync Release.
Please don't drag us out like that.
This is a problem.
But we understand the situation.
Seria, we'll help you. Right?
If we must.
Let's give it a shot.
What?!
Wh-What just happened?
Not bad, right?
Not bad.
But Seria,
your charms alone may not be enough
to make Lord Iemitsu fall for you.
You think so?
If you need help, call me.
Why not test our feminine charms?
We appreciate the help.
There's no concern about Lady Kasuga
discovering the male spirits
and complaining about it.
I see. I'm not too confident,
but if that's what you want, Cleo...
Indeed.
First, we'll achieve a high
enough rank for an audience.
Will being here really help with that?
It might be hard to get
the shogun's attention
without being adopted by a daimyo.
Lady Kasuga has deviated
from historical fact.
She grants opportunities
to those who work hard.
I see. That said, I don't
have any special skills.
I'll help you establish a positive record.
Thanks, Rui-chan.
We'll do everything we
can without being rude.
Okay.
We're done here.
We'll head over there next.
Could it be?
How truly beautiful.
Are you the girls sent by Settei-dono?
I'm Seria Aiba.
Rui.
I see. Raise your heads, Oseri and Orui.
I am Kasuga no Tsubone.
I run the inner palace on
behalf of the shogun's wife.
As you can see, there are
many maidservants here.
Though you were sent by Settei-dono,
gaining an audience will
still be difficult
as you're not daughters of bannermen.
I must also judge if you're
worthy of the shogun.
Y-Yes, milady.
Very good. Now, if you'll excuse me.
Oh, right. The girl assigned to clean
the bathhouse is sick in bed today.
Oseri, could you do it for her?
The bathhouse? As you wish.
Seria?
This is an opportunity for us.
Lord Iemitsu had an affair with
Lady Onatsu in the bathhouse.
So it's a chance to interact with Iemitsu
without achieving a higher rank.
But if he makes a pass at me...
Let me handle that.
Cleo?
Trust me to handle such matters.
I'm far better at handling men.
That's true, but...
We shall preserve your chastity.
If he makes advances,
we can brush him off.
Okay.
H-How is the water?
Not bad.
I see.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and wipe me down.
My apologies.
Is something wrong? Have I offended you?
No, you haven't.
That's enough. I'm getting out.
Yes, milord.
Raise your head.
You did well.
He knows who you are now,
and we confirmed his preferences.
Don't let it get to you.
We were told he's not interested in women.
Yes, but...
We should move on to our next strategy.
I'm doing this for Cleo, too.
I'll do whatever it takes to climb
the ladder and make him fall for me.
Low-ranking Maid
Gate Watch
Fire Watch
Tea Room Maid
Kitchen Maid
Living Room Maid
This is for you.
Yes!
You are hereby permitted to
receive an audience with the shogun.
Do not take the honor lightly.
Is it really okay for me to
wear something so beautiful?
It suits you, Oseri-sama.
I'm glad.
Please excuse us.
Starting tomorrow, you'll attend
the general announcement.
Your chance will come when Iemitsu
scans everyone in attendance.
I know. Follow the plan.
What is your name?
Oh, my.
Yes!
Great!
Of course.
Wait, why? I thought he just
had to invite me into his bed.
I can't let you leave now.
I'm not doing this.
In that case...
Bloodshed is strictly forbidden
in the inner palace.
Agreements cannot be broken either.
But...
Oseri, you caught the shogun's attention.
I ask that you bear his children.
N-No...
Now, come.
What?!
What is that?
Something must've happened.
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
Wh-What should I do?
We can't do much if you're
unable to wield swords.
This isn't what we agreed to.
We were told we only need to be invited.
Allow us to possess you.
We will defend your chastity.
But we need this area to reach
MiucS, and he's just a ghost.
Besides, I'm basically dead, right? I...
Then we should steel ourselves as well.
What?!
Seria, get a hold of yourself.
Th-This is... You may pass.
Thank you.
We're ready for you, milord.
Good.
Let me see your face.
Yes, milord.
Sorry, guys.
It's all right. You're doing well.
I knew it.
What?
We met previously in the bathhouse.
You thought you could
outwit me? How laughable.
What trick are you using? Show me.
I...
I didn't do that.
Oh? That will do.
Come closer.
What? N-No, wait.
The shogun's orders cannot
be defied. This isn't good.
We have bigger problems right now.
I have steeled my resolve.
Here I come.
Stop!
Who are you?
Hand him over!
No!
Let's go.
This way.
Huh? What?
Milord? Oseri, after them!
What? Uh, yes, milady!
Hurry!
Masamori? Shigezumi?
I'm glad you came for me.
Stop!
Wait!
Here I come.
I'm so glad.
Uh, yeah.
So, what happened after that?
The inner palace vanished, and we
successfully placed the Chiaku Flagstone.
Anyway, I wonder who that page was.
We don't know.
I'd probably recognize him if he
were a famous historical figure.
Was he really that handsome?
Probably?
What does that mean?
The circumstances probably
made him 30% hotter.
Maybe, but I'll have to thank
him if I see him again.
Like "Much Ado About Love"?!
In any case, we achieved our goal.
Thanks for the help, Seria and Rui.
Yes, sir.
Yukihito Miyata
Thank you, Settei-san.
Ah, clearing a path even
though I'm not certain
Advancing towards a faint light
Ah, on this path of thorns
To prevent the pain
from wilting our hearts
We pray
Buffeted by headwinds
The harder it is to walk
The less we're bothered
by this path of thorns
Fly freely up into that sky
It will surely be a delight,
now break your fate