Tonari's battle against
the Nokkers continues.
Fushi!
Do something! Please!
In the moment of certain doom,
Fushi's friends come to her aid.
I made it.
Meanwhile, Yuki's team rescues
Mizuha from the underground.
Clean Water
I can trust you, right?
All of you?
Could you please drink this?
This is a pact ritual that's been
passed down by the Guardians.
Those who become one of us, of our
friends, of our family, all drink this.
It proves that we will always trust each
other and would never betray one another.
Don't worry.
It's just water.
And if we drink it...
you'll come with us?
Yeah.
Are we sure about this water?
You can do it, right?
Don't do it!
Okay, let's go.
All you guys over there are
coming to my place, too.
Bon-san, could you contact Gramps
and let him know I'm bringing
a ton of people over?
My phone's busted.
Wait.
You're interesting, Yuki-kun.
You get hurt a lot, don't you?
You seem like the type to
not think things through.
What if it's a trap?
If the water is poisoned?
Mr. Yuki sure is a man of reckless courage.
You aren't one to talk, are you?
So, is it poisoned?
Of course not.
He's my dear underclassman at school.
It really is just water.
When I asked if you and I, human and mutant,
could be friends, you said yes.
Did we say that?
I believe what people say,
no matter what they are.
No matter what I am?
I'm Mizuha.
It's all back to normal!
The Nokkers are gone,
and the water was safe to drink!
The Nokker's still here.
And I've been talking to it this whole time.
Oh? So you mean...
it's still lurking in our midst?
So, what's your name?
Huh? I-I told you, I'm Mizuha.
Mizuha-senpai is right-handed.
It's gone.
Aoki-kun!
Vice President!
Get a grip!
Let's go see Satoru.
Don't worry about me.
We gotta go shopping for everyone's dinner.
Fushi will bring Mizuha-senpai's
Nokker to us.
And we can talk it over,
and they'll return Mizuha-senpai's
body along with all the others.
We can come to an understanding.
I have faith that we can.
Sheesh, you...
How happy-go-lucky can you be?
I wonder how Mizuha-kun would
have reacted if she were here.
I'd be happy just to see her
cringing at me like always.
Are you all right, Fushi-sama?
Sorry, Chamihiko-san,
but could you take care of Grandpa?
Sure, but why...
It's coming.
Fushi-sama!
Hey, Fushi.
Hey. What's up?
I've always wanted to fight
you properly sometime.
Which of us is stronger?
I'm pretty sure you'll
end up back in Paradise.
Are you giving up on your ambitions?
I'll reconsider if you defeat me.
Is this supposed to stop me?
You're too slow!
Why?
Why? Why? Why?
Why? Why?
Why?!
Why are you going easy on me?
Don't you see that I'm taking this seriously?
Were you influenced by that
friend of yours, Yuki?
I like that boy.
He didn't hesitate to drink
the water with Nokkers in it.
As a sign of friendship.
Yuki did?!
Don't tell me this is all you've got!
This ought to be enough space.
Go on and take your weapon.
Your bow.
Your sword.
You're right.
Yuki rubbed off on me.
I don't want to kill you.
I'm hoping that we can come to understand
each other while we're both alive.
Hey.
It isn't over yet, Fushi.
You moved your core.
Do you think you can defeat me in that body?
Are you really willing to do this?
What about you?
Aren't you cold in that
clothing made of skin?
Shall we continue, Fushi?
Do you want to find out how
meaningless your platitudes are?
Do you really want to go on?
You think my offer to debate you
instead of killing you is a platitude?
What do you expect? It's only human.
But neither of us is human.
God damn it, Chami.
There's still more ammo in the storage.
Heya.
Want some help, Mizuha?
No, Daddy.
He isn't using his true strength yet.
Cut him some slack.
We've already taken the best
of the Great Fushi's vessels.
He's only got the feeble ones left.
Oh, wanna use this, Fushi-sama?
No, thanks.
Entertain her properly, then, would you?
You still have some that
you can use, don't you?
You've been hiding some?
Show them!
I wasn't hiding any.
I was just waiting for the
right reason to face you.
The sixth descendant...
Kahaku!
The failure of a vessel!
Don't insult my friends.
Come get some more!
Let me set you straight.
Draw your weapon, Fushi!
What's making you strong...
is the blood of your ancestors
coursing through your body.
It hurts!
It seems you aren't accustomed to pain yet.
I doubt you're ready for death,
judging from your reaction.
Are you mental?
What are you trying to accomplish?
If you need a place to go,
I'll be your vessel.
Are you sure?
I'd take all your vessels from you.
I don't know how well I can keep
the contaminant that is you at bay.
But if it turns out that
you're stronger, well...
I'll cross that bridge when I get to it.
You don't have a plan?!
Wh-Why?!
Relax.
I let the main body evaporate.
No, I mean....
I figured it's time we head home, too.
Try as we might to kill you,
we couldn't find your core.
And we were no match for your birth parent.
Our battle in the current age is over.
In the current age?
We aren't done yet.
We're in the middle of living, too.
That one came here to be killed.
To start over.
The water here is contaminated with Nokkers.
Wash them away.
Take them to the sea, and they'll decide
for themselves whether to live or die.
Don't get the wrong idea.
You haven't won.
You're lucky I'm here, huh, Fushi?
Later.
Hey, Fushi!
You around?
Where are you?
Are you all right?
See? It's a total maze down here.
I can't believe Fushi-san's
group found their way.
Indeed.
Say, what about us?
Where are we right now?
Water.
Don't tell me you're lost, Prince.
Eh?
I thought you two were leading the way.
We weren't.
Didn't we tell you that
we don't remember the way?
Yipes! What if we're trapped?!
I didn't bring food or water!
Stay calm, please.
We'll bring some.
Really? Thankies!
Wait, no!
Y'all are ghosts!
That solves that problem, Prince!
You have water!
This is too much!
Nice, it's the exit.
This is the entrance!
We were looking for Fushi!
We're all the way back outside!
Bon.
Fushi!
Thank goodness you're safe!
Well? Did you settle things?
Settle things?
No.
It didn't work out.
We couldn't start anything over.
Spares that you kept for insurance?
Yeah.
I never used them.
That's absolutely fantastic.
Now, we should head back to school.
School?
Bon, I'm going to head there first.
Fu-chan!
Fushi-kun.
Guys!
H-Hey... um...
Just as you wanted,
I captured the Nokkers alive.
I'll send them out to sea later
and let them decide where to go.
What about Tonari?
Tonari's dead.
I killed her good.
What?!
Look at your face!
Don't freak out just because I'm dead.
T-T...
T-Tonari!
Shocked, huh?
That kid, Satoru, was it?
He brought me back to life.
What's up with him?
Do you know him, Fushi?
I'm sorry. It must have hurt.
This is my fault.
Stupid! Don't apologize for that!
Never mind that.
You should have told us!
We've been friends for centuries, you know?
You ought to rely on us.
No kidding.
You're getting an earful later.
Tanasen!
Huh?
Thank goodness she isn't dead!
What is this?!
What happened here?!
We did it.
Tee-hee.
We were fighting off a baddie.
Odd...
Not a single soul in sight.
No one's coming home.
What's going on?
The bear's gone, too.
I never would have thought
the day would come.
How many cups of rice am
I supposed to cook tonight?
Gramps!
I'm home!
Yuki.
I brought a ton of guests over.
Make, like, a hundred cups of rice!
Wh-Who's that behind you?
Didn't Bon-san message you?
Grandpa! Onii-chan!
Aiko!
I'm so glad you're safe.
What's wrong? What happened?
I'll explain.
But first, let's have dinner.
And then there was this flame, like, bam!
You wouldn't believe how bad it was.
It was insane.
Man, I'm impressed you kids
pulled that off on your own.
Only because Tonari-san was there.
Nah, it was mostly Aiko.
Her ideas and quick thinking saved us.
No, it wasn't that big a deal.
I couldn't have done anything
without the rest of you.
Here, Satoru-kun.
So he's the Black One that
Fushi-san was talking about?
Yup.
It's hard to believe...
but after seeing him capture the Nokkers...
Salt works on the Nokkers?!
Yes.
We've confirmed that holy salt is effective.
Although it only really
slowed it down a little.
See? I knew we should have used it!
My bad. We'll do that next time.
Next time?! No way, no more!
But we were so badass.
I kinda like this.
I don't care!
It's like real teamwork.
Huh? Did I say something weird?
No, it's not a teamwork thing.
Yeah, we were at each other's throats.
We aren't friends at all.
Aw, c'mon.
Anyway, what were you up to, Hanna-san?
I heard you were off somewhere with Yuki-kun.
Oh, um, well...
I...
I was, um...
I went to bring Mizuha back.
We couldn't bring her back.
Now, everyone, eat well.
Come with me.
Mizuha-senpai! We were waiting for you!
Welcome back!
Welcome home.
Thanks.
You did well.
Preview
In an effort to live alongside the Nokkers,
Yuki engages in talks with a certain person.
At a loss for direction, Fushi
grows increasingly frustrated.
Will he accept yet another power?
Coexist