Eek!
You've done it now!
H-How dare you?!
I won't go easy on you this time!
Mr. Hitoma, get over here!
We've come all this way,
so it'd be a shame not to enjoy the water!
No, it's fine.
I'm enjoying myself plenty.
Anyway, make sure you
don't lose your rings.
Here are four of the
director's gemstone rings.
If any of our students leave the barrier,
they'll revert to their non-human form,
and be unable to re-enter the barrier.
But if they wear these rings,
they can leave the barrier
looking the way they do here at school.
Oh?
If you happen to lose your ring...
It carries a very heavy penalty.
How heavy are we talking here?
That's for the director to decide,
based on the circumstances.
So it depends on the director's mood?
If you lose your ring,
you won't be able to go back.
Right!
Mr. Hitoma, you're not going to swim?
Come and play with us!
If an indoorsy type like me faced
off against you feral brats,
I'd end up with every muscle
aching in a few days—
I'm not feral!
I've spent my whole life with humans.
What?
So you were a pet for humans,
not a wild rabbit?
None of your business, Hitoma.
Stop prying.
Now, I'm mad!
I'll show you the aim of a true FPS gamer!
We'll beat you at your own game!
Let's all take Hitoma down!
Yeah!
Take this!
Episode 4
The Misanthrope and the Angel's Comet
Miss Usami, Mr. Hitoma.
I have something important to tell you.
Something important?
It has to do with Seiko Kizaki.
Did something happen to Seiko?!
During Mrs. Kizaki's checkup,
they discovered a serious health problem.
We've received news
that she's in the hospital now.
How's Seiko holding up?!
It doesn't look good.
Excuse me, Principal.
Would Seiko Kizaki happen to be...
It's just as you've guessed.
She's the reason that Miss Usami
wants to become human.
Seiko Kizaki, 76 years old.
Miss Usami's owner.
After discussing it with the director,
we will allow a special 24-hour leave
to the outside world for Miss Usami.
You'll let me see Seiko?!
However, not in your current form.
In the form you took
before you entered this school.
If you so wish, I'll be the one
to take you to see Mrs. Kizaki.
Mr. Hitoma, I thought you should know
about this as her homeroom teacher.
I understand.
Miss Usami, what is your decision?
Let me think about it.
Usami, you haven't left yet?
Hitoma.
I'm sorry.
I'm not sure what to say,
since I don't know all the details.
Just ask the principal, and you can
take your special leave at any time.
There's no point.
There's no point in seeing
Seiko in my old form.
She won't know how I feel.
I don't think that's true.
Even if you can't speak,
you can still move.
That's plenty to convey how you feel
if you meet her in person.
You don't know anything, Hitoma.
I...
I can't do those things
like a real rabbit!
What?
My true form...
It's not a rabbit.
I'm a stuffed rabbit doll!
Listen to this, Usami!
You see, I've found someone I like!
Ken, who sits right next to me!
We went to get some Calpis together today.
I was so nervous, I couldn't
tell what it tasted like.
Usami, Kenichi proposed to me.
He asked me to marry him.
But I'm still not sure about it...
Can I be a good enough wife
to win his family's approval?
Am I really the right one?
I wish I could hold a real
conversation with you, Usami.
But I'm just a plushie.
There's no way for me to talk to you.
That's why, if my wish comes true one day,
I have so many things to tell you, Seiko.
Hitoma.
I want to go see Seiko in this form.
But the principal and
director would never allow it.
So I need your help, Hitoma.
Help how?
I need one of
the director's gemstone rings!
I can't do that.
Those rings are locked away
in a safe in the principal's office.
Then let me borrow your ring!
No can do.
Breaking the rules will lead
to docked points toward graduation.
It'll make it hard for you to graduate.
I didn't come to this school to graduate.
All I want is to become human
and stay by Seiko's side.
You're the only one I can ask, Hitoma!
I'll do anything if you do me this favor!
So please, help me!
Hitoma?
I know!
Why don't you come with me, then?
What?
You'll basically be my chaperone!
There's nothing to be scared
of if we're together!
Scared?
Yeah, I'm scared.
I'm scared of hurting
one of my students again.
I'm scared of causing someone's misery.
I'm scared of being betrayed.
Hitoma?
Please...
I need your help.
You're prepared to face the consequences?
Of course.
I'm here!
No trouble slipping out of the dorms?
None at all.
I wasn't spotted by anyone.
The barrier extends to this cherry tree.
You need this ring's power in order
to go any further and remain human.
Going off of prior experience,
I and anything I touch can pass through
the barrier as long as I wear the ring.
That means as long as you're in contact,
the ring's effect is passed onto you.
From here on, we'll have to
keep holding hands...
Hey!
Don't look so blatantly upset at the idea!
Ugh...
Didn't we shake hands
back in the classroom?
That's different from holding hands.
What?
So be it.
Let's get going.
Hospital visiting hours end at seven.
Depending on when we arrive,
Usami has an hour max with Mrs. Kizaki.
Looks like this is it.
Are you okay, Usami?
I'm fine.
Calpis
Huh?
Usami.
What is it?
Will you be fine by yourself from here?
Won't it be easier to talk
with Mrs. Kizaki if I'm not there?
Huh?
What about the ring, then?
You want me to turn back into
a stuffed doll after coming all this way?
I'll let you hold onto the ring.
When I take the ring off,
I'll lose my memories from school,
but I'll remember everything again
when I touch the ring.
However, that doesn't apply to you.
You want me to go see her alone?
Well, you see, I stayed up
all night playing video games.
The lack of sleep's
finally caught up to me.
Besides, you made me suddenly
come all the way here.
I'd like a little time to rest.
I'll be napping, so pop in and
say hi real quickly to your friend.
Oh, but I have trouble sleeping,
so I took my usual sleeping pills.
You're so stupid.
Huh?
If you really were sleepy,
you wouldn't have to take pills.
That's true.
Maybe I'm stupid.
Stick out your pinky.
Okay...
Good night, Usami.
I hope you can have a good talk with her.
Who is it?
Do you have the wrong room?
No, I don't.
Are you friends with my granddaughter?
That's not it.
I'm the only one in this room.
It's the right room.
I came here to see you, Seiko.
"Seiko"?
I know it's hard to
believe, but I'm Usami.
Usami, the stuffed rabbit
who was always by your side!
Usami?
Sorry, I know that came out of nowhere.
It's okay if you don't believe
me since this is all so sudden.
For you.
It's Calpis, your favorite.
You said you had some
the first time you hung out with Ken.
How do you know that?
Are you really my Usami?
That's right.
I've been with you longer
than anyone else has!
It's me, Usami!
That's...
the hair clip I gave to Usami...
That's right.
Four years ago, when you
lost Ken, you felt so sad.
Usami...
Usami... It's really you.
Seiko.
I wanted to see you all this time!
Seiko, I have...
I have so many things to tell you!
Yes.
I'm sorry for leaving you so suddenly.
I wanted to become human
so I could be with you!
After Ken passed away,
you were always crying...
That's why all this time,
I wanted to say I love you!
All this time, I wanted to say thank you!
I feel the same way.
Thank you.
Usami.
I'll always love you, too.
Next year, I'll graduate and become human!
Really?
Best of luck. I'll be rooting for you.
Yeah!
I'll make sure I become human!
And then we can live together, Seiko.
I'll never leave you alone again!
We'll always be together!
Usami.
I'm sorry.
You see...
I only have a month to live.
So you see, I can't be there
to live with you.
I...
I don't want that...
Yes, I wanted to live with you as well.
If you'll be gone, then all
of my work is for nothing!
I'm sorry.
But I don't think that your efforts
were meaningless.
They are!
I've worked so hard just for you, Seiko!
It was a mistake trying to become human!
I should have just stayed
as a stuffed animal with you!
Don't say such sad things.
Usami, do you like humans?
I like you, Seiko.
I've been through a lot, but when all's
said and done, I still like humans.
Lots of humans are nasty.
Yes, but I still like them.
So you don't like stuffed animals?
No, I like them, too.
You say you like everything.
How easy to please.
Usami, what else do you like beside me?
School's not so bad.
Studying, too.
It's fun learning about new things.
And I don't hate humans, either.
I see.
Any plans for the future?
I'm still not sure.
But...
Oh, that reminds me.
Did you come here all alone?
Hitoma... I mean, my teacher came with me.
He was considerate enough
to let us talk in private.
Sounds like a great teacher.
He's not half bad.
Although he's unreliable.
Say, could it be that
you have a crush on him?
Wh-Where did that come from?!
Since I was a girl, all I ever did
was talk to you about boys.
So, am I right?
N-Not a chance!
You're the only one for me, Seiko!
Oh?
So he really has no chance?
You're a big meanie, Seiko!
Mrs. Kizaki, I'm here
to take your temperature.
Oh, is this your granddaughter?
Oh? Yes.
I'm afraid visiting hours ended at seven.
I-I'm sorry.
Seiko.
Thanks for all the
affection you showed me.
Thank you, too.
I'll always love you!
Thanks, Mr. Hitoma.
I got to talk to Seiko.
Mr. Hitoma?
I'm going to become human.
I made a promise to Seiko.
I know what I want to do in the future.
I want to help humans.
By becoming a doctor.
I want to help people spend more time
with their loved ones.
It's not easy becoming a doctor.
Thanks, Mr. Hitoma.
It's because of you
that I've found a new goal.
So sleepy.
And wait, who are you?
Wake up!
Hitoma.
Did you forget that we need
to keep holding hands?!
What?
It's time for us to leave!
The hospital's about to kick us out!
Hospital?
Oh, I remember now!
Did you manage to talk to her?
Yeah.
That's good.
You nincompoop!
Despite his appearance, the principal's
super scary when he's angry.
Hope you're hanging in there, Mr. Hitoma.
Thank you very much.
Well, I brought it upon myself.
It can't be easy taking a pay cut
for three months.
I'm glad I got off with just a pay cut.
That aside, Usami
was suspended for a week.
What's more, she lost 150 of her
points needed to become human.
I don't think she'll be
graduating this year...
Good morning, Hitoma.
G-Good morning.
What's the big deal?
That fishy look of yours creeps me out.
You're the one who scared me.
What's up?
I don't need you.
If you don't need me, why'd you come here?
Good morning, Miss Usami.
Long time no see, Mr. Hoshino.
Good morning.
How come you never add the "Mr." for me?
You don't deserve it, Hitoma.
Mr. Hoshino, please tell her off.
Our school values
the autonomy of its students.
Anyway, you need to work harder, Hitoma.
Do a good job teaching me
so I can become a doctor.
Work hard so I can earn my license.
I'll do what I can.
Next Episode:
The Misanthrope and Tobari's Hymn