Welcome! Step right up!
I'm bored.
My ban's finally lifted, but
Cecilia's too busy to hang out.
You won't find these anywhere else!
Kramen?
Oh, hey, Yoki.
Off work today?
Yeah, well, since I haven't bought
an anniversary gift yet...
You still haven't given her anything?
Okay, then! I'll help you out!
Maybe she'd like one of these?
It'll go great with a maid uniform,
and it's right in line with your tastes!
The only thing I'm into
is the maid uniform!
Nah, you gotta get this.
Like hell I do!
I've already bought what I came here for.
Oh, okay. Sorry, man.
That black full-length
coat is a chuuni's dream!
And that bat-shaped full-face helmet!
Awesome! It's perfect!
R-Really?
Would you like to try them on?
Of course. I want the
zig-zaggy sword, too.
Well?
This is indeed the appearance
my soul has long desired!
Yikes.
Are you serious?
Of course!
Now, Kramen, give me a quest!
I will handle any mission you
may have in the blink of an eye!
What? Didn't you take today off?
Yeah, but you know.
Is that...
a new shikigami of yours?
Who are you calling a shikigami?!
He's an old acquaintance. I'm giving him
some pesky quests I've had piling up.
We only have four Rank A quests right now.
Which would you like?
All of them.
What?! Four at one time?!
Sure. Leave them to me.
And, um... what's your name?
The Magic Swordsman of Black Lightning!
THE MAGIC SWORDSMAN OF BLACK LIGHTNING
You heard the man. Sign him up.
You will regret showing
yourself before me!
That is the power of my magic sword!
The heart of a dragon. All yours.
Thank you so much!
This will save my daughter's life!
He took down a dragon?
Incredible...
He's definitely talented, at least.
Well, this is the last quest.
Holy Bell!
Way to go, boss!
The target is up past here.
Roger dodger!
Dodger!
We'll be taking everything in here.
All of it!
Behave yourself and we won't hurt you.
Who's there?!
I've found you, Phantom Thief Envy!
Hup!
Don't think you can run from the
Magic Swordsman of Black Lightning.
If you come quietly, you won't
get hurt. What'll it be?
Wh-Wh-Who the heck is this weirdo?
He's making me embarrassed.
This clown stands in the
way of our ambition!
Get him, Jealousy, Heartburn!
Just leave this to us!
To us!
And now, it's showtime!
Taste my lightning!
It's all tingly!
Well, I can use magic, too!
You will become rust on my magic sword!
Don't worry. It's blunt-edged.
Th-Thank you.
You're unhurt?
Yes! Now I can deliver these Valentine's
chocolates to the townspeople!
Valentine's?
They have Valentine's
Day in this world, too?
What's going on?
Who are you?
I am the Magic Swordsman of Black
Lightning. No one to be suspicious of.
I knew it.
It's Yoki.
Did you do this?
Don't get the wrong idea.
These three are thieves.
I'll let all of you take
it from here. Farewell!
Wait!
No need to pursue.
We don't need to pursue
that guy, apparently.
A-All right.
The people are on the ground are
Phantom Thief Envy and his buddies,
as the quest described.
Let's take them in right away.
Right.
I'll take a look around the area.
So that's how Raven's
been communicating, huh?
What was he doing before
Duke joined the order?
I know you're still here, Captain.
He's so damn sharp!
I don't know how long you've
been a magic swordsman...
The Magic Swordsman of Black Lightning!
...but you should probably start
coming back to your senses now.
You get all embarrassed and start
thrashing around after every rampage.
It's a real headache, you know, Captain.
I thought you'd be more normal
since you came to the humans' city.
You might want to look in a mirror.
Hmph!
Isn't this all-black
outfit awesome, though?
I've done it again!
Here's your reward for nabbing
Envy and his buddies.
Thank ya!
What was up with them, anyway?
They used to be B-Rank adventurers,
but then they found some weird book in
a dungeon and went off the deep end.
What's that all about?
They said they were going
to destroy Valentine's Day
and started stealing cacao and chocolate.
I mean, I get how they feel, but...
Begin by melting it over hot water.
Teacher...
Very good.
First hurdle.
Getting the right water
temperature is crucial.
Miss Sophia, this won't crack.
Oh, my.
Thank you!
Not a problem.
You sure are making a lot.
I'll give them to the kids at the
orphanage and everyone who's helped me.
You're supposed to give your Valentine's
Day gift to someone special.
Don't you know anything?
You've awakened, boy?
Today seems to be the day
they call "Valentine's Day."
Y-Yeah?
Cecilia...
My guardian deity!
They're chocolates with magicite in them!
Th-Thank you.
Here, guardian deity. Open wide.
W-Wait... we aren't alone...
Yes, it's delicious.
Great!
Hey.
What's in the box?
Oh, this?
This is...
I-It's blinding!
That's an insane amount of energy!
That's...
Wait, it's chocolate?!
Today's Valentine's Day, you know.
Sophia made them herself.
The refined sweetness fills my
mouth! I feel like I'm in heaven!
Yes! My woman is the best in the world!
Lucky...
Just so you know, you can't have any!
I don't want any, damn it!
I hope you explode!
And that's why you're here, huh?
Well, I can't go back to my room.
E-Excuse me.
I'm not interrupting anything, am I?
Oh... um...
Go.
Yes, sir.
Um, Duke...
This is for you.
Are you sure I can have this?
Oh, um...
You've always been there for me at work.
I'm grateful, and I really respect you.
Really? Sorry to put you
through the trouble.
Feel free to come to me
for advice again anytime.
I will!
Sorry about that... I...
I hope you explode, too!
Yoki!
Raven... Not you, too...
I hope you explode!
Step right up! We've still
got chocolates and cakes!
I can't root for anyone's
romantic endeavors today.
What's that line for?
Drop off chocolates for
the hero right here!
Hero!
Please hurry!
If you want to give them to him
personally, the line's over there!
Damn it! What the hell?!
Just how popular can a guy be?!
This world is so unfair!
Oh, if it isn't the civilian.
Oh, hey, Mikana. Are you
getting in line, too?
I'm not sure. I'm not a
good cook or anything.
Maybe I should just go home.
Huh? Er, um...
Oh, there you are!
Yuga!
Sorry to keep you waiting. Good
to see you again too, Yoki!
What are you doing here?
Everyone's waiting for you.
Yeah, sorry. But I wanted to
get your chocolates first.
B-But...
they came out weird again this year,
so they probably aren't any good...
That's fine. I'll take them.
Wh-What the hell?!
See? They're no good, right?
This goes way beyond that!
What're you talking about? They're great!
For real?!
I just don't feel like it's Valentine's Day
until I've had your chocolates, Mikana.
Hey, isn't that Yuga?
Move it! Eternal Friend!
Welp, I still ended up here.
I'm so pathetic.
My, if it isn't Yoki.
Captain!
If you're looking for
Cecilia, she went to town.
I see...
Look what I got!
Here's some for you, too.
N-No... I don't want chocolates
from anyone other than Cecilia...
Oh? Mine aren't good enough for you?
Yay! More for me!
I'll take them.
That's a good boy.
Captain!
Envy has escaped from prison!
What?!
Thank you, Lady Cecilia.
That was...
We speak for all those
who have been alienated by the
blessings of Valentine's Day!
The chocolates!
How could this be happening?!
Serves you right!
Bring down the hammer on all those who
are fawned on for their good looks!
Bring it down!
Stop it!
Are you trying to ruin Valentine's Day?!
Shut up! A hot guy like you
who gets tons of chocolates
has no idea how miserable we feel!
No idea!
That's right! People like you are
always belittling people like me!
Watch out!
Are you okay?!
They're really making a mess of things.
I'll hold the monster here.
You guys get the townsfolk to safety!
This is the end of Valentine's Day!
Hold it!
Who are you?
Enough of this senseless violence.
Who the hell are you?
Are you?!
I completely understand how you feel.
If my position were slightly different,
I might be doing what you're doing.
It sounds kind of moving
if you're barely listening,
but what he's actually
saying is pretty damn sad.
But flying into a rage because
you didn't get chocolates
is the height of foolishness!
You look like you're in the
same boat as us, though!
I bet you haven't gotten any chocolates!
I did.
From who?
My friend's mom.
Wow. Embarrassing.
Doesn't admitting that
feel meaningless to you?!
It's not meaningless!
It's not as if you're holding out any
hope for Valentine's Day, either!
I am!
I won't give up on getting chocolates
from the girl I love
until this day is over!
The girl you love?!
See?! You want to get chocolates
from the one you love, too!
Getting chocolates from someone who
doesn't matter is just a headache!
It is not!
As long as their heart went into
that chocolate, it makes me happy!
Liar!
Yoki!
Cecilia!
No!
Wait!
Those are all of our chocolates!
We don't know what'll happen
if we damage that thing!
Give them back.
Give them back. Give them back!
Give Cecilia's chocolate back!
Oh, no!
You... were a girl all along?
Shut up!
There are girls who hate
Valentine's Day, too!
I-I don't want chocolates
from a tomboy like you!
But...
Nobody ever wants my chocolates.
So I... I...
That's not true.
Huh?
You can only say that because you're hot!
I'm happy to get chocolates from anyone
as long as their heart went into it.
Hero...
Here we go again.
You're getting all the glory in the end?!
This is why I hate hot guys!
Yoki, you did so well.
Oh, right.
Would you... accept this?
Of course!
Thank goodness.
Oh, she gave you some, too?
Those cookies are really good.
What? You guys got the same thing?
WITH MY THANKS FOR EVERYTHING YOU DO
Huh? There's a cake, too.
"With my thanks for everything you do"?
What? No fair! Why did only you get cake?
Huh?
It's one of a kind.
You mean...
Hell yeah!