In the near future, e-Pulse is
generated by human thoughts and emotions,
and used as an energy source
for AI devices called "Sapotamas,"
leading to a new development for humanity.
But from its shadows,
terrifying monsters have appeared.
Monsters that evolve by consuming e-Pulse.
They are...
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
Beyond where no one can stop me
I'll make my way there
As I seek the answer
Carve your emotion
It reverberates
The tempo that synchs
Is a pulse that slowly reveals
The hidden world
Record on top of the solid Baseline
Don't mess up tempo
Normal's not enough for me
Just keep howling, howling!!!
Howling like it's all you've got
Even if what you believe begins to blur
The reality that you grasp
Rings strong and true
nigirishimeru Riaru wa
uso janaku tsuyoku hibiku
Take away the Metronome
For this one and only JAM
Metronome topparau ichido kiri kono JAM
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
The emotional beat that rings out
kanjou no mama narasu kodou wa
Is the BPM that continues on and on
sou zutto hashiritsuzukeru BPM
(Let the beat lead the way)
The Cloudy rain swallows the city
matenrou nomikomu Cloudy Rain
Even if I link and the rhythm warps
I just make it part of my groove
rinkushite rizumu yoretatte
Groove ni shichaeba ii
Ride it like you see fit
norikonase omoidoori
(Let the beat lead the way)
Even if it hurts, I won't stop
itami daite mo tomarazu ni
Keep carving the beat
Won't back down
kizami tsudzukeru kodou
We can overcome anything
bokura nara donna koto mo norikoerareru
Drum to your emotion
tatakitsukero Emotion
Klay.
Hmm.
Can I get a Blood and Sand?
It's okay, Cougarmon.
That Tinkermon...
It would have sold
for at least 100 million Credits.
Your family has cost me
several billion in damages.
You owe me at least one drink.
Didn't you pretend
you weren't involved on the news?
A Five Star,
Klay the Surging holding
a Digimon black market auction...
Is Chairman Wong involved, too?
That old man's time has passed.
If I teamed up with the one
they called Kyo the Golden,
the World Union could be in our hands.
Don't you think so?
Chairman Wong thinks Digimon
are a power he's been granted.
True.
And you only see Digimon
as tools for profit.
You're both the same in my eyes.
So you won't take my offer.
Stay out of my way from now on.
I wouldn't want your family
to come to harm.
Hey! Are you saying...
Is Zakky here?
PROOF OF GENIUS
Here's extra for taking down
the Digimon auction.
We didn't mean to.
Why aren't we meeting at Garando?
The female buyer we arrested.
Someone Cold-Hearted her inside
the Ministry of Civil Protection.
How's that possible?
The real sponsor
of the Digimon auction silenced her.
I've been trying to catch him.
But he's protected by power and money.
Klay Arslan.
But he's a Five Star.
The Ministry was created by the government
on orders of the World Union, was it not?
And the Five Stars work directly
for the World Union.
To arrest him for his crimes,
I need concrete evidence.
Kyo Sawashiro.
I'm not taking the job.
You'll be well compensated.
Taking on a Five Star
will end in more than just bruises.
Klay runs the Tactics, right?!
He has Haruomi and Raito do dirty jobs!
We want to help them. And Hotaruko.
Stay away from this.
That's my answer.
What's with Kyo?
That Flanmon's a Five Star, right?
You mean Flaremon.
They reduced you to a Kekomon.
Did that really happen?
An Ultimate Digimon.
We're already struggling against Raito.
A monkey Digimon?
Could it be...?
Tomoro, you're here!
I'm here for a checkup...
The color of that e-Pulse!
That's the Digimon we encountered!
Give that back!
I've been looking for Asuka's e-Pulse!
Smash Beat!
Tomoro!
-What the heck?
-Ow, ya know!
Who will be the one
to challenge our champion?
In the blue corner!
A Cleaner from the Glowing Dawn!
It's Tomoro and Gekkomon!
Where the heck are we?
Check it out, ya know!
...defeated numerous Digimon!
Where's the monkey Digimon?
Look! I'm huge, ya know!
And in the red corner! A legendary
veteran fighter! His name is...
Tomoro!
Excuse me.
Look at this.
Greymon starts with a Mega Flame!
Has the rookie been incinerated?
Why am I watching a preliminary match?
Gekkomon evolved into Armalizamon!
Try a little harder,
or the betting won't get exciting.
What? Betting?
People are betting on Digimon battles?
But Greymon's unbeatable!
Someone hacked the system
and entered Tomoro Tenma.
Kyo Sawashiro...?
No. He'd never put his family
at such risk.
Shall we pay back the wagers
and void the match?
Find out who's behind this first.
Greymon!
I don't know what's going on,
but I'll take that plight, ya know!
You mean "Take that fight."
And don't take it.
Neutron Diffuser!
It's over!
My Greymon!
...if deleted or reverted
to In-Training state!
Don't!
Gekkomon and Tomoro will go up against
our seven-time champion...
Monodramon and Raito!
Raito?!
What are they doing here?
I'll cancel tomorrow's match.
No. The audience seems quite excited.
Then, after the match,
I'll have them both processed.
Good.
And find who hacked our system.
Yes, sir.
So, you got fired from Tactics
for deleting Tinkermon?
But Raito intends to win his way up
this colosseum and back into the Tactics.
Whatever. I'm looking for the Digimon
who stole my brother's e-Pulse.
Gekkomon, break open this cell.
Sure. But I'm kind of hungry.
Gimme your Sapotama.
Raito, we should tell them.
Huh? It's not charging.
I'm hungry, ya know.
Hold on.
What's going on?
In these cells, e-Pulse is absorbed,
preventing Digimon from feeding.
It's to keep stupid fools like you
from trying anything.
What?!
Just sit still until the match.
I don't have time for a match!
Don't do it! Let me go!
Please! I'm begging you!
Greymon's Owner?
Where are they taking him?
Losers all vanish.
That'll happen to you tomorrow.
Oh come on!
Not a word from Tomoro or Gekkomon.
If what that Hitomi girl said is true,
they were taken to the Mirror World.
Chiropmon is scouring the internet,
but we haven't found a trace.
Zakky?
We've got a lead.
Akasaka the jewel thief confessed.
Digimon are made to fight,
and wealthy people
all over the world bet on it
at a secret colosseum on the internet.
The Mirror World is a collection
of virtual worlds on the internet.
In a place that should be inaccessible
without a special pass,
they're betting on illegal Digimon fights.
This is Klay's main business.
The match between the champions
and the new challengers is beginning!
Bets may be placed
starting at a million Credits!
The challengers are Tomoro and Gekkomon!
What?!
Ever since I was a child,
they said I was a genius.
I could mimic anything I saw even once.
Games...
Sports...
Studies...
There was nothing I couldn't do.
The one thing I struggled at...
was controlling a Digimon.
But not anymore.
I'm going to win and force Naito to say,
"You're a genius."
I know. You're a genius.
You can do it.
I recognize that smell, ya know.
Hey! Get back here!
-Hey!
-It's fine.
Let them see their own fate.
Is it the monkey Digimon?
This is what awaits the losers?
How dare they!
You'll be brought here soon.
Now get out there!
Tomoro?
We can't leave Raito and Monodramon here.
Gekkomon can evolve
into their Champion form, Armalizamon.
But Monodramon can evolve into
their Ultimate form, Azhdarmon!
The odds are 90 to one
against the challengers!
My e-Pulse is flowing normally.
Go, Monodramon!
-Beat Knuckle!
-Already, ya know?
Raito, we're getting out of here!
Come with us!
There's those silly emotions
driving you again.
I don't intend to run away.
Aren't they forcing you to fight?
I'm going to keep winning.
That'll be my proof.
What do you need to prove?!
Monodramon!
I'll prove that I'm a genius!
Monodramon Evolution!
Rhamphomon!
An evolution to Rhamphomon already?
Will this end it?
Tomoro, make me evolve, too, ya know!
Tomoro!
The hacker is incredibly skilled.
It's almost like they know
our system inside and out.
Continue analyzing.
Let's just enjoy Raito's final match.
What are you doing, Tomoro!
You've gotta evolve, too!
Maybe he doesn't want to fight Raito.
The Ministry cannot allow
Digimon to be used for gambling.
I need evidence against Klay.
Please.
I've traced the stream
and got their location.
Cougarmon.
Are you sure?
You'll be facing a Five Star.
We'll just have to dig in!
We're going to rescue...
Tomoro and Gekkomon.
Huh?
Hammer Strike!
Raito, there's no reason for us to fight!
I'm a genius. I need to prove that.
So you're doing this for selfish reasons.
You're here to find
your brother's e-Pulse, aren't you?
Look who's selfish!
Uh-oh! They're moving to slam
their target from high up!
They're moving for their No Hope Fall!
What happens to the Owners who lose?
They're removed from the colosseum.
Beyond that isn't my concern!
They get Cold Hearted.
Did you know? That's what happens
to the people who you beat!
Raito!
Haruomi told us.
Commandramon didn't want
to do those dirty jobs.
Monodramon is hurting people by winning.
You're making them hurt people!
I'll ask you again...
Knowing what happens to the losers,
are you still going to fight?
Rhamphomon!
Rhamphomon Evolution!
Azhdarmon!
Azhdarmon, you're crying, ya know!
I'm going to fight!
Raito, give me more e-Pulse!
I can control an Ultimate Digimon!
Tomahawk Strike!
Tomoro, they're in pain, ya know!
They're suffering, ya know!
And still, for Raito...
Raito, stop this!
Trinity Lightning!
Gekkomon!
Here goes!
Pound the beat!
Gekkomon Evolution!
Armalizamon!
How?
Their attacks are faster and stronger!
How can they keep getting stronger?
Darn it! How is that possible?!
Stop it! Forcing them to evolve
is hurting them!
I've seen both Kyo Sawashiro and Naito!
Anything I've seen once...
I can mimic!
I'm a genius!
I can do this.
Raito... I'll prove that you're a genius.
Time for dull welding!
Neutron Blade!
Tri Carve Rain!
Raito, you're a genius.
I've already accepted it.
Your acceptance means nothing!
But...
I'm taking you down today!
-For your own sake!
-For your own sake, ya know!
These two...
I get it. They're both...
feeling the same emotion.
It's amplifying their e-Pulse,
giving them more strength!
Raito! I'll prove that you're a genius!
Azhdarmon always thinks only of me.
But...
Tri Carve Rain!
I...
Don't let the normal be normal
atarimae wo atarimae ni shinai
Playing to the score is not enough
gakufu doori ja monotarinaindayo
Take in everything, even the noise
And make it our own session!
noizu sura mo torikonde
jibun dake no sesshon wo!
Things won't change in others' hands
Boot! Boot!
hitomakase ja kawaranaishi
Reach out your hand
te nobase
Don't be scared to mess up, go on
Boot! Boot!
machigai mo osorezu susume
With courage
yuukan ni
Go tell the rules NO
Error, error
ruuru ni tatakitsukeru NO
error, error
Scale out? Bring it on
Error, error
sukeeru auto joutou
error, error
An unexpected code
Error, error
yosoku funou no koodo
error, error
Prompts can't control these feelings
puronpto nanka ja seigyoudekinai omoide
Give it a shout
kamase shauto
BRAVE! No more fear
BRAVE! mou kowakunai
Keep my head high
utsumuitari mo shinai
I've got someone who's got my back
senaka azukeaeru kimi ga iru kara
GROOVE! We can't be stopped
GROOVE! mou tomaranai
Our beats are in unison
yunizon suru koudou ga
We're going to update the world
kitto sekaijuu wo appudeeto shiteiku
With a bang
bakuon de
Up until now I've always
made my own decisions.
By facing myself and Pristimon,
we gained a place where we belong!
You're letting someone else
control your fate!
Are you really okay with this?
It's your life!
So decide for yourself, Granit!
Next time on DIGIMON BEATBREAK,
"The One Beside You"