Step right up and have a look...
It's time for Yamishibai.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
Round and Around
This is the story of a married couple who
will soon be having their first child...
I'm going to be on maternity leave soon,
so kids from other classes have been
dropping by to give their regards.
I see. Well, you're quite a
popular teacher, after all.
I wouldn't say that.
But they are excited to meet the baby.
Yeah?
And then...
Sensei, did you get a
round and around yet?
Not yet, no.
Won't be long, now, though!
Hey, hang on. What are you talking about?
What do you mean? The round and around?
What even is that?
You know, the thing
that connects you to your
mom before you're born.
Oh, I get it now.
You mean the umbilical cord?
What about it?
I think I'll make some tea.
I'm thirsty.
Yeah, okay.
What the hell?
Shopping District
It's Asako-sensei!
Hello there!
Hello.
Sensei, did you round and around yet?
Not yet.
Round and around!
It definitely doesn't look
like it'll be much longer.
That's right. I'm equal
parts scared and excited.
Oh, I was so nervous
when I had my oldest.
What is this round and around stuff?
Why am I the only one who doesn't know?
The baby says it won't be long now!
Round and Around
Almost time! It's almost time!
Thank you all.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Round and around! Round and around!
Round and around!
Shut up!
Why are you so angry?
And when it's almost time
for round and around...
Imagine yelling like that. Honestly...
People won't shut up about it!
From kids to the elderly...
Why am I the only one who doesn't know?!
What are you all talking about?!
They're just saying
it won't be long now.
Round and around... Round and around...
Round and around... Round and
around...  Round and around...
Is... Is that the round and around?
Grandma?! But you've been
dead for so long...
And my great-grandma, too?!
Don't! Stay away from Asako!
Don't touch my baby!
There, there. Ain't nothin' to fear.
Congratulations on a healthy birth.
Thank you so much.
You had a nice round and
around, it looks like.
Yes.
When we've grown old
and lived out our lives,
we all become a part of
the round and around.
It just shows how far back
these connections go...
By the way, where's your husband?
He ended up inside
the round and around.
Theatre of Darkness: Yamishibai
The end.