I just wanted to talk, man to man.
So talk.
I thought you and Mizuki-kun
were going out,
but it seems that's not the case.
I figured I might as well play along
with your little guardian act.
Don't touch him.
I mean, the way you snatched up
Mizuki-kun after that fainting spell...
Made me feel like I should ask permission.
So, you don't mind if I partake,
do you, Sir Guardian?
Who he goes out with
is none of my business.
But it can't be you.
I can see I'm not liked here.
But if that's how things are,
let me ask you this.
Are you saying that as a guardian?
Or is that your heart talking?
Hey, hey, Mizuki-kun.
What's up, Tamami-chan?
I feel like I'm doing my best here...
Trying to be as attractive as possible.
Wearing clothes I think guys would like.
But... But even then...
No matter what I do,
he just won't look at me!
Is Izumi-sama really that dense?!
Er, I wouldn't say that...
Okay, so, I was hoping
to ask your opinion. As a guy.
M-Me?
I'm considering telling
Izumi-sama how I feel.
What do you think?
Wh-Why are you asking me?
He said it himself.
That you're the only person
he can be around
for very long without getting sick of it.
What?
I see, I see. Sano said that, did he?
But confessing, huh?
I've never even thought about doing it.
Would I have fallen in love with Sano
normally if I'd met him as a girl?
Although if I'd met him as a girl,
we wouldn't have been able to have
the relationship we do now.
So even if I can't say I love him
the way Tamami-chan can...
Can Things Stay This Way?
I wonder how Sano feels about her.
I finished up all the cleaning.
I was thinking of taking a break myself.
Great.
Perfect timing.
Keep an eye on her for a bit.
K-Kagurazaka!
Got a date with a girl
I picked up yesterday.
Take care of her.
Later!
What a terrible brother.
Nice.
Kyomi-chan, does that feel good?
Yeah.
Ever seen this, Kyomi?
You make a water gun with your hands.
Wanna try?
All right.
He likes to complain,
but he's actually very caring.
What are you doing, Kyomi?!
That went up my nose!
Hey, don't laugh, Mizuki!
Sorry, sorry.
Heya, Makita!
Oh, hey. It's you guys.
You just get back from shopping?
For work, yeah.
Say, whatever happened to that girl
with the long hair from last year?
You dumbass. You know he
switches out girls every year.
Already kicked her to the curb?
So dumb.
This year's cutie is a cut above, though.
Already got one in your scope?
You know me.
The poor girl!
Yeah, this guy's only after one thing.
That bastard...
That's cold, that's cold!
Wow, you're pretty tough.
Hey.
Oh? Sano?
You idiot. Have you forgotten
you just collapsed?
Don't let yourself get a chill!
Your shirt's also see-through when wet.
But the sun's so hot today.
No excuses!
You don't have to get all mad about it!
Yeah, he's right!
Just wrap yourself in the towel already!
Gosh, even my underwear got soaked.
Sano was right.
At this rate, I'll catch a cold.
Sano-kun, are you around?
A light bulb in the
second-floor hall needs...
Mizuki...kun?
No way!
Sh-She saw me?!
Mizuki-kun, you're a....
Io-san, please!
Don't tell anyone.
I'm begging you!
First of all, cover yourself up.
We can't even talk with you like this.
You will talk to me, won't you?
Yes.
I can't believe this.
So you chased after Sano-kun
all the way from America,
and you even lied about your gender?
I'm surprised nobody around
you has figured it out.
Not exactly.
He hasn't told anyone,
but Dr. Umeda knows.
Also, I use a denim vest to bind my chest.
I see.
So that's why you
passed out the other day.
I can't say I like this.
I'm sure your parents are already plenty
worried about you studying abroad here.
If they found out you were at an
all-boys school, they'd probably faint.
I know that.
But I still want to be with Sano.
Nothing's going to change that!
Well said!
What I just said
was my opinion as a mother.
But speaking as a woman...
Attagirl!
It must be the pinnacle of male happiness
to have a girl go so far for him.
Yes, indeed!
Um, so does that mean
you won't tell anyone?
I would never!
And if you have any problems,
come to me and I'll handle them for you!
In an empire of only men,
a lone flower blooms!
I just love it!
What a delicious situation!
"If only I could change, then I would!"
That's the pie-in-the-sky
dream all girls share.
Right...
She is Dr. Umeda's older sister.
However, Mizuki-kun...
Yes, ma'am?
You must never forget that you're a girl.
Huh?
Even if you put on their clothes
and adopt their mannerisms,
a girl who sneaks into all-boys
schools puts herself at risk.
Besides... things can't stay
like this forever, can they?
Things can't stay like this?
Of course not.
At some point, your chest will get
too big to conceal with a vest.
It works for now, but...
Plus, you're in love with Sano-kun, right?
Then that's another reason.
Do you really want things
to stay as they are?
Sano?
Are you already asleep?
No.
Um, listen...
Would you say I'm girly?
What?
Did Makita say that to you?
No.
Why are you even bringing him up?
It's just that... I...
Do you really want things
to stay as they are?
Actually, never mind.
Sorry.
Good night.
I don't know why you're
overthinking things again.
But I know that you're you.
If you suddenly started acting like
Nakatsu, it'd be creepy as hell.
The hell'd you just say?
Ya wanna beat-down, dumbass?!
If you get it, then go to sleep already.
We've got another early day tomorrow.
Yeah.
But you know, Sano...
I thought I was fine
with things the way they are.
As long as it means I can be with you.
But what if things can't
stay like this anymore?
I don't know what I should do.
You know, I really don't care,
but why the hell do we have
to shell beans with these guys?
How should I know?
So, Kagurazaka...
What happened on your hot date
with that girl you picked up?
Oh, don't bring that up.
She dumped him.
Tamami!
Lookin' good, Kyomi.
You're a real big help.
Yeah.
Oh, he's right.
You're doing a great job.
What? I'll help too!
Can you really afford
to be so chill, Sano?
What are you talking about?
That creep Makita just
drove off with Ashiya.
And?
Shouldn't you be worried?
Everyone takes the car to go shopping.
Yeah?
Guess you better just pray nothing
happens in the privacy of that car.
What's taking Makita and Mizuki so long?
We need to start preparing dinner soon.
Oh, they called earlier.
Sounds like the engine stalled.
They said they'd be
about an hour or two late.
Hey, Izumi?
Don't tell me that Makita-kun's...
What's wrong, Makita-san?
It's about Sano-kun.
Sano?
It seems to me like you
have feelings for him,
but I think he only sees you as a friend.
I know that!
You should switch to me.
I won't ever leave you feeling bad.
Don't tell me he still sees me as a girl.
U-Uh, Makita-san...
I like you.
All this time, I couldn't
get you out of my head.
No!
Not so fast.
Hey! Makita-san!
I wish you'd quit being such
a little girl about this,
Mizuki-chan.
Stop!
Ashiya?
Are you okay?!
Ashiya!
Stop!
I'm scared!
Mizuki!
Don't worry!
You're safe now!
I'm here.
You're okay.
You're safe now.
The sun's completely set.
No signal
I figured as much.
What? Where am I?
I... What happened?
You awake now?
Sano!
Where are we?
I was trying to get us home when
I slipped and we fell down here.
Can you get up?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Are you all right?
Looks like it's sprained.
If Sano hadn't come
to save me back then,
I...
I'm sorry.
We're only down here
because I was careless.
That's nothing!
I'm the one...
I'm the one who...
You saved me, so thank you.
I was stupid. Really, really stupid.
If only I'd listened to what you said...
Stop it.
Blaming yourself in this situation
will just make you feel worse.
Sorry.
Still, it's true that you're dumb.
Come on.
Even with a swollen ankle,
you'll be all right, yeah?
Nothing else hurts, right?
R-Right. Thanks.
I found some fresh
spring water over there,
so I'm sure we'll be fine for now.
Welcome back.
Got your face rearranged?
Boss...
I told you, didn't I?
I don't care about your love life,
but what are you doing indiscriminately
going after a teenage boy?
Wh-What? A boy?
That's right!
Looks like he didn't get far...
You know that Mizuki and his friends
all go to a proper boys' school, right?
Where are they, anyway?
Wait, they're not back yet?
The moss is too slippery
everywhere to get up.
Not like you could climb with your ankle.
We'll just have to wait here for rescue.
I'm sorry.
I didn't say it to make you feel bad.
Nakatsu and Io-san must
be worried about us.
Yeah, probably.
I'm sorry I got you mixed up
in this weirdness.
Are you still going on about tha—
I was... really scared.
When I think about what would've
happened if you hadn't come to save me...
It's weird, right?
A guy being so unmanly about this...
I mean, almost being assaulted as a guy
is pathetic to begin with.
You're safe now.
Yeah.
The warmth you give off feels nice.
I think you're running a fever.
Hey, that's not funny.
I wasn't making a joke.
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I knew it.
You have a fever.
Really?
I didn't even notice.
If you're tired, you can lean on me.
Okay. Sorry.
Seriously!
Er, sor—
At least let me help you
at a time like this.
Not that I can do much more
than lend you a shoulder.
No, that's enough.
Thank you.
They're really late.
Let's just wait until morning.
If they're not back by then,
we'll request a search party.
We don't have time for that!
Io-san, can you get the car?
I'm going out right now!
Are you okay?
Yeah, your arm's nice and reassuring.
I'm going to climb up somehow
and call for help after all.
You just stay put right here.
I'll be right back.
No!
Don't go!
Please don't go...
Stay with me.
Damn it.
What should I do?
I wonder... What's that sound?
It's so soothing.
I'll always stay with you.
What is it, Yujiro?!
There you are!
Hey! Mizuki! Izumi!
Took you freakin' long enough.
Are you all right?
Yeah. It just hurts a little bit.
Good.
Looks like your fever has gone down too.
Is Makita-san still...
He left this morning.
I see...
If you're well enough, why don't you
go reassure those worried idiots?
Especially Sano-kun.
He held you so protectively
after you came down with that fever.
After that, take the day to rest.
So Sano holding me actually happened?
But the kiss... That was just a
conveniently nice dream, right?
Are you well enough to be up already?
Hey, Sano. Yeah, I'm fine.
Really? That's good.
We're going home tomorrow, so get ready.
Sano!
Yeah?
Um... th-thanks for yesterday!
S-Sure.
Well, I've still got some work to do.
Yeah, okay.
Break a leg.
It wasn't a dream. Probably.
Hey, Mizuki!
You all better now?
Yeah!
Sorry for all the trouble.
Though it wasn't for long,
having you here was a huge help.
Thank you!
Huh?
Kagurazaka?
What a relief I don't have to see
your stupid faces anymore after today.
You say something, Kagupi?
Do not call me that!
Why can't he just be upfront
and say he came to see us off?
Oh, where's Tamami-chan?
Beats me.
She came back in tears yesterday,
then crawled into bed
and hasn't come out since.
I'm guessing the teacher in the
back said something to her.
I'm considering telling
Izumi-sama how I feel.
I see.
Kyomi, take care, ya hear?
Okay, Kyomi.
Say bye to them forever.
You were a real royal pain,
but I can't bring myself to hate ya.
It's time to catch your train, kids.
See ya.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Heh, get him.
C'mon, Kyomi! Lemme go!
Kyomi...
My, my. Looks like she's taken
quite a liking to you.
Kyomi-chan...
Don't cry.
Look, I'm givin' ya this.
Make sure you take care
of it until we meet again!
Got it?
All righty now.
Come back next year.
As guests, you hear?
Thank you for everything!
School Festival
Mizuki-kun, what made you
fall for Sano-kun?
Wh-What's gotten into you, Io-san?
Was it his height? His cool demeanor?!
Oh, or maybe the flashes of loneliness
that break through sometimes?!
Wow, Io-san, your powers
of observation are amazing.
Next Time
I Don't Look Good in Women's Clothing!