Gross! Who makes chocolate
banana-flavored yakisoba?!
Get me the boss of whatever company
had the nerve to produce this crap!
How wrong do you have to
go to end up like him?
Jun, we want to defeat Ramaga.
We need your help.
To communicate with
the Divine World, you mean?
The what world?
A realm distinct from our world
and the Demon World,
where the servants of the gods gather.
Communicating with it is supposed
to require special spiritual training.
Servants...
...of the gods?
The Armor of the Supreme Emperor
was made in the Divine World.
As armors go, it's bad news. They say
it will "lead the world to its doom."
Supposedly, you need the
Three Sacred Treasures to summon it.
We know.
The Sword of Domination here,
the Jewel of Conquest, and...
The Mirror of Supremacy.
We want to know where to find it.
I can't help you.
I'm a failure at life. I quit my training
and let everyone down.
Jun...
Laugh at me all you want!
I grew into nothing but a fat, flabby pig!
I'm—
Jun, you...
idiot!
Remember now?
Remember how brave you used to be?
It's been 35 years, huh?
Since the last time you hit me!
Jun!
Nasti! You brought me to my senses!
How old-school can they get?
I don't believe it!
The chocolate banana flavor
is as good as I remember!
That's your problem?
Naumaku sanmanda bodanan abiraunken.
Are these "servants of the gods"
really out there?
O Divine World! Reveal to me the path!
I am called Sagume Yashima.
What business do you have
with the Divine World?
It's never worked before.
Lady Sagume Yashima!
So that we may halt the demonic invasion,
please tell us where we may find
the Mirror of Supremacy, key to the
Armor of the Supreme Emperor!
Very well.
We of the Divine World do not
begrudge you our aid to preserve order.
I shall illuminate its location.
Coordinates fixed!
Projected location is north-northwest,
at the foot of Mt. Shinshin.
The most likely candidate is
the Forest of Truth orphanage.
You mean...
EPISODE VII
MEMORY
So, the Divine World
has stepped in at last.
Sire, all has proceeded
as you foresaw—
Emperor Ramaga!
I will...
I will let no one interfere.
This "Forest of Truth" place
is definitely suspicious.
Yamato and Musashi having grown up there
seems like too much of a coincidence.
Why did you come in here?!
I never want to go back to that place.
Musashi...
Quit whining about it.
You know we've got to go.
Here comes the somen!
Time for the next round!
The Armor of the Supreme Emperor
could threaten the Demon World,
and we must prevent its
summoning at any cost, you say?
Naturally, Emperor Ramaga does not agree.
He desires it for himself.
Why tell me this?
Because you mourn Nezu's death
more than any of us.
Well, all right.
I'll take your deal.
You used your spirit to possess it?
That said,
I'm going to avenge Nezu my way.
Anayama...
I know. I'll pretend like it was my idea.
What are you egging on Anayama for?
I was hardly—
Don't give me that! I'm not letting you
run everything around here!
I could keep this up all day!
Bring it on!
I'll scoop it all up!
Don't you think it's strange?
We're out of the city.
Why are there so many Puppets?
Good point.
By the way, I'm still getting used
to the whole power of Light thing,
so why must I memorize
golden oldies as well?
DEMON ULTIMATE SONG COLLECTION 100
What's the point
of singing in battle at all?
Singing sort of brings us together.
You could say we sync up with it.
I'd like a more scientific explanation.
Try it. You'll see.
If that's your tune, then fine.
Come on, Musashi, Yamato!
Let's go with... "Yume o Shinjite"!
Wait, wait, wait!
We're not "syncing up"! I'm singing solo!
How am I supposed to "believe in dreams"
when I can't even count on my teammates?!
Shove it. I'm not in the
mood for that song.
You got a problem with my selection?
No, it's just...
Our... old teacher liked that song.
You mean the one
at the orphanage we're going to?
Yeah.
Why can't you follow the rules?!
Mr. Ujihara, I—
Bad children get punished!
What's your problem?!
Stop! Stop it!
I thought we'd never
have to see him again.
Mr. Ujihara...
Oh! How nice of you to come.
I don't see any kids.
That's right. The orphanage
shut down last year.
Still, I never expected you boys
would become Samurai Troopers.
So, Mr. Ujihara, about
the Mirror of Supremacy...
I'm sorry. I'd like to help,
but I can't even hazard a guess.
We know that it's here!
Sit, boy!
We may be able to come back
from this unprecedented disaster
if we can find that mirror.
MIRROR OF SUPREMACY
Does this look familiar to you?
It's hard to say...
Figures. The only guy who knows
what it looks like can't draw.
Jun, where did you see
the Mirror of Supremacy?
I've never seen it.
Huh?! But you drew it like
you knew what you were doing!
I let my imagination run wild, you know?
Could you be any more cringe?
How rude!
I can hear you! Don't think I won't cry!
Hey, why are we just
giving up and walking out?
Grilling that man won't get us anywhere.
Let's leave this to Yamato and Musashi.
CAT, LOVE -MUSASHI HOJO, RHINO BEETLE
There were always about
ten kids here in our day, right?
Yes, there were.
What you did was abuse
no matter how you look at it.
Hey.
I suppose it was.
I had everything all wrong.
I tried to force everyone into place.
It took you boys leaving
for me to finally see that.
I'm so sorry about those days!
Mr. Ujihara...
Any luck?
He says he really doesn't know.
Nothing, huh?
But we did get to make our peace with him.
That's a big deal for me.
It didn't feel that way to me, but
there is something different about him.
About that. Don't you remember
how he used to be—
Hey, doesn't something seem weird to you?
The Puppets aren't attacking this place?
Excellent!
A barrier, huh?
Some kind of force is keeping them out.
It's not demonic, either.
Who would do that?
Could it be the Mirror of Supremacy?
Okay!
We'll just have to search
every nook and cranny.
That ought to turn up a safe or two.
A safe?
That's it!
The day that Yama and I ran away,
we were playing hide-and-seek
with the others
and tried to find a hiding place
in Mr. Ujihara's office.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Maybe that's where it is.
Where's Mr. Ujihara?
Yama's talking with him downstairs.
You better keep your eyes peeled for him!
I know. Gimme a break.
I'm sure it was around here.
Found it?
Except it looks like it needs a passcode.
Just bust it open.
The mirror might be inside.
Do any numbers come to mind?
A birthday, maybe?
Mr. Ujihara's birthday?
I've got it. There was one day
a year he made us all sing.
APRIL
Why was I smiling back then?
Who cares? What day was it?
Oh, uh, April 13th. So... 0413.
It opened!
This is the Mirror of Supremacy?
So that's where it was.
Mr. Ujihara!
Where's Yama?
I had him take a nap.
Shion!
I could read all his memories except
the ones about the mirror.
You're not Mr. Ujihara. Who are you?!
His spirit can possess
any living thing he kills.
He's one of the Ten Warriors,
Anayama!
Correct.
Emperor Ramaga won't be too harsh
with me if I bring him that mirror!
I'm going to make you pay
for killing Nezu.
Yama! Shion!
I can't believe I let my guard down.
Where's Mr. Ujihara?
The real one is long dead.
I drew on his memories
to impersonate him.
I do pity the man.
If the Mirror of Supremacy
hadn't possessed him,
he might have led a different life.
What's that supposed to mean?!
The Three Sacred Treasures have
the power to amplify negative emotions.
So it was the mirror's fault
that your teacher sunk
to the dregs of humanity!
But negative emotions
are what demons thrive on!
Bring it on! We'll show you
what we're really made of!
Oath of Grace, emissary of Light!
GRACE
Armor of Light!
Armor-Gear in your first fight?
You've got potential, kid.
I know, right? Can't let Ryusei
see me look bad.
So the Samurai Troopers
have all assembled, huh?
You're here too, Sasuke?
I'm only tagging along.
Anayama, I leave the rest to you.
Mind your own business!
Damn it!
Yamato.
Relax. I'll send you
to see him in the afterlife!
Yama!
Look at me, getting played by a phony...
But it did help me remember something.
You were really little,
so maybe you've forgotten.
But when we first met Mr. Ujihara,
he was a real great guy.
Our memories of "Yume o Shinjite"
meant a lot to us.
We loved Mr. Ujihara!
Yeah.
What's with them?
They weren't in the mood for—
Shut up and join in!
JUSTICE
Secret Art: Geo Morph!
You think this is enough to contain me?!
Secret Art: Ice Cannon!
FAITH
Hey, don't give us this crap!
Who said you could just fade away?!
You went and changed
over some dumb mirror!
How am I supposed to
gripe at you if you die?!
Hey! You listen here!
Me and Musashi went
through hell because of you!
We cursed you tons of times!
But you know what?!
You gave us so much more than that!
So at the least...
let this one thing get through to you.
Thank you.
He just...
Yeah.
Now that got my blood pumping.
The fun's just getting started!
Wait!
Shut your mouth and watch!
His spirit's back in his real body!
He'll be tougher than ever!
You're kidding!
I'll skewer you all together
on my spear right here!
Anayama!
He brought it on himself.
Saizo...
Did that flash finish him off?
What's going on?
The Mirror of Supremacy.
Now we've got all three Sacred Treasures.
What's that?
What was this doing in the safe?
It must've really meant something to him.
I finally remember
why I was smiling when we sang.
It was because it made
Mr. Ujihara so happy.
LOVE
- MUSASHI HOJO
What a load of crap.
If you're watching this video, I assume
you've returned as Samurai Troopers.
Yamato, Musashi...
and you too, Shion and Kaito.
How did he know our names?
Shion and Kaito, you were adopted
as babies, so you might not know,
but you all spent time here.
Translation\h\h\h\h\h\hWilliam Varteresian
Timing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Editing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRiley Dalton
Quality Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSMR
Translation Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMichelle Tymon
EPISODE VIII
AGAIN
Armor races through your heart.