Wh...
What was that?
We said, anyone who would
defy us must die.
It's no use! They've been
completely brainwashed!
Outta the way!
Y-You guys...
Come on! What are you doing?!
Help!
Who're you?
Electro-Wave Human, Tack'!
Riderman!
Mitsuba!
It looks like...
We have to do this.
Let's go.
Hold it.
We've... finally been reunited, boys...
And you're leaving already?
You're still alive?
Aniki, this is your chance!
Get out of here!
Hurry!
I'm so glad you're all alive!
You risked your lives
for a scumbag like me...
Thank you.
I couldn't have asked
for better brothers.
.44 Magnum!
Nakao-san!
H-Hey.
I'm all done over here.
Man, you got your ass kicked.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Now, we've got a monster to beat!
A-Aniki...
You guys...
When you hit us, Aniki...
that snapped us out of it.
I'm... I'm so...
We're so sorry, Aniki!
Please forgive us!
I'm the one who should apologize.
I'm so glad you're alive.
And I'm sorry I didn't
come back to help you.
Aniki!
What's going on here?
The power of love freed them
from their brainwashing!
Nakao-san, we don't have
a lot of time. We need to hurry!
Right.
We'll show you the way!
Hey.
Thinking about it, if we're waiting for
the signal at the climax of the show...
We're gonna have nothing
to do until then!
You've got a point.
As important as the plan is, the sooner
I get to fight Shocker, the better.
Damn you, Mitsuba.
I need to avenge Grandpa and Grandma!
We should've gone straight for the
Bat Man instead of loafing around!
How about you fight me, then?
I-It's you!
The Spider Man!
Y-Y-You wretch!
Rider...
Transform! V3!
I'm joking.
You guys really are entertaining.
I'm looking forward to
seeing how this turns out.
He vanished?
Looks like you guys can still transform,
even without the brainwashing!
Just like you, Aniki!
This way!
I had a feeling you'd turn up.
Raiko...
W-Wait, please!
Aniki?
M-Maybe you...
aren't brainwashed anymore, either?
We spent all that time eating
and training together, y'know?!
Come on!
I'll say it again.
I lov—
Aniki?!
A-Aniki!
Even more traitors?
You're all going to die.
Mitsuba-san.
Leave her to me.
Go on ahead.
Understood!
Die!
You'll be fighting me.
I'm glad you're the one
who stayed behind.
Pro wrestling is all about
rubber matches, right?
This time, I'm going to beat you
until you stop fighting back.
Who do you think you are?
You look stronger than before, too.
That works for me!
Master Bat Man. It's time.
Love's an amazing thing, huh?
There's stuff out there that I love.
And people I love, too.
That fact alone is enough to make me
feel like I'm on cloud nine!
Raiko, you must really
love pro wrestling.
Hang on, how do you two know—
We don't.
But...
This old man taught me something.
Even a combatant can get stronger
by training hard enough!
Raiko!
Even if I'm still a combatant...
Where is this pressure coming from?!
I can become stronger than a monster!
Why... can't I...
move?!
Raiko!
You really do care about me!
I'm so...
damn happy!
Seriously, I love ya, Raiko!
Did that finally shut you up?!
I... feel I should ask...
Are you even our enemy anymore?
I am!
But all this "I love you" stuff...
You're dead!
Rainmaker.
My move...
is faster!
Ultimate...
Electro-Wave Throw!
Unbelievable...
You countered Kazuchika Okada's
Rainmaker with Naoya Ogawa's STO...
It's called an
Ultimate Electro-Wave Throw.
I lost again.
To a normal human...
not even a member of Shocker.
No. Her power...
That's not the kind of thing
half-baked feelings could produce.
It's the strength of her resolve...
she was more determined than I was.
I... want to be... stronger.
Are you all ready?
Okay.
All okay here!
I'm in position too.
You won?!
Great job, Yuriko-san!
All right.
Everyone. Thank you so much
for coming out today.
And before the show ends,
we have the best present ever to share
with you, our beloved fans.
Now!
A fire?!
Emergency. Emergency.
There is a fire in the arena.
Today's concert has been canceled.
All attendees,
please follow staff instructions
and evacuate in an orderly fashion
via the nearest emergency exit.
I repeat...
Emergency. Emergency.
Careful, everyone!
Don't run, please!
Follow the individual in front of you
to the exit without rushing!
This way!
Don't let a single one of them escape!
Yes, sir!
I don't think so!
Raiko! To save you...
I'm gonna take the boss's head!
Tojima-san! Ichiyo! Now!
LET'S DO THIS, SHOCKER!
Let's do this, Shocker!
What the hell?!
V3...
Rider...
Double Kick!
Master Bat Man!
Who are you people?!
V3.
Kamen Rider!
And we've waited long enough!
Your scheme ends here, Shocker!
You ruined everything...
And now you all die.
Impressive.
But will you be able...
to survive this time?
NEXT TIME
I WOULDN'T
MIND DYING
TODAY
I WOULDN'T MIND DYING TODAY
ILLUSTRATED BY: MASATO HISA