Goodbye.
It feels unreal...
how little I'm sad about it.
Three-Year Journal
"Asa."
"I'm writing this journal to give to you
when you turn twenty years old."
"Your name was chosen
with a great deal of care."
It embodies the beauty of all new things
that come with each day.
Sis...
When and why did you grow to hate me?
Asa's Personal Belongings
Moreover, without my own hatred for you,
would I have ever become a writer?
Journal with Witch
Episode 6\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hOverlap
Good morning. Late morning, actually.
Ditching today?
Huh?
School.
It's summer break! As of today.
Wanna go somewhere?
Uh, no. I have to work...
Makio-chan, what days do you have off?
Days off? I don't really have any.
Dang.
Except you're home all the time,
so it's kinda like you're off every day.
I sorted what looks like junk
from the important documents.
Okay. Where are you going?
Band practice.
This one upperclassman keeps
picking on me for being a beginner.
Heme Iron
What's that about?
"Great, it's the newbie."
They say that?
Yeah.
Well, you've already started learning.
Hey, that's good! I'll use that next time.
"I've already started learning!"
Anyways, I'm off!
Sure.
Right... She'll be home every day
until September.
Quit it. This was your idea.
Lunch...
I'm home.
What the heck?!
Welcome back.
Never mind that!
This room looked normal before I left!
Huh?
Oh, yeah...
Um, I'll clean up in half an hour.
Come on, just do it now!
Uh...
Now's not a good time.
You know, I've been wondering
for a while now.
How does it even get like this?
And you're always
forgetting what I tell you!
Why is that? Why can't you
do something so simple?
Why can't I do something so simple?
It's okay. Don't be so down on yourself.
No worries.
A lot of novelists are like you.
Although it can get you
into trouble with your taxes.
Yes, that sounds a lot like me.
Wait, you mean that was mandatory?
I'm sorry, um... I don't understand
this system very well...
Makio? Makio!
Huh?
Were you even listening to me?
Uh... I guess not really.
Darn you.
My bad.
Makio, did you do your homework?
Makio-san?
Makio.
Makio!
H-H-Hang on...
Give me a minute...
Do you need to get that upset?
I'm only stating the obvious.
What upsets me is up to me!
You don't get to decide that for me!
What's "obvious" to you
doesn't come so readily to me.
My mind is constantly busy.
I easily lose sight of things.
I'm a terrible liar.
And I'm more comfortable alone.
For whatever reason, I was born this way.
Just like how you were born
to hate being alone.
It's not something you get to choose
or shame others for.
Just like you can't understand
the suffocation I feel,
I can't understand your loneliness.
Yes?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I have plans with Asa today.
Is today Saturday?
Yes.
Hey, can Emiri come over on Saturday?
Hmm...
It's Saturday already?
Come on in.
Something smells good.
Oh, I was feeling on edge,
so I'm baking a cake.
Feeling on edge?
Wait, where's Asa?
She said she's at the convenience store.
You didn't notice?
She may have mentioned it,
but I can't say for certain.
This one's your standard tea.
And here are a couple of flavored ones.
I also have black bean tea, green tea,
roasted brown rice tea... That's expired.
Oh, and milk. Have whatever you'd like.
Nothing is also an option.
You mean I get to choose?
Yeah.
What's taking that girl so long?
That one, huh? You got it.
Um... Why aren't you married?
Huh?
You're not, are you?
W-Well, no.
Why do you ask?
It's just that...
My parents keep telling me
I'll get married one day, but...
I'm not saying this
just because I'm single,
but I don't think it's "normal" to be
married or "weird" to be unmarried.
Naturally, same goes
for not wanting to get married.
It's not that I don't want to, but...
Okay, then what about someone you like?
Do you have anyone like that?
I'm not sure.
Oh?!
I mean, I have someone who
I consider a friend...
I'm fine just being friends.
If being your boyfriend makes you hate me,
I'd rather go back to being friends.
Please, don't push me away...
I'm back! Sorry about that, Emiri!
Asa!
Guess what? Makio-san and I
were just talking about love.
What? No way! You mean Kasamachi-kun?
What?! Who's Kasamachi-kun?
You call him that?
It's personal, so I'm not telling.
But you told Emiri!
Oh, the cake's done.
I want cake.
It needs to cool down first.
Once it's cool enough to touch,
you can take it out of the pan.
It'll taste better once fully cooled.
Okay!
But it smells so good.
I dunno if I can wait.
Me either!
Sorry I'm late.
He's a little pampered,
but I promise he's a good guy.
What's that for? Cut me some slack.
Is beer okay?
Yeah.
I'll order some other stuff for us too.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kasamachi.
I'm Koudai.
Hi...
Kasamachi
Thanks for today. And the food.
My pleasure. It was a nice change of pace
\hfrom eating alone. Let's do it again.
Sure, I'll reach out sometime.
Hey. I feel bad with you coming over and bringing food all the time, so how about we go out for some drinks for a change? Now that Asa's settled in and all
Hang on. Where's this feeling coming from?
Um, a-are you okay?
I'm fine. Excuse me for that.
Can I help you?
Oh, right. It's nothing urgent,
but I had an idea I wanted to run by you.
Hey, I think it's cool now!
Let's eat!
How much do you want?
Let's see... I dunno.
A foreign land, you say?
Yes. Sorry, more on that some other time.
Oh, of course.
Sorry to bother you at work.
I'll be in touch again soon.
Okay. Thank you.
I thought I told him I prefer
to be contacted by email...
Thanks for today. And the food.
My pleasure. It was a nice change of pace
\hfrom eating alone. Let's do it again.
Sure, I'll reach out sometime.
Hey. I feel bad with you coming over and bringing food all the time, so how about we go out for some drinks for a change? Now that Asa's settled in and all
Kasamachi
Today
Sure, I'll reach out sometime.
Hey. I feel bad with you coming over and bringing food
\hall the time, so how about we go out for some drinks
\h\hfor a change? Now that Asa's settled in and all
Oh no! Did I just—
No way, no way, no way, no way...
Hey. I feel bad with you coming over and bringing
food all the time, so how about we go out for some drinks
for a change? Now that Asa's settled in and all
Today
Read
I'm in. Let's get some greasy Chinese!
You okay? I heard loud noises in there.
I'm fine. You remember
that lawyer, Tono-san?
He says he wants to meet with you
sometime. He should be in touch.
'Kay.
Embroidery?
Yup. I joined the crafts club.
Yeah? Sounds like fun.
It is.
Actually, it's more like... calming?
I get pretty lost in this.
It's like I forget about other stuff.
That sounds addicting.
It totally is. Time literally flies.
Whoa, it's this late already?
A friend who gives you refuge...
That's what I'm saying! Time flies.
You're so right.
I'm not sure if you'll like it.
I may be completely
off the mark, but here.
A movie?
No matter who you fall in love with,
or who you don't...
It's a story about how there's
nothing wrong with that.
You might find some refuge in it.
Find refuge?
There you go again
with the difficult lines.
Recommend me something too!
Hmm... Mad Max: Fury Road.
What's that? Sounds scary.
Journal with Witch
By the way, how did you solve
the bento box dilemma?
We have a three-meal rotation.
Some kind of kinpira sauté,
some kind of sweet and salty sauté,
then some kind of grilled meat.
Hey, not bad.
And with summer break now,
you don't have to cook.
Between making bento boxes
and having her home every day...
I'm not sure which is more
draining, to be honest.
You really do love your solitude.
You bet I do. What of it?
Here ya go.
The herb chicken fry
and a spring onion salad.
Looks amazing!
Darn right it is.
Thanks.
I need some beer to go with this.
That's spicy! But it's good. Wow.
It's nice to start
drinking early like this.
Yeah.
Did you leave work in the dust today too?
Actually, I've kind of been
in a rut recently...
Kasamachi-kun, do you still lift weights?
Lift weights?
You've been training, haven't you?
I mean, I wouldn't call it that.
I just like working out. That's all.
Which reminds me, get this...
Hang on a minute. What the...
So I go to the gym because
I like working out, right?
And I make bento boxes
of what I want to eat.
Has he always been this... hot?
So someone goes, "You sure love taking
care of yourself, Kasamachi-san!"
That's gotta be a dig, right?
Taking care of yourself?
Okay, here's your gyoza.
You've always been the target
of that kind of slander.
I mean, teasing, I guess.
Yeah, the whole "pampered" thing.
It's because you look like you
can take it. That's why.
He's a little pampered,
but I promise he's a good guy.
Well, with people pointing fingers at you,
you can't help feeling it's a dig.
Good times.
But I appreciated that you didn't
pile on and tease me too.
I didn't?
Makes sense. I like pampered guys.
What?
Er, um... You never told me that.
Do you have anyone like that?
Snap out of it!
Speaking of pampered guys...
How's that young attorney of yours?
Huh?
He seemed pretty pampered too.
I was just wondering if I could
speak with Asa-san alone.
But I wanted to make sure I'm not
overstepping any boundaries.
He's your typical eager beaver.
Eager beaver? That's a rough nickname.
Um, I took the liberty of reading
through some of your novels.
Apparently, he doesn't read
any fiction whatsoever.
Really?
Oh, why thank you...
To be honest, I don't read novels,
so I couldn't understand them.
Are middle schoolers your
main target readers?
Y-You said you don't read novels?
That's right. Not at all.
Not at all?
Or movies or manga.
Anything of the sort.
I see. So you don't require much
storytelling in your life.
I'm sorry.
No, it's fine. Some people don't need it.
Need what? Storytelling?
What for?
For me, stories were like
friends that gave me refuge.
Especially as a child.
Refuge...?
Like someone introducing me
to a foreign land.
A foreign land, you say?
Yes.
Sorry, more on that some other time.
I take it he's not your type, then?
Huh?
Yeah, I guess not.
Hey, can I order this thing
with chives and mochi?
Which one?
Oh, looks good.
And what about this one? The bok choy?
Cool it.
This isn't right...
I mean, he's... He's...
Treat him right.
He's your friend.
But I want some!
Go away, damn it!
I'm the one who broke his heart
and hurt him to begin with.
Can we get two more beers?
As well as the chive and mochi
stir fry and the bok choy.
I couldn't possibly...
You wouldn't understand, Kasamachi-kun!
Can I have the last gyoza?
Oh, sure.
I don't have the right to fall for him...
Not again.
Wanna take a stroll around
the park and walk this off?
You must really love
taking care of yourself.
Are you trying to make me cry?
What about you? Do you exercise?
Not really. Actually, not at all.
Then I'll have to drag you out
for a walk every now and then.
Looking back now, I used
to be in much better shape.
Told you.
When I go on walks alone,
my mind starts to wander.
It's nice to walk with someone
and talk for a change.
Just for a change, huh?
Yup. You know me too well.
Well, it took me long enough to get here.
I should've gotten some coffee to go.
Too bad there isn't
a coffee shop around here.
S-Sorry. Did you not want to?
N-No, it's not that.
Actually, I'm dying to.
What? R-R-Really?
Um, thanks, I think?
Ugh! I'm just so confused!
Okay, what's wrong?
Confused about what?
You're important to me.
And you're also my friend.
I feel like I'm sullying that.
I see you're overthinking things again.
I'll regret it if I don't
think things through.
Well, you don't need to.
We can stay friends.
I won't meddle in your business.
If we desire each other, then fine.
And we'll lean on each other
in times of need.
How's that sound?
Isn't that way too unfair to you?
No, it's not. Actually,
it's more unfair to you.
I want you to need me around somehow.
Not that I want you to be down, of course.
Why can't I do something so simple?
I don't deserve help from anyone.
That's what I keep thinking.
Why would you say something so sad?
Sorry, sorry, sorry!
Damn, here I go again,
making the same mistake.
It's so hard...
It really is.
Treating someone right...
It's such a simple, difficult thing.
You know, you've always smelled nice.
Ever since we first met.
Other men don't smell like this.
Do they?
They don't.