Strongest Because of Imperfection
So they survived.
What a persistent lot.
They're after the new Diva.
They won't have an emotional
reunion on my watch.
Chill out a bit, Apollo.
Let me take care of them this time.
Thanks for leading them here, Medea.
This is rare.
You've always preferred to be in
the shadows, outwitting the enemy.
Well, I could use some exercise.
In exchange, I want to ask you a favor.
The Mirage appeared
simultaneously in 25 locations.
Not to mention...
They're all political hubs.
There's no logic
in setting targets like this.
It's an attack solely to put
the whole Earth in chaos.
Who knew they'd be the one
to give us a signal?
Yes. They don't care
about the consequences.
Which means our kids
are closing in on Nagi.
Now this is a race, SI-VIS.
Do you take me down first
or does Earth perish before that?
Ready, set... go!
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
It's Show Time
The price of living in the time of freedom
"So, what do you want to do?"
Just standing there with my empty body
Like a calling to protect the world
I craved an unequaled gift
Lost in night's darkness
Until a voice called out to me
Like the light that declares the dawn
I'll take you with me at
any cost (I pray and wish)
Beyond the Echo-verse (To the future)
Just being with you makes me strong
It's not an exaggeration
That encounter was a supernova
(Our eyes were locked)
In an instant, everything that I am
(In an instant)
Will be changed forever (Just to be)
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
Destiny is Calling us now
Just to be who we are
Just to be by your side
Everyone, can you hear me?
Loud and clear.
Oh, wow! How are you doing this?
Connecting Harmonia and
myself through Metis.
I didn't think Earth technology
was capable of this.
It's not Earth technology.
It's my skill.
Now we're ready for the live concert.
But we can't tell what's really
going on over there.
So you're the stage director
of SI-VIS today, Medea.
I always do my best.
So the rest is up to SI-VIS.
So cold!
Can you say something that will,
I don't know, boost our morale?
Which makes you, Rui,
the supervisor for today.
Work with her and
lead the concert to success.
Are you sure you can trust her that much?
Shouldn't you trust her more than anyone?
As women who loved the same man.
You can sympathize with her, can't you?
According to Harmonia headquarters,
we have about thirty minutes
before the Mirages close.
We have to rescue the Diva
before that and stop the Mirages.
It's a race against time.
You say that, but will saving Nagi
really stop the Mirages?
The situation on Earth
must be dealt with,
but rushing into things
just to fail won't help.
No, we should take our chances
with the time limit of thirty minutes.
Because that man is most likely
playing games with you.
Come on. Come on. Come on!
I will reunite you guys.
Just like Romeo and
Juliet on your planet.
Is that...?
Kyoya is here.
Lord Archon was right.
If we use her, we can revive XENOS
without relying on Earth.
I am Kyoya of SI-VIS.
I'll make sure everyone survives!
How fortuitous.
With Earth and
the new Diva on our side,
our revival will be a
hundred years closer.
Medea-san, are these...?
Yes, the people of XENOS.
They placed their hope of resurrection
in us and went to sleep.
A Mirage?!
What the heck is that?
A trap?
No. This is most likely
a trap as well as a chance.
There's only one XENOS left who
would do something dramatic like this.
I know! It's that pervy old man!
I can no longer tell
what Samael's true intention is.
But it feels to me like it is
very personal and impulsive.
He wants to fight us?
I'm sure he's waiting for us with
a hostage of one plus billions of people.
You mean Nagi and...
The lives of the earthlings.
If we crush this Mirage, then the Mirages
on Earth should disappear as well.
It wouldn't make sense to
put on a show like this otherwise.
Then all we do is to take the bait
with everything we've got.
Everyone, just do it as usual, okay?
Until the live concert begins...
Or until those 25 cities disappear,
we've got 15 minutes left.
What emotions are you going through?
Are you all right, everyone?!
Medea-san!
Now's not the time to worry about me!
Telling him that is pointless.
He can't even protect himself,
but he tries to protect everyone.
That's mean.
That's...
A revived cyborg?
As expected of the pervy old man.
I knew he had bad taste, but this is peak.
Here goes our all-out attack.
Everyone, let's go!
No, that's not it!
Let's just do our usual.
Leave this to us and keep going!
Soji, μ...
It's a race against time!
Our combat power won't change
that much if you aren't here!
But...
I think you'd be better off
if we weren't with you.
I bet there'll be a full display
of embarrassing lines like,
"Give back my Nagi,
you scoundrel!" and whatnot.
Oh, come on! You guys
never listen to me!
Okay, I'll go do my solo.
But we'll do the next
song with the full cast!
You're going, too!
Please. I need you to back him up.
Make sure our leader looks cool, will you?
"Our leader"?
Is that how a leader should be?
Orphe led and guided
everyone from the front.
He produced results on his own.
He never showed his weakness.
But that boy...
Sorry, but leave the princess
and I alone, will you?
I've done your bidding so far, haven't I?
Yo, Princess.
Kyoya is coming.
Yup, your knight will arrive soon.
To kill me.
You're wrong.
Kyoya won't kill or hate.
He's a true hero who saves everyone.
But I kinda need him
to fight me, you know?
Otherwise, there's no
growing stronger, you see?
Nagi!
Welcome to my homeland!
The Diva's Knight
and successor of Orphe!
Nagi!
Kyoya!
Set Nagi free!
If you want your princess back,
try and stop this Mirage.
If you manage to do it,
I'll give you a reward!
I'll stop every Mirage
on Earth, not just here.
Because its core is right here.
You must stop this, Samael!
You touched her power, didn't you?
Then you must have realized
that there's a way for both
XENOS and the earthlings
to survive without taking Earth!
Apollo, Orphe, you...
Why can't you be a bit more flexible?
Who cares about the future
of the human species?
Samael!
You must have known...
What we're doing to take Earth.
What we have done.
Our friends who entrusted the future
of XENOS to us and went to sleep...
Our friends who went to sleep,
believing that they'd wake up one day...
We've consumed their lives to be here.
That's why... That's exactly why!
Now might be our chance
to stop the cycle of loss.
This is a one-in-a-million chance!
Right.
You should stick to your beliefs, Medea.
And I will do the same.
Why, Samael?!
Is that all you have to say?
What is Lord Apollo's opinion?!
I can't imagine him
tolerating your reckless behavior!
True, Apollo probably wouldn't
condone my purpose.
But he'd allow me to destroy
SI-VIS to gain Earth.
That's how he is.
That can't be...!
If you don't have anyone
to protect, find someone.
Get to know someone well enough
that they're no longer a stranger!
Did you hear that, Medea?
How about you?
You lost Orphe, the only love you had.
Can you say the same thing?
Orphe might be gone,
but his wishes will live on forever.
For people he's never met,
for people from different cultures...
and even for people
who are yet to be born,
he served his mission and gave his life.
I want to be someone like that as well.
Yeah!
Aren't you blessed to be able to live on
with just the memories of loved ones?
No, you're just caught up in a curse.
It's a foolish way to live!
I will stop you, Samael!
Nagi and I, with the song of SI-VIS!
Go ahead and try.
Come at me with your little live
concert, a farce you all believe in!
Even the pain I locked up
I threw it away with a trembling heart
Otherwise, it is the end of humanity!
Silence is swirling
You must hate me.
You must want to kill me.
A breath signals the beginning
Kick me with the intent to kill.
Punch and pierce me with your fists!
Sounds come flooding back,
illuminating the darkness
If not, then die!
Our dissonance swells
Give your life to XENOS and disappear!
The dreary world spreads
as far as eyes can see
What the hell?!
You die!
Is this guy for real?! Shut the hell up!
Kill him!
Get lost! Get lost! Get lost!
Run through to the ends of the Earth
Idea is rising rapidly.
Arrows pour down endlessly
Three hundred thousand,
three hundred fifty thousand...
But we let out thunderous roars
B-But this is...
Strike a chord that fuels clenched fists
Take this!
What was that?
Looks like you're ready
to kill me, earthling!
N-No, that wasn't...!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Our fate stands in front of us
All we can do is to tackle it head-on
Stop it, please!
Now set your heart ablaze
until there's nothing left
This isn't... This is not...
Not the voices we wanted to hear!
Who rings the bell of blessings?
I want you to enjoy our performance!
Don't get hyped up
about people getting hurt!
Souls, resonance, an impulse
that pierces our brains
Earthlings, XENOS...
Tears, the surge of pain
rising in a blink of an eye
you both lost.
I... I alone am the winner!
Push away the unsteady mist and shout
Now you will kill until
both sides are destroyed!
Sing out loud at the top of your lungs
It's the ultimate gift from me,
Because words will turn into
weapons wrapped in passion
who lost family, friends,
everyone I've ever loved!
Go without hesitation
Let the lives of all of us here
shine brightly
Take it!
Medea-san!
Please cut off the cheers from Earth!
But the only reason
we can stand against Samael—
If we win like this, then we've lost!
Stop it, Samael!
I want to save them all!
Not just the people
on Earth, but XENOS, too.
And you should be saved as well!
Stormy winds, freezing fingers
Is that so? I'm the opposite.
Running through the land
that was torn apart
I want to destroy them all.
The people on Earth, XENOS...
Two wishes that will never cross forever
And the one who deserves
to be destroyed more than anyone...
is me, who can't do anything
but get revenge!
The color of darkness eats away the light
Oh, the back of my throat
is completely dried up in misery
Samael. The weakling who was consumed
by hatred because of his kindness.
Your heart that craves
destruction will save XENOS.
On the stage of pure darkness,
heartbeats resonate
If your loved ones are not among
the ones who get revived,
With bated breath, it starts moving
it just means you were out of luck.
Toward the time that leads to the future
We have to connect with Earth!
As loud as it can be
Not now.
What we need to rely on is not hate!
Friends, comrades,
people who live in the same world...
Let our song pierce through
Even those who live in different worlds...
We need kindness to protect everyone!
At the bottom of the desolate heart
But that's nowhere to be found right now!
Even if wounds and scars
may forever leave marks
It all makes up who I am
A Chariot?
Sorry for the delay!
June-kun?!
It's not just him, got it?!
Let me hear the cheers…
Your solo part is over!
Why? Why?
Led by the stars
Team Formation for
the Next Concert
Center!
Kyoya
Soji
June
Did he give his and
Lukos's Pandora to SI-VIS?
Yes. I received it.
Staying close, I feel your warmth
What did you do, Krios?!
This is Nagi's masterpiece!
Write some awesome music for it!
Did you form a bond with an actual
earthling that's not even Orphe?!
Passing on love, united through hearts
Are you seriously willing to follow the
immature aspirations of these brats?!
Turning it into a mighty power
Our resolution won't waver
Bet on everything you have
You're imperfect
and not enough in every aspect.
Now draw a breath
But that's why everyone
can't help but rally around you.
Let it resonate
and resonate forever and ever
Being imperfect is your biggest advantage.
Go on, go on to the unknown world
Reach out your hand
and the world will expand
So that's the kind of leader you are.
This is going to... end it!
Sing and sing forever and ever
SI-VIS!
Until our wishes reach you
We'll play the melody of hope
Samael!
Come back to us!
For me to be defeated...
and to make them stronger was my purpose.
So why...?
Why am I frustrated?
The Mirages over the 25
cities are all disappearing!
Not only me, but he moved Krios as well.
It wasn't just Kyoya-san,
but all of SI-VIS.
It's a group that's nothing more
than a bunch of friends
led by an inexperienced leader.
But they've done
what Orphe never could.
Orphe, did you foresee this?
Were you hoping for this outcome?
No, probably not.
Knowing you, you were probably
trying to protect them on your own.
But your overeagerness created
a new savior who isn't overeager.
It's all thanks to you, Orphe.
I'd imagine this isn't the result
you were hoping for, though.
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Tomoko Takedani Sater
Krzysztof Kunc
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Michelle Tymon
On the musical stave
/ In the musical stave
WOW, I let my feelings play
/ I hid my feelings
My bright future / My pitiful past
WOW, started to shine
Unparalleled / Challenges ahead but
With a smile on my face
/ I'll embrace them
I feel like I can even change
the world with you
(3, 2, 1, Singing over)
Intertwining harmony (Harmony)
I wouldn't have believed in miracles alone
This breathless heartbeat (Heart Beat)
I'll let it resonate in
the night sky with my voice
My... our dream at full blast
Singing over, forever
Lan lan la la la
I will stop Lord Apollo.
He's the only one left.
And there's no one who
supports him anymore.
You should join us and—
It's too late.
That is not true!
Why don't we work together?
To find a way to save this planet,
Earth, and all the people we love.
Unfortunately, I've already
made a deal with the devil.
In exchange for the power
to destroy everything,
I promised to devote
everything to the Diva.
Lord Apollo is not an absolute evil!
He is simply obsessed with saving XENOS.
Apollo?
Oh, right.
You don't know true evil, do you?
True evil?
Samael!
Farewell, Medea.
Kyoya!
Nagi!