Dearest comrades, please respond.
We have received your mayday.
We are capable of bringing aboard
all who wish to join us.
We will be entering stationary orbit
around your planet soon.
The specific date and time
according to the global standard time—
I will call rain down
upon this dry planet.
A rain of a thousand immigrant ships.
A "Genesis Flood" Big Fall.
Nai, I will stop you.
And how are you going to do that?
Are you up and around already?
Ready as always, better than ever.
Besides, if I stayed in bed all the time,
it'd get the kids worried.
So?
According to Melanie, Octovern
was able to repel the Ark's attack.
They're accepting refugees
from other cities and towns.
Word's gotten out that the city
will protect people.
So Nai will be coming to Octovern.
Sounds about right. And?
I have ideas... about how to stop Nai.
Let's hear them.
Well...
It's no good.
The town down below is all empty.
No food, no water, no nothing.
Just like we figured.
It's a total ghost town.
Even if we seriously cut back, we have
maybe a week's worth of food and water.
One week...
And even if we wanted to take refuge
in Octovern, all the cars are gone.
Walking there is out
of the question, so...
Either way, we don't want
the kids at Octovern.
We can't use the radio either.
What to do...
Home.
Home?
Your house?
Luida would accept the kids.
I'll go ask her myself.
We could get there in three
or four days by motorcycle.
That sounds like a good idea.
But will that leave us enough time
to deal with Knives?
Nai can't do what he wants
until the immigrant fleet arrives.
We have enough time
to visit Home, return here,
and then make for Octovern... I think.
Sounds like our only option.
I'll be back before you know it.
Don't you worry.
Take care out there.
I'm off.
Good luck!
You can't drive?! You dumbass!
Are you all right?!
Are you sure about this?
Maybe I should...
No, Nico. You're still in rough shape.
I'll go.
It's all good. I know exactly
where Home is now.
I see.
Thanks, Livio.
No need to thank me.
I want to do what I can for the kids, too.
We're counting on you.
Yes, Auntie... Aunt Melanie.
Okay, I'm off.
Ouch...
Oh! My bones!
It's fine, it's fine!
I'll be all fixed up in no time.
See? Good as new.
And again, I'm off.
How's it look?
It's been five days.
He should be back any moment now.
I hope he isn't lost in the desert
or being chased by a pack of Worms.
We have to trust him and wait.
Melanie, how's our food and water?
I'd say two more days left.
I see.
That's right. We're all going to space.
A great voyage across the sea of stars!
We'll leave this star and find a new one.
I'm sure we can find a great new home.
Are you coming with us, Nico?
Of course I am.
Auntie Melanie, too?
All of us together!
Let's travel and eat tons of great food!
Yeah!
Hey, Nico.
Which way is the spaceship coming from?
That's...
I don't know.
That way? Or maybe that way?
It's that direction.
How do you know?
That's the direction of the home star,
where everyone living
on Noman's Land hails from.
You mean Earth!
I see. So it'll be that way.
Can we see them?
No way you can see them!
Oh, there they are!
You're lying!
I'm not. Look. One, two... Thirty ships!
Yeah, you're right. Look at that guy
waving from the window.
What? Where, where?!
You tricked me!
Vash, did you come from Earth, too?
I've never been to Earth either.
We were born aboard a ship in transit.
"We"?
I have a twin brother.
Wow! Do you have any other family?
Rem...
A woman named Rem Saverem raised us.
Is she your mom?
Yes, she was like our mom.
Rem was kind and taught us many things.
I know. I'll share with you
something she use to say.
Listen well.
We all have a blank ticket
with no listed destination.
What you put there is up to you.
No matter the darkness you find yourself in,
you'll always have that ticket
waiting for you to write in where to go.
A blank...
...ticket?
Everyone, put out a hand.
For you, and for you, and for you.
You all have a blank ticket.
With this, you can go anywhere
and be anything.
As long as you have your ticket,
you can endure any hardship.
Just as I have.
Remember to take good care of your ticket.
Right!
Meryl! Hurry, hurry!
Jessica!
Meryl, Milly! The motorcycle!
We saw it, too!
Vash?!
Undertaker?!
Hello.
Who are you?
Do calm yourselves, you three.
Yes, of course. Sorry.
I thought for a moment...
Maybe Vash or the Undertaker came back.
They aren't here. But they're safe.
They're somewhere else right now.
They're running out of provisions
and in need of help.
I came here to let you know.
It took him five days to get here,
no rest or sleep.
You went five days without sleep?!
It should have taken me
only three days, but...
Yeehaw!
Nice ride!
Take it!
Well, well...
Oh, no!
It's reversed?
And several other unforeseen issues arose.
I'm sure of it.
That's Livio the Doublefang's voice.
Is he here to kill us?
It doesn't seem that way.
So you want the children
from the Hopeland orphanage
to take refuge on this ship,
is that right?
Yes.
I understand the situation.
Then...
However,
we cannot accept
the children here at Home.
They're here!
Yay! Over here!
Vash!
You dummy! I've been so worried!
Sorry, Jessica.
Boy, am I glad you're all right!
Meryl, Milly... I'm sorry I worried you.
You really did.
You owe us an exclusive interview!
Moreover...
Yes.
What happened to your hair?
I got a makeover. Looks good, right?
That's so wild of you!
I sort of caused him a lot of
mental stress... of a certain kind.
It's not your fault. Don't even start.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah. I just almost died for a bit.
What?!
I'm more or less fine now.
That "more or less" is dubious.
You have priors.
Really, I'm fine.
Really?
Really, really fine.
Can we trust you?
You can trust me.
I can't die. I've gotta
protect these kids.
Enough already. Yikes.
So?
What's all this?
We wanted you to take in the kids
from the orphanage.
Why did you all come here instead?
We spoke to Luida, and...
We cannot accept
the children here at Home.
B-But...
Luida!
It's too dangerous.
We're almost done repairing the engines.
This ship will fly again soon.
We must go and finish
our fight against Knives.
So, Livio...
We implore you instead.
Please let the children and
noncombatants on this ship
take refuge in Hopeland.
That's what she said.
Good call.
That's Luida for you.
We brought lots of food and water,
so we should be fine for a while.
But still...
What are you fools doing here?!
Is there a problem?
We are also noncombatants.
The children need their
music lessons every day.
Huh?!
All right, kids, it's lesson time.
Okay!
Hey, Your Majesty,
give us a new puppet show
after our music lesson, okay?
Absolutely not.
Yay!
All right!
I shan't do it.
I can't wait!
I said no.
We should accompany Vash to Octovern.
Yes.
We will observe and record
everything to the bitter end.
Yes.
History will know how we upheld
our pride as journalists.
Yes!
Okay, everything's ready.
Batteries are full, too.
We can go anywhere now.
Milly?
Yes?
M-Milly, Worm! There's— You're— Worm!
Oh, I'm so glad!
About what?!
It's from my big sister.
My dad, mom, sisters, brothers,
nephews, nieces, and cousins...
They're all safe!
Huh?
I think they're near Octovern,
though, so that's a bit worrying.
What are you talking about?
Oh, I did mention that I'm from
a family of Worm tamers, right?
Never!
You can understand the Worms' language?
I don't understand it, no.
But there's... something
that comes across to me.
Thank you so much!
How do they know you're here?
Worms can communicate
their feelings instantly,
no matter how far away they are.
Their hearts resonate.
My big brother told me so.
Or was it my sister?
They resonate, huh? Oh... I remember.
The individuals are connected, right?
Anyway, I'm glad your family is safe.
Yeah!
You still haven't told me what
you're planning to do about Knives.
I'll convince him to stop.
You gotta be kidding.
I'm serious.
But if I can't convince him, then...
Then what?
I can access plant cores.
Nai is also a plant, so I should be
able to access his... I think.
And?
My power as a plant is to take away.
I can get a hold of the plants Nai
has taken in... and take them away.
Without the power of those plants,
there's no way Nai can
take down the whole fleet.
I see. But will it work?
If you fail...
and do Lost JuLai part two,
that'd be bad.
Almost the entire planet's
population is in Octovern.
You wipe them out, we're talking
the worst ending ever.
Sorry.
I know. That's why,
just to be safe, I want the Ark...
I want Nai to be as far away
from Octovern as possible. But...
Resonance... That's it! Resonance!
Meryl?
Why don't you just let them
know where you are?
If you're a plant, maybe you
can tell Knives your location.
Similar to how the Worms are connected.
What are you talking about?
How is that...
Is that possible?
I might be able to do it.
Seriously?
Yeah! And if we do that...
We might be able to finish this without
waiting for the immigrant fleet to arrive,
or for Nai to show up at Octovern!
Thank you, Meryl.
But even if I can tell Nai where I am...
will he come?
Of course he will.
Wolfwood?
No matter how bad you might be fighting,
big brothers always want to keep
their little brothers close.
Nico...
Not talking about you!
Just generally speaking.
I get it.
You don't get shit!
So, where'll it be?
Where do we want to lure him?
There's a good spot.
A place to settle this...
Yes!
Jessica, take care
of the little kids, okay?
I will! And when you come back,
I'll finally put this on your coat!
All right, kids, be good.
Good luck, Nico!
Take care!
Be back soon!
Good luck, Livio!
This is all we've got.
It's better than nothing. I expect thanks.
H-Hey...
The future is in your hands,
Nicholas the Punisher.
No, Nicholas D. Wolfwood.
Didn't expect this from you.
Also, thanks for letting us live.
Please come back alive.
You still have a promise to fulfill.
Yeah.
Don't cry.
I'm not crying!
Don't go taking this guys too seriously.
That's mean.
Quite uncalled for.
Yeah, Wolfwood.
You really are too nice.
I have to say, I didn't expect this.
I assumed you'd be against
me and Meryl coming along.
How would I ever stop you?
Point taken.
Still, I was surprised, too.
Same, actually.
Yes, it is dangerous,
so I'd prefer it if you weren't coming.
But...
We want to help you carry it.
You're not in this fight alone.
What's that look on your face?
What is that look on your face?
It's nothing.
But Meryl, Milly, I want you
to promise me one thing.
Promise?
Don't do anything dangerous.
Of course we won't.
We have to leave a record.
A record of all that's happened.
Oh, Meryl...
What is it?
Oh...
Good luck!
Come back in one piece!
Take care, everyone!
We're off!
Now, kill me! Kill a human!