Mizuho's not the only one that's
been looking your way, Kizuki.
I love you, Kizuki.
I can't go out with you, Airu.
Because I love Mizuho.
But...
You're someone who's
very important to me, Airu.
I want to keep going to school
with you tomorrow.
And talk about a bunch of things
and laugh with you.
Yeah.
I'll take a raw sea urchin pasta
and the gnocchi with gorgonzola sauce.
Who makes an order instead
of a normal greeting?
Also, I'm still prepping.
I know.
I was just kidding.
This place looks like it's doing well.
Of course it is.
I'm a master chef.
A master at cooking, sure.
But what about your personal life?
I heard Kizuki's back.
So? What are you going to do?
What do you mean?
Well, I guess you've always
put your friends first.
I'm the third lead.
Therefore, I'll get to
take everything in the end.
What did you say?
You're hungry, right?
Eat this.
Mi-chan.
Oh, you're in your room.
Why didn't you answer?
This year's New Year's Eve party
will be at Izumi-san's house.
Are you listening?
Uh-huh.
I noticed that the boys
aren't over today either.
That's rare.
Is it because you'll all be
busy applying to universities next year?
Maybe they started studying.
Sorry to bother you.
I'll accept everything.
This is the outcome
Every Score Shall Absolutely Improve!
Determination and Effort
of the decisions I made.
Izumi
Hello, everyone.
It's a busy time of year.
But I'm glad you could join us here
at the humble Izumi residence
to celebrate the New Year.
There's only a few hours
left of this year—
You're taking too long!
Cheers!
You get drunk way too fast, Nishino-san!
I always make Mizuho feel sad...
And she seems to have
a lot on her mind lately...
She didn't even come
to tonight's party...
I'm just so worried for my girl...
Oh, come on. She's at that age.
I'm sure there's just
a lot going on in her life.
She's right.
Uh-huh.
Just leave her be.
Mizuho-chan's going to be all right.
Do you really think so?
We can only shut up, trust,
and watch over them.
But in my case, if my kid
needed me, that's when...
I'll give it my all to protect them,
even if it means making
an enemy of the whole world.
Izumi-san, you're so cool!
You really are!
Okay then, cheers!
Cheers!
Thank you so much.
Happy New Year!
Happy New Year to you, too!
Ugh.
He's down already.
So useless.
Dad's definitely gonna be hung over.
What's this?
Blam!
Good Vibes!
A pic from when I was in high school.
You're so young here!
You're even more flashy than I am!
Cute, right?
Did you get your tan from the beach?
At a tanning salon.
I tanned nicely, right?
Seriously?
Everyone said they wanted to see it.
So I brought it out.
Mom.
What's up?
I... confessed...
To Kizuki. On Christmas.
And he rejected me.
Back in middle school.
That's why I ran away from home.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you
this whole time.
Don't apologize.
It doesn't matter.
Whether you're a delinquent,
or ran away from home,
or who you fall in love with...
Since the day you were born,
you're my irreplaceable son.
I'm sorry you had to bottle all of this up
on your own this whole time.
Thank you for telling me...
I'm sure you gave it your all to confess.
Want some hot cocoa?
Yeah.
Wanna do something for the first sunrise?
A Christmas present?
I didn't give you mine yet, right?
Come to Koigahama Beach right now.
What? Right now?
I didn't even go to the Christmas party.
I can't accept a gift...
Are we just not even going to
see each other anymore?
Is this what our relationship amounts to?
Remember when you moved to Koigahama?
You and I were the first to meet
before anyone else.
And then we met the others.
We'd play until we forgot
what time it was.
We'd fight and make up.
During summer break,
Christmas, and even New Year's.
No matter when and where,
we brought chaos together.
So now that you and Kizuki are going out,
you're going to reset our history?
Just like that?
That's not like us at all.
C'mon, Airu.
Ah! Stop that!
Your hands are cold!
Help me, Shin-chan!
Don't come near me.
You're late.
I called them, too.
This is your Christmas present.
So don't you dare say you don't want it.
Syugo!
Syugo barged into my room
and forced me out of bed.
I was studying when he suddenly came in...
You better be grateful for me!
We are! Really!
Guys, it's been too long!
This feels a little surreal.
We...
Oh!
...are changing
in every waking moment.
Whoa!
No one can stop us from changing.
We can't go back either.
But...
We've moved forward, huh?
Yup.
Thank you, Syugo.
This is the best Christmas present.
R-Right?
Though it's the new year now.
Thanks, Syugo.
I'm so happy that I got to see
the first sunrise with you guys again!
That's not your line to say!
You're the one to blame, Kizuki!
You messed up our Christmas party!
Take responsibility and go for a swim!
What?!
A long time ago...
You were on your high-horse and told me
to "go get what you want to get."
You fit the "honor student" role better.
Shin, I've told you before.
The one that gets it all
in the end is the "third lead."
You can keep being the "honor student"
for the rest of your life.
Huh?!
Wanna go visit the shrine
while we're at it?
I wanna go!
Oh wait, I'm still in my pajamas.
Sheesh.
Go get dressed, Kizuki!
We're moving forward. Together.
Later!
Bye-bye!
Hey you!
Where's Hazawa-senpai?
I didn't see him in the classroom.
Maybe he's at swim club?
I want to be blessed
by his face before I leave.
Let's check out the pool then!
Kizuki's popular as always.
And sometimes that pains me.
Kizuki!
Are you trying to go home without me?
W-Well, I...
After all, we're a couple now.
Let's go home together.
Kizuki's my boyfriend and...
I'm his girlfriend.
But...
Why can't I be more honest about this?
How could I be such a sinful guy?
To think that I'd get these from
Kasumi-senpai and Fuka-senpai this year...
My popularity is unstoppable
with the older ladies.
What are you talking about?
They're boxes of love.
Say what?
I felt bad receiving Valentines
every year, so I planned this.
Karaoke Chocolate
Trading Party
RSVP
A karaoke chocolate trading party!
A-As expected of a social butterfly...
By the way, where's Shin-chan?
He was headed to cram school.
So he ran away from us.
Yup.
Um, Kashiwagi-kun...
Don't want it.
But I haven't said anything yet!
Just leave it.
His "don't speak to me" aura
is off the charts...
In that case, let's head home.
Oh, Mizuho.
Just so you know, you're not getting my
special homemade chocolates this year.
Huh? Why not?
Like I can give it to someone
with a boyfriend!
See you two later!
Oh, yeah...
Valentine's Day...
I haven't planned anything.
It's nippy, but feels good out.
I panicked and bought some chocolates...
But just how do I give it to him?
What do I say?
I was thinking how amazing it is
that I get to keep you all to myself.
Oh, sorry.
I... I'm still not used to this.
L-Let's go home.
I'm a certified clown for sure.
It's no good...
I'm not fit for romance.
If this persists, I'll never change.
Kizuki
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Let's go
somewhere on Sunday!
Turns out I'm going with the Southern Kanto Select Team for training camp. Starting tomorrow until the 16th.
It's at the international swimming pool.
Training camp?
Those that finished 1000 can take a break!
Mizuho
I see, that's amazing! Gotcha!
Good Luck!
Yeah!
He hasn't messaged me...
Are you busy with practice?
Why did I let go of
Kizuki's hand back then?
Oh! Thanks.
It was under the TV.
I knew I must have
dropped it at your place.
I'm glad.
What's wrong?
You seem down.
What? Really?
Kizuki
Incoming Call...
Slide to Answer
Hey! Mizuho!
Kizuki! Guess what—
Kizuki? Who are you talking to?
Give it back, Taiyo!
We have a meeting at 4:30, Kizuki.
Hey, Mizuho—
Gather around!
Sorry. Maybe later, Mizuho.
Call Ended
Kizuki's world...
keeps expanding.
No time to feel nervous.
Knowing you, you must be
thinking something dumb
like "Oh no, I'm no match for Kizuki..."
You're loved by the person you love.
You're in the best possible reality.
Do you understand that?
That's a huge miracle.
Airu...
Thank you.
Even if it's just for a second...
The next station is: Hiyoshi.
The doors on the right will open.
I need to see Kizuki.
And when I do, I'll tell him my feelings.
This is it.
I think it was at the Sub Arena.
You there!
Are you family with the athletes?
Or a former player?
No, I'm not.
You can't enter without
prior approval for entry.
Oh.
Th-Then could you please get this
to Kizuki Hazawa for me?
We get people like you
a lot around this time.
Fans like you, bringing
chocolates and such.
"Fans" like me...
We don't accept things like that.
I couldn't tell him
that I'm his girlfriend.
I need to go home.
I wanted to see Kizuki.
Ouch.
I shouldn't have worn my new shoes.
Whoa!
I rushed out and bought some chocolates.
Acting like a girlfriend
all of a sudden...
I feel so stupid.
I'm going nowhere, all alone...
Found you.
Kizuki!
What are you doing?
Coming out here all on your own?
Oh...
This is the first time I've seen him
make such a scary expression.
What do I do?
I made him upset.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to see you, Kizuki.
I was going to leave
as soon as I gave you this.
Sorry for being such an inconvenience...
Don't do things like this!
I heard from Coach
that a girl came to visit.
I immediately thought
it was you, so I rushed over.
I was so worried you'd get lost.
You wouldn't even answer your phone.
Don't worry me like that!
You're loved by the person you love.
You're in the best possible reality.
I... If something
happened to you, Mizuho...
I don't know what I'd do...
Kizuki.
Hmm?
I want to kiss you.
I understand now.
To be a "girlfriend" is to be
the person most precious to someone.
Kizuki. You smell like the pool.
And that's a huge miracle.
# 17 Feelings That Won't Go Away