Oh!
Himari's participating in the banquet?
9th Squadron
(Head of House Azuma)
Tovera Azuma
Yes, Mother.
9th Squadron
Second-in-Command
Maia Azuma
She's gotten cocky after defeating Yachiho
in the intersquad exhibition match.
She doesn't realize that she won
'cause Yachiho's got a soft spot for her!
9th Squadron
Homare Azuma
Will Himari show no promise
and be clipped from the bush?
Or will she bloom
where she's been planted?
Either way,
we need to be in tip-top shape for
the fight against the Eight Thunder Gods
and the Supreme Commander election!
This is how we purge weakness
from our household!
What a joyous occasion!
I'll take care of Himari.
Make her cry like when we were kids.
You have no right to decide
who gets to kill her, Homare.
Hard to take ya seriously when
you're dressed like a clown threw up!
Maybe I'll just lop your head off next.
Except you can't.
Finding it difficult to move, Homare?
Maia!
We slayed plenty of Shuuki today,
and yet they still have so much energy.
They've got the right attitude.
There's no room for weaklings
in the Azuma Family.
My heart sunk and I no longer feel hope for the future
It felt like time froze and now it's all over
Brooding and silent
The umbrella of my heart began to open
Still, I kept my chin up and went on
I won't ask you to comfort me
I want to grow strong and focus on what's ahead
But weakness crushes me
Meeting you is what filled my world with light
I didn't have an ounce of hope, and yet I could laugh
Ordinary conversations always brought me a smile
I won't say thanks 'cause you'll blush and laugh
But I'm thinking it
Can I move forward from here?
O light, come to me
The Azuma Banquet
Episode 5
Mere steps from the Tamagawa Passage
lies the Azuma Estate.
Just like old times, huh, Himari?
Knock it off.
I don't remember this place fondly.
If you're nervous,
why not hold your big sister's hand?
And get made fun of?
Glad you made it to the Azuma Banquet!
Lady Tovera?!
When did she...
You are such a cutie pie, Yachiho!
The jewel of our family!
Snuggle, snuggle, snuggle!
Lady Tovera!
Himari's here, too... Right there.
I see you still haven't quit
the Demon Defense Force.
Are you disappointed?
As long as you show promise,
we won't have an issue.
Otherwise, you'll be dealt with
before you sully the Azuma name.
You two are spoiling them,
coming to watch like this.
We've heard the banquet's quite ruthless.
They're our dear squad members.
We won't try anything funny.
It's a competition, fair and square.
In that case, I'm not worried.
Himari's strong.
Commander...
Oh-ho...
This will also reflect on
Kyouka Uzen's character.
I can gauge whether
she's a worthy ally to our family.
Here, I brought a small token
of my appreciation.
These are my favorite!
Yummy!
Um, who is she?
Himari and Yachiho's grandmother.
Just call me Tovera, kid!
I figured Fubuki would
sweep the competition this time around.
But if Yachiho's participating,
things could get interesting!
My goal is to prepare for the future.
Yeah, sure. If you say so.
Anyways, everyone's here.
How many of each?
Four from the main household.
MAIN
BRANCH
Four from the branch family.
This is going to get exciting!
Are they all in the Demon Defense Force?
Only five out of the eight.
Why did you answer that question?
The Azuma Family has its fingers
in a lot of different pies.
Those two are a part of
a special police force
Sorako Azuma
Takemi Azuma
that investigates crimes
involving abilities.
Now then... Let's cut to the chase.
Welcome to the Azuma Banquet,
a match that will determine
the next head of the family!
The eight of you will fight
to the finish in the other dimension.
If you're incapacitated or give up,
you're disqualified.
Whoever's left
becomes the new family matriarch!
Yumina Azuma
Is that all?
Suffice to say...
What's that?
The gate to the other dimension.
There's not an Azuma alive
who doesn't know it.
...we'll stagger your starting positions.
You'll enter one at a time.
So it's a battle royale.
I'll just thrash the losers
and ride the wave to victory.
Whaddya think, Himari?
You remember, right?
How I made you cry over and over
in this very courtyard?
I'm surprised you'd come back here
after all that trauma.
What are you, a masochist?
Hey, you listenin' to me?
That dumbass Homare...
I'll slap the shit out of her,
then rewind time and bail Himari out.
You remind me of Yachiho, but not quite.
What?!
You're a real nasty piece of work.
And I won't hesitate...
to kick your ass!
You bitch!
Enter now, pass on through
What narrow path is this?
It's the narrow path to Tenjin Shrine
Please let me pass on through
Those without a reason
may not pass through
To celebrate this child's seventh birthday
We come to offer our ofuda
We're the last ones.
Good luck, Yuuki.
Thanks!
It may be scary, but enter now
Pass on through
We're going to watch from the sidelines.
When the fight begins,
it'll be displayed here.
Oh, look. They wasted no time.
Unbelievable.
Announcing you'd be at the beach before
ever setting foot on the battlefield?
Our little stepsister's
awfully full of herself.
Hunting you down
would only take time and effort.
You're working as a team, am I right?
I'll take both of you on at once.
The main household
and its endless arrogance...
We have a strategy to deal with you.
We're going to seize the Azuma Family
for ourselves!
Of course I ended up on the far side.
Gotta take Homare down
before she finds Himari!
Wow, it's like a real island.
Don't expect your wounds to heal
after combat in this dimension.
Be careful.
So it's totally different
than the intersquad match.
Thanks for not complaining
about having to come with me.
What? It's a little late for that.
As long as we're here,
let's kick some ass.
Make sure they feel it
when they get their just desserts!
Sounds like you've got
the 7th Squadron spirit, Yuuki!
We've been training in preparation
for the Azuma Banquet.
I'll show them the fruits of our labor!
Although, some of it
was pretty embarrassing.
No! Focus, focus!
There you are.
Homare!
After I tie you up and take you hostage...
I'll be free to finish off Yachiho.
Not bad. I better kick it up a notch.
That's Homare's program input!
Her ability just now...
Did she use it to track us down?
But why did she take off her uniform?
Because she's a nutjob!
I've got sensitive skin,
so it lets me absorb a whole lotta data.
Homare's ability is known as "Python."
Her actions are programmed,
input into her brain...
then her body executes
said movements to a T.
Though she cannot modify
the input actions,
her body is significantly augmented
while executing them.
Brand Break
All within the projected range.
Yuuki!
She managed to evade my Brand Break?!
Her body's that much more enhanced
as a result of her program input.
Python...
It's a tricky ability.
Data acquisition complete.
It's checkmate in three turns.
Yuuki!
First, I do damage to slow you down.
Two turns left.
What's wrong, Himari?
Gimme what ya got!
You don't stand a chance!
All right...
If you insist, then who am I to refuse?
Yuuki!
Yeah, I should be good to go now!
We'll show her
just how extraordinary Slave can be!
Heavenward!
Heavenward
That's game over.
Not yet!
If Yumina can land the shot...
Their sniper has been taken care of.
I thought you had a strategy
to deal with me.
You're wasting your time.
Even now, I'm getting stronger.
She's been second to none
ever since we were young.
And she keeps getting better?
I can't... compete...
Now we wait for Homare.
What was that?
So the little brat
had an ace up her sleeve.
Eternal Chains: Slave
Whirlwind "Heaven"
Yuuki must've recognized
his potential to evolve.
I'd expect nothing less from my slave.
A massive buff for
a limited amount of time, I'm guessing?
I won't bother to explain.
You'll lose before you even catch on!
Looks like someone's all bark and no bite.
If I keep my distance,
her buff will wear off soon enough.
That's when I'll crush her!
Wha-
We got her!
Good work!
Hey, take it easy!
You're already worn out!
I don't need my ability.
I can fight with my bare hands!
You want a fight?
I'll give you one.
I warned you, didn't I?
That I'd kick your ass!
She took the bait!
I might be hurt,
but she can't beat me hand to hand.
I made you cry five times!
Let me jog your memory!
Wh-what in the hell?!
Going hand to hand with the 7th Squadron?
Are you stupid?
Quit lookin' down on me like that.
You're part of the main household,
through and through!
I'm gonna take everything
from you pretentious pricks!
The Azuma Family will be mine!
You're angry at the Azumas.
Welcome to the club.
Well, be that as it may...
So strong...
...it's time you got your just desserts!
Well done, you two!
Talk about an upset! Nice job, Himari!
"Heavenward"...
Marching for the heavens.
Now it all makes sense.
Guess I oughtta go fetch the losers
while the combat's on pause.
Please forgive me.
I couldn't stay in my Slave form.
What's with the formality?
It's just... you were amazing back there.
Whatever.
Stick out your tongue.
This is such an... indecent reward.
Huh?!
Do go on.
Cipher, cipher
One person sneaking a look at me
Spinning in a symmetrical loop
Tired of always being scored
Where did that accomplished feeling go?
Where? Hey
On the verge of a growing panic
Always matching the pitch
Being on full alert gets frustrating
The glass slipper is already lost
It's the worst
Let's stop this already
Anticipating an epic duel
Do you get it?
Cipher, cipher
One person sneaking a look at me
Stories full of only you
Why can't you just be a loser?
Cipher, cipher
The chains might have me too far gone
Nonfiction that puts me on edge
Can't accept a draw
Had a good run
Who's sneaking a look at me?
CHECK OUT
It makes my blood boil
every time I think about it.
The reward I gave Yuuki Wakura...
I can't move again!
You have to pet my belly, too?
The reward wasn't over yet?!
I'd better make this quick!
A complete and utter beast.
Next time, I'm going to make sure
Yuuki Wakura knows
which one of us is the dog.
That's why I ordered one of these.
I am Ren Yamashiro, Supreme Commander
of the Demon Defense Force!
And I will be obeyed!
A New Azuma
Episode 6
Next time, Episode 6: "A New Azuma"
Here is today's bonus.
The hell kind of outfit is that?!
It suits you well, Homare.
Is this revenge
for that pink monstrosity?!