The Hellhorde and Imperial Army have been
locked in battle for many years.
Led by their grand inquisitor,
Torture Tortura,
the Hellhorde's elite inflict
their torture on a daily basis.
She faces fierce beasts, flames,
unknown devices and spells,
yet the princess does not give in.
She would never give in.
She would never let the words,
"I surrender!" leave her lips so readily.
Meanwhile, the princess's former friend,
the assassin Sakura Heartrock,
fails to assassinate the Hell-Lord,
and sets off on a new path.
Sakura-chan, 'tis finally time
for your first torture.
Will you really be okay on your own?
Yes. I feel like I'd lean
on your help with you there.
Okay, time to give it my all.
I've committed a lot
of terrible deeds in my past.
So to make amends...
from here on out...
I'll make people happy through torture!
What?
Princess?
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Ex.
I've made up my mind.
I will never give in to their torture!
Man, if I haven't heard that before.
This time, I'm dead serious.
Which is why I'm giving you this.
A lightning amulet.
This allows you to activate
a lightning spell with your mind.
The moment you think, "Her Highness
is gonna cave to the torture,"
What?
you can fire a lightning spell at me.
Agh
The pain will help me
regain my composure...
I've calmed down.
and I'll be able to
hold off on surrendering.
Is that the only way
you can control yourself?
Where'd this thing come from, anyway?
After a torture the other day,
while we were on a stroll,
I got a tour of the Hellholm armory.
A tour of their armory
in the middle of a stroll?!
For an enemy nation's princess?!
Hmph
Hmph!
Just goes to show how much they trust me!
That's when I secretly
borrowed the amulet.
Betraying their trust...
You're sure about this?
Yeah, go ahead.
Do I have it in me, though?
To fire a lightning spell
at Your Highness?
Rest assured.
After making up my mind,
I won't be folding so easily.
Princess.
'Tis time for torture.
This will be your torture for today...
Fried chicken.
Looks yummy!
I-Is something wrong, Princess?
N-No, not at all.
Nice going, Ex.
I was able to stay strong, thanks to you.
Glad to hear it.
You were going on like,
"Do I have it in me?"
Yet you didn't hesitate to activate it.
I, too, was surprised
at my complete lack of resistance.
Are you really okay?
Don't worry about me.
Perhaps you should ask
the same of yourself.
You're right, I do love fried chicken.
However...
Do you know which piece is my favorite?
Verily, fried chicken comes
in a variety of pieces.
The thigh, popular for
its fatty dark meat.
The wing, with its chewy
eating experience.
And more, all with their own appeal.
But the piece that you're most fond of...
'Tis none other than...
The drumstick!
You got it!
What in the world has
been going on today?
Don't worry about it...
You're right on the money.
I love drumsticks.
The way they look gets me so excited.
It is the shape you
associate most with chicken.
Incidentally, the meal
that I purchased today
happened to contain only
a single drumstick.
In other words...
After I eat this one,
there will be no drumsticks left.
W-Wait, I give in. I'll talk!
This is for Her Highness's sake!
I will steel my heart
and carry out my duty to the end!
You monster!
Wh-What is this, Princess?
You're glowing!
Th-This is the strongest strike so far!
I feel like I'll pass out
if I drop my guard!
However, I'm the Princess and
Commander of the Imperial Third Legion!
A measly lightning strike like this...
Cannot stop me from surrendering!
Surrender by Might
Try using that iron willpower
to endure the torture instead!
The princess
confessed
Delicious!
Drumsticks are the best!
They just scream "chicken" to me!
Would you like to try
the other pieces, Princess?
Really? Awesome!
I love fried chicken!
It's imperial custom to eat egg
dishes around the end of the year.
Makes you wonder how it got started.
I've also bought the items you asked for.
With biscuits?
Of course, and vanilla
ice cream to go with them.
You must be a mind reader.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"Princess
Torture planned to use
the leftover chicken for rice pilaf,
but there was none left in the end.
An experimental spell went haywire...
splitting up Torture into good
and evil personalities.
Right now, my good self is trying
to find a way to turn us back.
So for today's torture, it'll be me,
the evil Torture, who's in charge!
Time for your torture, Princess!
Your evil self still shows up
for work, huh?
I'm not really sure what makes her evil.
For today's torture...
Straight out of a plastic bag?!
The Torture I know would never do that!
So this is evil Torture!
Pretty low bar for "evil,"
don't you think?
Do you really think I'd yield
to such slapdash torture?
Take a look!
This is your torture!
An éclair!
Your Highness!
Number one... It's number one...
There are all sorts
of great pastries out there,
but taking everything into account,
like taste, availability, and price...
The number one, tried-and-true pastry
that won't let you down...
is a convenience store éclair!
That light, crispy dough,
thickly coated in chocolate...
And filled with a rich, gooey custard!
Perfect in every way!
You may be evil, but
you're still Torture!
It's the perfect torture!
Huh?
I don't think she feels
as strongly as you do.
I want it... I want to eat it!
However!
I'm the Princess and Commander
of the Imperial Third Legion!
I will not give in to your torture!
I will not crave that éclair!
Yeah! You tell her, Your Highness!
What are you talking about?
What?
I got one for you, too,
so let's enjoy them together.
Huh?
You'll give it to me even though
I haven't surrendered?
What about the torture?
Oh, right.
I'm supposed to get
a secret out of you for the torture.
Well, whatever.
"Well, whatever?!"
Didn't I say I'm the evil Torture?
My feelings come before the rules.
And nothing beats sharing some
good food with other people!
E-Evil Torture!
Time to eat!
Yummy!
This is great!
The chocolate's not too sweet, either!
It's so gooey!
The
Next Day
I managed to return to normal,
but my head still hurts from yesterday.
My evil self technically
wrote up a report...
but it's completely incoherent.
Dear Usual Torture
A letter?
m 0 0 l 200 0 200 40 0 40
The evil Torture said
she didn't need it,
but since the éclair was good,
here's a secret for you.
Dear usual Torture,
The evil Torture said she didn't need it,
but since the éclair was good,
here's a secret for you.
All clownfish are born as males.
How honorable of her.
Thank you, Princess.
I may not be able to remember it...
but I seem to have had fun as well.
"Torture" Report Form
It was totally
awesome
Looks like you're back
to your usual self, Torture.
Allow me to apologize
for the inconvenience.
Still, I've had enough.
Why are all of these
experimental spells going haywire?
Actually, there's a reason for that.
What, you're here to make excuses?
Go ahead, let's hear them.
Currently, Hellhorde R&D is experimenting
with treating lumbago via electrotherapy.
But a lightning amulet they were using
has gone missing from the armory,
leading to calibration issues that
have resulted in these frequent errors.
What?
A what amulet?
'Tis a lightning amulet.
Ah.
So it's not as though R&D is
frivolously causing all this mayhem...
U-Um, uh, well...
Excuse me, I've been paged.
I'll be back when 'tis time
for your torture, Princess.
I think it'd be best if you apologized.
The princess
apologized
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
I've committed a lot
of terrible deeds in my past.
So to make amends,
from here on out...
I'll make people happy through torture!
What?
Princess?
Wait, is that you, Sakura?
Sakura? The Sakura that we know?
I'm sure of it,  although it was hard to
tell at first with that outfit...
Sakura, you...
You're alive?
What a relief.
Why, Princess?
I was deceiving you the whole time!
I could tell.
Your attack that day...
It was a strike full of hesitation
that lacked your usual commitment.
That told me everything.
I knew that deep down,
you didn't want to kill me.
I could see it in your eyes.
That you had no choice in the matter.
It was the same for me.
I didn't have a choice in the matter.
Which is why...
I'm so relieved to see
that you're alive and well.
Princess...
Thank you.
Yes. I had no choice in the matter.
That said, I truly
enjoyed our time together.
All that time, I couldn't
help but think...
How nice it'd be
if we were really friends.
Sakura.
I've also always...
Your Highness?
No.
Let's see if you can get
the rest out of me.
You're an inquisitor now, aren't you?
Show me what you can
do with your torture!
Yes!
We may have had a painful past,
but now things are different.
We're no longer from rival nations.
I'm just a prisoner,
and she's my torturer.
There's nothing strange about a prisoner
and her torturer being friends.
Isn't that right, Sakura?
That's amazing, Sakura!
Did you practice that a lot?
After a torture, you're supposed to
complete a report immediately after.
But I'll make an exception this once
and give her an extension.
The princess talked.
Just her and Sakura, late into the night.
Hellholm Happy Farm
Still, I never imagined you were
the one Sakura had failed to assassinate.
I sure was surprised.
I'm sorry, Sakura-chan.
Oh, no.
Hellholm Happy Farm
Petting Zoo
I'm to blame as well
for omitting the details.
Well, I'm sure there's
a lot we still have to talk about...
But let's forget all that for today...
and have fun at the farm!
Hellholm Happy Farm
Petting Zoo
To celebrate the princess
and Sakura's reconciliation,
they're taking a group trip to a farm.
Your Highness!
Don't run off in excitement
or you might trip!
I know!
A goat!
So cute.
This is my first time at a farm.
Mine as well.
The empire's not without farms,
but they have handlers to do all the work.
Everyone.
They're selling animal food over there.
I wanna feed them!
Here's some food for you.
Feel free to take more.
Is it good?
They're so adorable!
Huh? You're not gonna
feed them, Princess?
Well, I never even looked
after my own steed.
So I don't have any experience
feeding large animals.
I'm a little scared now that
I've come face-to-face with them.
What?
How pathetic.
Hey!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Now that I can be honest with you,
I blurted out how I really feel!
That's how you feel about me?!
H-Hey, I can do it, too!
Hands-On Milking
You're good at this, Sakura.
How was it?
It was my first time...
But it was warm, squishy, and fuzzy!
Squishy and fuzzy?!
You're right!
It's squishy and fuzzy!
Squishy 'n' fuzzy!
Your Highness, your face! Your face!
This milk's amazing!
You can really tell that it's fresh.
So creamy!
It really is delicious.
Soft-Serve Ice Cream
Made with Fresh Milk
Pork-Wrapped
Rice Balls
They have a store that sells soft-serve
ice cream using the same milk.
I'd love to try it, but...
It's a little too chilly out
to be eating soft serve.
I want some!
Maomao-chan's full of energy!
Let me go and buy some, then.
Who here wants some soft serve?
I do, too, of course.
This is great!
It's so rich and creamy.
Huh? Sakura-chan, you tried
to assassinate Princess-chan?
Yes...
She even got a slash in.
Huh...
Pretty wild. I mean, you two
are friends now, right?
Yeah! Friends!
Awesome!
Mm-hmm.
Big news, everyone!
It looks like there's
a giant maze over there!
I was the one who found it.
Let's all go check it out!
Yeah!
We can't skip out on that!
Maze Adventure
Get a move on!
They're all
great friends
Sakura... Sakura.
Sakura.
We're here.
Huh? Oh...
Good morning.
Good morning, Sakura-chan.
I slept like a baby.
We did play lots today!
Yeah, you were out like a light.
Take a look.
Asleep and completely defenseless!
Not very assassin-like of you.
Like you weren't asleep, too.
You just happened to wake up first.
Hey! You-chan!
I got a photo of her. Look.
What?
You're right!
In-chan!
Not very commander-like of you.
Ugh, I can't believe I was drooling!
Delete it! I'm begging you!