Damn it.
Have you ever given any thought to
what would happen after you died?
I mean, considering our line of work,
it could happen at any time.
It can't hurt to hear if you all have
any last wishes you'd like fulfilled.
That's dumb as hell.
I'm invincible, so I ain't plannin' on...
dying.
Go on, Malta, your turn.
That's exactly what I'd
expect from you, Joe.
Personally, I think about that
sorta thing all the time.
But I'm not into the sappy,
sentimental thing...
When my time comes, make sure you send
me off with a big bang.
You're a weird guy, Malta.
Why even worry about what
happens once you're dead?
Considering we're all...
bound for hell, anyway.
I wanna just be gone,
like a bubble popping.
Just like you're about to be, Ishino!
Because I attack!
Agreed.
There's something unsettling about
leaving traces behind once you're dead.
But I do hope that whoever
delivers me to my end...
will die with a...
Spell
Targeted player must expend two resources
or their attacking unit will be bound for one turn.
glorious death knell on their lips.
Martyr's Resentment
You're bound.
Unfortunately for you, I don't
intend on going out without a fight!
We'd always act tough about this stuff.
Or maybe it was more like
putting up a front?
Because, and I hate admitting it,
Ishino, Joe, Malta, and I...
We acted like we weren't afraid of
death in order to seem impressive.
Ishino the Musician.
Out of all of us, he was the most
repulsive, obviously fronting liar.
You coming by today?
I've got work.
What the hell, you dumb bastard?
Scum of the Brave
A Brave's Sins
Hey, Joe. Any progress
with Ishino's recorder?
The cops still have it.
Should know about the
contents by tomorrow.
How're things on your end?
Count Croix of the Six Senses was a bust.
They don't seem to know
who did Ishino in, either.
I had Malta do some digging,
so it's legit.
Yeah? I managed to turn up a lead.
Those folks with the badge
with the split-face dragon?
The buyers are familiar with them.
They're known as the Half Dragon.
The Half Dragon?
They've been dealing some drug
called E4 to the Dark Lords.
And the Count of Amber Thorns
was one of their regulars.
Or... have you really taken it?
I take it you heard this from Matsugi?
Yeah.
He sold Ishino out to the Half Dragon.
Turns out, Ishino had killed
a handful of Dark Lords
who'd been customers of the Half Dragon.
Matsugi didn't know who
their boss was, though.
That's next, then.
All right. I'll look into it.
You know how drug crews can be.
Watch your back.
Yeah. Let's meet up in
his garage on Tuesday.
Malta, if you wanna eat, you
better wash your hands first.
Come on, can we just
kill this guy already?
He's one of the bad ones.
Don't be stupid.
He's what you call a
civilian collaborator.
We gotta treat him real nice, y'know?
Come on, laugh, kid.
This is the kinda thing
you wanted to see, right?
Gimme some E3.
Fifteen doses.
That's a whole lot at once.
Could be bad for you.
I'm buying for a whole group.
That's what they all say, at first...
Just hand it over already!
Exams are at 17:00 on Friday.
Observers are allowed, so could you come by?
Aki is asking.
Busy right now.
We need to move carefully.
That duo, Levy and Ido...
If we try to track them down
but do it sloppily, we'll
be the ones who end up dead.
Who was giving the orders?
There were four other people's
blood on Ishino's body.
They waited until his E3 wore
off and then did him in.
Going after a single target
with a squad of goons...
Who do I know that operates like that?
The Count of Twin Pincers?
Records Room
Shinjuku Dark Lord
Response Team
We've got plenty of cases
involving his underlings
and people who used to work for him,
but his own bounty is kinda iffy.
That's an ex-Brave for you!
He's smart, in a chickenshit way.
Didn't you know each other
way back when, Yashiro-san?
Nah. Not at all.
You know, a civilian posted a bounty for
one of the Twin Pincer's minions!
The Advancing Party
Harumi Koji
Youth!
Hope!
A Future!
His own father actually posted it.
Guy's a mid-sized politician...
We really talking about this right now?
The bounty is a beefy twenty mil!
But he needs to be taken in alive,
and in decent condition.
It's this boy. And he's this
girl's brother, apparently.
Oh, I recognize these two.
Only the brother has a bounty!
According to his father...
I realize that, as a politician, this
kind of thing is shameful to request.
But still, I earnestly wish
for my son's safe return.
A-As for my daughter,
I always half-expected a girl
like her to be led astray...
But my son!
He's always been serious,
and a good boy!
Please, return him to me!
So he said.
Kid's apparently only sixteen!
Poor little fella.
Age doesn't mean anything.
Their ether perceptions were pretty nasty.
Especially the girl's.
When I ran into her a few months ago,
I had to turn tail and run.
I might run into them while
tracking down Twin Pincers,
but I can't guarantee
that I take them alive.
Is that so?
I thought it was a
pretty delicious offer!
Whatever, just tell me where
I can find the bastard!
Submitted for your consideration!
The Dark Lord known as the
Count of Twin Pincers.
Majority of his rap sheet consists
of kidnapping and human trafficking.
He was a Brave until four years ago.
The name he went by back then...
Doesn't really matter.
He was always something of a busybody.
Got a group of friends
and they operated something that
resembled a school for swordsmanship...
But a hunt went bad, and his
entire gang was wiped out.
Long story short, he couldn't make
ends meet as a Brave after that.
These days, he trains combatants for the
Dark Overlord, the Coffin Count of Storms.
Oversees them, too.
They number around a hundred.
The majority of them are kids from
around town with no place better to go.
Some ran away from home,
some couldn't stay with their
parents or within the system,
some are foreigners
who couldn't return home...
or their kids.
And he's looking after kids like this?
Are we sure he's a bad guy?
Dude stole a panda corpse.
A panda?! He's an absolute monster, then!
And good at running away, too.
Best way to get any intel is gonna
be taking one of his people alive.
The money is pretty appealing, too.
Scum of the Brave
Let's make this as nonlethal as we can.
You got it.
None of you are a match for him.
Fall back!
I told you all to back off, damn it!
Who gave him E3?!
We're abandoning this place!
Scatter! Now!
They're kinda overprotective,
considering I only came
by to have a little chat.
You could've been a bit
more amicable about it.
I have no idea what
happened to the Musician.
Wasn't he a deviant serial killer?
With no shortage of vendettas, I'd wager.
Agreed.
But he was trying to learn about E4.
That monster you cooked up...
you used some of it to make him, right?
Is the Coffin Count of Storms
the one distributing E4?
You're sorely mistaken.
We've been trying to figure out
what that concoction is ourselves.
How do I know you're not working
for the Half Dragon yourself?
Because, maybe, I'm trying to kill them?
They're a bit like arms dealers.
They provide E4 and E3 procured from
illicit sources to weaker Dark Lords
in an attempt to disrupt the status quo.
They provoke conflict between the
Dark Lords to boost their own business.
Some real warlords, huh?
And who's running the show?
Couldn't tell you.
But they're our enemy, in any case.
My personal goal is for stability.
I want a powerful Dark Lord, such as the
Coffin Count of Storms, to reign over all.
Their business is an obstacle
for that goal.
I believe we can work together,
in regards to the Half Dragon.
Work together, my ass.
You're asking for a lot, after
all the times you've tried to kidnap me.
Hey there.
I'll save the rest of my
questions for your big brain.
Especially since we've got a
big old bounty here with us.
Coach. I won't let them take Yoshi-kun.
No matter the cost.
It won't come to that. I swear.
Yashiro the Reaper! Malta the Mole!
For the sake of my minions,
you two will perish here!
Not bad.
Settle down, now.
You ran from your old man, right?
I get what that's like.
When I was little, mine made
me fight boars and bears...
Talk about a nightmare.
You can always run again,
after we send you back.
You're old enough to manage that.
Things will work out.
Help...
Coach, please save me!
I don't want to go back to that house!
Don't want him talking, huh?
You just blew a huge bounty for me, man.
You think I'm silencing him?
Neither of them ever
wanted to return home.
It's that simple.
I made a promise that, if it ever looked
like they were going to be dragged back,
I would kill them myself.
I granted a sword for those who
had to do battle with fear.
I provided a life of dignity to children
for whom there was no other salvation!
What bullshit. And that's the job you
think is fancier than being a Brave?
What else could I do?!
Being a Brave is no different
than being an executioner.
How convenient it must be
for the masses...
Letting us filthy outcasts
clash amongst ourselves,
wiping each other out!
That's what awaits you!
You will lose everything!
He can control other
people's gloves, too?!
Sorry, Malta. I underestimated him.
Kinda feel bad for them.
Yeah.
Harumi
We offer our condolences.
Making a damn fool of me!
Aren't you embarrassed?!
Have you no shame?!
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Next Time
Pantyhose are essential
to a classy lady's look!
I once tore three pairs of my mother's.
I wonder if there's some trick to it?
And you're asking me why, exactly?
You think I have any advice to offer?
A Brave's Legacy
Next time, Episode 9:
A Brave's Legacy.
What is your deal?! Do you have any
idea how annoying and obnoxious—