The inner room?
He wasn't here.
That can't be. Where did he go?
Don't tell me he ran outside.
This is bad, Hijikata-san.
In his condition? Impossible.
Did someone help him escape?
This way.
Come on.
Blue Miburo
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Come on, men! Dance!
It shows no sign of stopping.
Will the swallow take flight?
Nio, what are you playing at?
Don't tell me you plan to help me escape.
Are you telling me, Serizawa Kamo,
to turn tail and live on?
What would a shameless life get me?
What would that leave?
I have no unfinished business!
What the...
Why the hell am I thinking of you?
You're having a kid? Why should I care?
I'm a samurai.
I can't settle down and start a family.
Have it if you want,
but raise it yourself.
What a waste of time.
If that baby was born
and lived long enough to grow up,
I guess it would be around their age now.
You were the worst of them.
Always hesitating.
No faith in yourself.
Constantly failing.
Manly
Always worrying
what other people think.
You couldn't be farther
from Serizawa Kamo's ideal man.
Bah! Now I've got myself pissed off!
I want to give him a good thump
and kick right now!
Come here. I'll give you a bath.
I thought I picked him up on a whim...
You good-for-nothing!
Can't you even pour tea right?
...and came down so hard on him...
Taro, put more oomph in your step.
Y-Yes, sir.
...because I felt guilty about
not looking after my own kid.
But if I was doing it to atone,
would it have killed me
to give him a hug just once?
Will I survive this?
Is that future possible?
I'll live.
I want to live.
Serizawa-san, I have kept you
waiting for far too long.
Death.
Take my head.
I hope I can trust you to do it properly.
Who do you think you're talking to?
Show me a death
worthy of Serizawa Kamo.
No.
What am I thinking?
Isn't this the future
I wanted more than any other?
You said it. How I've waited
for this, Sir Kondo.
A friend of mine died.
If your death leads to the future...
Did he take his own life?
Yes.
But he left many things behind.
Wh-Who the hell are you?
Can't you even tell friend from foe?!
Let us through.
Leave it to a real samurai.
Where would the Miburo be without you?
I won't lead you wrong.
He was an extraordinarily clever man.
Bylaws
Yamanami, I want you to have this.
What are you thinking?
I won't dance to your tune.
Welcome.
I wonder just how much
of this he planned.
That doesn't matter!
It has nothing to do with us at all!
Please calm yourself and listen.
This isn't only relevant to us.
You also have—
No!
No, never!
I won't move from this spot!
Quit your whining, you insufferable bitch!
Oh, dear. I lost my temper.
I sent Itosato to Fushimi.
What? Ito-chan is safe?
Join her and leave Kyoto.
Won't you please try
to start new lives in peace?
I assume you can find
your way from here?
Yes.
The Miburo's future
hinges on this mission.
Our involvement must never come to light.
We cannot allow Hirama to escape.
I'm counting on you, Harada-san.
Get back here, Hirama!
Fight me fair and square!
Don't you want to fight for Serizawa?
What kind of friend are you?
Are you crying?
Is this how you repay him?!
What?
Don't forget! The Miburo wouldn't be
who they are now without Serizawa-sensei.
None of you appreciate
his real significance!
Losing him would be a blow to the nation!
Isn't that laying it on a bit thick?
Harada, you picked
the wrong man to follow.
I decide who I throw my weight behind.
That's fighting dirty!
Die!
No chance!
I'll expose your wickedness to the world.
You'll what?
Don't you forget it!
Damn it. Where'd you go?
Say something!
Get out here, Hirama!
C-Crap. I've totally lost him.
What? What happened?
What the hell...
Shimada, bury him deep.
Shinpachi.
I still don't approve of your methods.
Yet I have no choice
but to carry this secret to my grave.
I cannot allow you
to shoulder the burden alone.
Allow me to share the blame.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I only wondered what my pupil was up to.
Your lunges need work.
Screw you!
Is that it? Is that how much
you care about Serizawa?
Let it all out.
I'll make you spew your heart out...
till you've got no dregs
of regret left in you.
This is the Yagi residence.
It's the Miburo's base of operations.
That's Taro-kun.
He does... all sorts
of odd jobs around here.
When I met him,
he looked so lifeless that I couldn't tell
what he was thinking.
I'm going drinking.
He followed Serizawa around like a puppy.
Sensei! Y-Your coat.
Hurry up with it!
But before I knew it,
he'd become a good worker.
Take care of mine, too.
Well, be seeing you.
Jackass.
He cursed everyone
but Serizawa behind their backs.
But then, Nio came.
Taro-kun, do you want
to practice sumo with us?
No way in hell!
Hurry up!
He seemed livelier after that.
I doubt he even considered
learning the sword.
But then...
Just recently, he started
taking lessons from Nagakura.
Even so...
Damn it!
His center of balance is off.
And he swings with his arms.
He doesn't have close to enough training.
But in spite of that,
look how much stronger having
something to protect has made him.
If I don't get to Serizawa-sensei,
he'll... he'll...
You couldn't do anything
even if you were with him!
Move! Let me through!
Why are you so hung up on Serizawa?!
The Yagis and Kondo's gang
have done just as much for you!
And don't forget Nio.
Or me.
You guys don't get it.
When Sensei...
Before he faces everyone,
he pauses, just for a moment.
That's the time it takes him
to become Serizawa Kamo.
Only I know about it,
because I followed him around.
I like that about him,
and I respect him for it.
He likes living it up in a big group,
and when he ate
and drank with everybody,
he looked truly happy!
He spent so much time
surrounded by people.
But I'm sure he plans to die alone.
So why shouldn't someone stick with him
to the end, even it it's only me?
You moron.
You really are as stupid as they come.
I can't keep going much longer.
And I'm out of time.
This is good enough, right?
Listen, in a real fight, hold your sword
to make it as short as you can in.
Sh-Short? But then, it won't reach.
Wouldn't that put me
at a huge disadvantage?
No matter. Fight like that.
This swallow is but one bird.
You must scatter feed before its flight.
Nagakura, I'm gonna use it.
What is that stance?
Is that his idea of
a secret weapon? Idiot.
You'll never reach me from there.
Don't you even know your own range?
You're forgetting someone.
Taro.
He'll stick with Serizawa
to the bitter end.
Hajime, he's your job.
You want me to kill him?
Don't even joke about that!
In that case, you handle Taro!
I'll kill Serizawa.
I don't mean that.
What, then?
I want you to save Taro.
Shut up.
It's really coming down, huh?
I wonder if it'll stop by tonight.
Beats me.
Do your best for Taro-kun.
I know that.
And with all of it in mind,
I'll make him wish he'd never crossed me!
You've only just started training.
You can't defeat a master in a fair fight.
Your enemy will soon learn
to gauge your range.
Therefore, shift your right hand down
without revealing your grip.
As close to the pommel
as you can manage.
Thus, your blade will grow
one hand-width longer.
And then, the swallow will soar.
Swallow.
I missed!
If your enemy strikes first,
draw without hesitation as he pulls back.
Learn with your body.
Make drawing your sword a reflex.
That blade will keep you safe.
Strike back.
No. Stop!
Dodge!
Please dodge!
Too slow.
You're much too slow, Sir Kondo.
Now, I think it's time
we put an end to this.
Yes, Serizawa-san.
Prepare to die!
That's the Kondo I know. Well struck.
Niimi-san.
May I ask you one final thing?
You and Serizawa-san have gone about
causing mischief for a long time.
Serizawa-san grows bored easily,
causes trouble, and then moves on.
But you told me you've come
to like Kyoto and the Miburo,
and you wish to stay with us longer.
What exactly sets the Miburo apart
from all that came before?
Serizawa was different.
He was the big-hearted,
jovial version of himself that I liked.
Maybe finding an equal for the first time
took a weight off his shoulders.
You mean...
Yes.
I'm nothing but grateful to him.
No. I'm going to see this through.
Watch to the end and never forget.
This is Serizawa-san.
This is...
Serizawa Kamo.
Serizawa Kamo
Next time
Niimi—no, Iori, it's almost time.
I promised you a finale worthy
of Serizawa Kamo.
Well, the end is closing in now.
I have no remorse. No regrets.
I didn't leave any unfinished business.
Can you see this, Nio?
This is the future I wanted
more than any other.
Next time: "Blue Era."
Blue Era