I hope it hatches soon.
Hajime bought me this egg,
and the guy said it was lucky...
I bet there's something
amazing growing inside!
All right! Off we go, dragon!
Looking after an animal sounds like
a lot of work. Let's just eat it.
How could you even suggest
that?! Absolutely not!
This egg is lucky! And it's going
to hatch an incredible dragon!
I'm sure of it!
Yeah, if you say so.
Dragon...
My dragon...
H-Hajime! It's all tiny!
What is it?
Breakfast?
No! Is food the only
thing on your mind, Hajime?!
That's rich, coming from you.
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
EPISODE 5: WHAT'S HATCHING
Good morning!
It's adorable!
It sure is. I take it your egg hatched.
It did indeed!
Say hello to Dragon!
Is that... its name?
It's pretty obviously a sparrowflier.
SIZE COMPARISON: SPARROWFLIER VS. RIRUI
A LARGE BIRD THAT NESTS IN THE MOUNTAINS.
OFTEN HEARD CHIRPING IN THE MORNING.
Well...
It's cute, so who cares?
If you say so.
Still, women really love
cute animals, huh?
HE WAS ACTUALLY HOPING TO GET TO PET IT
Come to think of it,
I had a pet once too.
I'm surprised you had the
time to care for one.
What kind of animal was it?
A dragon! It was a
dragon, right, Hajime?!
I found this dog who'd made
himself at home in the slums.
Smart little fella, too.
Whenever I had spare time,
I'd teach him all kinds of tricks.
But one time, the rain
kept falling and didn't stop...
Which meant no work, and for me,
no food for two or three days.
He saved my life!
Hajime...
Don't take your eyes
off your birdie, Rirui!
Now, what's on the menu today?
Try hard to be helpful, Dragon!
That's called a slime. They react
to sound, so stay quiet, okay?
H-Hey! I said to be quiet, Dragon!
Seriously, shush!
U-Um, Hajime...
This, uh...
With how loud this thing chirps,
I guess it's a bad match for slimes.
Y-Yeah! I guess you're right.
Thank goodness. He's not mad.
Hajime must think Dragon is cute too!
He's seeing how tender the meat is!
That's why he took his gloves off!
Dragon! You watch the
room while we're gone.
Be good, understand?
Take this!
Hyah!
Gimme those eyeballs!
Dragon has trouble fighting slimes,
so Rirui will have to work twice as hard!
RIRUI IS NOW LEVEL 3!
We're back home, Dragon!
What the hell?!
U-Uh, Hajime...
The damn poultry took a dump in my bed!
Hajime, its name is Dragon, not "Poultry."
Oh, yeah, is that right?!
Fan-freaking-tastic!
Come on, Dragon! You can do it!
Aw! Dragon, you're not
supposed to fall down!
I'm not sure Dragon can
handle this kind of thing...
But if it's not useful,
Hajime's gonna eat it!
Maybe he did that at one point,
but he's a proper adventurer now!
He'd never do something
like that, right, Hajime?
Come on! You can do it, Dragon!
The trick is stability!
There you go! Now move forward!
I really hope he doesn't ask
me to cook the little guy...
Rirui, time for work.
Understood!
I'm patrolling the village
perimeter today.
What is it? Something up?
It's nothing!
Hey.
Good luck today!
Dragon, today you're going to follow
Rirui's example and learn how to work!
I'll help out too, so let's do our best.
C'mon! Quit pooping all the time!
Your life is at stake, Dragon!
"Dragon," huh?
Great. More crap.
Wait...
I think this came from a rabbit bear.
They're not supposed to be
on this mountain.
And if it builds a den here,
that'll spell trouble.
Okay, Rirui, we're gonna track it down.
Try to stay close and...
It feels weird without her.
So, we fold it once like this,
then again like so.
And that's how you do it.
I see! Okay, let's do it, Dragon!
Yes, just like that! Nicely done!
Very good, Dragon!
Hey!
Dragon! What are you doing?!
It's fine! We just need to wash it again.
A rabbit bear, you say?
Yeah, but I couldn't track it down.
They breed quickly and attack people...
I hope we can deal with this
before they spread too much.
Gotta wonder why it's come
around these parts, though.
We've had so many cold days,
there's probably not as much
to eat in the mountains.
So it made the trek for food?
Mr. Shinonome.
Can the guild officially hire you to track
down and exterminate this rabbit bear?
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
Is something wrong, Natalie? Are you okay?
Huh? What do you mean?
I'm totally fine...
See?
Natalie, take the day off.
You're worn down from working too much.
But...
We're going to be busy later, and there's
stuff I wanted to take care of before—
No. You know how dangerous
illness can be.
In that case, Rirui and Dragon will
handle all of Natalie's work for the day!
Thank you, but it's my work,
so I should take care of it.
Come now. I know they'll do their best.
But it's my job...
Enough already! Go get some rest!
I'm being c-c-c-c-carried...
See what happens when you push yourself?
Aw, Dragon. Try and be more careful.
Is that Natalie's lunch?
Yup.
Rirui can take it to her!
Yeah? Then you go right ahead.
Mommy, am I doing a good
job with cleaning?
Yes, you really are!
I'm impressed, Natalie.
Thank you so much for helping out.
I'm gonna keep working hard!
You really let your guard down
when you get sick, I guess.
I'm so lonely, Mommy!
Are you okay?
How long have you been there, Rirui?!
For a while.
Sorry that I'm not your
mommy. You're lonely?
I-It's not like that, Rirui!
Mom... Er, my mother died three years ago,
and I'm just feeling weak
because of this cold, s-so...
Y'know?
Want me to give you head pats?
I'm fine, really!
Want me to nurse you?
I don't have milk, but...
That's quite all right!
Rirui, Dragon, thanks for today.
It's okay! We want you to
feel better soon, Natalie.
Besides, pitching in helped me
learn how hard your job is.
It's rough at times, true,
but I get to help out adventurers,
so it's also fun too.
Help out adventurers?
All I can really do for them is make
sure they have a clean place to rest.
And I want to be able
to provide that every single day.
I bet you'll be a great wife, Natalie!
Wh-Where'd that come from?
But...
Not for Hajime.
That doesn't sound good.
I'm gonna head out again tomorrow,
but it might be faster to hire a beaster
who's got a nose for tracking.
Maybe so.
What am I gonna do?
Is it that hard to find a rabbit bear?
I've spent a long time dungeon crawling.
Don't have much experience tracking
down quarry out in nature.
There are things even
Hajime can't do, huh?
What nice weather!
You look better.
Oh, good morning, Hajime!
I got some good rest thanks
to Rirui and Dragon.
Glad to hear it.
Hajime!
We're going with you today!
I'm busy looking for the rabbit bear.
You oughta help Natalie again today.
Rirui is supposed to be an adventurer
and wants to do her job!
You're both working hard!
Well, Rirui can too!
Just don't get in my way, okay?
And that goes double for yakitori there.
That's not its name!
It's Dragon, Hajime! Dragon!
Good luck, adventurers!
We're off!
These markings...
Might be a little too close
to the ground for a rabbit bear.
Hey, Dragon! Where are you going?!
Get back here! Dragon!
So noisy...
Wait, Dragon!
Honestly.
Dragon?
There's a bunch of Dragons!
They're sparrowfliers.
Maybe they noticed one of their
kind was around and came by?
Man, they're even noisier when grown!
Wh-Whoa there!
Where are you going, Dragon?!
Hey!
If it isn't the rabbit bear!
Is this for real? Then was
all that racket before was...
something yakitori here did
to track down the rabbit bear?
Nice work, Dragon!
Now leave the rest to Rirui!
I swear!
And that's a job well done.
H-Hajime, did Dragon help?
Yeah. A lot, actually.
There are sparrowfliers
all around these parts.
Being able to get info from them
is bound to come in handy.
Hell, he might be more useful than you!
Are you okay, Rirui?
I'm good!
Gotta work hard to be more
helpful than Dragon!
Here are your drinks!
You never know when to keep
your mouth shut, do you?
Excuse me. I'm looking for
a woman named Veronica.
Tanya?
What brings you all the way out here?
There's something I needed
to inform you of.
And what might that be?
I'm afraid your shop, Succubus Wings,
has gone out of business.
Oh, Master Rishat!
It's time we settle things, Veronica.
NEXT TIME: DECISIVE BATTLE
IN THE DUNGEON ATTACK!