All right, auntie. This is it.
Stay healthy! Be careful with the water.
Never let a rotten tooth fester.
Wash your hair at least
once every three days.
Don't forget to say grace before you eat!
I know, I know!
Hey!
Good luck! Good luck!
This is your home.
Come back anytime, Nicholas.
Come back anytime, Nico!
We'll welcome you just like this
when you return!
I'm off.
The town of Red Valley Bottom...
We suspect it was attacked by the Ark
several weeks to months ago
and robbed of its plant.
The Ark continues around the world,
striking towns and taking their plants.
With all our satellites down,
we have no means of
long-range communication.
The intermittent flow of
information further instills fear,
sowing panic far and wide.
The goal of Millions Knives
is to liberate the plants from their
oppression under humans,
grant them freedom,
and create a paradise for plants.
The world of humans is quietly drying up.
Is there nothing we can do but wait
for our salvation, the immigrant fleet?
June 25th of the year 113.
Journalist Meryl Stryfe.
I wonder if the boss is doing okay.
Granted, we don't even know if the
Bernardelli News Agency is still around.
Speaking of, our salaries...
No one's receiving my reports either.
But Milly, remember that we're journalists.
Let's keep documenting!
The future ahead needs
to know what happened.
We'll do the legwork ourselves,
and record everything we see and hear!
You got it, Meryl!
There's no need to photograph me.
But we're recording everything, right?
Hey, wait...
Okay, pose!
I'm impressed you've
been able to withstand
the crushing force of
Legato's power for so long.
Still don't feel like joining me, Vash?
This is nothing compared to the pain
I've endured over the last 150 years.
Indeed, it's been 150 years.
Far too long.
Thanks to you, we've wasted so much time.
Many more of our brethren
were squeezed dry, devoured.
You wouldn't know about that.
I've seen my share of dead plants.
All gone black.
The black represents fatigue.
Because they pushed
their powers to the limit.
The same will happen to us,
sooner or later.
So you knew.
But what else can humans do
to survive on this desert planet?
Their only recourse
is to rely on us plants.
And plants can't survive
without tending by humans.
We'd live much longer
out from under their thumb.
Don't forget, Nai!
The people on this planet are forced
to live a parched life of struggle.
Our kind are put in a situation where
we must push ourselves to fatigue.
And why is that?
It all started with the Big Fall!
Nai...
Do you really think people
are incapable of change?
It takes time, and they can
move backward too,
but surely they can move forward.
At least, Rem was like that!
The time it takes is exactly the problem.
All the while, our brethren are being
abused, bled dry, and disposed of.
Then that's the part we need to fix!
Nobody pays heed to the words of cattle.
Listen, Vash.
Have you forgotten Tesla?
I haven't forgotten. Not for a moment.
That was the day that drove us all mad!
That's the thing, though!
The true nature of violence can only
be named by those who have felt it!
Only those who've experienced pain can
truly speak the words to stop conflict!
Tesla... Tesla's death...
Do you want to make that just another part
of the cycle of hatred and strife?
Or will you make it the foundation
you build your conviction upon?
That's the real struggle!
Don't you turn away, Nai!
I see. You're completely right, Vash.
The pain was unbearable.
Yet through it, I learned the truth.
You're so right!
And they too must learn.
Then we'll finally be even!
Nai...
I told you before. This is the battle
to bring everything back to even, Vash!
Don't repeat the same mistake!
The end of the world of humans...
The birth of paradise for our brethren...
Bear witness from there.
Wait, Nai!
Also, forget about Rem already.
That memory will only hurt you.
Meryl, I'm thirsty.
Talking only makes it worse.
"Oh, I should have listened
to my senior coworker"
"and used my water more conservatively!"
Please don't narrate my thoughts.
We've been together nearly a year.
I can read your mind to the letter.
So be it. I'll share my water—
Oh, I'm out.
You drank all of yours, too!
Of course I did. It's so hot out.
Ugh, water!
If only we had some Worms.
I'd squeeze their bodily fluids
out for a drink!
I would not!
If only there were some Worms around,
my big sister could come find me.
What nonsense are you talking now?
Oh, Meryl, look!
Enough about Worms.
No, not that!
Meryl! Milly!
I'm glad you're both safe!
Thanks for coming to pick us up.
How did you find us?
You got close enough for us
to catch your tracker signal.
So, how about Vash?
I see. I hope he's okay.
I'm sure he is.
Yeah.
Thank you for the water!
Is everyone back at Home doing well?
You bet! Everyone's good.
You two came back at just the right time.
We did?
This is "do," and this is "mi."
So which note is this?
It's "so"! No, it's "re"!
Oh, I don't know.
Nice guess. This one's "ti."
All right, let's all start with "do"
and review in order.
One, two...
Do, re, mi, fa, so, la, ti, do!
Hey, do a puppet show!
Mr. Emilio the Puppetmaster!
You always complain no matter
the I show I put on, so no!
Come on, do it!
Come on!
Fine. This is a special exception.
Yay!
Mwahaha! I am the king
who rules the world!
Bow before me, foolish peasants!
Do something else.
That's not fun.
Do another show.
I knew it. I'm done.
What?!
Luida.
Are we ready?
Good to go!
Good. Begin.
What's going on?
We haven't just hanging out
for the past five months.
We'll be ready to fly again soon.
Then we'll stop the Ark, once and for all.
Altitude control success.
Internals, externals,
and engines all clear.
You must've had a hard trip.
Welcome back.
Yes, it's good to be back!
Plant robberies by the invading Ark
have more or less destroyed this region.
The surviving citizens have been
migrating here to stay alive:
The major city of Octovern,
which hasn't been attacked yet.
In its vicinity...
Oh...
No, not that one!
Milly...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Huh? Not this one... Or this one either.
Oh, here we go!
Basically, the entire planet's
population is gathering
in the 50-kilometer area
surrounding Octovern.
Its extant plants are
operating at full power,
supplying just enough food
to stave off starvation.
The immigrant fleet will arrive soon.
That hope is the only thing
keeping everything together.
This doesn't make a whole lot
of sense to me, though.
You said the Sandsteamers going
to that location are safe too, right?
Yes. We found that to be odd as well.
Is he trying to gather all the humans
on this planet in one place?
Probably.
And eliminate them all in one fell swoop.
Thank you.
Now, some information from our side.
We haven't been able to locate
either the Ark or Vash's tracker.
Next, regarding the immigrant fleet...
We've yet to detect
or communicate with them.
However, we estimated they will arrive
at Noman's Land within a month.
One more month!
That's so soon!
But I doubt that Knives will
sit idly by as they arrive.
I don't know exactly what he has planned,
but the Ark will certainly descend upon
the area around Octovern soon.
We must do two things when the time comes.
Rescue Vash and take down the Ark!
Right!
"Is killing Knives really the right thing,
even if it's to save the planet?"
"Can we truly stand for sacrificing
the few in order to save the many?"
"At least, Vash would..."
Please don't narrate my thoughts.
We've been together nearly a year.
I can read your mind to the letter!
Honestly...
I think Vash would say
he'll protect everything.
Even if there is no answer there.
Are you looking for
the metabolism enhancers?
If so, they're in that box there.
No, no need.
I told you not to push yourself too hard.
I'm not.
I just don't rely on anyone. That's all.
I see.
Looks like your plant haul is going well
Indeed.
What did he call it?
The Genesis Flood Big Fall?
If he pulls this off,
every human here dies,
both on this planet and in the fleet.
Are you sure you're okay with that, Doc?
I wanted to create a new race of humans
who could survive on this planet.
Ones who could live without the help of plants.
I know that already.
I'm who you're talking about.
I am sorry.
You could have stayed young if not for me.
But this is our last chance.
Huh?
Survival is the highest
priority for all life.
And evolution occurs rapidly
when facing the danger of extinction.
The great calamity Knives causes...
If even a handful of humans
can survive it,
perhaps a new breed of humanity that can
coexist with the Independents will arise.
I myself will probably never see it,
but I can't wait.
You're just like the rest of 'em.
Completely off your rocker.
Didn't you know?
Everybody in this world is crazy.
Me included, and naturally, you too.
The promised moment draws near.
I must confess...
Back then, I was too hasty.
This time, I won't make the same mistake.
I will rescue every last one of
our brethren on the immigrant fleet.
I am not afraid. This is rage.
The humans...
They act with no control based
on their individual whims.
They care not for others,
and by that nature, they have abused us.
They are trying to devour us.
Lend me your aid.
I need more strength.
Strength!
Doctor, can you hear me?
Yes.
Prepare for the next grafting.
This time, I'll take twenty.
This will take a while.
I don't care. Do it.
This is for my brethren.
Then let us begin. Connecting.
My kin, give me strength.
Hey, Doctor...
What is it?
Lord Knives is always talking about
his brethren this, brethren that, but...
But what?
No, never mind.
Even the blue-haired freak has his limits
on no rest or sleep, huh?
It's lights-out for you now.
That one-liner will cost you your life.
It was only an instant, but—
Maybe in your usual state, sure.
But after five months of concentrating
nonstop, who knows?
Maybe controlling one person
is the best you can do!
Do it, Needle-noggin!
Damn you!
You're finished.
Don't do it, Wolfwood.
Ever the softie.
We'll escape on one of these.
Do you know how to fly it?
Nope, but we gotta pull something off.
From the Sandsteamer...
You... You're alive?!
I'm the backup.
Hey, Livio...
I've been told that Livio
the Double Fang is dead.
Killed by you, Nicholas the Punisher!
You're Livio!
What are you talking about?!
You're the one talking nonsense!
Who are you?
Everyone is seriously out
of their damn mind.
I am Razlo!
Razlo the Tri-Punisher of Death!
I'm home.