Hey there. Is Eraser around?
I have a report on my
recent patrols for him.
He's not here today.
He's been working with
the cops a lot lately.
Besides, I thought that kinda
stuff was Midnight's thing?
Maybe you should ask her to come over...
Nah, I'd feel bad interrupting
someone when they're working.
But you don't mind coming here and
interrupting us when we're working?
Also, Pop is the one who gets
along with Midnight, so...
Come to think of it, where is she?
She's been getting ready for the
Captain's farewell event around the clock.
Oh, the Captain Celebrity thing.
It's gonna be at the Sky Egg,
right? Sounds like a big deal.
You gonna be helping out with it?
They said I'd just get in the way
and asked me to not get involved.
Oh, I get it.
Yeah, don't really see
you being much help.
[Catastrophe]
Great upheaval in society or the natural world.
Major change.
Can also refer to a tragic outcome in stories.
Often accompanied by destruction.
Zero Hour
Regarding the record of the vigilantes'
activities you gave me the other day.
I'll get right to the point:
it's come in incredibly handy,
and provided us with a vital lead.
By taking the small-time
criminals noted in it,
along with the personal information
of the instant villain victims,
and indexing it with the customer
list from Hong Kong...
We've got a list of individuals who would
fall into "friend of a friend" territory,
for both the villain attacks
and the drug operations.
But half of them are involved with a
mid-sized pharmaceutical company,
Onomura Pharma Corp, as either
employees or contractors.
Onomura... doesn't ring a bell.
What's their deal?
For the most part, they produce and
sell drugs wholesale to hospitals,
which is why they're not particularly
well known to the public.
They may be the Factory's
base of operations...
And if not that, one of
their other hideouts.
Either way, we're getting closer
to the root of the operation.
I can't say I'm thrilled as a police
officer to have to rely so heavily
on anonymous tips, but...
Oh, when it comes to that—
Fuhgeddaboutit!
What's it matter where the tip comes from?
If it gets results, then that's
that! Who cares about the source?
That's the whole rational thing!
Ain't that right, big guy?
Here we have our reinforcements
from Osaka...
The BMI Hero, Fatgum.
Nice to meetcha.
I'm with Osaka PD! The name's
Kaniyashiki! You can call me Kaniko.
Hello there.
Officer Kaniyashiki has been
working on the investigation
to nail down the drug trafficking routes.
Fatgum is...
Here as a precaution, in the event of
more altered villain combat, I take it?
You got it!
This luscious bod o' mine's basically
invulnerable to impacts!
If it turns into a slobberknocker,
I can handle it!
Up 'til now, I handled the investigating
and Fatyan was the muscle—
But if a villain pops outta nowhere,
there's no telling if I can
hit the scene in time.
Got in a real mess the other
day because of that!
And it ain't like I can
back her up all the time.
A frame like mine isn't a good match for
sneaking around or wearing disguises!
That's where you come in, big guy!
Investigation
Eraser, we'd like you to
accompany Officer Kaniyashiki
Combat & Investigation
as an investigator with combat potential.
Combat
I'll be backing you two up,
but it'd be a relief
knowing we've got someone
who can handle a scrap
on the scene already.
And I'm thrilled to be working
with such a handsome fella!
Does that mean you're always
thrilled to be working with me?
What're you talking about, porky?
Come on, big guy, say something!
This don't look good, Fatyan!
He's not playing along at all.
Am I gonna be able to work with him?
Maybe you oughta act like an
even bigger goof than usual?
What're you yappin' about?
My best schtick, the Heike Crab face, only
works when I'm playin' the straight man!
It ain't funny enough to work
as a punchline, anyway.
Yes it freakin' is!
Why, you little...
You wanna get snipped?! I can snip ya!
Snip ya real good!
And you want me to get in on that?
No, not exactly.
Naruhata x Hong Kong
Onomura Pharma
\h\h\h\h\h\hKaniyashiki
\h\h\h\h\h\hEraser
\h\h\h\h\h\hFatgum
In summary, we're going to be
working with other departments
to investigate Onomura Pharma.
The three of you will be
responsible for direct contact
with a number of their employees.
It's a dangerous role, considering the
chances of encountering a villain, but...
Well, if one does actually show up...
That keeps things nice and simple, right?
Right?
Alright, let's start digging!
Look lively, folks!
The suit looks nice on you.
Why am I stuck wearing this...?
Hey, think of it as practice.
If you get into hot water in the future,
you'll hafta apologize in one of those!
That is not going to happen—
Let's get a move on! Excuse me!
Seriously, why all the dressing up?
Come on, it's fine!
But why, though...?
It's fine, trust me!
Store Open
But...
It's fine! Fine, fine, fine!
And bingo.
Entry pass
Huh?
That hair...
It really is Kaniko!
I didn't know she was in Tokyo.
Is it for Kanidoke business?
And the person she's with...
Eraser? Does he know her?
Man, it's a small world.
A few of the girls don't have
the choreography down yet,
but the dance club captain is providing
them with individual coaching...
You're ordering new costumes?!
Then we'll have to get everyone's
measurements at the next practice!
Oh, the sooner the better? Understood!
I'll call the others and get back to you.
I'm back.
Hey, you wouldn't believe
who I saw in town...
Sorry, but I need to make
some urgent calls for Makoto!
Okay.
Yu? It's Pop! I was hoping to get your
measurements for our new costumes...
Okay! Same for Miu, right?
Right, see you at practice!
Dude, what are you doing here?
It's not like you need anything.
Well, Pop seemed really busy, and
I didn't wanna get in her way...
Again, how does that justify
getting in our way?
Man, Eraser finally stopped
dropping in all the time,
and now we've gotta deal with this guy.
Oh, actually, speaking of Eraser...
What do you mean he was
going around with a chick?!
I know her, too, by the way.
So, who is she?!
Well...
The official idol of the Kanidoke!
Hey. It's been a while.
Anything new to report?
I'll also take a coffee. Black.
Eraser!
You're dating a frickin' idol?!
For real?!
Damn you! I am so jealous!
What are you talking about?
Who cares?! Set up a mixer with us!
We wanna meet idols!
Welcome to the final Captain Celebrity
stage show at the Tokyo Sky Egg.
Attendees with tickets are asked to
please line up at the entrance gate.
We've got merch over here!
I'll take a hoodie!
I'll take a fan, and a towel, and...
Two copies of the program.
Here they come!
Here they come.
Wash!
The fastest!
The strongest!
The most illustrious!
Competing to see whose Quirk shines
brightest, Japan's greatest heroes!
And yet!
A strange, powerful visitor decided to
make his presence felt among their number!
One remarkable individual who flew
in all the way from America!
He swooped up the American hero
rankings with his flight Quirk,
ranking in the top 10 every
year since his debut!
And his name...
is Captain Celebrity!
In the year since arriving in Japan,
he's learned about manly
ruggedness and Japanese spirit!
That's right, this isn't the same
C.C. we first met a year ago!
Let's go, C.C.!
Go, go, C.C.!
C.C.!
He's an all-new man!
An evolution of invincibility!
After taking Japan as a second home,
this soaring superstar is about
to touch down once again!
This is Captain Celebrity!
Blue 1.
We're at the back entrance, and have
finished deploying to the loading dock.
Red 1. We're ready to move.
Commence operation.
And there's my entry pass.
Move out!
We'll be making a move on the
Onomura Pharma Kanto R&D Center.
Our target is this research wing,
on a corner of the property.
So, that's the Factory's HQ?
We'll be launching an investigation on
the suspicion of producing illegal drugs.
The goal is to secure evidence of
human experimentation and modifications
and any suspects who might be involved.
We're just gonna grab anyone
we can find, then, yeah?
Except...
There's a chance that the kidnapping
victims may attack us.
That's...
The same type of villain as the one
from the Christmas incident.
Is this one gonna blow, too?!
If a Quirk causes those explosions...
Then I can stop it!
Fatgum, now's your chance!
I'm on it!
So many bomber villains...
Not good! Can I stop them
all with Erasure at once?!
Okay! Now's our chance!
Damn, they scared me!
Just raiding the joint, huh?
I figured they'd show up sooner or later,
but this is way sooner than I expected.
Didn't have a chance to let
the research staff escape...
Though this makes sure they won't talk.
But, man, talk about bad timing.
This next plan was just gonna
be about tormenting C.C.,
but with my bomber stockpile gone, I'm
in an "everything must go" situation.
And on the day of an event
at the Sky Egg, no less.
Oh, this is gonna be an
absolute catastrophe.
I have something to show all
my guests here tonight.
See? This is my baby, who
was born just this year!
He has my eyes, doesn't he?
Takes after his mother
otherwise, though.
The best of both worlds!
Wait, that picture...
I know! Let's get a word
from my wife, too.
Now, this is gonna be a surprise,
so keep quiet, everyone!
Hi, honey!
Chris? Do you know how late it is?
Sorry. Forgot about the time difference.
Were you asleep?
The baby finally went to sleep.
I was hoping to do the same, for once...
What do you need?
Uh, I was talking to
everyone about you...
About me...? And who's everyone?
Wait. Chris! You didn't show the
picture to anyone, did you?!
The one where I look like a mess!
I mean, I guess it's fine if it's the
people you're working with over there.
Like, five or 10 people.
Five... right...
What, is it more than that?
Oh, you got carried away at a party or
something and showed it to everybody, didn't you?
You had some event in Tokyo, right?
Was it at the after-party?
Tell me the truth. I'll forgive you
if it was no more than fifty people.
Well, it's uh... f-fifty...
What was that? I didn't hear you.
It's just... the event
is still ongoing...
And I've got... a crowd
of fifty thousand.
Uh... honey? Honey!
Let's just move onto the
next segment. Please.
Roger.
Let's see some wrestling!
Yeah!
Wash!
It's almost time for the next segment.
Can you check on my boss, Koichi?
Sure!
I wonder where the Captain went?
Maybe to the lower observation deck?
Hey, the Sky Egg's gift shop!
I oughta come back here.
Oh, there he is! Hey, Captain!
It's almost time.
Right. I know, I know, honey.
This was all my fault. And I
didn't mean to break my promise.
It's just... I was feeling
a little proud.
No, you're right, it
wasn't just a little.
You're completely right. I'm sorry.
We really are high up.
Huh... I wonder what that is?
A fire?
And...
I think something's headed this way?
Aren't those—
The same villains from Christmas?!
What is this? Why are we shaking?
An earthquake?
Boy!
You all right there, my boy?!
J-Just barely!
But there's more incoming!
No problem! I'm faster and
stronger than these things!
Even your suicide attacks won't cut it!
I don't care how many of you there
are, I don't see myself losing!
But would you look at that?
It's headed this way!
And this one...
seems way bigger!
Another explosion!
And a huge one, this time!
Oh, no...
The tower's in rough shape.
And the dome—!
Captain, are you okay?!
I'm telling you, my boy,
this is a piece of cake!
But I definitely have my hands full.
So, as I was saying, when
the hostages are in danger,
all that speed and power
gets taken off the table...
Let's see what kind of
fight you put up, now?
Come and get me, you lousy villains!
I can endure another one
or two explosions, easy!
Oh, that's exactly the plan.
After all, this experiment
is all about you...
So, let's start with three hits.
Don't forget the regeneration Quirk my
cluster bomber's been infused with!
How many dynamite punches will it
take for you to fall, I wonder?!
Captain—!
I've always been popular. When I
became a hero, no one was surprised.
But I wasn't a real hero.
Not in the truest sense.
Next time: Balloon Soul.
I was empty on the inside...
until I met you.