Ramaga!
You told me you wouldn't invade so soon!
Did I?
If you wish to save your
friends, do as I say.
Ryo...
What should I do?
I have your son.
Gai will choose to become a
Samurai Trooper in order to defeat me.
Guide him well.
Kaito Uesugi, Yamato Hojo,
Musashi Hojo, and Shion Ishida...
I've assembled the team you asked for.
Nasti!
The demons took Mirei!
Try anything funny and I'll put you
back in the storeroom.
I know.
Ramaga, can you hear me?
What is it?
I hear you've captured Mirei.
She has nothing to do with this.
Release her.
Even though she looks like this now?
Is that... Mirei?
EPISODE XI
RETURN
Wow.
So this is the might of
the Armor of the Supreme Emperor.
Sorry,
but we have to keep going!
Mirei...
Rest in peace.
Zealous Flash!
Mirei!
It's just like with Ryusei.
I ache like crazy right here.
So do we.
I commend you, Gai.
Truly, you are worthy
of becoming my Puppet.
Cut the crap!
Ascend those stairs.
I await you in my keep.
You okay?
Yeah.
That took a lot out of us.
We've got to go anyway.
What a bunch of dum-dums. No way
they're winning in the shape they're in.
I bet they think it's worth
risking their lives trying.
What's this? Sticking up for the enemy?
If the prince and his pals pulled off the
supreme arts, the woman would go free.
Wasn't that the deal?
The situation changed.
But as a result, the Armor of the
Supreme Emperor is now complete.
So what?! That makes everything okay?!
Yeah! Yeah!
We have a duty to obey
Emperor Ramaga's commands.
Could you say the same thing
to our fallen comrades?
Tell me, is our fight
worth risking our lives for?
Children,
it's time you prepared for the show.
I see.
They even got Mirei.
I bear responsibility.
We will review your conduct once
the Demon Outbreak has been dealt with...
assuming that day ever comes.
The Samurai Troopers are our only hope.
I was dubious about entrusting
Japan's future to children at first,
but not anymore.
I'm proud of those boys.
We're the ones who're gonna save
the citizens of Tokyo, Japan,
and the world! Like wham!
You guys got that?
Don't look at me.
I guess that's fair. You wouldn't know
about doing the right thing.
Hurry up and become
a superhero like me before—
Cockroach!
What?
It's just a Gubbarjo.
You and your demonese!
That's obviously a cockroach!
Wait, "Gubbarjo"?
Where have I heard that before?
Man, you look like a Gubbarjo!
Hold up! You mean you were
calling me a cockroach?!
I mean, it fits, right?
Yeah.
It does not! Don't you encourage—
You don't have to force it.
Huh?
We all know losing Mirei's
hardest on you out of all of us.
I'm not forcing anything.
Problem?
Nah. Like Yamato said, I still don't get
what doing the right thing really means.
Me neither.
The more I fight, the less I understand.
For now, let's beat Ramaga.
That's what's right for us.
Yeah.
In the fifteen years since your birth,
how I have longed for this day...
Skip the stupid intro.
Don't be so hasty.
At least allow me to summon my guests.
Commander!
I'm sorry, everyone.
I know I should be ashamed to face you
and that I have no right to speak to you.
But please, defeat Ramaga!
I don't need you to tell me that.
Now get up already.
I can handle the likes of you seated.
Okay, adding fuel to the fire!
Oath of Righteousness, emissary of Fire!
RIGHTEOUSNESS
Armor of Heat!
Try some of this!
What?!
Boys...
That didn't always have
a bell on it, did it?
No.
Ryo gave it to me.
So this is the government's
demon-fighting HQ, huh?
Isn't it silly, me being in charge of it?
No, you're the perfect choice.
Here.
To celebrate your new job.
It has the same properties
as that monk's staff
that saved us from so many scrapes.
Keep it as a charm.
Thank you.
Ring that bell,
and I'll come running anytime.
So I've continued to ring this bell,
hoping the staff's power
would bring back Ryo's soul.
Then that's why you kept working
and communicating with Ramaga?
If Ryo awakens, we can separate
his body from Ramaga and guard
the Armor of the Supreme Emperor.
That was my hope.
I wondered about that
irritating ringing sound.
I never imagined you were trying
to revive Ryo Sanada's soul.
But he is no more.
Hey! Eyes on me!
Follow Blade!
Gale Force Break!
Crusher Bullet!
Explosive Thunder Attack!
Blaze Slash!
Don't you think it's time you invoke
the Armor of the Supreme Emperor?
We'd have busted that out
already if we could.
If only we had more strength left...
You seem to be laboring under
a misapprehension.
The Armor of the Supreme Emperor
does not require strength.
It draws on the resonance
and empathy between you five.
Very well.
I will pull the trigger for you!
But how?! They weren't wounded
by Demon Soldiers!
That's impossible.
You need to stick the Demon Element
in someone to make them your Puppet.
Just so.
But what if humans already
had the Demon Element within them?
Thirty-five years ago, before the late
Demon Emperor Arago was slain,
he imprinted negative emotions,
the Demon Element, onto this land.
Over the years, it has seeped
into all of Tokyo.
Now, merely setting foot in the city
introduces the Demon Element to the body!
So you can turn them into Puppets
without touching them?
Indeed. I will now transform
every last human into my Puppets.
You shall resonate with hatred for me
and become as one!
Like hell we will!
Watch helplessly from there
as the humans you failed
to protect meet their end!
Tokyo!
Succumb to the demonic!
Kakeru!
Sora!
Sora! Kakeru!
Kako! Shunpei! Everyone!
Help!
No...!
Mom, I don't want to die!
Someone! At least spare my child!
So this is the end.
Everyone...
It's just not fair.
The protection of the Divine World?
How ironic. You have the lives
of the masses in your care,
yet you alone are spared.
How could this happen...?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What the hell?
It's just a bunch of people I've never
even talked to turning into Puppets.
So why does it hurt?
RIGHTEOUSNESS
Why does it hurt so bad?!
This is all your fault,
Ramaga!
WISDOM
You've crossed every line there is.
Now you need to pay!
Supreme Art: Void of the Five Skandhas!
Supreme Art: Vigor and Vitality!
Supreme Art: Unparalleled!
Supreme Art: Light Beam Flash!
Supreme Art: Mind Clear!
Good! Show me what the Armor of
the Supreme Emperor is capable of!
Like scorching heat,
I'll incinerate your mortal shell!
Yes! More anger!
More passion! More shouting!
Those boys are giving their all.
We should think about
why we're still alive, too.
Ryo, save them!
They need your strength!
Ryo, please wake up!
Incredible.
But...
That bastard Ramaga is smiling!
This is it!
This is the power I've been seeking!
Come on, Ryo. Why won't you answer me?
You told me you'd come running, remember?
So what was the point...
the point of...
Please, wake up!
I'm begging you.
Please, save us all.
Blaze Slash!
I have you now!
Wha...
The armor went to Ramaga?
No!
At last.
At long last, the armor is mine!
Game set, huh?
Now, Gai,
shall I claim your body next?
Once I have that,
I will achieve per...fec...tion...
Wh-Why? How?
How are you...?
Stay back!
Kill... me!
Ryo!
Hurry!
Kill me...
while you can!
Hey, then what happens to Mr. Sanada?
He may well die.
But now's our only chance!
What should we do?
Enough yapping!
Shut up and watch!
Burn!
They did it, Nasti!
There's Ryo.
Yes... Thank goodness.
Was that the Sword of Domination's power?
I get it. The sword can neutralize
Ramaga's demonic power!
That's what we tried to do for Ryu.
Nasti, this only worked because
you rang that bell for me.
Welcome back, Ryo!
I owe you my thanks as well.
So you're the Samurai Trooper
of Fire, huh?
That's ancient history.
You're the emissary of Fire now.
What impudence.
You have earned my wrath!
Okay, Dad, time for the big finale.
Like scorching heat...
Like a raging wildfire...
I'll incinerate your mortal shell!
Translation\h\h\h\h\h\hWilliam Varteresian
Timing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Editing\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hRiley Dalton
Quality Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSMR
Translation Check\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hMichelle Tymon
EPISODE XII
EPILOGUE
Armor races through my heart.