'Tis time for torture, Princess.
Today's torture is...
Japanese rice pilaf.
Japanese rice pilaf?!
Curses!
What kind of rice pilaf is it?!
That's what you're worried about?
Is it a classic
five-ingredient Japanese pilaf?
Or a salmon and mushroom pilaf?
Or maybe it's a baby sardine
and seaweed pilaf!
Why do you know so much
about rice pilafs?
Without further ado...
Let us begin the torture, Princess.
I forgot to turn on the rice cooker!
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
I can't believe I made
such a basic mistake...
I'm so sorry, Princess.
Don't beat yourself up so much, Torture!
Everyone makes mistakes.
If you forgot to cook it,
you can just do it now!
Feel free to use one
of my cell's sockets!
Will that be all right?
If I start it now, it'll take
about fifty minutes to cook.
Of course it's fine.
We can spend our time waiting
having a nice one-on-one chat.
Princess...
Is this what you'd call a torturous wait?
Torturous wait?
Oh, is that right?
Uh-huh.
Just the other day, the three of us
were playing a fighting game...
Keep practicing those combos!
Get consistent with your short hops!
At first, it was You-chan
and I teaching In-chan...
But before we knew it,
In-chan was better than both of us.
You must have done
a good job teaching her.
What? You think?
Well, I'm sure that played a role.
I am a legion commander, after all!
Part of my job as commander
was teaching new recruits.
I didn't get many other chances
to interact with people,
so I had a lot of fun training them.
I'd also befriend the few
girls I met who were my age.
We even used to have
tea parties together.
That sounds lovely.
Speaking of which...
A new recruit has joined us recently.
Oh?
It won't be for some time,
but she'll be torturing you, too.
Yeah? I'll look forward to it.
It's funny how this
sounds normal to me now.
You know...
We've never really had
a nice, long talk like this before.
I suppose we haven't.
'Tis a common occurrence
when you meet for work all the time.
Guess so.
We got to spend this time
because you forgot to cook the rice.
Maybe it was for the best, in a way.
I had fun talking
about all this stuff with you.
I did, too.
Looks like it's done.
Indeed.
Okay...
Time to get to surrendering.
I'm glad I got to talk to Torture
for so long today.
And I managed to remember
a lot about the past.
Oh yeah, I forgot I used to keep
a diary before I came here.
I'm pretty sure I wrote in it the day
before I was captured...
Is something wrong?
No...
Huh? Did I remember to put my diary away?
I put it back in the drawer
and locked it up, didn't I?
Did I? I did, didn't I?
Your Highness?
I can remember writing in it
but not putting it away.
Did I leave it out on my desk?
That'd mean anyone could read it
if they entered my room!
I can't let that happen!
I need to do something about this!
'Tis time for torture, Princess.
I yield!
What?
Torture hasn't brought anything out yet!
The castle's west tower, fourth floor.
The room at the very end.
That's the weak point.
Burn it down!
Your Highness?!
At least wait and see what it is
before you surrender!
Follow the proper surrender etiquette!
No, what the hell
is "surrender etiquette"?!
Is there a reason you're
so desperate to give in?
You see...
So that was it.
You forgot to put your diary away?
Yeah.
I'd do anything to stop my diary
from being read!
The humiliation!
Did you really forget to put it away?
I'm not sure.
Honestly, the possibility is low.
But now, I can't get
the idea out of my head!
Burn it all down...
Please don't wish
for your homeland to burn down.
I'm afraid burning
the castle down is not an option.
However, I can see if you'd be
allowed to temporarily return.
There's a chance they'd say yes to that?
Why can't I remember if I put it away?
I can remember picking up
the book I use as my diary...
By diary, do you perhaps mean...
a book with the Royal
Empire's emblem on it?
Huh? How do you know that?
Among your possessions...
Oh! That's right!
I put it in my bag since we
were setting out on a long expedition!
And then I was captured, which means...
That's right.
It's in the Hellhorde's custody now.
Huh? Wait, then...
I'm so glad I didn't leave it on my desk!
If anyone had read it,
I'd pass out foaming at the mouth!
I see now.
So that book was your diary.
Eh?
I thought it was a poetry collection
since it was so romantic.
Ah.
So you really did read it?
You have the wrong idea, Princess!
In case it held any imperial information,
I had to go through all of your belongings
with our intelligence unit!
May I ask how much of her diary you read?
Please accept my apologies.
We read through it in its entirety.
Your Highness?
Your Highness!
Princess!
The torture was called off,
so here is the unused...
Ankake sauce over fried rice.
Is it to your liking?
It's so gooey.
I wish the princess
could have tried some.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Sunday
Inki's Place
Gourmandization
Classroom
What are you up to over there?
I'm on torture duty tomorrow.
My torture is showing her a movie,
and stopping just when it gets good.
I'm picking out the movie.
Oh?
I'm trying to pick one based on
what Princess-chan likes,
but it's proving to be tough.
She's enjoying herself.
Why not just go with your favorite movie?
I'm scared to pick my favorite!
Scared?
I really, really love
my favorite movie...
If Princess-chan doesn't like it...
This movie's not very good.
Just show her another
one if that happens.
It's not as simple as that!
Wh-When someone rejects
your favorite thing...
It's like having your
heart's spine snapped in half!
Does your heart have a spine?
B-Besides, my favorite movies aren't
the movies I recommend.
I-I like my all-time favorite,
but its reputation's not great.
Ranking
Reviews
I-It'd objectively score around a sixty
if you deducted points for its flaws.
B-But when awarding points based on
my personal opinion, it gets a million!
You don't see In-chan being this honest
with herself too often.
Anyway, I'm scared.
I can't.
I'm just too scared to do it.
Still, isn't it fun when other
people like the things you do?
I don't know much about them,
but isn't Princess-chan a movie buff?
P-Princess...
Time for your torture...
What's wrong, In-chan?
Are you feeling sick?
I...
I?
I brought a movie for us to watch!
This movie's not very good.
Um...
That movie was great, In-chan!
The plot wasn't exactly easy to follow,
but its overall ambience was impeccable!
I know, right?!
Wait, the scene with the milk
being poured at the beginning...
Yeah, yeah! You got it!
It was symbolizing Aurelia's fate!
It was?!
Let's rewatch it! One more time!
Yeah, sure!
Inki had a lot of fun
Really?
I'm glad Princess-chan
ended up liking it.
Yeah.
I couldn't have done it
without you encouraging me.
Inki, what was today's secret?
Ah.
It was so much fun, you forgot to ask?
Yeah! So awesome!
Your Highness, what is it you've
been binge-watching lately?
A foreign drama series!
I borrowed it from In-chan!
It's very exciting
and full of cliffhangers.
Okay, next up is the sixth
and final volume!
Huh?
Life
\h\h\h\h\h\hSeeker
Volume six is missing.
Did In-chan forget to include it?
Princess-chan.
Looks like you watched
the foreign drama I recommended.
Yeah!
I'm dying to watch the rest.
Princess, time for your torture.
C-Come again?!
Last time, the torture
completely slipped my mind.
You had to go back and ask, didn't you?
I won't be making
the same mistake this time.
If you want to watch the rest,
you'll have to tell me a secret.
I get it now!
Both that movie and this foreign drama
were part of your torture!
Our friendship all this time...
was that a lie as well?!
Nope, our friendship's the real deal.
Your Highness?!
We may be friends, but this is my job.
Damn you and your professionalism!
But don't think you've won!
I'm dying to know what happens next,
but I'm the Princess and Commander
of the Imperial Third Legion!
My real-life exploits are far more
exciting than any foreign drama!
I will never yield to the likes of you!
Besides, I can watch
the rest whenever I get out of here.
Now I have more to look forward to!
I see...
Princess-chan.
Who's your favorite
character in this show?
Huh?
I guess it'd be Carrie.
Carrie?
She's the main character's daughter.
He's spent many years
fighting as a mercenary,
but his dream is to return home to his
wife and daughter one day.
Carrie's so cute, isn't she?
You said it.
We only see her in flashbacks,
but man, she's adorable!
Will we ever get to see what
Carrie looks like now, all grown up?
I hope she gets to live happily
with the main character.
Oh yeah, talking about
Carrie reminds me...
Do you remember the assassin
in a gas mask from volume five?
Huh? Sure...
Don't spoil me!
What?
Hearing you talk about Carrie
reminded me of the assassin.
Not bad, In-chan.
Your Highness! Calm yourself!
Damn you!
That's playing dirty!
But I won't...
The main character's favorite food.
The piano back home.
The left-handed artisan.
Stop it!
Stop rattling off what
sounds like key phrases!
It's working, In-chan!
The torture's doing a real number on her!
But it's true that the piano back home...
wasn't covered in any dust.
Ah!
I can't stop my brain from using
the phrases to connect the dots!
The Sherlock inside my mind! My Holmes!
Please calm down!
A master detective like Holmes is nowhere
to be found in that head of yours!
The seven dolls.
The aunt's birthday.
Stop! Please stop!
I want to enjoy it spoiler-free!
The clock in the plaza.
I'll talk...
Your Highness?!
The princess
confessed
I'm so happy that he got to live
with Carrie again!
The assassin didn't have
anything to do with her!
Looks like the two
of you have similar tastes.
Nothing beats a happy ending!
I see.
So this is the king's
favorite horror movie.
Knowing the enemy's tastes may
prove important to winning this war.
Then I shall have to watch it.
However, a bath will have to come first.
If I watch a horror film first,
I'll be too scared to take one.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
I get it now...
Sakura-chan, thanks for coming
with me to shop for torture devices.
No, it's the least I could do!
I spent all my time studying the blade,
which left me with no other strengths.
Shopping's about all
I can do to help out.
I wish there was some way
I could be more useful.
Well, best of luck with that.
I'll be heading back for now.
Sakura-chan.
I was planning to make pancakes today.
Could I ask you to assist me?
You'd be okay with that?
I would appreciate your help very much.
Hellholm
Communal
Kitchen
There's no need to mix so vigorously.
L-Like this?
Yes, you're doing great.
How's it look?
Right as rain.
The batter's starting to bubble!
It should be just about ready.
Time to flip it!
I did it on my first try!
Impressive work.
First the whisk, now this.
You're great with utensils.
When it comes to handling swords,
I was always best with a dagger.
Maybe tools this size
just come naturally to me.
I see.
So this is where your strengths lie.
My strengths...
The pancakes are all done.
They look great!
Yes, they look scrumptious.
Your very first torture implements.
Yes.
I hope they like these...
'Tis time for torture, Princess.
I'm the Princess and Commander
of the Imperial Third Legion.
No matter the torture,
I will never give in!
Looks yummy!
Delicious!
The princess
confessed
Sakura-chan.
The torture target said they
were delicious.
Series Total
Hell-Lord's Choice Awards
A group of elite mercenaries willing
to take any job for the right price.
Stanegger, the leader of Purple
Meteor Storm, hides a secret.
The fact that he has
a loving wife and daughter.
The enemy organization can
never learn of their existence.
He must protect
his wife and daughter
Why did Stanegger, the infamous
lone warrior, get married?
Why does he continue to fight
for Purple Meteor Storm?
Is it weakness to have
a family? To know of love?
What does it truly mean to be strong...?
Witness the gripping twists
and turns that will leave you breathless!
The Life Seeker Blu-ray
box set is available now!
Life
\h\h\h\h\h\hSeeker
Life Seeker
m 0 0 l 235 0 235 10 0 10
Available now!