Quick! Get back!
Stop him!
Hey!
Pass it!
Hayase-senpai.
Good job.
Nice one.
Get back on defense.
It's me.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I have a favor to ask you.
Festival of Offerings
Episode 4: A Replica Cries
Our last day?
Why's that?
I was created so Shuya
could have his revenge.
Revenge?
I'm supposed to lure out Hayase and
beat him up beyond all hope of recovery.
Hayase will claim Shuya did it,
but at the time of the attack, he'll be
elsewhere with plenty of witnesses.
So he'll have an airtight alibi.
What are you talking about?
It all goes down next Monday.
But why?
Because he wants revenge.
But why must you do it?
Why can't Sanada-kun beat him up instead?
What Hayase-senpai did
was absolutely horrible.
It was, but...
Shouldn't Sanada-kun
beat him up himself?
Why must you shoulder that burden?
You don't want to beat anyone up, do you?
Your hands are so gentle.
They weren't meant to hurt anyone.
I'm here because Shuya needs me.
No! You're...
You're here so we'd meet each other!
You're here so we could go to the zoo.
So we could go to the amusement park.
So we could go to an aquarium.
To a movie theater.
I never realized we'd have
such a packed schedule.
And next year, we'll go see
the fireworks together!
Actually, I don't care where we go.
As long as he's smiling next to me.
You're right.
I don't want to beat him up, either.
Right.
I'll call Shuya.
Shuya Sanada
You can listen in.
Hello?
Shuya, I'm sorry.
I can't go along with your revenge plan.
If we hurt Hayase-senpai,
it'd make us no different from him.
A replica is supposed to follow orders
from the original.
But Aki-kun is completely
rejecting that rule.
He crossed that line
without putting on airs.
So you're saying
I shouldn't have my revenge?
No, I'm saying there's
a better way to get revenge.
What way?
Like a real athlete would.
Like we could.
All right.
If that's how you want to do it,
then go ahead.
Shuya Sanada
He gave the okay.
Oh, thank goodness.
It's still going down next Monday.
I also want you to do something for me.
Me?
If you can, I want you to be there for me.
If I know you're there,
I don't think I'd lose to anyone.
I want to go to school
in your place next Monday.
For now, come inside.
We can talk about it.
Okay.
That explains everything.
Who knew Sanada had a replica, too?
Yeah. Sorry for not telling you sooner.
It's fine.
I actually sort of get it.
Huh?
As for Monday, go ahead.
We can switch places.
However...
I'll need one thing in return.
What is it?
Ask me for anything.
I'll even get a perfect score
on the next test.
I'll do whatever you want.
I want to watch, too.
I want to see Sanada get revenge
on Hayase-senpai.
Suru-Sei Boys' Basketball
Thanks for three awesome years!
Make it to the Inter-High next year!
Thanks a lot!
You all did great!
Today
@Hayase
Let's settle it 1 on 1
I'll announce the starters for
the prefectural prelims.
Shuya Sanada.
Here.
Suru-Sei Boys' Basketball
Thanks for three awesome years!
Make it to the Inter-High next year!
Thanks a lot!
You all did great!
Today
@Hayase
Let's settle it 1 on 1
You got it
Message sent
So Hayase-senpai
really did injure Sanada-kun?
I guess. But Sanada-kun told the teachers
he fell down some stairs.
Oh, he did?
There. We're all good to go.
Thanks.
Sorry for asking such a weird favor.
Don't sweat it.
I'm always happy to oblige.
They're here.
All right.
We're going live.
Hayase-senpai.
Thanks for taking time out to come here.
You sure you're fully healed?
I'm able to manage it day-to-day.
Glad to hear it.
You even joined
the literature club, they say.
So here's how it's gonna go.
If I win, you have to apologize.
For breaking my ankle.
What? He really did it?
No way.
And if I win?
If you want to break my other leg...
We'll play one-on-one
with no time limit.
The first to make a basket wins.
I'll start on defense.
Oh? You sure about that?
This way, it'll be a fair fight.
Ready when you are.
What the hell?
Did he just fake getting faked out?
It's my ball now.
Way to go, Sanada-kun.
This is getting wild.
Your ankle did heal up.
I'm glad you see it that way.
I'll have my payback, Senpai.
Go in.
Senpai, remember what you taught me?
Playing man-to-man
is all about your acting chops.
Who makes a shot like that?
Dang.
Looks like I win.
Do you know why I didn't squeal on you?
Huh?
I did it for the team.
The prelims were on the line.
I didn't stay quiet for you, Senpai.
Senpai?
That was...
It was just an accident.
But I'm sorry it happened.
Okay. Nice game.
You rock!
That was intense!
Did you get everything?
No problemo. I caught every second.
Sanada-senpai was amazing.
Yeah. He really was!
Anyway, I'm heading back to class now.
I haven't eaten lunch yet.
Sure. And thanks again.
Don't mention it.
I'm spent.
You were incredible.
Score.
Group Call
Shuya Sanada
Sunao Aikawa
Aki
Accept
Decline
Nice work.
Yeah.
You really beat him.
Thanks to me.
You did great.
Yeah.
Still, you know...
It doesn't even hurt for you.
So, yeah, I bet that helped.
Sorry. Bear with me.
Yowch!
Group Call
Shuya Sanada
Sunao Aikawa
Aki
Leave
Turn On Video
Mic
Speaker
Of course it hurts for him!
He played through the pain
for that entire one-on-one!
Hold on. Does that mean
you feel pain, too?
When your head hurts, mine hurts, too.
When your stomach hurts, so does mine.
But you've never once mentioned that.
I couldn't tell you.
I couldn't.
I just want to be useful to you, Sunao.
After all, I'm her replica.
Whenever I see Sunao lying in bed
worry-free, I feel relieved.
It's proof that she still needs me.
So Aki-kun must also—
I think we'll leave the call now.
You two originals can have a private line.
H-Hey, wait—
I wonder what Sunao and
Sanada-kun will talk about.
I'll bet Aikawa wants to ask Shuya
how he deals with a replica.
Huh?
Unlike you, Shuya has never
made me disappear.
He hasn't?
Right. I take over for Shuya
at school and at home.
I see.
If he did erase and resummon me,
I'd probably come back chubby.
Shuya's been cooped up
in his room after all.
Thanks, Nao.
I've never played basketball before.
But you didn't practice anyway.
You wanted to show you could win
purely by using Sanada-kun's skills.
Yep.
But I wasn't even sure that I'd win.
I was a nervous wreck.
But I made it through
because you cheered me on.
You heard me?
I did.
You said "go in" right at the end there.
It's true that you were awesome,
but you shouldn't do this anymore.
You need to take care of yourself.
Okay. You win.
I mean it. Never again.
I promise.
So this is me, Aikawa.
Uh, yeah.
Group call
Shuya Sanada
Sunao Aikawa
I think this is our first time
speaking to each other.
Mm-hmm.
I'm still surprised you have a replica.
Me, too. I was shocked by yours.
Even so, I've gotta hand it to him.
He's supposed to be me,
but it's like he has what I don't.
I can definitely relate.
Huh?
Nothing.
I'm happy for you. You got
your revenge on Hayase-senpai.
Well, yeah.
Group call
Shuya Sanada
Sunao Aikawa
You're right.
It's thanks to everything he's done.
Of course it hurts for him!
He played through the pain
for that entire one-on-one!
I know.
Ta-da!
Title: Dual x Duet
Ritsuko Hironaka
At long last, I finally
finished my first draft.
Whoa.
Nice job.
Thank you all very much.
Now I have to do a bunch of revisions.
I pray that Ricchan wins the novel prize.
You do it too, Aki-kun.
U-Uh, right.
Me, too!
I'll come with you to the station.
Uh, what about your bike?
It's fine.
I'll just have it camp
overnight at school.
Then, why not?
You got it.
You can lean on me if you want.
You can even rest on my lap.
I wonder what's going to happen next.
Shuya will probably erase me for good.
I think he'll recover eventually.
He'll get to the point
where he can go to school himself.
And when he does...
He won't need me anymore.
But he can't.
You know that story you mentioned?
I think it was The Mermaid's Return.
I bet that's pretty much
what's gonna happen to me.
A six-car local train to Hamamatsu
will arrive shortly on track 4.
I'd like to go to a movie.
How about now?
No. Let's go tomorrow.
Please board the train at spots
7 through 12 as indicated on the platform.
Sorry. I know I shouldn't make promises.
But still, whatever happens, I'll...
I'll still...
Nao!
Translation: Gad Onyeneho
Timing: Mariana Martinez
Editing: SMR
Quality Control: Riley Dalton
Translation Check: David Saylor