Good. It's finally back to normal.
You really do look better
with hair, Hajime.
That's rich coming from you.
I guess it's almost fall.
It's been ages since I've come
to the dungeon market!
Yeah? That so?
Well, they tend to coincide
with the busy season,
so it's hard to find the time.
What a cute pendant!
It's so nice. But maybe
a little too expensive.
Miss, I'll take this.
Certainly.
She'll be wearing it, so hold the box.
P-Please, I can't accept this!
How much do you do for us?
Plus, it looks good on you.
Hajime, you're a womanizer.
If you wanna pay me back,
how about letting me touch your boobs?
You're awful!
A man's never given me a present before!
But these chills...
I-It's not what you think, Rirui!
Hey, Hajime!
Rirui wants a present too!
Well, if you insist.
You love meat, right?
Well, don't hold back! Chow down!
Not like that! Stupid Hajime!
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
EPISODE 11: THE POWER OF CHARM
Well, that explains why
you're in such a bad mood.
Rirui wants Hajime to look
at her more like a woman.
Then you'll need to work
on your womanly side.
You mean, like, bathing thoroughly?
Not exactly, no.
You need to put in effort
to be beautiful, like me.
Do that, and men will
shower you with gems.
But Hajime never does that
for you, Bosslady.
Aren't you beautiful?
That's the thing about that idiot!
All when he's got a childhood
friend this gorgeous!
Who does he think he is?!
But I'd hate to rely on
my succubus powers...
I'm talking about the charm Mystic Eye.
This would be enough to make him
give me whatever I want.
Except it's temporary,
and it would feel like cheating.
If it'd make Hajime love Rirui,
I might use it.
Well, aren't you intense!
Bosslady, how do I use that charm power?
It tends to vary between individuals...
You'll just have to wait
until yours comes to you.
I see.
I'm sure you'll get it eventually.
Now cheer up! I'll do something
nice for you tomorrow.
Something nice?
There!
How cute!
Your makeup looks nice, Rirui.
Hey. What's everybody doing?
Hajime!
Huh? Rirui, your lips are
real glossy this morning.
You must've had meat for breakfast!
You're gonna get fat at this rate.
Ow!
You're awful!
Get out there and find your sensitivity,
wherever you dropped it!
What gives?!
Look, I'm sorry.
I thought your lips were greasy.
What does Rirui have to do
to make you like her like a woman?!
Uh, Rirui?!
Oh, is that what this is?
You're fine the way you are, Rirui.
I bet you'll be a lovely lady
when you grow up.
H-He likes her as she is?!
Not good enough.
He's trying to brush me off.
In that case...
If I get stronger, I bet I'll get it!
So I need to level up and start
controlling Hajime with my charm power!
Man, someone's fired up today.
I wonder if it's what I said.
I dunno if it's that she's motivated.
She's kinda scaring me.
You think?
Rirui!
Squishy?
I'm sorry!
Hey! This is dangerous! Stop!
I said stop, dang it!
This is bad!
Gotta bail!
Get up! You know where its heart is!
You saw one stripped
and cleaned, remember?!
Let's see...
Right here!
Nice one, Rirui.
Hajime!
Rirui's covered in blood.
You did it, Rirui!
Maybe Bosslady is right.
Even if I used my charm to control Hajime,
I bet I wouldn't feel like this.
RIRUI LEVELED UP.
SHE LEARNED THE CHARM SKILL.
Did you learn some kinda skill?
Couldn't hurt to try it once.
Wink!
Oh, didja get blood in your eye?
What is this?! It's awesome!
Wink!
A charm skill, huh?
Looks like a big level gap
renders it ineffective.
Pretty potent, though.
I finally got a succubus-y power,
but it only works on these guys!
I bet I can do it this time!
Big wink!
Got something else in your eye now?
Darn it! This isn't what I wanted!
THE POWER OF HER CHARM...
SEEMS INEFFECTIVE ON HUMANS.
AN ADVENTURER'S DAILY GRIND AT AGE 29
Good morning!
And a good morning to you too!
Anya?!
It's a mask of the deer god!
The festival's coming up,
so I went ahead and made it!
There's a festival?
One dedicated to the deer god, whose
domain is bountiful harvests, apparently.
Morning, Cocko.
Good morning.
What's a bountiful harvest?
It means there'll be lots of food.
There's a whole buncha stalls at the
festival with tons of tasty stuff to eat!
Really?!
Yeah!
Hey, why don't we run our own stall?
We can cook up the meat we
bring in from the dungeon!
Yeah! Sounds great!
Okay.
How about you, Cocko?
If you really need me that badly,
I guess I can help.
Okay, we'll run it together!
Yes, we will!
There you go. That's the ticket.
Knock it off!
You're taking forever to make anything!
What is your problem, Rotton?!
We're making ours carefully, unlike you!
Yeah, that's right! Don't get in the way!
That anteater of Rotton's
is pretty aggressive.
Stop that!
What do you guys want?
Maybe a licking from Kaiser here?
You should run!
It's really, really sticky!
Winky!
K-Kaiser?
Sic 'em!
S-Stop that! Hey!
Wh-What're you licking me for?!
Kaiser, stop it! Leave me alone!
It's so sticky!
U-Um...
Thank you for helping us.
The dark power dwelling
with Rirui ran wild!
What in the world are you talking about?
H-How cool!
I like the sound of a dark power!
Your name's Rirui, right?
Let's all make deer god masks together!
Yeah, let's!
Masks for the festival?
Yeah! We promised to get together
and play on the day of the festival!
Also, I'm going to run
a meat stall with Anya!
A meat stall?
We're going to cook the meat
we collect from the dungeon!
I'm really looking forward
to the festival!
Rirui's stall is doing big business...
A festival, huh?
I'm trying to remember what they
were like when I was a kid.
Staring out at the commotion
from the alleyways...
All I did was watch.
Here's hoping that all
of that fun stuff...
will be what Rirui actually
gets to experience.
There's magic beasts nearby.
Here they come!
Over there!
Be careful!
Damn it, why are all these
rabbit bears attacking?!
Oh no! One got into the village!
R-Resident adventurer...
What's up?
Uh, a bunch of them suddenly
started jumping the gate.
This's never happened before.
What's the cause?
Mountain wolves too?!
The moon is lovely tonight.
Chair.
Yes, ma'am!
You landed your marks
perfectly. Good boy.
Th-Thank you so much!
Chairs don't talk.
Now here's your reward, swine!
Thank you so much!
And some more!
You guys got plenty of energy,
considering the hour.
Well, the full moon is soon.
It stirs the blood of us ancient species.
Doesn't look that full yet.
Oh, come on...
Did I not explain this to you
when you adopted Rirui?!
If you're going to raise one
of my kind, you had better—
I get it, okay?
Leave things to me.
See ya around.
So, as the full moon approaches,
their blood starts to stir, huh?
The chains on her charm skill
were glowing just now...
Welcome to our stall...
Anya, you gotta put more
meat on the grill...
This is gonna be great!
We had better go grab a bunch of meat!
Rirui is going to hunt her heart out!
Rirui, Anyango.
I hear you're running
a stall for the festival?
We're gonna be grilling some meat!
I know I'll want some!
Yeah! We'll be waiting!
That can't be easy between two kids.
If you need help,
you give us a shout, okay?
Thank you so much!
This is gonna be great!
I can't wait to start cooking, Anya!
Rirui.
Did you have a dream last night?
One where you were fighting, maybe?
I don't think so.
And you weren't using your
power to control dreams?
I wasn't. I slept all night long!
Is something wrong?
Nah, never mind, then.
It went that way!
Is something the matter?
You look concerned.
Is something bothering you?
And then we can serve all different
cuts of meat!
Oh, I get you.
Well, you know how there have been magic
beasts showing up in town late at night?
Oh, about that!
Thank you for pitching in every night.
With the cause unknown,
everyone's really worried.
It's been a real headache.
Let's bring Cocko in
and have a strategy meeting!
Yeah, let's do it!
Of course it's nothing
but trouble for the village...
Um, Mr. Shinonome?
Nah, it's nothing.
Rirui. Rirui!
Rirui's arm is glowing!
Can you make it stop?
Doesn't look like it!
I see.
Why is Rirui's arm glowing?
Well...
It's a sealed power!
But your dark, forbidden power
is beginning to awaken!
Really?!
I can't believe it...
Rirui's dark dragon is on
the verge of awakening!
You really love dragons, huh?
Well, this leaves us no choice.
Rirui will use this power...
to be of use to everyone in the village!
Rirui, keep that power a secret.
Why's that?
Well, a secret power
sounds cool, doesn't it?
True!
All right, back to bed with you.
I've got some leftover work to do.
Bed for me!
NEXT TIME: A HOMETOWN AND FRIENDS