Dorm 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 2\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 3
Listen up, punks.
The chicken fight coming up
is the last event of the day.
We are seven points away from the lead.
We still have a chance.
Let's do this!
All right!
Ladies and gentlemen, the event
we've all been waiting for!
Today's highlight: the chicken fight!
I didn't know this wasn't just a race!
Dorm 1 is in blue bandannas,
Dorm 2 in white, and Dorm 3 in red.
Anyone who gets theirs taken
is out of the game.
Tennoji!
We won't let you win!
Begin!
Fierce skirmishes are
breaking out everywhere!
Nakatsu, to the right!
Got it!
First one!
It's eat or be eaten!
This is a truly fierce, manly showdown!
Where's Tennoji?
What's this?!
Dorm 2's attacker has
fallen from his horse!
Medical Tent
You got away with some
minor scrapes and bruises.
I know you were only
trying to help a friend,
but I can't believe two grown
boys got crushed like that.
Put a sock in it.
Th-Thanks.
And sorry.
It's fine, it's fine.
Don't sweat it.
Right, Izumi?
Sure.
More importantly, are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. Totally fine.
It's just a scratch.
But that guy from Dorm 1...
That was definitely on purpose.
If Sano and Nakatsu hadn't protected me...
So, well, Dorm 1 beat the
pants off of Dorm 2 today.
Nanba-senpai?
Conference Room
Dorm 1
Dorm 2
Dorm 3
We've got two days left.
Of course, the arts-focused Dorm 3
is planning a comeback of their own.
We can only compete with good ideas!
Our first-years have an arcade.
Our second-years, a themed café.
And us third-years, a mystery show.
No holding back.
Go all out.
I felt it...
Yeah, he's ready to kill.
Don't worry!
You all came up with good ideas,
so just keep up the good work
and rake in the student and public votes!
Damn that Nanba.
How about sparing a single thought for us?
Ow!
Are you okay?
Let me see it.
Oh, good.
It's not swollen.
Does it still hurt?
I'm sorry.
It was my fault.
It's nothing serious.
A-Anyway, during the chicken fight,
that guy did that on purpose, right?
You think they have it out for you?
Why me, though?
Nothing comes to mind?
No.
All right.
Well, can't hurt to be cautious,
so keep an eye out.
Yeah.
I mean, it's not even like
he really did anything to me.
I can't just assume he's behind it.
Okay, I'm gonna go shower.
He's hiding something from me again.
Since it's some fool from Dorm 1,
it's either that moron Tennoji
or one of his goons.
This leaves me no choice
but to be on the lookout.
Wait, why do I have to do that?
Guess that's just how it goes.
Got it. Got it.
MärChange
Ta-da!
What do you think?
I can't get outed!
Wh-What?
Is it that weird?
I know it's too late, but it's
really a shame about you two.
Don't say that so genuinely.
Yeah, seriously!
Just give us a normal compliment.
Yo, Ashiya! Looking good!
Noe? Sekime?
Hey!
Hey, Noe!
This thing is hella tight!
Talk about bulky!
All right, man.
I'll let it out under the arms,
so hold still.
Noe, you're, like, scary good
at making this stuff.
H-How cute!
Nakatsu, you dumbass!
You're gonna get your dress all dirty!
Huh? Where's Sano?
He's getting ready!
I'm coming in!
Where's my wig?!
I-I hope Sano doesn't look like that.
Don't move.
You'll screw up your eyeliner.
Okay, all done.
Wow, Sano!
All right, who's up next?
Me!
We've got no time, so we'll
skip right to the foundation.
Wow, how pretty! Beautiful!
Yo.
What costume is that?
Yang Guifei, apparently.
Can you stop staring like that?
Aw, what's the harm?
You look so good!
Dude...
Day two of the school festival
is now officially open!
Have a blast!
Buy your tickets here!
MärChange
Welcome!
Party of three over here!
I shall show you to your table.
This is an all-boys school, right?
Got it!
Coming right up!
Ready to order?
Looks good, huh?
Thanks!
The beauty pageant contestants have been
posted in the lobby of the western wing.
Tomorrow's twelve finalists
will be determined by today's vote.
23 Ashiya Mizuki
Make sure to cast yours!
I don't know, man. I feel like this
year's contestants are a cut above.
You can say that again.
Hey, they said there's a
really cute girl in 2-C.
No way! For real? We gotta go!
He's still a guy, dumbass.
Two iced teas, please!
And I need a coffee.
On it!
Hello! I'm with the executive committee.
I've come to do a survey of the
beauty pageant contestants.
You're Ashiya-kun, contestant 23,
and Nakao-kun, contestant 18, correct?
Yes!
Yeah...
The votes for you two are coming in hot!
So, let's hear your measurements!
What?!
Go on!
Well, from the top, I'm 74-60-78.
Oh, but don't tell anyone!
And you, Ashiya-kun?
Er, well... I'm, uh...
See you!
Th-That's none of your...
Uh, Ashiya-kun?
...business!
He sure is fast!
Guess that's that.
Shall we move on to the next class?
Isn't he supposed to be injured?
Looks like he's in top form.
Calm down.
We just need to make sure he's out of
the 2,000-meter race on the final day.
Yeah, and we've got plenty
of ways to do that.
Man, I never should've
entered the beauty pageant.
What are you talking about?
Crap! Those two again?
I'm not even trying to spy on them.
Why are they always...
D-Doctor?
Hello there, Ashiya.
Love the outfit.
What are you doing out here?
I was just taking a little break,
but then I found myself
rooted to the spot.
"A little break"?!
Is that what a teacher calls
drinking on the clock?!
I've got nothing better to do.
I'm just supposed to accept that?
You're the one who up and disappeared!
And now you come back
and hit me with that?
Cut the crap!
Minami...
Doctor?
So he's still not over it, I see.
That girl was Minami's tutor in his last
year of middle school. They dated.
Pretty sure it wasn't until they broke up
that he started acting
like somewhat of a player.
Nanba-senpai...
Do you have any idea what I've
been going through since you left?
I am so sorry.
I know there's no excuse for what I did...
But I really did love you.
I did.
Please believe me.
Believe you? What the hell
am I supposed to believe?!
Minami...
You're leaving me.
You... You're abandoning me!
Minami, let me go!
Go.
Go wherever it is you're going.
Who's there?!
Oh no!
The doctor's gone!
Minami.
You and I were just kids back then.
Goodbye.
Who's there?
What a pathetic sight to witness.
So... who was she?
Someone who threw me away three years ago.
The first woman I ever fell in love with.
That "if we can be together,
I don't need anything else" kind of love.
But one day, she disappeared
without a single word.
I thought I'd forgotten her
and everything about her.
When I saw her again, I was forced
to admit that wasn't true.
She told me she's getting married.
The guy she's marrying
is about twice my age.
I don't even know what to say.
Ashiya, can I just ask you for one thing?
Where the hell did he go?
Can I have a hug?
Just this once.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
Nanba-senpai...
Just kidding!
Senpai!
You just look so adorable,
I figured a womanizer like myself
couldn't let this one chance slip away!
Are you annoyed?
Not at all.
It's so like you, I'm impressed.
So, Ashiya, are you in love
with anyone right now?
Nice and honest.
Cherish it.
You'll never be in love like this again.
Once this love is over,
you might fall in love with someone else,
but the love will never be the same.
Love also matures.
Which is why it must be tended with care.
So that your feelings may bloom.
Speaking of, I really need to grow up.
Hey, Ashiya Mizuki!
How long are you going to play hooky?!
Nakao-kun?!
Well, I've got to get back.
Don't you ruin this for me!
Right.
I want to go have fun too!
Get back here this instant!
I ought to head back too.
That is all!
A-Apologies for that!
The announcement booth was hijacked.
Why...?
Why the hell am I hiding?
MärChange
Sorry I'm late!
You're beyond late.
It's Alice! She's so cute!
Sorry, sorry!
It was really bad because we didn't
have enough people to cover the tables!
Miss, over here!
Coming!
Sano? You changed?
What's up with him?
Alice...
Thanks for waiting!
Hey, is this girl here too?
I bought it from that guy
selling photos earlier.
Your class sure has a lot of hot girls.
Huh?
Hmm. She's okay, I guess.
You know that's Nanba-senpai, right?
When he was a first-year.
Hey, lemme see that!
Me too, me too!
The hell are you doin'?
I didn't get a look!
Wasn't expecting to run into this
embarrassing relic while doing my rounds.
Never thought my old library would
see the light of day this quickly!
That Nanba Minami...
Always acting so high and mighty
just 'cause he's a little good-looking.
He makes me sick.
Now he'll regret incurring my wrath!
What's the cause
for celebration over here?
Nihonbashi...
Wh-What? You got a problem?
I've got proper authorization!
This individual is authorized
to vend independently.
Nihonbashi Wataru
Osaka High Festival Executive Committee
Yeah?
Ever hear of the right of publicity?
I know!
Why don't you enter
the beauty pageant too?
Just two hours remain in day two!
Dorm 1\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 2\h\h\h\h\h\h\hDorm 3
This is our interim update.
Dorm 1 has 104 points.
Dorm 2 has 101 points.
Dorm 3 has 110 points.
Dorm 2 is dead last!
I guess it makes sense that the artsy dorm
would dominate the second day.
Apparently 3-B's haunted house
is a huge hit.
That tracks. Himejima,
the Dorm 2 RA, is their class rep.
Guess it's the real deal with make-up
tech he learned in Hollywood
and even projection mapping.
Damn Masao...
Our mystery show isn't bad
content-wise, but give me a break.
Hey, Sano.
Your Yang Guifei was really popular.
You're not doing it anymore?
Get lost.
Ooh, someone's in a mood.
I'm busy. I've got no time for you.
You're not cute at all.
Just look at how Ashiya does it.
Senpai, what are you doing?!
How dare you, Nanba?!
Hands off!
Just playing.
Sano!
I'll help you with the trash.
Leave me the hell alone!
It's right over there.
Did I make him angry somehow?
You're saying you don't
understand how boys think?
In fact, they're actually
quite delicate beings.
Of course there are things a tough
girl like you wouldn't understand.
Is that how it is?
It is indeed.
Speaking of, what happened with Minami?
Sounds like the kid's
finally moving on, eh?
He said that love matures,
so he's got to grow up too.
He also said I should
tend my love with care.
So that my feelings may bloom.
What a pompous little brat!
Well, on that note, how are things
going between you and Sano?
Are you using protection like you should?
It's not like that!
Sano doesn't even know I'm a woman!
Then what is it like?
Wh-What do you mean?
I mean, he said I was...
a very important friend.
Which is...
I guess that's fine for now.
But there will come a time
that's not enough.
I'm sure.
He's such an idiot.
It's always been that way!
What the hell are you yelling for?
Sano...
I'm sorry for shouting at you earlier.
I was in a bad mood,
and I took it out on you.
That's all. Nothing more.
Let's go.
We've still got to clean up
and get ready for tomorrow.
Sano...
Hurry up if you don't want
to get left behind.
Ashiya!
Are you okay?
Are you hurt?
No...
What happened?
Did a flowerpot fall?
Holy crap, that was close!
I'm scared to look up.
What if there's someone there?
Day two of our school festival
has officially come to a close.
I'm overthinking it.
We've checked Dorm 2
two days in a row now!
Is your injury better?
Even if getting hurt is part of the game,
that guy belonged to our dorm.
We'll call that round a draw.
I'm sorry about what happened.
I hear you'll be in the
2,000-meter race tomorrow.
We'll settle the score there for sure!
We won't lose this time.
Still a big-mouthed brat, I see.
Let's go, Kitahanada!
Right!
Tennoji might actually be a decent guy.
I heard a flowerpot fell.
Better be careful.
It couldn't be...
Sano, your Yang Guifei was so good!
Stop it. I don't want any
compliments for that.
How should I put it?
The sensuality was off the charts!
Get those stars out of your eyes!
I knew it. You have talent.
What talent? And what do you mean,
you knew it?!
Next Time
I Was the Same