Isn't this...
Yes, it's the hole Richeh opened again.
The Dragon's Labyrinth
How many times is that now?
I've lost count.
Anyway, let's find
somewhere covered to hide.
I think it's getting colder in here.
T-Tetia.
You... dropped this.
Thanks.
Um... are you okay?
Yeah, I guess not...
I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
And, um...
Y-You'll be cold without a cloak,
so wear mine instead!
I'll just snuggle up close!
Coco?
I feel really safe when I have it on.
When I'm wearing my cloak,
nobody can see that I'm shaking with fear.
Knowing that I still look like a witch
on the outside helps me be brave.
So I want you to wear it right now.
You'll be a lot more help than I've been.
What the?!
What are they doing?
It's warm.
A cloud?
I'm sorry I looked at you
like this was your fault!
It's fine. It is my fault, anyway.
And it's not like you actually said it...
If I acted like it, it's no better.
I took my fear out on you.
I've been doing this longer than you.
I'm supposed to protect you.
Tetia...
But you are protecting me!
Look how warm this spell is!
I feel super relaxed even
though we're in danger!
It's amazing! Magic is so powerful!
It's my very own creation.
When I was a little kid,
I dreamed about napping on a cloud.
So I've been trying out different things.
It's not finished yet, though.
Once it is, I'd like to
submit it for approval
as a general-use spell
for everyone to try.
It might not be the most
useful spell out there,
but it's my dream,
and that means a lot to me.
So you should wear your own cloak.
Let's not take off our novice cloaks
until we're back home safe
and we all become real witches together.
Okay?
Yeah!
I heard all that.
If you want to lie on top of this,
it needs to be made of
a substance with more mass.
Too cold outside.
Richeh's coming in.
If you want people
to be able to fly on it,
you'll need a cloud-like
material to substitute.
Like cotton.
But then it would just be
a normal mattress!
It's fine to talk about dreams,
but how about reality?
How are we going to get out of here?
This whole area seems
to be under a spell,
which is why we keep ending
up at the same place.
Any kind of magic—even the forbidden
kind—needs a Casting Seal to work.
We need to find out where it is and—
Excuse me.
I think I saw the Casting Seal... maybe?
You're right. It's up there.
Yeah. A Casting Seal.
Huh? Does that dragon
look bigger than before?
Or we're getting smaller
with the rest of the space.
Either way, if the dragon is protecting
the Casting Seal, we'll have to beat it.
I'm thinking fire magic—
Um...
I don't think your fire spell
did much to it before.
Pardon?
Um, I mean...
You slowed it down,
but I don't think you actually hurt it.
So... I don't think fire
is the way to beat it.
What do you propose, then?
We don't beat it.
Are you still mad about what
I said before or something?!
No, no!
You and Tetia just gave me an idea...
I have a plan.
I don't know if it'll work, but...
I'd like to try it.
You mean...
Yes!
The plan to make Tetia's dream come true!
What are you talking about?
Well, Tetia's cloud made
us feel warm and safe
in this bitter, cold place, right?
So what if we make a
cloud bed for the dragon,
so it would stay there
instead of attacking us?
I doubt it's going to go that—
True.
All are helpless before
the power of a warm bed!
Even dragons, probably!
Yeah, that's right!
But... that's...
Look, give me a minute
to work through this.
Humans certainly find warm
beds irresistible, but...
Coco? Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing!
I was just wondering
if the dragon was okay.
The dragon?
When we ran away before,
it slammed hard into
a pillar, nose-first.
At the time, I was too scared
to think twice about it,
but I'm thinking it was
probably really painful.
And that's why, well...
That's why I thought this
plan was worth trying!
Master said that the spells
that aren't forbidden
are the ones that bring happiness to all.
So I want to show the dragon
some kinder magic.
If this works, no one has to get hurt.
Not us, and not the dragon, either!
Good point!
And if Agott helps us,
it'll probably work even better!
You're acting like you have ideas.
Well... maybe I do.
Then let's do this together.
You're the best at drawing
seals out of all of us.
We'll have a much better chance
if you're on the team.
Well...
Fine.
Yay!
Hey, watch it!
Thanks, Agott!
Forget about me!
Let's talk strategy!
Okay!
You want to be able to lie on it, right?
Yes, I want it to be like
a nice, fluffy bed!
Something as fluffy as a cloud,
but with proper substance...
Something we can find here...
...and that could withstand
a dragon's weight.
Shredded paper!
We could tear up all four of our
Quires and it wouldn't be enough.
Cloth!
Hair.
Not nearly enough.
And are you willing to give those up?
Sand...
What about sand?
The Wall Breaker spell!
We can create a very fine sand
by busting up the walls and floors.
Of course! Who doesn't love
lying on a sandy beach?!
Smart thinking, Agott! Smartygott!
The more signs drawn to the seal,
the finer the sand it will produce.
More so if the seals are smaller.
Leave the tiny seals to Richeh!
So fast!
That's Richeh's specialty!
Tetia, think of a spell that will
gather the sand in the central plaza
without packing it too hard.
I'll try to think up an enveloping spell
that will keep it in place.
You got it!
H-Hey!
What should I do?
Just stay out of it.
I've agreed to your plan,
but you're not at a skill level
where I can trust you with a spell.
The best thing you can do
is stay out of our way.
How does she draw such a perfect circle?
She draws the circle in
the air a few times first,
then starts at the point closest to her.
Do Tetia and Richeh do it the same way?
How have I been doing it?
The place to start... the final shape...
I guess I never gave much
thought to that stuff.
I'm going to try it.
Until I can do it like they can...
I'm going to try it!
Like this... and then...
Then this...
It's cold.
Yeah, it's gotten pretty dark, huh?
Should I start a fire?
I'm out of paper.
So am I.
It's hopeless.
A Sign of Convergence
would pack it too hard.
What if you wrap it in a membrane of air?
Too weak. It'll still fall apart.
What about reinforcing it
with fine strips of cloth?
Just wrapping it up in that
won't be enough.
And it's going to get even colder, so—
Forget it.
There's gotta be something...
Need an idea... An idea...
There must be a way.
The perfect idea...
I...
I did it!
Um... why are you casting tha—
It's stable.
She cast a Pyreball!
Yours used to go out right away, right?
When did you learn to make it so good?
I've been practicing just now.
I was watching you all do your thing,
so I did it over and over until...
That's amazing!
Coco, you did it!
Well, anyone can learn
with enough repetition...
Repetition?
Repetition! That's it!
Everyone ready?
Ready anytime.
All right, let's go!
Coco!
Thanks!
It's definitely bigger than before.
We have to finish this quickly.
Richeh, go on ahead!
Right.
Done!
Coco!
Right!
Make the sign to close the rings.
Right.
Three...
Two...
One...
Richeh, next station!
Right.
It noticed!
We need to meet up!
Did you finish your rings?
All activated.
Great.
Repetition?
Yes.
To keep the spell from falling apart,
we'll wrap it in repetition magic that
constantly returns it to its initial form.
In other words,
envelop the Wall Breaker/Billow Cluster
combination in a Repetition Spell
Coco!
to create a cloud of sand.
Given the size of the dragon,
we'll need five, I think.
Current status?
It's wary, but almost there...
If we can sync the positioning and
timing right to combine five into one...
Even if it sinks with the beast's weight,
the sand cloud will keep trying
to return to its original shape,
and maintain its nice fluffiness.
I call it...
The Dragon Disabler Cushion!
Wrong. It's the Serpent's Bed of Sand.
That's much cooler!
Smartygott!
Smartygott.
Enough nonsense.
Now's our chance to get past it!
Tetia?
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
I just couldn't help but look.
That dragon looks really happy, huh?
I think this is the first time I've ever
made someone happy with a spell.
Who'd have thought
it'd bring you such joy?
Well?
Yeah, I think this is it.
What kind of spell is it?
I've never seen it before.
Master might know, I suppose.
They're in here?
I don't sense anyone.
Did they move on already?
Huh?
I thought this alley was paved...
Maybe they removed the
flagstones at some point.
Brushbuddies are drawn to
the smell of Conjuring Ink.
Is this—
Get back!
Why didn't you think
before breaking the seal?!
It's what brought us here, isn't it?!
Look up, everyone!
I can see the sky!
Is that the way out?!
Get down!
Ago—
What do I do?
I'm not wearing my Sylph Shoes...
Master?
A dragon, is it?
Master, I—
It's coming. Hang on.
I need my hands free. Hold on tight!
Yes, sir!
You're safe now.
I think it's unconscious.
Agott?
R-Right...
Master!
Tetia! Richeh!
I was so scared!
How did you get here, sir?
I was searching for you when
the space opened up around me...
Where's Coco?
Hello, Coco.
I've waited so long for the
seeds I planted to sprout.
How did you like the
assignment I gave you?
Did it aid your growth?
I know. I'll give you a gift.
I'll teach you things that Qifrey can't.
And when the day comes...
Yes, what a day that will be!
Coco!
Master Qifrey...
Everyone...
Is Agott—
I'm right here.
Thank you for this, Tartah.
Sure.
I'll see if I can get Grandpa to come by.
Thank goodness.
Wait, is this Kalhn?
Yes, we all made it back!
Thank goodness
I was able to find you.
You were unconscious on the tower stairs.
The stairs?
Wait... did the Brimmed Caps
do something to you?
No! I'm just a little spaced out.
Um...
Coco?
Are you okay?
Yeah... I'm fine. I'm fi—
I'm sorry.
I got you all mixed up in this.
I'm really...
really sorry.
Tetia told me what happened in there.
And what you all did there.
It sounds like you saved them all.
Ideas are as important to
spellcasting as penmanship.
Let's work hard to nurture that talent.
Okay!
Coco! I'm so glad you're safe!
I'm sorry I worried you!
I'm sorry, Richeh, and Agott...
I wasn't worried.
She was totally worried.
I saw your cloak—
They're not just safe, they're thriving!
Yes, thanks to all your help.
It's awfully late.
Why not get a room at an inn—
Mr. Nolnoa.
I have a serious favor to ask you.
Eh?
There's a Casting Seal
drawn on the back of this.
I need to know what's in the ink.
Will you look into it for me?
Let's see. What's in the ink?
And please don't tell the
Knights Moralis about this.
B-But we have an obligation to
report Forbidden Magic sightings—
Do not tell anyone of this.
Not anyone.
Honestly. I wonder
what's happening here...
Isn't that Coco's?
Or perhaps... what's about to happen?
Whoops! I forgot.
Episode 6:
A Light on a Rainy Day