No...
N...
No!
This is...
Oh, Yuri.
Comet...
You're awake already.
We're all in the cafeteria
eating right now.
Yuri?
Am I looping over the same time again?
The real me woke up, and the universe...
Am I going to keep looping
in this world line without Gnosia?
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
I repeat.
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
I wonder what that means.
Wait, isn't the sick bay where you...
No...
Comet!
Wait!
No...
This is just going to keep happening.
No matter how many times I loop.
Huh?
EPISODE 17: BUG
Calm down. Calm down.
There has to be some way out of this.
Right now, I should be in the pod
receiving treatment.
And yet, the universe wasn't destroyed
and the current me is still here.
Which means that as long as
the real me is still sleeping,
we don't yet count as a dual existence.
If I'm able to solve this predicament
before the real me wakes up...
What should I do?
Should I halt the treatment?
Then the me inside there will...
But I'm the fake one here.
How can I even be thinking about this?
Crap!
You need to think.
The important thing here is to make
sure the real Yuri doesn't wake up.
There's no reason to halt their
treatment and take their life.
Maybe I can just postpone
the time they wake up...
But... then what?
Am I just going to leave them there
indefinitely until I find a solution?
Isn't that the same as killing them?
Even if I make sure to avoid the real one,
the moment someone sees there
are two of the same person,
the universe will be destroyed
by the dual existence.
The only way to get out of this
is for one of us to disappear.
You are a foreign object
anomalous to this world—
to this universe.
You are a Bug.
Disappear...
Yeah.
Given the situation,
there's only one fair choice.
Best of luck.
Yuri.
Jina...
What's the matter?
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
I repeat.
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
Thank you.
Huh?
I hope you find happiness.
Yuri?
Yuri!
Didn't I... die?
Wait... Even after that,
the loop is still going?
No way.
I can't even die?
I'm going to keep looping
like this even if I die?
That can't be...
No...
No...!
Calm down. I need to calm down.
I won't solve anything by panicking.
If dying isn't going to work,
I need to think of something else!
The real me is inside the pod.
They're the one who's supposed to be here.
They're the one who should be protected.
I need to save them from
becoming a dual existence.
In order to do that, I need to figure out
how to eliminate the Bug—me.
To do that, I need a way to prove
that I'm something that shouldn't exist.
Once that's established,
I should cease to exist.
I need to prove that I'm the fake!
There has to be some way.
I know!
Me...?
Yeah, LeVi confirmed for me
that you have Engineer credentials.
Er... I do, but...
So I want you to use them
to investigate me.
Huh? Investigate you?
B-But why?
The reason is... actually
a bit hard to explain.
Is that a no?
I mean, I don't mind...
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
I repeat.
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
Please! There's no time!
O-Okay! Um...
ENGINEER CREDENTIALS
If she uses her Engineer ability,
she should be able to tell what I am.
That will be undeniable proof
that I'm the fake.
If that's established
without doubt, then I should...
This is...
ENGINEER CREDENTIALS
Y-Yuri! Yuri!
Yuri just...
disappeared?
That didn't work either?
Dying doesn't work.
Proving I'm fake doesn't work.
If I don't do anything,
the moment the real me wakes up,
the universe is destroyed,
and I'm right back to where I started.
Does that mean...
I'm trapped in this time loop forever?
Ooh! I've been lookin' for ya, Yurinchy!
I went all the way to your room
to share some goodies with you,
but you weren't there! So I've been,
like, wondering where you went.
Here, eat up.
What's up? You look like
you've seen a ghost.
Wh-What is this? Wasab—
Was it?!
Jina made them, so I figured
there was something up, but...
Jeez...
You feel a little better?
Huh?
You've been wandering around looking like
you wanted to die or something, Yurinchy.
SQ...
Yikes, was it that strong? My badsies.
Whoa! There, there.
What am I going to do with you?
Here.
I see.
And that's why you wanted to disappear.
But nothing I do is working.
So the universe is just gonna explode?
I'm sure you don't believe me, but...
It's not that I don't believe you.
There's just something, like, bugging me.
Are you really okay
with all this, Yurinchy?
I dunno if you're a Bug
or a fake or whatever,
but you've lived all this time, right?
You've been working real hard
every single day.
And yet...
I'm still a fake, though.
I thought about this over and over,
but the other me is the one who's real.
I don't have any memories.
I'm a Bug that shouldn't exist.
I'm not even human.
But, y'know...
I don't deserve to live!
My, what an unruly child.
In that case, I guess cute li'l SQ
doesn't deserve to live either.
Huh?
Why do you think my name's "SQ"?
You're the 511th copy that Manan
failed to transfer her consciousness to.
Well, look at you, smarty-pants.
Despite how cute I am,
I'm still a wittle one-year-old.
So we're pretty much in the same boat.
And I don't even know
if I have my own consciousness.
I'm a failed version
of a poor-quality copy.
That makes me an even worse
fake than you, Yurinchy.
No...
But, y'know...
Food tastes delicious when I eat,
my heart skips a beat
when I see a hot guy,
and it's fun when my nails turn out nice!
I'm pretty sure that means I'm alive.
So it doesn't matter
if I'm a fake or a copy.
What matters is that I'm alive.
I'm about to say something
really embarrassing,
so make sure you hear me loud and clear.
You've got this! Don't cry!
You silly thing!
Girls totally fall for cuties like that.
SQ...
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
I repeat.
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
Setsu...
There's something
I want to talk to you about.
You're... a Bug?
Yeah.
And if I don't do something, the universe
will be destroyed by the dual existence.
I had no idea things like this
could happen in these loops, too.
Er, sorry. I've actually only
looped a few times so far.
I see. This Setsu still doesn't
know much about the loops.
This isn't good. I'm just going to make
them more nervous talking about this.
So what's going to happen?
What should I do?
You'll just have to do your best.
But...
But there's one thing I know.
You're going to continue on an
amazing journey through the loops
and help everyone—me included.
Really?
Don't worry. You've got this.
Believe in yourself.
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
I repeat.
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
I don't have time to be depressed.
I need to think.
Thankfully, there aren't any
Gnosia infectees in this loop.
Which means I can talk to any
of the others without worry.
With Setsu out of the question, the one
who's probably best able to help me is...
You've recovered already?
This should put off the destruction
of the universe for a while.
But isn't this just
delaying the inevitable?
What's important right now
is buying some time.
If what you said earlier is true,
when you restart the loop,
everyone else's memory is reset.
So you'll have to start all over again.
Yeah, but...
Before we go any further,
I want you to show me.
Oh, right. I guess I promised you that.
Huh... I never thought I'd get to
study a living sample like this.
Doubt not, fear not, and know.
Knowledge will save all.
It's not responding.
It's definitely attached itself to you.
My condolences.
Now you know that I'm not lying, right?
About the looping, and about being a Bug.
That does seem to be the case.
But then, the solution
is actually quite simple.
Huh?
Ha! Do try and use your brain for once.
You've been conflating
two distinct phenomena.
The Bug version of you and the real you...
When the two of you meet, it gives rise to
a dual existence, destroying the universe.
That's the result of one phenomenon.
But your continued existence is the
result of a different phenomenon—
the time loop you are currently
subjected to by the Silver Key.
Two separate phenomena entirely.
Your inability to leave this loop has
nothing to do with your status as a Bug.
The cause is right there before you.
I see.
From the looks of it,
your Silver Key isn't filled yet.
It still thirsts for information,
which means...
It'll keep returning me to whatever world
line still has information to find...
until I gain what it wants.
Well? How does it feel to be entirely
at the Silver Key's beck and call?
It sucks.
But it hasn't been all bad.
I got to find out a lot about all of you.
I got to talk to everyone a lot,
and I've really come to like you all.
Even you, Racio.
Hmph.
The fact that I keep getting brought back
here no matter how many times I loop
means that there's some information
that I can only gain here.
Information that I can only gain
within this short amount of time.
Someone I can only meet
at this exact opportunity...
That's it!
Do you understand?
No, not at all.
I figured as much. Considering how
dated this instant learning system is.
Can you get up?
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
Wait right here. I'll go
confirm what's going on.
I repeat.
An anomalous lifeform has been
detected within the sick bay.
Hey, you didn't even scar. Good for you.
I heard you were hurt pretty bad.
Really? I honestly don't remember...
Huh, is that so?
Well, I wanted to thank you.
I'm Chipie.
It's thanks to you that everyone
on board was saved.
Thanks.
I really don't remember...
Well, the one who actually
led everyone was Setsu.
According to an eyewitness,
you tried to protect Setsu
back then and got hurt.
I see.
Though it doesn't seem that Setsu
realizes that you saved them either.
Well, anyway, glad you're all right.
It would've been a real downer
if you'd died after all that.
Um...
Could you please not tell
Setsu about this?
I don't want them to worry.
Sure. I'll pass that on
to the others, too.
Wait, not again...
An emergency advisory has been issued
from Liu-An's control tower.
We will now evacuate
from Liu-An. I repeat.
An emergency advisory has been issued
from Liu-An's control tower.
We will now evacuate from Liu-An.
Liu-An?