It's summer!
There's watermelons! Ice cream!
And barbecues!
Sounds like you just want to eat!
Well, duh!
Did you guys put on your sunscreen?
Yup!
Yes!
An idol's skin is their life!
I always immediately turn bright red.
This is so fun and exciting.
Even Rintaro looks like he's having fun.
Mm.
Also, Rintaro, your arms are huge!
Look at those muscles!
Ooh!
And actually, I've been working out, too.
Hey! That's public indecency!
Jeez, would you guys calm down?
It's already hot as is!
You're all so full of energy.
And so, it's begun. Ready, and...
F/ACE's Super Exciting Summer Vacation!
Yay!
Wow, you're all so unique.
Maybe you guys don't even need a script.
Thank you.
I can't believe you're actually directing
one of F/ACE's shows, Arimoto-san.
Freelance Director
Yuu Arimoto
Arimoto-san.
Apparently, he's a famous
director in the business.
Actually, I'm pretty
interested in Tamon-kun.
When a guy like that messes up,
it makes for great TV.
Depending on what's featured, the agency
might have to reject some footage.
There are a total of
fifteen staff members.
The only ones who know
about Tamon-kun's real nature
I'm just kidding. We'll do our jobs
and get plenty of footage.
are Fujita-san and myself.
Tamon-kun...
I hope he can stay Hottiehara-kun
for three days and two nights.
After I graduate high school,
I'm gonna get my license,
and I'll be the one driving next year!
Well, I look forward to that.
Hey!! It's just like sweeet magic!! Aha!
Hi, it's me!
The one with that killer smile!
Stealing your gaze with a shocking style!
Smooth as ever, I escort you
And this voice, seducing you
Ah, come on, let's dance;
I'm aiming straight for your heart
I am your ace darlin'
Confidence? Yeah, I've got plenty
Please Please
Whisper just to me, call my name
You're too popular,
it drives me crazy and I'm not okay
But I'm sorry, losing's not my thing
Hey, girl
Look this way!
I see your smile, smile, smile,
I wanna make it all mine
Crash, crash, crash,
our special connection shines
Dance, dance,
our world is non-stop groovin'
I'll show you my perfect
A-side, side, side
And my private B-side, side, side;
I'll show you everything
So take my hand and let's roll
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
Sweetie honey Sweetie honey
It's a spell that makes your heart race
We can't go back
You're falling in love with me, c'mon!
Sweetie honey
Sweet Sweet Sweet magic!!
First comes rock! Rock, paper, scissors!
Aw, I lost.
F/ACE and the Summer Vacation
Natsuki, you'll be the ref.
Okay!
Okay, let's split up into teams.
I mustn't look directly
at heaven on earth.
Here I go!
Is this the Louvre for beautiful faces?!
The British Museum of fine bodies?!
That's one point.
The Shoso-in of bursting smiles?!
My very own personal World Expo has begun!
And cut!
Sorry about that!
Are you hurt at all?
Um... are you okay?
Jugemu, Jugemu Goko no Surikire Kaijarisuigyo no Suigyomatsu Unraimatsu Furaimatsu Kuunerutokoro ni Sumutokoro Yaburakoji no Burakoji Paipopaipo Paipo no Shuringan Shuringan no Gurindai Gurindai no Ponpokopi no Ponpokona no Chokyumei no Chosuke.
Jugemu, Jugemu Goko no Surikire
Kaijarisuigyo no Suigyomatsu
Unraimatsu Furaimatsu
Kuunerutokoro ni Sumutokoro
Yaburakoji no Burakoji
Paipopaipo Paipo no Shuringan
Shuringan no Gurindai
Gurindai no Ponpokopi no Ponpokona
no Chokyumei no Chosuke.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I have to do my best
to make sure Keito-kun doesn't
decide that I'm a crazy fan.
Kinoshita-san, could you take this?
Right away!
That chick is only fawning
over Tamon as usual...
I guess it's better than acting
like that towards anyone.
We're going to start rolling again!
Okay!
I want someone like that...
to have feelings for me!
Tamon!
It's all good!
Dang it!
Have feelings for me?
Great job, everyone.
We'll resume shooting at 6 PM,
so everyone take a break until then.
Okay!
We'll be heading back to our rooms now.
Great job, everyone!
You, too!
Great job!
Kinoshita-san.
Yes?
I'm sure the boys are all tired,
so could you go check on them?
Yes, sir!
It's me, Kinoshita.
I've brought some snacks...
Balloon
Flower
Did you come to sneak into our beds?
I'd be less obvious if I did.
Stop crying! God, you're annoying!
Hngh
I'm so sorry!
What happened?
My face just won't move anymore...
I was just yelling at them both because
they didn't want to leave their room.
We're still on day one!
What about the shoot after this?
Pull yourselves together!
Waaah! He yelled at me!
I said shut up, you dumbass!
Please stop!
It's not like his face muscles are going
to recover just by you yelling at him!
Well, my face is exhausted from keeping
a slight smile on my face the whole time,
so what am I supposed to do?!
Ta
Tamon-kun Smile Please!!
Tamon
A foldout fan?!
Tamon-kun, please smile!
Smile! Please!
Yes, oh, smile!
If it's for you, my priceless smile
will cost you 0 yen.
Let's keep this up just a little longer!
Are you guys with me, my bros?
Of course.
You don't need to tell us twice.
Perfectly cooked.
This looks so good!
How many skewers do you want, Rintaro?
Okay!
Hey, can I roast some marshmallows?
That's a dessert, so not yet.
Let's roast some veggies
that are great for your skin.
Boo, you meanie.
You're older than me, so please
don't say such childish things.
All right, you two.
Let's eat in peace, okay?
Everyone's so professional.
I can't believe they're
the same people from earlier.
Okay.
This one's ready.
How is it, Rintaro? Is it good?
Yeah. It's good.
And cut! That's a wrap on day one!
Thank you very much!
I'll go ahead and take these.
Oh, I'll help, too!
Hey, thanks!
Then could you put these away
in the storage shed behind the gym?
Right!
Today's shoot was so much fun!
I'm looking forward to tomorrow, too!
I'm also...
That bath felt great.
Hello?
It's me.
Who...?
I said it's me, damn it! Figure it out!
You forgot your damn fan,
so come to the room now to get it!
You've got ten seconds.
Th-That selfish gorilla...
It's me, Kinoshita.
Come in.
Wha—?!
Why are you dressed like that?!
Well, you said to come over now.
I'm sorry that I'm not
exactly presentable right now.
I-I-I never said you were unpresentable!
Where's Gloomyhara-san?
Probably taking a bath.
How would I know?!
Ta
Tamon
Come over here!
Hmph!
I'm sorry. I brought so many with me
that I didn't notice I was missing one.
You brought more than one?!
Yes. I tried to account for every issue
Gloomyhara-san could run into during camp
and prepared all the variations I could.
Don't Die
Don't Run Away
Cameras Aren't Scary
Gross! You're so, so creepily gross!
Because of these?
Damn it! She's so tenacious!
No one is this dedicated!
Hey!
Keito-kun?!
That woman didn't sneak in here, did she?
Balloon
Flower
Get lost.
I guess I don't see her. But be careful.
Fans are the devil.
Seriously, what the hell happened?
Um...
I figured if he saw you,
it'd cause you trouble.
Oh... Thank you very much...
Seriously...
Why's it gotta be him and not me?
By "him," do you mean Tamon-kun?
Huh?! U-Uh, I...
I'm not sure how to respond.
My feelings for Tamon-kun are just
so great that it's hard to explain,
so can I just read these sutras
I compiled over the last two years?
What the hell is that?!
I don't even want to hear
a sentence of that!
If you're done here,
then get the hell out!
You big dummy!
I can't believe he called me
over just for this.
Kinoshita-san?!
Ta
Tamon
Huh? Gloomyhara-san?
Why do you have that on your face?
I dislike having to bathe with
other people, so I'm exhausted...
Yet you can barely keep your clothes on
when you're Hottiehara-kun.
Oh, sorry you have to see me like this.
I forgot my fan and
Sakaguchi-san summoned me.
Ouri-kun did?
Is that Darkhara-san?!
I just went to get my fan!
Er, no, I mean...
Were you okay?
I'm sorry?
I asked if you'd come along...
Thinking back on it now,
it was really annoying of me to ask.
I'm sorry that
I was only thinking of myself.
What?
I know this work is new to you.
Have you been doing okay?
Has Ouri-kun been impossible
to deal with at all?
Has Keito-kun been mean again?
Oh, I'm totally fine!
You just need to worry
about yourself, Gloomyhara-san!
That's why I came along
as your housekeeper.
Farewell!
The most nutritious part
of a fish is their bones.
Yup. Like calcium and iron.
Sardines and mackerel are actually
quite delicious down to their bones.
I don't like bones, though.
Why couldn't they be born boneless?
I'll eat every bit of 'em!
That's just red snapper,
so it's not going to work!
Wait, really?
And
Cut
And cut!
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Fortune
Big Curse
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Let's see
some PDA!
This is the last scene for day two!
We'll be shooting a test of courage!
Let's all give it our best!
Can someone who's free go check
on the speakers in storage?
Yes! I can go check!
Could you split up into
groups of two and three?
Is everything ready?
Yes, sir!
I can't seem to find them...
Did I check the wrong place?
Huh?
What's going on with the speakers?
I had the part-timer go check on them,
but she's not back yet.
Don't have a part-timer
do any final checks!
We're about to start shooting any minute!
I'll go check on her.
The speakers are in the storage shed
behind the school building, right?
Yeah. There are two storage sheds,
so go to the right one.
They're not in the one behind the gym!
Got it!
I'm so sorry about our staff.
What's up? Is there some kind of trouble?
I'll go look for her!
Huh?
Hey, Tamon! You better come right back!
Someone, please!
Why won't it open? At this rate,
the shoot will be affected...
What should I do?
Kinoshita-san?
Gloomyhara-san?!
Thank goodness you're safe...
Gloomyhara-san.
I didn't know what I was going to do
if I found you as a corpse.
Someone! Please!
Someone, please! We're in here!
What are we going to do?
What if this door never opens again
and both the shoot and show are ruined
and Kinoshita-san
and I end up as mummies,
and we end up finished both
socially and physically?!
This isn't good.
It'd be fine if it were just me,
but Kinoshita-san can't end up wrinkly!
Even if the shoot resumed, he won't
go back to Hottiehara-kun after this.
I'm so sorry!
They say that I'm rejuvenating eye candy,
but that doesn't actually exist!
Please calm down. It'll be okay!
If you're missing, someone will notice
immediately and come open the door.
But what if it doesn't open?
It will!
Do you see the part-timer girl?
She's not here.
Damn it, where'd they go?
Now the shoot's gonna
have to pause... Oh.
I-It'll be okay! It'll be okay!
I'm sure everything will work out!
If Tamon-kun's shoot gets ruined...
You're not okay, are you, Kinoshita-san?
Huh? Th-That's not...
What?!
You must be tired, Kinoshita-san.
I'm not, though.
You are!
There's no way you could make
those fans instantly either.
I figured you made them
after finding out
about the training camp...
N-Now that you mention it,
I might be a little tired... maybe?
I've been watching you more than
you realize, Kinoshita-san...
Hey! Is someone in here?
If you're in there, say something!
Let's open the door.
We're here! We're in here!
I'm so sorry! I should've
been more careful.
No! The door was broken
and shut on its own!
Hey, Tamon! Are you okay?
That woman didn't try
to do anything to you, did she?
What do you even mean by that?
Er, everyone... I'm sorry!
This is actually all my fault.
The storage shed behind the gym
wouldn't open from the inside, right?
I actually rigged it so that
it'd only open from the outside.
I wanted to get some footage
of Tamon-kun genuinely being surprised.
Tee-hee!
Whut?!
You don't need to do anything like that.
We'd still make sure the show
was plenty entertaining!
We'll do our very best!
I am really scared, though.
F/ACE has the absolute best members.
You can count on us.
Okay, let's do this.
Sorry to keep everyone waiting!
We'll now start the test of courage shoot!
Thank you very much!
They're finally starting
their final shoot.
Everything went by so fast.
There we go.
They're making you do
stuff like this, too?
Tachibana-san.
Tamon doesn't like carrots,
so remove those.
We don't want his real self peeking out.
Make sure the knives cut well, too.
He's insanely clumsy,
so he'll get hurt otherwise.
Understood.
Ugh, he's such a handful.
You must actually really
love Tamon-kun, Tachibana-san.
What?
When you compliment Tamon-kun
while you're all together as F/ACE,
that's genuine, isn't it?
Why do you think that?
Because I don't think it's possible to
move people's hearts with insincere words.
You have a lot of fans, Keito-kun.
Of course, you also have
the most fans that are so passionate
that they're a bit insane.
Tamon-kun and Ouri-kun aren't lying
when it comes to what's
the most important.
So I figured that you
were probably the same way.
I...
When you're a fan, both time
and money melt away instantly.
You sure are tall, Rintaro!
There's no time to spend
anything on anyone shallow.
I'm super jealous.
Gimme some of your height.
I'm just doing this for the money.
Everyone, please get into your outfits!
We'll be right there! Let's do
our best on this last shoot, guys!
Yeah!
Watching him pisses me off.
He's more awesome than anyone
when he's got his shit together.
Well, maybe you could try being
a little nicer to him?
I don't need any advice from you.
I'm the leader of F/ACE, after all.
You are.
I'm gonna go finish getting changed.
Right!
Ooh!
You're so good at cooking, Keito.
I used to help out in the kitchen
when I worked at a café.
Not to mention,
I have five little brothers,
so I'd be in a kitchen a lot
since my parents were always working.
Wait! You have five brothers?!
I've never heard that before!
What? I never told you guys?
No?!
Oh, I see.
And that's a wrap!
I didn't know what to expect
when I was told
I'd be going to this training camp, but...
I think things worked out
surprisingly fine
because Tamon-kun was pretty reliable.
Gloomyhara-san!
Kinoshita-san! Are you on a break?
Yes. What are you doing?
Well...
I know we're here for work,
but we came all the way to the ocean,
and I was worried that you might not
have gotten to do anything summery...
so I was taking pictures of the ocean.
What?
I was going to show you later...
but look.
A hermit crab...?
I'm so sorry I suck at taking pictures.
I do suck, don't I?!
You don't.
I just thought this was
very much like you, Gloomyhara-san.
Th-Thank you very much.
Today, I found out why Keito-kun became
an idol for the first time.
Tachibana-san?
He always mentioned that it was
for money, but it's actually...
My brothers have middle school,
high school,
and uni entrance exams coming up.
And um... I wanted to
help out my parents a bit.
It was so his family could smile.
I want to do my best with Keito-kun
as the center of F/ACE.
I'll do everything I can to support
the brand new F/ACE, too!
Kinoshita-san!
So cold!
Are you okay? You should probably
change before you catch a cold.
I wouldn't catch a cold from this!
I slept like a rock
last night, so I'm fine!
Oh...
You're right.
Your complexion looks much better today.
Uh huh...
Na na na...
I wonder what the world
would look like without you
When I look back,
you've always been by my side
Teaching me what "warmth"
and "happiness" feel like
A speedboat sails across the endless skies
An unwavering course,
a straight shot down the middle
An unbreakable red balloon
found nowhere else
Is this "fate"? Or just a "coincidence"?
Like a wilted flower coming back to life
A light that shines
Through the impossibly dark night
(Light of your soul)
I wanted to grasp it
(I love you so)
So I strived for it
Wanna keep going, wanna keep growing
Bringing our flowers and dreams
into full bloom
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTranslation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hSubtitle Timing:
Editing and Typesetting:\h\h\h\h\h
\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hQuality Control:
\h\h\h\hTranslation Check:
\hMichelle Tymon
\h\h\h\hMariana Martinez
Ashley Barboza
Alicia Ashby\h\h\h\h
\h\h\h\h\h\hSriram Gurunathan