In the near future, e-Pulse is
generated by human thoughts and emotions,
and used as an energy source
for AI devices called "Sapotamas,"
leading to a new development for humanity.
But from its shadows,
terrifying monsters have appeared.
Monsters that evolve by consuming e-Pulse.
They are...
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
darenimo jama wa sasenai sono saki he
Beyond where no one can stop me
mayoinagara kotae sagashi tsukisusumu
I'll make my way there
As I seek the answer
kizamitsukero Emotion
Carve your emotion
hibiiteiru
It reverberates
tashika ni shinkurosuru Tempo wa
The tempo that synchs
sukoshi zutsu
kakureta sekai abaiteiku hakudou
Is a pulse that slowly reveals
The hidden world
yuraganai Baseline no ue de Rec
Record on top of the solid Baseline
Don't mess up tempo
futsuu ja monotarinee
Normal's not enough for me
Just keep howling, howling!!!
Howling like it's all you've got
shinjiru mono ga nijimisou ni natte mo
Even if what you believe begins to blur
nigirishimeru Riaru wa
uso janaku tsuyoku hibiku
The reality that you grasp
Rings strong and true
Metronome topparau ichido kiri kono JAM
Take away the Metronome
For this one and only JAM
unaru Mad Pulse kanjirunda
I feel a roaring Mad Pulse
kanjou no mama narasu kodou wa
The emotional beat that rings out
sou zutto hashiritsuzukeru BPM
Is the BPM that continues on and on
(Let the beat lead the way)
matenrou nomikomu Cloudy Rain
The Cloudy rain swallows the city
rinkushite rizumu yoretatte
Groove ni shichaeba ii
Even if I link and the rhythm warps
I just make it part of my groove
norikonase omoidoori
Ride it like you see fit
(Let the beat lead the way)
itami daite mo tomarazu ni
Even if it hurts, I won't stop
kizami tsudzukeru kodou
Won't back down
Keep carving the beat
bokura nara donna koto mo norikoerareru
We can overcome anything
tatakitsukero Emotion
Drum to your emotion
One of the world's
biggest philanthropists...
Klay Arslan, holds charity auctions.
They're a front for an illegal
high-price Digimon auction.
According to rumors.
Why by someone that famous?
His secret name is "Klay the Surging."
He's a Five Star.
Fine bark?
No, a "Five Star."
They're five super-powerful Cleaners.
The Ministry of Civil Protection is asking
that we investigate the Digimon auction.
The reward is a million Credits.
We're in!
Right?
What?! Why not?
You prefer to avoid the Five Stars?
Correct.
Even if I join in the mission?
She'll waive her finder's fee.
Kawarazaki can't move publicly,
so he needs our help.
We only investigate.
Don't do anything dangerous.
BLACK MARKET AUCTION
Wow, do we look out of place.
What do you expect?
Even I couldn't get in here
without this ID the Ministry provided.
Does everyone in here know about Digimon?
Most are just upper-class people
who only know about the charity auction.
Only a select few are allowed access
to the underground auction.
So how do we get in?
Well, well.
Long time no see.
I didn't expect to run into
Maki Kutsuwada herself here.
You're as beautiful as always.
I see you're well, Mr. Arslan.
Ever the enthusiastic
philanthropist, I see.
As fortune allows. Apparently I made
the most donations in the world last year.
That slimeball is a Five Star?
And they know each other.
Maki has always been a bit of a mystery.
If you'll excuse me.
I still have people to greet.
But we've barely spoken. What a pity.
I'm flattered by your interest.
Do enjoy yourself.
What a creep.
Sir.
Track the lady back there.
That woman?
She's a top information broker.
She has a lot of
legitimate connections, too.
The Klay Charity Auction
will begin in 20 minutes.
You there.
"I seek the Land of Mirrors."
-What?
-Huh?
Pardon. My mistake.
He mistook me for a servant!
He said something cryptic, didn't he?
It's a password!
Follow them!
I'll keep the muscleman busy.
This is just an investigation.
Don't do anything risky.
Excuse me.
Yes?
"I seek the Land of Mirrors."
Please take the elevator.
Your chariot awaits.
That woman...
She's that Digimon buyer.
We found it. We're going in.
Is this the place?
My friends, welcome to our secret auction.
Let's begin the Klay Charity Auction.
First up is the fabled painting
by Teruo Tanaka, Black Cat.
Lot number one...
With an explosive body,
it's a Bombernanimon!
I don't need a girlfriend!
Somebody please just buy me!
We've lived a life of shame,
but we'll make it worth your while!
Weren't they taken by the Tactics?
It's them!
What are they doing here?
Probably security.
So they're involved with this, too.
I get it.
A Digimon requires an Owner.
So a Digimon Auction...
...is also human trafficking.
Talk about sickening.
So Haruomi and Commandramon
would have been taken here, too.
I got proof.
Shall we go?
Let's find some more evidence.
Sniff, sniff.
800,000.
800,000 Credits.
A million.
A million Credits.
Do I hear more?
I guess not.
Lot number one, Bombernanimon.
Sold for one million Credits!
I smell Digimon, ya know!
Hey! Are you okay?
Tomoro.
Let me guess what you're thinking.
Huh?
If I'm right, then we leave right now.
Leave?
No way!
I knew it.
We're only here to investigate.
You heard Kyo.
Don't do anything dangerous.
So we just leave her behind?!
Listen. We're not playing hero here.
Why are you crying, ya know?
Lick.
Tonight's premium item.
Lot number two.
The miraculous fairy, Tinkermon!
Its Speed Nightmare attack is
a hallucinogen with premium market value.
And the Fairy Powder from its wings
has rejuvenating qualities.
Good lord...
That's...!
That idiot!
Stare...
What are you doing?!
We've got no choice! Dig in!
Rapid Burst!
This is...!
Reina? Why...?
What choice did I have?
Let's finish this and get out of here!
Catch them!
Everyone, get out of here!
Tomoro Tenma!
You. What the heck are you doing here?
Stop showing up everywhere.
I knew you guys weren't normal Cleaners.
But I didn't expect human trafficking.
I'm just following orders.
Orders? From who?
Like I'd tell you, stupid.
We should be safe now.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Hand over your Chiropmon.
It's going on auction with the others.
Roll, roll, roll, roll!
Pshh!
Kaboom!
Time for some payback! Take this!
Go on.
Right!
Let's go!
You won't escape.
Gekkomon!
Yum! Yum!
I've never had food
this good before, ya know!
-Ta-da!
-This isn't the time to be eating!
Let's go, ya know!
What's wrong? Bring it on!
Tomoro!
Right!
Let's go!
Pound the beat!
Gekkomon Evolution!
Armalizamon!
After them!
Oh no you don't, ya know!
On your six! Incoming!
Now go catch them!
Murasamemon?
I told you to investigate only!
Kyo!
Kyo Sawashiro...
and his Ultimate Digimon!
Tomoro Tenma.
I'm better than you!
I'll show you a true genius!
Rhamphomon, let's do it!
Raito!
I'm not yet...
I can do this!
Shut up and obey me!
Understood.
Rhamphomon Evolution!
Azhdarmon!
That's his...
...Ultimate Digimon.
See that? This is what I can do!
Azhdarmon!
Go!
Kyo!
No!
Darn it!
Not that way! Why won't you obey me?
He's lost control?
Armalizamon!
Tomoro!
Okay!
Armalizamon!
Your aim sucks!
Now!
Yes!
Stupid parlor tricks!
Now finish off Murasamemon!
Not that one, stupid!
No!
Tinkermon!
No need to be so sad...
Once I'm gone...
you won't have to suffer anymore.
Tinkermon...
Tinkermon!
You!
You ignored my orders!
It's not Monodramon's fault!
Don't make them evolve
when you can't even control them!
Some genius you are.
Hotaruko and Granit managed
to stop the products from escaping.
So you won't be punished.
But you don't seem to understand
the financial value that Tinkermon had.
You've cost Sir Klay.
And you'll pay for it.
It's too bad.
But at least everyone's okay.
BREAKING NEWS
ILLEGAL DRUG DEAL AT AUCTION
This just in.
In a shocking turn of events,
an illegal drug deal was conducted
during the Klay Charity Auction.
KLAY FOUNDATION CEO
KLAY ARSLAN
This despicable act is an insult
to the spirit of moral citizens.
The ringleader was captured
by the Ministry of Civil Protection,
but is maintaining her silence.
How did she even get arrested?
I see. You caught her.
Yes.
Found you.
You're under arrest
for the illegal trade of Digimon.
Anyhow, the reason you're here...
is because Kawarazaki
has a special reward for you.
Oh.
Speak of the devil.
atarimae wo atarimae ni shinai
Don't let the normal be normal
gakufu doori ja monotarinaindayo
Playing to the score is not enough
noizu sura mo torikonde
jibun dake no sesshon wo!
Take in everything, even the noise
And make it our own session!
hitomakase ja kawaranaishi
Boot! Boot!
Things won't change in others' hands
te nobase
Reach out your hand
machigai mo osorezu susume
Boot! Boot!
Don't be scared to mess up, go on
yuukan ni
With courage
ruuru ni tatakitsukeru NO
error, error
Go tell the rules NO
Error, error
sukeeru auto joutou
error, error
Scale out? Bring it on
Error, error
yosoku funou no koodo
error, error
An unexpected code
Error, error
puronpto nanka ja seigyoudekinai omoide
Prompts can't control these feelings
kamase shauto
Give it a shout
BRAVE! mou kowakunai
BRAVE! No more fear
utsumuitari mo shinai
Keep my head high
senaka azukeaeru kimi ga iru kara
I've got someone who's got my back
GROOVE! mou tomaranai
GROOVE! We can't be stopped
yunizon suru koudou ga
Our beats are in unison
kitto sekaijuu wo appudeeto shiteiku
We're going to update the world
bakuon de
With a bang
Tomoro's competing
in an illegal colosseum?!
That guy... Why does he always
get caught up in these messes?
Probably because he's too impulsive.
That's right,
he should think before he acts.
He'll get a good talking-to
once he gets back.
Tomoro's a bit careless, ya know!
I don't want to hear that from you!
Next time on DIGIMON BEATBREAK
"Proof of Genius"