Tips from Makio-chan
Vocab
Pick a main theme
Focus on what I want to say most
Write with
the intent to kill
Sounds scary
What do I want to say?
I don't have anything to say...
Nothing to say
Have things settled down?
Yeah, for now.
Glad to hear it.
Yeah, I guess.
Kasamachi
Actually, can I vent for a bit?
That's rare for you.
I've learned it's not
always bad to complain.
Go ahead.
I have to admit I was
shocked when I first heard
that my stubborn old man
was in the hospital.
But what's been the biggest headache
is his damn attitude toward
the hospital staff.
That's a strong tone!
Are you good?
Isn't someone going to hear you?
It's fine. I'm outside right now.
But man, I hope I don't
turn out like that.
With the nurse,
he was all like, "Hey, you!"
Who knew he'd be this bad
even on his sickness?
I seriously couldn't believe it.
I hear you.
Well, I suppose it means
he's well enough to be rude.
Kasamachi-kun.
Yeah?
It might take time, but I hope
you break free of that curse.
You and me both.
Although I'd say you're
further along than I am.
Well, you learn to pass down
the good and get rid of the bad.
Curse...
Curse
C-u-r...
Journal with Witch
Episode 10\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hBind
Emiri, do you want soup too?
Yeah, but I don't need toast.
Here, take it to the table yourself.
You're a high schooler now.
Okay.
Put the paper down, darling.
Right.
Emiri, don't forget your lunch.
Okay.
Makio-san told me she was having
a hard time making bento boxes.
Kojima-san is actually a scientist!
I wonder if novelists have
to pull all-nighters.
Someone that pretty works in science?
I dunno.
It's funny, 'cause last time I went
over there, she was day drinking.
Her dress underneath the
white coat is a nice sight.
Really? I wish I could do that too.
What are you talking about?
That's considered sexual harassment
in this day and age.
She's shared some other photos
with us for our viewers.
I'd say that comment itself is harassment.
Huh?
Always has been.
Kojima-san is sharing her life as a
woman in science on social media...
Oh... Right.
The same route to school as always.
Crowds of people. Children running.
White breath.
Vending machines with cocoa and...
Milk Cocoa
Hey, let's go skiing.
A poster's smile.
Um... Bicycles. Trains.
"S" for... school field trip.
"P" for... puffs of cloud.
"D" for... dwarf flying squirrel?
"L" for lines of trees along traffic.
"C" for...
Curse.
How did that turn into a word chain game?
Emi—
Emiri!
Oh, Chicchi!
Hey, and Asa.
"Chicchi"?
Chiyo-chicchi and I have
chemistry together.
Huh.
Emiri and I are gonna be pals
in the science track next year.
Pals?
Wait, you're choosing the science track?
I guess so after all.
And the way she says your name...
Yeah, like the English "Emily."
I've been asking Chicchi for advice
since she's doing science.
Yeah, I'm gonna be a doctor.
Wow.
Since both my parents are doctors and all.
Isn't that awesome?
Not sure how I feel about following
in their footsteps, though.
Catch you later.
Morning, Sakura!
Morning!
Hey, did you hear
about the pop quiz in math?
It's not a pop quiz.
They told us last year.
What? I totally missed that!
Come on, first-years!
Run like your life's on the line!
Yoshimura, pick up the pace!
Roger that!
Run for your life.
Run, baseball team, run.
What? No way.
For how long?
Hey, there she is.
Get a load of this.
Apparently Shinozaki's
going out with Hashiba!
Can you believe him?
Cool.
What's with that reaction?
Well, I don't really care.
But he tried so hard to get with you!
Don't you think it's way too soon?
It's fine. It's not like I like him.
Dang. She's too good for him.
Shut up.
Class is starting. Get in your seats.
"What happiness to sit in intimate
conversation with someone of like mind,
warmed by candid discussion of the
amusing and fleeting ways of this world...
But such a friend is hard to find,
and instead you sit there doing your best
to fit in with whatever the other
is saying, feeling deeply alone."
Take note from Morimoto
and remember to review your exercises.
Great job.
We covered this in class.
We'll have end-of-term exams next month.
Someone on the science track.
With a perfect score on her quiz.
Okay, get your textbooks out.
Let's move on to today's lesson.
Cloudy skies are a pest.
Starting on page 234...
How did you do on the quiz?
Bombed it. I didn't study at all.
Neither did I.
November 27th
Juno-san
I want to become the person I want to be!
November 27th
Juno-san
I want to become the person I want to be!
I want to become the pers—
What?
Really?
Oh... Wait, what day is it?
I'm home.
Oh. Right.
"Welcome home."
Never mind that.
So, what day will that be?
Huh? No, I don't remember.
I don't intend to.
All right. I'll ask her.
Yeah, she comes first.
Okay.
Mom
Hey, listen...
I'm home.
Oh, yeah, welcome back.
So, it's almost—
Wait, that reminds me.
Huh? What?
When's your birthday?
September 4th.
Sorry, I totally screwed that up.
Well, you didn't seem
to celebrate yours either.
So I just figured birthdays
weren't a thing here.
It's not like that's a rule or anything.
And never you mind about my birthday.
Adults have enough reasons
to get together to eat and drink.
I'm sorry. We'll celebrate this year.
On both of our birthdays.
Oh, okay.
And to make up for missing
your last birthday,
we'll have a little party
to celebrate our first year together.
Wow! Okay.
Also, one more thing...
I meant to talk to you about this.
We're coming up on the anniversary
of your parents' death.
If you want to do something for it,
we'll fit that in too.
Do something for it?
Could be anything.
We can visit their grave
or have a monk come over.
Something typical like that,
or, if you want, maybe talking
to me or someone else.
Whatever you'd like.
Of course, doing nothing
is also an option.
Just think about it.
And let me know anytime.
Okay.
Thanks for today, Juno-san. I had fun.
I'm glad you could blow off some steam.
I bet it's tough to welcome
a kid out of the blue.
Yeah, I guess.
She kind of reminds me
of a dog. Like a shiba.
You're not the first to say so.
Maybe it's her eyes.
Well, until she goes to college
or legally becomes an adult...
I figure I'll do my best until then.
So just a few more years.
I don't know about that, Koudai-san.
I'm a grand old adult myself, but I'm
still just a kid in front of my mom.
The same will go for her.
I mean, I know in your case,
you're not mother and daughter by blood.
But still, I expect there'll be something.
Even into adulthood.
Probably forever.
You made a deal with the devil.
That makes it sound bad, but...
There's no "until so and so"
or "until this is over."
I don't think that's something
you ever get to cut completely off.
Yeah...
You're right.
I know I am.
Oh, that's right.
I have a favor to ask of you.
What? You're freaking me out.
Remember that old picture of yours
you showed me before?
Can you send it to me?
What? Why?!
It's my favorite. Please!
To help me get out of my rut! Come on!
That has nothing to do
with writer's block!
I'm not doing it!
Please!
Ah, how cute.
That's going in my favorites.
But still, I expect there'll be something.
Even into adulthood.
Probably forever.
Sis! Mom wants to take a picture of us!
What? Again?
Hurry!
What are you talking about?
It's been a whole year.
Hurry it up, Sis!
But Makio always goofs around.
Don't be like that.
You'll be happy to look back
on these when you grow up.
I bet she didn't want to die...
Journal with Witch
There she is!
Takumi, Takumi, Takumi, Takumi! Big news!
What's going on?
Didn't you hear?
The band club is having
an outdoor concert on campus
to welcome the new students in April!
Huh. Where?
In the courtyard concourse!
Wow, that's cool.
No, that's not the point.
They're picking the lead
vocalist by audition!
Huh...
Hello?
We're all talking about auditioning!
It's finally our chance to shine!
New Club Captain   Second-Year Misaki Oki
What's the harm?
We're only playing
with one acoustic guitar.
Let's kick off the new term
by switching things up.
No application requirements!
But what about lyrics?
I haven't been able to write
an original song yet.
You don't need any!
You can audition with any song.
Let's show 'em our chops, Takumi!
What do you say, Asa-chan?
Hey, what if we try writing
our own original songs?
Are you being serious?
Sure am. I don't want to be a
face in the crowd forever.
Original songs, huh?
Th-Then I'll come up with the lyrics!
I can't write any melodies,
but I think I can manage lyrics.
My aunt's a novelist,
and she says anyone can write.
That can't be true.
Great! Then I'll give it a shot too.
We can muster one song
if we work together.
Wait, I'll pitch in too.
Don't leave me out.
Perfect. Then it's settled.
I've got a feeling the tides
are about to change.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Good.
We got this!
Yeah!
What was all that for, then?
78th Hachioji District Elementary
Choir Competition
Curse...
I'm so screwed for the mock exams.
Same.
What difference does it even make
if we can get into a good college?
I know. It doesn't matter
how smart girls are.
We end up getting married anyway.
Makio-san would get riled
up if she heard that.
Nah, she'd just ignore it.
"It's not even worth
listening to," she'd say.
Asa
Sorry, Miri-chan!
I got stuck doing some paperwork.
Thanks for waiting.
I was about to give up and go home.
My bad.
No way! That's way too strict.
That's an all-girls schools for you.
Is that your parents?
Asa
No, a friend. You know...
The childhood friend who lost her parents.
Oh...
I feel so bad for her.
I can't even imagine.
Yeah, I don't know...
Our whole families were close.
Like, we had sleepovers and stuff.
So it was a big shock for me too.
It hit hard, but...
Asa
Emiri
You up?
Yeah, I am
What's up?
I don't know.
I couldn't help thinking...
I don't know
Emiri
You up?
Yeah, I am
What's up?
We got in an accident on our trip
You up?
Yeah, I am
What's up?
I don't know
They're dead
Yeah, I am
What's up?
I don't know
We got in an accident on our trip
What's up?
I don't know
We got in an accident on our trip
They're dead
My parents
What do I do
I can't ever quit being her friend now.
My parents
What do I do
I...
Isn't that awful?
I still think it sometimes.
It's just a lot.
But you haven't quit
being her friend, have you?
You haven't quit, Miri-chan.
I mean, I don't actually plan to.
Even though she gets
on my nerves sometimes.
We're friends, after all.
You're kind, Miri-chan.
Really?
Yeah, you are.
I definitely think so.
That's what I really...
like about you.
Tell me that more.
Won't it get old?
Is that even possible?
Emiri's not reading my texts.
Maybe she's at cram school.
I know, but still.
Why don't you reply to texts, Makio-chan?
I only do that sometimes.
Sometimes I do reply.
There you go again...
Okay, so why don't you sometimes?
Why?
I need to protect my peace
and quiet sometimes.
Your peace and quiet?
Yup.
Isn't that lonely, though?
I'm sure it's not for you, but...
Quiet
You're starting to get it.
Not really.
Quietness
Lonely
Is that kind of like the desert?
I'm sure that depends on the person.
It could be a grassy field, a forest,
a mountain, or even the beach.
Huh...
Curse
Nothing to say
What's this again
Curse (pronounced kers)
Noun; transitive verb
A spell cast to bind someone.
See "break a curse."
Also, restricting freedom via
psychological coercion.
Curse...
78th Hachioji District Elementary
Choir Competition
Good job. How was it?
I had fun!
It's too bad you didn't win.
What? I didn't really care about winning.
Oh, you didn't?
What should we do for lunch?
Hey, Dad!
What did you think of my singing?
Ouch, Asa. Stop yanking.
What? Um...
I guess...
you stood out.
What's that mean?
She should just lie low.
Huh?
Tamashiro-san.
She stands out enough as it is.
Do you not like Tamashiro-san?
What? No, nothing like that.
I just mean she shouldn't stick
out for the wrong reasons.
Since she's finally not getting bullied.
You never know when your
standing might change.
Yeah... You're right.
Hurry it up, Yoshimura!
The upperclassmen
will let you have it again.
Is it just me, or are they tough on me?
It's 'cause you're our
rising star. That's why.
Whatever.
You're not auditioning?!
Nope. I'm not.
Why not?
'Cause. It's scary standing out.
And singing in front of people? No thanks.
Then why are you in a band?
That's why I chose the bass.
Either way, I'm not doing it.
Aw, and here I thought
you really had a shot.
See you after school.
At the time, I was searching
and searching far and wide.
To the point I got tired of getting mad.
I'm thirsty...
Should I be giving water
to my own loneliness?
Would that help me find it?
Find what I should be searching for?
What the hell?!
How could something like this stand?!
Chiyo?
So no matter how high I score,
I could get rejected just
for being a girl? Seriously?
Uniform Point Deductions for Female Applicants:
Nitto Medical University Accused of Arbitrary Manipulation
I can't believe it...
How could this have been
going on all this time?
I'll never let it go...
Never! Not ever!
Damn. She's really mad.
Morimoto's scary, man.
I couldn't look away.