Sunday
Good morning, Your Majesty.
Morning, Kanadge.
Since we're working on a weekend,
let's head straight to the venue.
Sure.
He made sure to recline the seat.
How considerate of you, Kanadge.
Thank you!
When traveling by car, the Hell-Lord
must always sit in a fully-reclined seat.
As for the reason why...
To avoid this!
By the way, this is
a Hellhorde company car.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
m 0 0 l 230 0 230 80 0 80
Hellhorde Performance Award Speech
Don't forget to smile!
Thank you all for gathering here today
for the Hellhorde Performance Award Ceremony.
(Make sure to pause!)
To foster further growth and
peace in the Demon World,
the members of the Hellhorde spare
no effort working diligently daily,
in the area best suited to their talents.
* Take a breath. Calm yourself!
Among them, the people we recognize
today have made significant
contributions to the Hellhorde this quarter.
Have you memorized your speech for
the Hellhorde Performance Award Ceremony?
Yes, barely.
But I'm getting nervous.
I know you'll do great.
Oh.
Drive-Thru
There's a Mark D's.
Should we stop to eat here?
Drive-Thru
I remember Your Majesty saying you
wanted to try their limited-time burger.
No, it's fine, but thank you.
I've got no appetite right now
with these nerves.
Not to mention the item
I was interested in...
Grand Croquette Burger
is only sold on their lunch menu.
That's right, they're still on
their breakfast menu right now.
Although the breakfast menu
is great in its own right.
That's true.
You know the one they have
with a meat patty between two pancakes?
Yes. I love it.
I love putting the hash brown you get
with the meal inside the sandwich.
That sweet and salty goodness,
plus the hash brown's crispy texture...
It's the best.
Hey...
Why would you say
that after we've passed it?
S-Sorry.
I want to eat it really badly now.
Should I turn back?
No, we've almost made it to the venue.
Let's keep going.
I'm sorry.
Demon World Cultural Center
West Parking Lot
It looks like there's
a corner store nearby.
Do you need me to get you anything?
Your Majesty?
That Mark Dragon is around
a kilometer away.
Two kilometers for a round trip.
My body should be able to
withstand that distance.
What?
Hell-Lord Speed Form!
Hell-Lord Speed Form
I'm gonna go stop by the Mark Dragon.
Drive-Thru
Will this be for take-out or dine-in?
So that'll be one cheeseburger?
Would you like fries with that?
Put the hash brown between
the patty and the egg...
Here I go.
Delicious!
Immediately after biting into
the fluffy pancake and juicy patty,
I get the crunch from the hash brown...
What an exciting surprise.
My fangs are crying in joy!
The rich, slightly melted cheese...
And that firm egg is great, too.
Which will you get,
the whites or the yolk?
It's a matter of taste, but I get
a little happy when it's the yolk.
You could say that...
All of the ingredients
are in perfect unity.
A quintuple combo of delicious.
Not a single weak spot.
Truly splendid!
I'm glad you like it.
It really does taste
good eating it like this.
I was so nervous
that I couldn't eat breakfast,
but thanks to you, I regained my appetite
and shook off my nerves.
Thanks, Kanadge.
m 0 0 l 230 0 230 80 0 80
Hellhorde Performance Award Speech
Don't forget to smile!
Thank you all for gathering here today
for the Hellhorde Performance Award Ceremony.
(Make sure to pause!)
To foster further growth and
peace in the Demon World,
the members of the Hellhorde spare
no effort working diligently daily,
in the area best suited to their talents.
* Take a breath. Calm yourself!
Among them, the people we recognize
today have made significant
contributions to the Hellhorde this quarter.
I'll knock 'em dead.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"Princess
Aside from Speed Form, the Hell-Lord
has multiple forms, such as Attack Form
and Defense Form
Meanwhile
Today is Sunday.
Since there's no torture today...
The gang is here for some bowling.
Why?
Good luck, Princess-chan.
Just relax.
Bowling? I know the rules, at least.
You throw the ball down there
and try to get the highest score, right?
That's right.
Your Highness?!
Go!
Prin-Prin
Vanillucky
Yes! I got a goal!
The G stands for "gutter ball."
Never seen a gutter ball like that.
You didn't know the rules at all, huh?
That's not it, Princess.
You don't launch the
ball through the air.
The objective is to roll the ball
to knock down the pins that are lined up.
Oh, really?
Let me show you how it's done.
I'll be taking over
for your second roll, Princess.
Second roll?
First, place your fingers inside the
ball's three holes and take position.
She's dead serious,
even when it's just a game.
The standard is a four-step approach.
That's the Senpai I know!
I'm learning so much!
Begin your swing on the second step.
Don't exert too much energy here.
Let the ball's weight do the work,
with your shoulder acting as a pivot.
On the third step, your arm
should reach its highest point.
On the fourth step, bend your left
knee as you firmly plant your foot.
Think of it as shifting your weight
from the right leg to the left one.
Follow through and release the ball.
Is it okay that you
didn't knock down any pins?
Isn't the point to knock them down?
Well? Well? Well?
Well?
Shut your mouth!
Huh? Why are you mad at me?
That one's on you, Princess-chan.
I agree.
Your Highness is at fault.
Prin-Prin
Vanillucky
So be it.
Let me, of the noble House of Peschutz,
teach you how it's played!
You brought your own ball and glove...
Are you a pretty experienced bowler?!
Nope! I just bought these!
So you just like to look the part!
Prin-Prin
Vanillucky
I wanted to look cool
in front of the princess...
Stay strong, Vanilla-senpai!
Sure.
Okay, let a former school basketball
player show you how it's really done.
We're not playing basketball.
Oh, but my bowling skills come
from being on the basketball team!
Family restaurants! Karaoke! Bowling!
The three main places you can find every
basketball player in the world!
You're insulting all
the basketball players!
Here I go! The true power of someone
who was on the basketball team!
Looking good.
Next I'll aim for the right,
with a little bit of spin...
Vanillucky
youk
In-In
Yeah! How do you like that?!
No real opinions
to offer one way or another.
Looks like I'm up next.
There!
In-chan threw it with both hands.
Is that allowed?
You're mostly free to throw
the ball however you like.
However, you'll find it's not so easy to
knock down the pins without proper form.
The only thing she has is proper form
Yes! Got a strike!
Th-The game's only just begun!
Yeah!
Hi-yah!
They all had fun.
Why?
Demon World Ristorante e Caffè
Sayizatso
Hell-Lord Pharmacy
Prescriptions Filled Here
Well? Did you find them?
I found the spot here with the eyeball...
That's where things start getting hard.
Oh, found it! Here!
What?
You're right! The clouds are different!
They also enjoyed
the spot-the-difference puzzle.
Seriously, why?
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
This is really amazing.
Nah, it's not a big deal...
Yoo-hoo. What are you up to?
Master Mama.
Vanilla, can I show this to Master Mama?
Sure...
The Elite Li'l Kitty
Look, Vanilla made this picture book!
What? That's amazing!
You published a picture book?
No, I found a printing service that
lets you print books in small batches,
so I used it to make this.
Wow, that's incredible.
The drawings are so cute.
I could swear it was professional.
It's my dream to put out
a real picture book someday.
That's great.
It just so happens that picture books
are why I'm here today.
What?
A Hellhorde employee in my year later
quit to become a picture book author.
He won a newcomer award some time ago,
so we're celebrating with drinks.
Gekkou...
You know him?
Y-Yeah...
They released his book that won
the award, so I read it, too.
I really liked it.
You follow his work!
I read about him in an interview.
He said that he wrote tons
of picture books while working.
I want to ask him about that...
If possible, I want him to read my book
and give me his thoughts.
But I'm sure I'd just be bothering him...
Would you like to meet Gekkou, then?
What?
I know he'd love to hear
how you felt about his book.
You could show him your
picture book as well.
No. It's fine.
Are you sure?
I'd be too embarrassed
to have him read it.
Oh...
I'll see you around.
Yeah!
Are you sure about this, Vanilla-chan?
I'd feel bad intruding
on their celebration.
The Elite Li'l Kitty
And the idea of showing it
to a pro author...
I just made this as a hobby...
For now, it's just a hobby,
not to mention it sucks.
And I don't have the talent...
I think it takes courage, not talent,
to make your dreams come true.
Giant!
Rats! She's gone!
Her long stride means she walks fast
when she's by herself!
Stomp
I've got this!
Master Mama!
G-Gekkou.
I-I liked your newcomer award-winning
book, What's a Ninja? a lot.
I really look up to you!
Look up to me? I'm not sure how to react.
Well, thank you.
I'm really glad to hear that.
A-And, well...
I-I wrote this picture book.
You wrote this?
Yes.
It's my dream to become
a picture book author like you.
Could you take a look at it?
Of course. It'd be an honor.
It's a wonderful thing to have a dream.
Yeah.
What's your dream, Master Mama?
My dream?
I don't have one!
Bam
You don't?
I'm happy just enjoying
every day to its fullest.
It's lovely having a dream,
but you can have fun without one.
Guess you're right.
Princess!
How'd it go?
I want to write more now!
And I'd love to read more from you!
The Elite Li'l Kitty
The Elite Li'l Kitty.
The elite li'l kitty was better
at everything than all the others.
She was always first by a mile!
Award
No one else could even hope
to compete with her.
But no matter how many times she
came in first or got compliments,
she still felt weird and wiggly inside.
Until one day...
The li'l kitty made a friend!
The li'l kitty had fun doing all
sorts of things with her friend.
The li'l kitty found out how happy
it made her being with someone else.
The End
The end.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Translation Check:
John K.
Edgar Cruz
Salem Alabanza
Alicia Ashby
Sho Stifler
Chuo Hellway
Hellholm
The National Inquisitors Conference
ran longer than scheduled,
and now it's gotten late.
Perhaps I should have booked a hotel,
like His Majesty suggested.
No, I was planning to go see
Mille-chan's baby tomorrow!
I must return home tonight!
A rest stop?
I should take a short break
and grab some coffee.
Rest stops these days are
getting more and more luxurious.
I haven't been to one with just bathrooms
and vending machines in ages.
Time for some coffee...
I-I don't believe it!
Hot snacks!
And this here is...
An instant noodle vending
machine you don't see anymore!
And one for soba and udon!
This is the last place one would expect
to find all this treasure!
Everything this world has to
offer is right here!
So this is where the One Piece was,
the greatest single treasure of them all!
Tasty potatoes deep-fried in oil.
Let's start with some french fries.
Open the lid, being careful
not to burn yourself...
Sprinkle the included salt
packet unevenly on purpose,
creating pockets of salty
and not-salty regions.
They're great.
You can really taste the potatoes.
So salty! Jackpot.
A way to enjoy fries that differs from
the calculated taste at a restaurant.
Next up is...
Soba & Udon
Some soba.
Tempura Udon
Tempura Soba
It's filled to the brim with broth.
These machines are old.
It adds to the charm.
It's delicious.
This soft and spongy mixed tempura...
I enjoy a good, crispy
tempura added at the end,
but when it gets soft
and soggy like this...
I love that, too!
I can feel the flavor filling my mouth!
This slightly cheap fish cake...
But for this soba...
Yep, this is fine. The best, even!
That was great.
There's nothing but trees around us,
so it's pitch-black outside.
A world of total natural darkness,
separated by bright artificial lights.
It feels like I'm on a spaceship.
I wanted to try some
instant noodles as well,
but I really have no room for them.
Even though instant noodles eaten outside
are thirty percent tastier.
Preferably with a fork
against convention.
I suppose I should get going.
Hot and ready in sixty seconds.
This is a souvenir.
A late-night snack.
You don't come across
a piece of treasure like this very often.
Just a little more driving,
and I'll be at Bonepile Junction.
Off we go!