Here's what you asked for.
You want me to make five
more just like this, right?
This boy's name is Sigma.
He's twelve years old.
He's ambitious and clever.
The parts are a bit stiff at first,
but they'll loosen with use.
He's the kind of person I'd want for
the royal accounting department...
Just let me know if
there are any problems.
Oh, there you are, Sei-san!
I've been looking for you.
I came to get this.
It's for you.
Huh? What for?
You'll be able to do
calculations faster with it.
I'll teach you how to use it.
So learn.
So this is for work after all...
My workload has only increased
since the expedition.
I no longer have time to double check
the accounting department's math.
As Aresh-sama said, I need to
be training the next generation.
Shiraishi-san still lives in the palace
but spends her days visiting the church.
Oh! My maids all complimented
you, Sei-san!
We need to finalize the plans
for the miasma observation project
before the purification is done.
They said the more they polished,
the more you sparkled!
We'll have to arrange the next expedition
carefully with that in mind.
They hope to take care of you
again in the future!
By the way, my father was
promoted from viscount to earl.
So now I'm the son of an earl!
Aren't you royalty to begin with?
Maybe I'll use my connections
and get promoted in no time!
You're going to be my boss?
I can't wait.
I-I was just kidding...
Well, I'm glad you're doing
better than I thought.
Huh? What do you mean?
Didn't Aresh-sama ask for you after
we got back from the expedition?
You looked so pale when you returned
that I was worried about you.
Oh...
I heard Seiichirou
stayed the night with you
and that you prepared him
an outfit for the banquet.
Yes.
You don't have to do that anymore.
Huh?
Don't do anything.
I'll take care of everything for him.
Oh, hang on, Sei-san!
Why don't you, uh... show me how
to use this for a bit over there?
I will later.
What are they doing in my room?
Huh?
Where's my pen?
Where are my work documents?
That's what you look for first?
Aresh-sama?
What in the world is going on?
I bought a house.
You're moving.
What?!
ISEKAI OFFICE WORKER: THE OTHER WORLD'S
BOOKS DEPEND ON THE BEAN COUNTER
EPISODE 7: I WENT ON
A TEMPORARY ASSIGNMENT
It's simple.
You're in dire need of my care since you'd
die the moment you leave my sight.
So there's nothing to worry
about if we live together.
But even then...
I can't believe they moved my
things while I wasn't here.
That was his doing. I've been tricked.
Let's head there now.
Listen, you can't suddenly
spring this on me...
But isn't everything
more efficient this way?
Don't think those are magic words
to make me do whatever you want!
Welcome home, milord.
Kondu-sama, I am the butler, Valtom.
And I am Milan, the maid.
H-Hello. My name is Kondou Seiichirou.
It's nice to meet you.
Let me show you to your room.
Come with me.
E-Er, I've never lived with
a maid or butler before...
Why not just pretend
you're staying at an inn?
Easy for a little rich boy
like you to say.
Here we are. This is your room.
Well? Do you like it?
It's so lavish that I'm uncomfortable.
Really?
There isn't any flashy decor,
and I chose a small, simple mansion
since it's just the two of us.
Yeah, well...
Call it a difference in values.
Oh, my pen and documents!
Thank goodness!
Well, it looks like it'll be
easy enough to work here.
Seiichirou, what kind of place
did you live in before this?
It was an ordinary dormitory-style
apartment with a single room.
The apartment I rented once I took a job
was just a place to sleep...
What kind of house were you born in?
My family lived in a two-story home.
The first floor had a living room,
a changing room, and a bathroom.
The second floor had three bedrooms.
Mine was on the southernmost side.
We also had a yard just big enough
to hang our laundry and futons.
Isn't that rather tiny?
Yes, well...
My country is a small one
without much land.
So that's normal for you?
Let's put your work on hold for today.
There are more important
things to tend to.
We still have three days before
the expedition, Aresh-sama.
The barrier is plenty effective
with one night of casting,
so there's no need to do it now.
Wouldn't spreading the
casting over three days
cause less magical energy strain on me,
leaving me better prepared
for the expedition?
Stop using reasonable
arguments I can't refute.
I'm just following your example.
Dinner is served.
I'm saved...
This is delicious.
I'm glad to hear it.
This is the cook, Pavel-san.
Apparently, he's an apprentice to the
owner of that hole-in-the-wall restaurant.
Your hands have stopped moving,
young master.
I keep telling you to
stop calling me that.
The butler, Valtom-san,
has served Aresh-sama at his
family estate since he was a kid.
Aresh-sama seems powerless against him.
Please allow me to clear
the empty plates.
Thank you.
The maid, Milan-san, returned
to work after raising her children.
Kondu-sama.
We will do our best to improve your
resistance and maintain your health.
Please let us know should you
have any requests from now on.
Thank you very much.
Here you go. This is quite nutritious.
Trimp...
TWO WEEKS LATER
When did you sneak in?
You're awake?
Aresh-sama, why do you sleep
in my bed every night?
Got a problem?
I thought I locked the door...
I've objected many times to no avail.
If I work too late into the night,
he drags me to bed.
Even though I already make sure
to retire before midnight.
In truth, I'm aware of what's going on.
He's using healing magic on my
magicule-weakened body every night.
Minor healing spells
can be cast via touch.
We've only gone all the way twice:
when I took too many tonics
and when I was assaulted.
Both were necessary "treatments,"
so there was no way around it.
I don't plan on letting anyone
else take care of you. Got it?
Sei-san!
Is there something on your mind?
No. More importantly,
what about the documents?
All flawless!
Thanks to this tool you gave me,
calculations have been a breeze!
Sounds like you can take on
a bit more work, then.
Ugh, I said too much!
The second expedition is now over.
If we successfully complete
the purification on the next,
we'll have the miasma and the damage
it's causing in each region under control.
Currently, the kingdom is prudently
allowing the holy maiden to rest,
so a date has not yet been set
for the third expedition.
Nevertheless, it should depart
within a month's time.
Next, we'll need to get a budget approved
to fund the research for our return home.
Even after delegating some of my work
to subordinates, there's lots to do.
And if I take work home, I can't get much
done thanks to a certain someone.
Still, we're making such smooth progress
because Aresh-sama is coordinating
with other departments in advance.
Aresh-sama...
Returning home, huh?
That will mean leaving
Aresh-sama's side...
Looks like I really need to think
about things seriously soon.
Sei-san! Sei-san!
His Excellency is calling for you!
Huh?
Prime Minister!
What's the matter, Commander Indolark?
What do you mean, what's the matter?!
Why are you sending someone from the
accounting department to the church?
The person in question has
already agreed. Isn't that right?
Quite correct.
Well, to start, why don't you have a seat?
There's nothing to worry about.
Seichiro's tea was specially
prepared for him.
Aresh-sama, as I explained yesterday,
I'm being sent to the church
to investigate,
as they've yet to submit their
income and expenses report.
I understand that.
However, there's no reason
why it has to be you.
It was my decision.
Seichiro was the most suitable person
to handle the miasma project.
The church houses sacred relics.
Several barriers are cast on them, and
the magicule concentration there is high.
The likes of you have no business there.
And yet Seichiro survived the
demon forest without any issues.
That was...
First things first, Commander Indolark...
As the commander of the third royal
order and the son of an earl,
you should be more aware
of your powerful influence.
What?
I understand you're
worried about Seichiro,
but your favoritism is so
obvious that it's troubling.
Seichiro is planning the miasma
countermeasures on my orders...
At least, that's the story on paper.
If you side with him on top of that,
he gains enough political power
to breed unnecessary resentment.
He has a point...
He'll only be commuting
to the church for a month.
I'm sure any dishonorable rumors about
the third order will die down by then.
Aresh-sama, it's not a bad deal.
If I secure the church's cooperation,
we'll make great strides
toward the miasma countermeasures
and relocation magic research.
When Aresh-sama casts off
his commander persona,
he sometimes looks a bit childish.
What are you laughing about?
Your hair is still damp.
How many times have I told
you to dry it properly?
I'd say I dried it thoroughly enough.
How so? Good grief.
What a nice fragrance.
The accounting department
seems to like it, too.
There, it's dry.
Thank you very much.
I'm not angry.
But when even mere wind magic
like this makes you feel sick,
why do you keep choosing to go
places that are dangerous to you?
Honestly...
The church has a special barrier
around it and, above all,
the act of prayer releases
magical energy.
It's a hostile environment for you
on par with the demon forest.
Regardless, I had no choice but to accept.
Then please ensure that I'm extra safe.
Ninety percent of the Romany people are
monotheistic and worship the god Abran.
This place is thirty minutes by carriage
from the Romany palace.
It has about fifteen clergymen.
Even including the caretakers in
the orphanage run by the church,
the staff still numbers under twenty.
This is such a large church that
it's probably safe to assume some
of its operation is outsourced.
He applied a very thorough
barrier yesterday.
I'll be fine. Just fine.
Nice to meet you.
I'm from the accounting department.
My name is Kondou Seiichirou.
Please lend me your—
No way am I helping you out, old man.
What are you standing
around for? Hurry it up.
Um, I'd like to meet whoever's in charge.
The priest is busy.
He doesn't have time for you.
Then may I speak to the person
in charge of accounting?
Not happening. Everyone's busy.
I'm here on official orders from the
royal palace to conduct an inspection.
Did you hear that?
This arrogant man thinks he has
the right to inspect the church!
Civil servants from the palace
are really something else!
No matter how you look at it,
I'm not welcome here.
But this is my job.
Even the church won't get away
with refusing to cooperate.
In any case, no one here
is going to work with you.
Just do whatever you want
until your time is up.
Oh?
So I can do whatever I want?
Is this the library?
Their management of it is terrible...
I reviewed their income and expenses
reports from prior years,
but so much of them was unclear based on
the old accounting department standards.
What are you doing here?
A white robe indicates either royalty
or a churchman ranking priest or higher.
I'm sorry for intruding.
My name is Kondou Seiichirou, and I'm here
from the royal accounting department.
The royal accounting department?
What business does a civil servant
have with the church?
A church leader doesn't even
know about the inspection?
We haven't received your income
and expenses report from this branch,
so I was ordered to come conduct an audit.
Our income and expenses report?
That can't be...
He's been kept in the dark, then.
Why is a civil servant from the accounting
department alone in the library?
Was no accountant or
guide assigned to you?
Someone greeted me when I arrived,
but I was simply told to do as I please,
so I began my investigation.
What? Who was your guide?
Now, what should I do?
I took that boy at his word.
Either way, there's no
reason to protect him.
I didn't get his name,
but he was a boy around thirteen or
fourteen years old with green hair.
Selio, was it?
Selio, come to the
reference room at once.
I've yet to introduce myself.
I am the priest here at the Romany royal
capital branch of the Church of Abran.
My name is Siegvold.
I was away at another branch for a few
days, so I didn't realize the situation...
I apologize for the rude reception.
I thought everyone connected
to the church disliked me,
but this man seems different.
However, this room is where
we keep important documents
and literature valuable to the church.
Outsiders are not permitted to view them.
I apologize for trespassing
without realizing that.
I'd like to once again request permission
to conduct my inspection.
S-Siegvold-sama, did you call for—
What're you doing here?!
Selio.
It won't do to run around
the church recklessly.
I-I'm sorry.
Is this who greeted you?
Yes.
Selio.
I wasn't informed of any inspection
from the royal palace.
Who instructed you to meet with him?
I... I...
Bishop Mateus sent me a message and...
And?
Th-This guy did this all on his own!
This civil servant is visiting
our church for the first time,
so he has no way of knowing
which areas are off-limits.
Was it not your job to guide
him on such matters?
W-Well, there's just so much to do...
More important than guiding this
civil servant through the church?
N-No...
Why did you leave the room?
I went to call you for lunch,
but you weren't there...
You told me to do as I pleased.
That was just a figure of speech!
Selio, lower your voice.
Be that as it may,
please understand that certain areas
are restricted within the church.
I understand.
Neglecting to tell me which areas
demonstrates their naïveté.
Everything is without lock or caretaker,
just like this unguarded library.
It is already the second earth hour.
I bid you to call it a day.
In that case, I will return tomorrow.
Selio, please see him out.
You disappeared from that room,
so I thought you went home already...
Well, I'll be off now.
I'll be watching you starting tomorrow!
Don't think you get the run of the place!
It'd be better if you just
don't come back at all!
Bishop Mateus and Priest Siegvold, huh?
You're late.
Aresh-sama... you're home early.
Isn't part of your job finishing
tasks within work hours?
How are you feeling?
Perfectly fine.
And your mood?
Not bad.
Are you hungry?
No, not really...
Let's take a bath.
Huh?
I'll recast your barrier there.
H-Hey! Wait—
How was it at the church?
I could hardly call it comfortable.
As expected.
But you're still going back
tomorrow, right?
Yes. That's my job.
Aresh-sama, thank you for casting
the barrier spell on me.
I'll try my best to be home
on time starting tomorrow.
Just don't push yourself too hard.
Okay.
It's not just me.
Everyone in this mansion
is worried about you.
That's why you have to come home safely.
Seiichirou, you aren't alone.
Right... Thank you.
EPISODE 8
I WENT TO WORK ON MY DAY OFF