Episode 12
This day was bound to come eventually.
Go on!
Huh?
Remember, come back immediately
once you confirm this is fake.
These are all the magical
artifacts you gave me before.
Take them for self-defense.
Sister!
I... I shouldn't have doubted you!
I don't know why!
Really! I really didn't want to doubt you!
All right.
Just remember to come back quickly.
I will!
Sorry to trouble you three with this.
Three days have passed since
the so-called execution day.
I don't think Ma Xianhong is stupid
enough to fall for this trap.
Do we still need to wait?
Are you guys still waiting?
Because of the mole?
The intel we're sending back might
reach the killer and Ma Xianhong.
They might let their guard down.
That's the plan, right?
Heh, and also take a few extra days off.
What if he actually shows up?
Won't you be in danger?
Zhang, you were seriously hurt, right?
That's why I brought two masters along.
Don't worry, if he brings people along,
I'll escape through the secret
passage in the bunker.
I see... As long as you
know what you're doing.
Take care.
We look forward to good news!
How likely do you think it is
you'll win this bet?
Not very likely...
The odds of Ma coming here to check on
the Shanggenqi Mutants are very low.
But the odds of him coming
to find me are very high,
because I added
a bit of extra information.
Something no one but Ma would notice.
Hey, Ma, remember the black
puppet that got smashed?
I, Zhang Chulan, did that!
The black puppet
shouldn't have been there.
Adding that changes the
entire message's meaning.
Ma, this stupid trap was
set by me, Zhang Chulan.
I went to all this trouble just to leave
a message that only you can understand.
Well, we'll leave after today.
You might not come here,
but I don't think you'll sit
still after seeing that message.
As long as you're still alive
and everyone's looking for you,
it's best to meet
in this godforsaken place.
Zhang Chulan, you want to see me, right?
I have a score to settle with you too!
You are...
Damn! Seeing that face right now
makes me want to beat the crap out of him!
Control my expression!
Control my expression carefully!
Never mind who I am.
I heard you guys dealt with my friends.
I'm just here to figure out why!
I can't tell you the specifics,
but suffice to say it's
a complete fabrication!
In a week at most, you'll be
able to contact your friends.
If you don't believe me,
I can take you inside for a look.
It doesn't sound like a lie.
That does put my mind at ease.
But you captured them just because
of a guy called Ma Xianhong?
Is that true?
Who is this Ma Xianhong guy?
My friends never mentioned him...
Are you Ma Xianhong?
Someone he sent?
No way!
I've never heard of that guy.
That... that was close!
I thought he realized!
No? If not, why only come after
the execution day has passed?
Whatever. If Ma didn't send you,
then never mind what I'm about to say.
But if you do know him,
and don't want something
bad to happen to him,
then pass on this message.
He's in grave danger now.
He needs to contact me,
in whatever way he deems safe.
But he must contact me.
All right, let's eat.
Thanks!
Ma Xianhong, here's yours...
Ah, no thanks.
Bao'er, what did you just call him?
Ma Xianhong. Isn't this the guy
you've been waiting for?
No... but his face, height...
Yeah, apart from the face and height,
nothing much has changed.
Still the same smell, strong and pungent.
Bro!
I've been waiting here for ages!
Zhang Chulan! Get up!
Aren't you my god-uncle?
I can't accept this!
That was just me running my mouth, Bro!
You have to forgive your
mischievous little brother!
Bao'er! Didn't I tell you to prepare Bro
so he can dish out some discipline?
Give it to him!
Here!
Bao'er, do you have a grudge against me?
Bro, for the sake of our elders,
please spare my life!
If you could remove the
thorns from the stick,
I would be even more grateful!
The Heaven Communicating
Talisman was easier to learn...
Turn around!
Okay, Bro!
I told you to turn around and stand up!
Zhang Chulan! Don't think I'll let you off
because you're being shameless! Get up!
You have to go the extra
mile to correct a mistake!
I don't know how else I can
convince you I mean you no harm.
Have a look at this.
I bet he won't come!
I'm not betting.
Ma Xianhong, if you did come,
well, we're not here anymore.
We didn't do this to catch you.
Zhang Chulan just wanted to see you.
If you're looking to settle scores
with Zhang Chulan,
make sure Bao'er records
a video for us to enjoy.
But the kid really
doesn't owe you anything,
either in principle or in practice.
If you really do lay into him...
Ah, never mind.
Forget what I said.
I'm not very good at threatening people.
Zhang Chulan, you went through
all this trouble just to see me.
What exactly do you want?
To have a heart-to-heart conversation...
Bro, I'm getting up, I'm getting up!
Go ahead. Since you want to talk,
I'll listen to what you have to say.
Our conversation back in the
village wasn't finished, right?
I told you my story.
Now I want to hear yours.
Are you trying to pump me for information?
I just want to hear about
your past with your family,
and about how you lost your memory.
Before my grandfather died, he said that
he masterminded the Jiashen rebellion.
But in my memory, he never
complained about his situation.
He didn't see himself as a victim.
He felt he deserved it.
Isn't that interesting?
I really envy you.
At least you got to spend a
few years with Master Zhang.
I never met my great-grandfather,
but I often heard my
grandfather talk about him.
Hey, Xianhong! Daydreaming again?
Why have you been staring at
that thing so much lately?
Bro, haven't you guys noticed...?
I told you to leave Xianhong alone.
He's always been like that.
Who in the village even plays with him?
I think Xianhong's got a screw
loose from being alone too much.
You two little rascals!
What are you saying?
Grandfather!
Tell me, what's wrong with Xianhong?
Hey, Grandfather, didn't you make
a bead for everyone in the family?
Xianhong said if you stare at that
thing long enough, it'll glow!
Huh? What do you mean, Father?
You want Xianhong to learn from you?
Grandfather, did you make all of these?
Hmm, do you want to learn
how to make these with me?
Yes!
Your great-grandfather taught
me how to make these.
Back then, he said,
"Yuanlu, you know...
I'm not qualified to pass this on to you.
I'm not worthy!"
He also said,
"Yuanlu, I understand
all these principles,
but I still can't get
past this mental barrier.
These skills were created by my own hands,
and I really don't want them
to die out there.
Back then, I was too young to understand
what your great-grandfather meant.
It wasn't until I fully inherited
his techniques that I realized.
"I can't bear to let them be lost either!"
I was just a kid back then.
How could I have understood
what he was talking about?
From then on, I lived with
Grandpa and learned from him.
Looking back, I think he was
testing me in every way,
but he was also hesitant.
If only you weren't cut out for it,
or if Master Yuanlu had been
ruthless and let it die out,
we wouldn't have so many problems today.
Zhang Chulan, I think you're heartless.
What are you talking about?
Go on! Continue, continue!
Grandfather! Look at mine!
How's this? Check out this work!
It's not finished yet!
I've only been learning from
my father for a few days.
What do you think?
Better than Xianhong, right?
Why don't you teach me too?
Go on, get out of here!
Your old man's skills are more
than enough to teach you!
Xianhong, everyone else
has already finished.
Why are you still fiddling
with this one part?
Grandfather, maybe I'm really
just not cut out for this?
I wasn't trying to compete with Xianhe.
But now that I've started,
I can't let this material down...
Let this material down?
Yeah. Once this material is in my hands,
what it ultimately becomes
is entirely up to me.
I've seen good things.
Your products are all
good things. They glow.
Anything that passes through my hands,
even the tiniest component,
if I don't see that light, I won't let go.
Xianhong,
all these years, I've been watching you.
Today, I will pass on to you the true
skills your great-grandfather taught me.
But you must swear to me!
Never show anyone the artifacts
created using the methods I teach you!
You may only use them when you
and our family are in danger!
And after that?
You didn't follow Master Yuanlu's words,
and revealed Divine Craftsmanship.
I didn't.
Until those people came for us,
I always kept my promise to Grandfather.
Grandfather, what happened?
Someone chopped off his leg!
Father!
Grandfather, what's the matter?
Xianhong, go get my...
my tools and yours, and bring them here.
Then come see me.
The rest of you, get out!
All of you, out!
Grandfather, I've brought
everything you asked for.
Who on earth did this to you?
I don't know them!
Xianhong, take the family and leave!
Escape now! Don't worry about me.
How could I...
I'd never abandon you, Grandfather!
Grandfather!
Go! They're coming...
They're coming to
steal Divine Craftsmanship.
Your great-grandfather Benzai
passed away so many years ago.
I was careless! They never gave up!
Xianhong, you must understand
how dangerous this is for us!
They haven't made their next move yet.
They're giving me a chance!
They want me to hand over
Divine Craftsmanship!
Don't worry about me.
Run, all of you! Run as far as you can!
I'm just a burden to you now!
No way! Either we leave together,
or I'll stay behind and
fight them with you!
I'm not leaving you alone here.
So stubborn!
You're a good kid in every way,
but so stubborn!
Fine then, let's go see the others first.
Hey, sir, why are you getting up?
You can't be discharged yet!
We're here.
Grandfather, slow down!
Let me help you!
No need!
If I need help just to walk,
then I'm really a burden to you!
What happened after?
You and Master Yuanlu went home.
What happened next?
I've already told you what I can tell you.
So that means...
you lost the memories of
your family from then on.
You can't tell me
what happened after that.
The memories after that
must be related to the people
we're up against, right?
What exactly are you trying to say?
I need to confirm something first,
in case you were involved.
Did you do this?
No.
What about Guo Liang?
Have you ever suspected
the people around you?
I see.
Zhang Chulan, you're here to sow discord.
Something's wrong with Ma
Xianhong's current condition.
Any normal person would
definitely be suspicious
if they went through what he did.
Unless I can figure out what the
people behind Ma did to him,
I won't be able to get him
to come over to our side.
Calm down! I'm just here to pass on a
message from our Company's Chairman Zhao.
Chairman Zhao? Zhao Fangxu?
Zhang Chulan. I mobilized
the Company's resources
and went to all this trouble to help
you carry out this entrapment plan.
And now you want me to let him go?
And call off
the Company's manhunt for him?
How does the Company benefit from that?
If Ma Xianhong really shows up,
it proves there's a rift between
him and the people behind him.
That's already a gain from this operation.
To deal with someone like Ma Xianhong,
you need to show goodwill.
You have to win him over!
I understand what you mean.
But why would I go to all this trouble?
I heard that Chou Rang still
hasn't backed down, right?
Do you think you can handle his idol
Ma Xianhong with forceful methods?
I've given this some consideration.
What if we can get the
Lyu family to cooperate,
and use their Bright Soul Skill?
What's wrong, Zhang?
Why are you laughing?
Nothing, I didn't realize you'd
already given this so much thought.
Are you being sarcastic?
Of course not!
You're a big shot with
unparalleled foresight!
You handle things far more
thoroughly than us small fry!
Cut the crap. Tell me!
What do you really think?
It's a good idea.
Bright Soul Skill might even
help Ma recover his memories.
But if we just grab him
and mess with his head,
then after that, we'd have
to lock him up forever,
or kill him.
Given Ma's character,
he'd definitely become the
Company's mortal enemy.
So what? What's that got to do with you?
That's what I'm saying!
What influence could a
little ant like me have?
I'll follow your orders.
Chairman Zhao?
I've always wondered,
what did Master Xu see in you?
Are you teasing me?
I'm not teasing you.
I'm afraid of you, big shot!
Big shots have foresight,
and they often don't notice
the little ants at their feet.
But it's usually the little ants
that can bite the big shots!
If I really handled
Ma Xianhong so brutally,
would you be disappointed in me?
I'd be surprised.
I don't think someone like that
would've joined Master
Xu in protecting Bao'er.
All right, I'll consider what you said.
But there are two conditions.
First, you need to confirm that you
didn't kill any Company personnel.
Second, the conflict between you and the
Company isn't completely resolved yet.
After we deal with the current situation,
we can sit down and discuss
the matters regarding
Divine Craftsmanship and
the Cultivation Furnace.
In the meantime, you can go anywhere,
and the Company won't
consider you a fugitive.
Oh, right. I heard you're
looking for your family?
When it comes to finding people,
the Company is definitely more capable
than you and your companions.
What do you think?
In the end, you're still
trying to sow discord,
to pick us off one by one, right?
You're thinking the worst of us.
But Ma, you're not so powerful that
the Company can't handle things
without getting rid of you.
I genuinely don't want you to go
down with the people behind you.
You're actually a decent person.
Have I ever done anything bad?
I heard you're looking for your family?
When it comes to finding people,
the Company is definitely more capable
than you and your companions.
Think about it carefully...
Ma!
You really screwed me
over back in the village.
Zhang Chulan,
I can't trust a word you say anymore.
That's right.
That's right, Ma!
We've only met a few times in total.
You have no reason to trust me!
Your lost memories and
missing family might be
connected to the people around you now!
Don't believe that either!
Zhang Chulan, are you saying Sister—
Never mind, Ma!
That's not the point.
The point is, I can't be
trusted, and not just me!
Don't trust anyone!
Don't trust anyone?
Don't trust anyone...
Ma, you...
Zhang Chulan!
I'm fine!
Don't move!
Catch.
This is... a magical artifact?
What's it for? How do I use it?
Ma!
Don't follow me!
Let me think alone for a while.
At least leave a phone number, Ma!
What's wrong, Zhang Chulan?
What are you thinking?
Like you said, Ma Xianhong
really did show up,
and he didn't turn on you.
Haven't you achieved your objectives?
No, something's wrong.
Master Lingyu, Bao'er,
a slight change of plans.
Go after him! Go after Ma Xianhong!