Hello. Who is this?
Hi!
Oh, Kayama. Haven't heard
from you in a while.
So, how's life as a teacher treating you?
It's really fulfilling!
My students are all so
adorable and motivated.
The material has been
incredible to teach, too.
You learn so much yourself
when you're teaching.
There's just something about a school.
It feels like a place where you belong.
If you say so. Can't say I was ever a fan.
Don't remember school being a lot of fun.
No sense in being picky, though.
It's a job.
Not my job, though.
It's going to be.
You'll be teaching in the hero course,
here at our alma mater, U.A. High School.
That's a really strange
thing to suddenly assume.
Yamada's going to be working
here next semester.
After that, it's just a matter
of you answering the call.
I don't appreciate the idea of
being tied at the hip to him.
Besides, I don't think I've ever said
anything about wanting to be a teacher.
Yamada mentioned something—
that you need someone pushing you,
or you never make up your mind.
Then pass a message to him from me: "You
need to learn to keep your mouth shut."
I personally get the feeling that you're
trying to ignore something important, too.
Let me rephrase: You both need to
learn to keep your mouths shut.
Come on, I'm trying to have a serious—
I'm on patrol right now and need to go.
Unbelievable. And completely irrational.
Okay, time to get to work.
flashback
Recollections of the past.
During a story, they will sometimes act as an
interlude to show what happened prior to current events, as in a "flashback scene."
Rain and Clouds
I love bullying the weak!
Like little kids! And kittens!
Little Red Riding Hood over
there better watch herself!
I'll lead him away! Grab the cat and run!
Hey, there! Get a load of me!
You look like prey, too!
I'm right over here!
Thanks, Eraser! That was a nice save.
What are you doing, man?
Well, I was sliding along when...
What's up? Is something wrong over there?
And when we were trying to decide what
to do, he showed up out of nowhere.
What?! A cat?! Let me at it!
And then he attacked us.
Well, that's simple enough.
Thanks for saving me!
Take good care of the kitty!
You be careful on your way home!
Yeah, hello? This is Eraser
Head, the pro hero.
I've caught a thug,
and he needs to be taken in.
Right. I sent to the location over GPS,
so if you could confirm...
Looks like it's about to start pouring.
So, what's the plan for the cat?
Well, I guess I'll take it
back to my place for now.
You gonna keep it?
Er, I hadn't really decided.
You'll need to feed it and
clean up after it daily.
Can you handle training?
Not to mention vaccinations
and getting it fixed.
And if it gets sick, a vet
can cost more than a doctor.
You're a student, right?
Will you be able to look after it
even after you've graduated?
On the longer end, cats can
live up to twenty years.
Are you prepared for
that kind of responsibility?
I honestly can't imagine that far ahead...
If you can't look after it,
then don't drag it around.
Go put it back where you found it.
Do you... not like cats?
That's not why I'm telling you all this.
It's just, you haven't looked
at it for a while now.
No sense in getting attached.
If you can't take responsibility for it,
then you shouldn't get involved.
You're pretty level-headed, Eraser.
It's not like that.
I just know my limitations.
I'm not All Might.
There's a limit to the amount of
power that a single person has.
And in my case, I still
don't amount to that much.
I've felt that way ever since I was a kid.
Whether I wanted to or not.
What happened to you?
Forget your umbrella?
Well, it's time for morning assembly,
so hurry and get changed.
No, it's fine.
It matches my state of mind.
Whatever that's supposed to mean.
And what happens if you get sick
because of your state of mind?
Staying healthy is part of your job as a
student, and the path to becoming a hero.
Yes, sir.
This "path to becoming a hero" stuff.
Can't even picture it.
I'm powerless.
And there it is!
Shota Aizawa's pity party!
Class 2-A
Hizashi Yamada (Age 16)
Hey, yo, are you seriously spiraling
first thing in the morning?!
It was so funny! Let me run it back
for everybody one more time!
According to young Aizawa:
"I'm... powerless."
Put a sock in it.
You're hilarious, bro! Negative!
Passive! Could use a sanative!
So obnoxious...
Whoa, there, Hizashi!
What're you picking on Shota for?
How could you? You're unbelievable!
Don't start in on him without me!
Dammit, Shirakumo, where do you
think you're coming in from?!
Sir! A third-story window, sir!
My Quirk, Cloud, is handy
for getting around!
I don't care what your Quirk is,
you're supposed to enter the
classroom through the door!
Yes, sir!
Now sit down already!
I need to take attendance.
Hey! Anybody got a towel?
I'm soaked!
Yeah!
Get a move on!
Also, Shota.
This is your umbrella, right?
I found it.
Shirakumo, was the umbrella with a...
Hey, hey, Oboro!
Whacha stripping for?!
Do you know how nasty wet underwear feels?
Cover up already!
You freak!
Don't you folks worry!
Feast your eyes upon this clever
application of my Cloud Quirk...
Just when it looks like you're
gonna see something, you can't!
Pushing the fluffy envelope!
And there's the most lovely
little creature inside...
You need to knock that off, now!
There's girls in here too, y'know!
You suck, Shirakumo!
Go to hell!
Ta-da!
So cute!
Come on, Oboro, I can't believe
you picked up another one!
All right, attendance! Starting at
the top of the roll with the boys!
Aizawa!
Here.
The rain stopped.
Ooizu.
I still don't amount to much.
Yo.
Katasugi.
Sir!
Kuga.
Not that I ever really expect to.
Yep.
Sarudo.
Here!
Shirakumo.
I couldn't even save a single cat.
Tendo.
Yeah!
Niragi.
Here...
Fujimi.
Mushimori.
Here.
Yamada.
Yeah!
Pipe down, Yamada.
That sense of resignation I felt...
It started to gradually change
in the summer of my second
year in high school.
Now then, as with every year,
the majority of students in their second year
will undertake a work study
over summer vacation.
Which means, even if it's
in a learning capacity,
you're going to be working
alongside pro heroes.
So be on your best behavior!
For those of you who haven't secured
a spot yet, start thinking about it.
Aizawa. Shirakumo. Yamada.
I'm talking about you three,
do you get that?
Yes, sir.
Right.
Yeah!
Pipe down, Yamada.
All right, I want all of you in your
costumes and over at the training grounds.
We're going to be working with
Class B on practical exercises.
This'll be a chance for you all to
verify your strengths and weaknesses.
For those of you further along,
I want you to shore up your weaknesses
before the work studies begin.
For those lagging, try and get a feel for
what you want to do with yourselves.
We'll start with 1-on-1 combat practice.
Begin!
Your opponents will be randomized!
Make use of what makes you special!
Whoa, there!
Yeah!
Time for rescue training!
Teamwork is crucial in
a crisis environment!
Make sure to execute on
your individual roles!
There's still folks over there!
Dance lessons!
Heroes are representatives for
multiple aspects of society!
Without popularity, you can't expect
commissions, which means nothing to do!
You need to express yourselves,
and in a way that will win their hearts!
Days later
Faculty Room
How did things go with the three of them?
The ones who don't have work studies?
I think Yamada will be fine.
Yeah!
His Voice Quirk has plenty
of applications, whether in combat,
rescue, or entertainment.
That kind of versatility might make it
hard for him to settle on a specialty.
But in the future, that could just mean
that he'll end up wearing many hats.
As for Shirakumo,
his grades aren't remarkable,
but he's got a bright, positive attitude.
Hey!
He'll probably march to his own drum,
no matter what he ends up doing.
That just leaves Aizawa...
Well, I think he's trying very hard.
He gets above-average grades in both
practical training and his studies.
But I will say that
for as hard as he tries,
I think he doesn't have an image
of what he wants to accomplish.
And until he figures that out,
it's going to work against him
in terms of finding employment.
With a Quirk like his... makes
me wonder if that's part of it.
That reminds me, in combat
practice the other day...
You are such a pain, Aizawa!
I don't care what that Erasure
of yours is supposed to do,
but I hate the way you wipe out a Quirk
and then you start whipping
that nasty rag of yours around!
When you're involved,
the battles get lamer.
Which makes me look bad!
Not to mention, there's no
point in any of that crap
if you can't actually stand
your ground in a fist fight!
So knock it off with the
stupid gimmicks already!
That's enough, Sensoji!
You all right, Aizawa?
Yessir.
What does he want from me?
That's just how my Quirk works.
At the end of the day, my Erasure just
makes things harder for other people.
It's not like I'm producing
anything positive.
Much less making anyone else happy.
So, all this stuff about making
the most of your Quirk,
what its applications are, and
what I want to do with it...
I really don't have a clue.
Why not just make life
harder for villains, then?
Focusing on combat?
Sure doesn't fit his image.
Well, with superhuman combat, it often
boils down to how Quirks interact.
But with your Erasure, it doesn't matter!
It'll always boil down
to regular melee combat.
That's a talent!
I'm not exactly good at
melee combat, though.
Especially when going against big guys.
Hey, hold on.
You can't give people food
to cats. It's bad for them.
Oh, okay.
Glad I had some spare cat formula.
I don't really approve of you bringing
him to school like this, but...
Well, it's better than leaving him
alone at home all day, right?
And you're here at school
to look out for him.
How's he been doing his business?
Everything alright there?
Most of the time, he just
goes on my gym clothes!
You got me again!
That's so nasty!
You really need to take
care of housetraining.
Well, hello there, boys.
Enjoying your lunch up here?
It's that third-year!
Kayama!
She's so cool!
You know the roof's
supposed to be off-limits.
Did you come here without permission?
That kind of rule-breaking...
is awesome! It just screams "youthful!"
And what brings you up here?
I was on my way back from my work study,
and had some paperwork at
the school to take care of.
As for why I'm on the roof specifically...
I love it up here!
You're a real rule-breaker yourself!
I've gotta ask...
Are you not gonna wear
anything under that coat?
It's my costume!
Is it some kind of material
that's invisible to idiots?
Like the empress's new clothes,
or something?
Nice snark!
I love being an idiot!
Because she looks naked to me!
Hooray! Hooray!
You just don't get it...
It's as bold as it is practical!
And provides the perfect kind of
support for my Quirk and how I move!
This design that I came up with
by focusing on all those elements
is the very model of functional beauty!
I have absolutely nothing
to be ashamed of!
Maybe you should take another look at it.
Shota!
Quit trying to ruin the awesomeness!
If you see something this beautiful,
and find it to be shameful?
It just reflects the
shame in your own heart!
Well, I can't blame him for
thinking that way at the moment.
It's the fate of people who are
always on the cutting edge.
But you wait and see!
In one year, I'll have redefined
what's acceptable to wear in Japan!
Fun fact: in one year,
there will be a legal debate
about the acceptable level of
exposure in hero costumes.
The law changed before what
people considered acceptable!
I guess I was too much of a pioneer!
Never mind me, though,
What's up with the kitten?
It's...
Shota and I found him!
That doesn't mean you can
bring him to school.
Let me see!
Where'd you come from, little kitty?
Will rubbing your belly-welly
make you all sleepy-weepy?
This is kinda embarrassing.
Does he have a name?
Uh, well...
Not yet.
Well, what are your favorite foods?
Sushi!
Fried chicken!
I'm, uh, not particular.
Out of those, I think I'd go with sushi.
And you're a fancy piece
of sushi, aren't you?!
I'm gonna eat you up!
We're looking for a permanent
home for him, too!
Well, unfortunately, I'm going
to move out once I graduate,
so I won't have the time
to take care of him.
They say that single women with cats
have a harder time getting married.
That's what you're worried about...?
So, I won't be able to foster him for long!
Make sure to find a real
owner for him soon, okay?!
This is one of those situations where
she ends up keeping him, isn't it?
Yea.
The next day
I still think it was irresponsible to
hand over a living being so casually.
It's Kayama. It'll be fine.
Besides, we're not really in a
position to be looking after a cat.
You mean the work studies?
I heard Yamada just got his sorted out.
Some kind of combat-oriented agency...
He's getting the details in
the faculty room right now.
Wouldn't have pegged him
for a combat-type.
When it comes to public speaking,
he even has his own podcast.
They say the work studies are about
getting the kind of experience
you wouldn't be able to
have on your own.
I guess if you go around fighting on
your own, you're basically just a thug.
Oh, there you are! It's the roof gang!
Hey there, Kayama.
Thanks for looking after the cat!
Here's what Sushi was up to today.
Oh, that was a big poopie!
What a good boy!
You can see that we're eating, right?
You were worried about toilet
training though, right?
So, that's why you came
to show us the video?
Not exactly.
I needed to tell you
that I've got a home
for anyone who doesn't
have a place to belong.
It's not like we're picking
up stray cats every day.
That's not what I meant!
My boss says that anyone who doesn't have
a work study can come work with us.
And when you say your boss...
He's the boss of the agency
that I'm doing my work study at!
The head of the Purple
Revolution Agency!
The noble hero, His Purple Highness!
What do you think?
Think... about what?
He seems like quite a character, actually.
Oh, that's the best part!
You... think so?
I remember what he said to me.
"What we can't do alone,
we can manage, together."
Next time: Glass Sky.
The clouds that were blocking the sky
from view... are starting to clear up.