Pawn Shop
Hoppers
And this happened at a mixer?
Right.
Out of the instant villain incidents
over the last few weeks,
we've had several people testify
to having attended a mixer
with a group of female college students.
I guess I see it.
The dealer inserts themselves into
a casual get-together like that.
Might be an ideal situation for
handing out samples of a drug.
I put together a list of students
who were hosting these kinds of
things from area universities.
I was hoping you could look
into the Naruhata group.
I'm gonna have to politely decline.
Parties, celebrations... never really
did well with that kinda thing.
This is your job.
You can't be picky about it.
I'm just trying to say, I know someone
better suited to this kind of work.
All of the boys attending are with Narufest.
We don't need to check them out.
Among the two girls, Rin Yaritezawa
here is our main target.
She's been a witness to a few incidents
so far. A real person of interest.
I appreciate you doing this. It's a lot to
ask since I just ran into you.
It's really all right.
I got invited to a mixer with
the guys from the Mad Hatters!
Man, what am I gonna do?
Being able to help you
is an honor, Midnight.
Pop, I'd like you to talk
to the shy girl, Hina.
Just make small talk and keep her occupied.
That'll let me focus on checking Rin out.
All right, let's do this, Pop—I mean, Kazuha.
Right, Mid... er, Kaori.
team up
When multiple individuals work together.
Usually in the form of cooperating towards a mutual goal.
The Man Returns
Ringotaro Pub
All right, is everybody drinking?
Because I sure am!
Yeah!
This is really something.
I've never actually been to one of
these before. It's kinda overwhelming.
Me too. I usually just tag along with Rin...
So, I kinda feel out of place.
How do you and Rin know each other?
We've always been together...
I am not having any fun at all!
I know! I brought our latest CD.
They might be a band.
They're playing at department stores!
How lame is that?
We're really proud of this new one.
Tell me about it!
And then this guy. I don't
even know what his deal is.
I mean, sure, I know a lot of people.
I'm good at making contact
and organizing stuff...
And as a result people started making a
fuss about the "Yaritezawa Connection."
So everyone starts assuming
that I'm a friend-of-a-friend!
Don't be shy, now.
Oh, that's okay.
Now I have to deal with these strangers
That's impressive!
showing up out of nowhere
after some cancellations...
This weird chick has taken the wheel!
Someone's a big drinker!
Plus, they all look
like they're loving it!
Do I even need to be here, really?
For all the effort I put in,
I still don't have a boyfriend.
Off to the bathroom? Don't fall in!
Koichi! What is wrong with you, man?!
Lay her down facing up,
and get a cushion for her head!
I'll get a server!
Is she okay?
Are you all right?
S-Sorry...
Don't worry about it!
I'm good at this kinda thing.
Just relax.
Women
What? What was that?
What do they think they're doing?
They think they can all get
together to fawn over Rin?
I'm the one... it's me... It's my job
and only my job to look after Rin.
And that guy—
Let me wipe that pretty mouth of yours.
Is he trying to seduce my Rin or something?!
Unacceptable! I won't allow it!
He has got to pay for this!
Another type of Trigger?
Right. From what we've seen, the victims
of the instant villain incidents
involving these mixers have no
recollection of having been dosed.
We had thought that the
previous cases like this
had been induced by bees with some
kind of injection ability...
But these newer ones might not
even involve an injection?
Right. Which suggests a dosage
form that could be taken orally,
something that could be mixed
in with food and drink.
I get it.
Someone's been spiking the drinks
at a party, in other words.
Y'know, everyone tends to believe that I'm
really social and kind of a party girl.
But it's not like I have any real friends.
People just turn to me because
they think I'm useful.
And even though I realize it,
I guess I pretend not to...
Sorry, something must be wrong with me!
I've totally let my guard down today!
This isn't good! What should I do, Koichi?
What's gonna happen to me?
Rin, you shouldn't push yourself!
Maybe lay down some more?
Don't you think, Koichi?
That's it, girls! You're doing great!
Just let it all out!
Youth is all about your mind and your body
exposing things that you
might otherwise keep hidden!
What are we looking at here?
How did Koichi end up the
center of attention?
And Hina is back for action!
H-Huh?
You seem... kind of different.
It was getting hot,
so I took the sweater off!
She suddenly kicks into
high gear, sometimes.
Exactly! I guess I'm a slow starter?
But once my engine gets going,
you better watch out.
I start to lean in.
Great, now she's going after Koichi, too.
I've got your drinks.
You can just leave them there.
I'll handle serving.
Now that's considerate!
Who ordered what, again?
Don't worry about it! It's just drinks.
This creep who pretends to be a
nice guy to get close to Rin...
I need to teach her that
all men are just animals!
Koichi! Go on, drink up!
Oh, sorry, I'm actually underage.
I'll take that one, then.
Oh, then how about a cola?
Or maybe ginger ale?
You can't stand carbonated drinks,
right, Koichi?
Y-Yeah.
How'd she know that?
I'll take the cola.
Ginger ale me!
I guess it's oolong tea for you,
Koichi? Let me grab that.
Terribly sorry, these
were for another table.
Our bad, we already started
with a few of them.
Huh, my eyes feel funny...
What the hell?!
My Quirk!
Look, just friggin' drink already!
What the heck?!
Hina?!
Multiple Quirks going berserk all at once...
Just like the instant villain
outbreak in the spring.
That happened in the streets,
but this time, it's indoors.
A stuffy location with bad ventilation.
Which means it's the perfect
playground for me!
Now, boys. Come and get it.
Quirk: Somnambulist
R-Rated Hero, Midnight!
Quirk: Somnambulist!
A scent she emits can force
people around her to sleep!
And it's more effective on men than women!
And now that the boys are all asleep,
time for a little girl talk.
Hina, before I ask you about
where you got that Trigger,
why don't you tell me about yourself first?
Why are you doing this?
B-Because... because Rin is
always hanging out with guys!
I don't like that! I hate
it! And it's not my fault!
I see. That's what pushed you to this point.
Don't worry, sweetie.
I make it a point to help
lost little lambs like you.
And I happen to have a soft spot for
these kinds of youthful antics.
They're delicious!
You could've left that part out.
I can't believe I got caught up in another
incident. And at a mixer, this time.
Not only that, but those
girls I was drinking with...
Wh-What about them?
They were all just... kinda weird,
and scary in general.
I wonder what that was all about?
All of them? Every one?
Surely one must've seemed nice, right?
Nah. They were all scary.
Maybe you're misremembering!
Try harder! Come on!
Pawn Shop
Hoppers
The analysis of the orally
administered version is finished.
Its effects are weaker than earlier
doses, without added psychotropics.
Which means it can't be used
to turn users into villains.
But it runs the risk of wider
distribution as a new casual designer drug.
I see.
Seems like they've gone
in a different direction.
There's been a decrease in instant
villain incidents since summer ended,
and in their place, we're seeing
more of the modified villains.
Yeah, like what happened to Kamayan.
And the octopus from the other day.
I'm inclined to think that their focus
is going be on the modified villains,
and maybe this new Trigger is a way
to select for potential candidates.
Then the idea is to use the weaker Trigger
to cause a bunch of Quirks to run wild,
and if they see anything that looks
useful, they kidnap and alter that person?
That would have them manufacturing
villains like a literal factory.
That's just your theory, though, right?
Couldn't it just be someone else
trying to drum up new business
now that the crab route's
shut down, officer?
Not likely. From what we learned from
the suspect behind the mixer incident,
it's likely the person who gave her
the orally administered Trigger
is the same villain who destroyed
the evidence of the crab route.
The one with the acceleration Quirk.
We investigated the bar that had
been used for the drug deal,
but it had already been cleared out.
We're one step behind.
Between this and the crab stuff,
this guy is good at cutting his losses.
You're gonna need to lock down the distro
beforehand if you wanna get him.
But judging from the
composition and packaging,
Evidence
it's likely that this new type of drug is
coming in from the greater Asian market,
and being distributed at
the individual level.
So someone's personally importing the stuff?
That'll make it harder for the domestic
cops and heroes to do anything about it.
If making any public moves
is gonna be a problem,
maybe I should take care of it quietly.
No, there are... legal issues with that.
I was joking.
You sure didn't sound like it, Eraser!
You trying to join us on
the other side of the law?
Well, that's no good.
Better be more careful who I socialize
with. Might be under a bad influence.
There he goes again!
Can you believe how rude this guy is?
Hong Kong
I could use something to eat.
You got any dim sum?
This is an apothecary.
Don't they say food's the best medicine?
Are you a tourist? Where are you from?
I've come a long way, taking seven
turns to follow the Nathan Road.
Come inside.
What were you looking for?
I don't need drugs. Just some answers.
If you're not here to buy,
then you're not a customer.
And things have been rough
around here lately,
so I've made a point of periodically
changing the password.
Anyone who tries to get in with an old
password definitely isn't a customer.
I can appreciate a man who's cautious.
We don't appreciate
window-shoppers, old timer.
You might want to change up your
bodyguards while you're at it.
Whoa, there.
No need to get tense.
Like I said, I'm just here
to ask a few questions.
Who... are you?
I'm between jobs at the moment,
so really, just a tourist.
You're not police. A detective?
Or a hero? Wait... It can't be...
Hyper Quadfist?!
Impossible! He's supposed to be dead!
With his identity exposed,
and his Quirk stolen!
You're right. And I'm sure that
man died a long time ago.
But right now, in this place...
Here I am.
Okay, I think I'm getting the hang of this.
Take the left hand, and...
Dude, you're twitching.
You're gonna cramp up.
Shut up and watch!
Like this... hell yeah!
Tail's cramping up, dammit!
How'd you manage that?
I think the nerves must be connected...
you get it, right?
How could we? We don't have tails!
Hey, Tamao.
Maybe you should play yourself, instead
of expecting everyone else to?
Isn't it supposed to be
good physical therapy?
Nah. I never really liked the
guitar that much, anyway.
I was mostly playing it to
get on my dad's nerves.
Then let's get on his nerves some more!
Huh. You're actually pretty good, Soga.
He used to play a bit
back in the day, right?
Why'd he quit?
Guitar got smashed in a fight and that was that.
Nothing good comes from having
a short fuse, am I right?
Here. It was out of tune.
Some people who want to play
don't have the instruments.
If you've got the chance,
then quit whining and do it.
Except it was your own fault
when yours got busted!
Easy there, Rapt.
Hey. Been a while, people.
It's him!
Fist geezer!
The beard looks nasty.
Oh, I guess I have been
roughing it for a while.
Doesn't matter where you've been,
I doubt it justifies ditching
your family for this long!
Come on, it's fine.
The old coot's just taking up space,
even when he's around.
I'm taking off then.
I hate to trouble you, but I actually
need to take off again, today.
You're apologizing to the wrong person.
You've got a point.
I'm sorry, Tamao. I just need
to drop by and visit someone.
I'll be right back, this time.
Shave that gross beard first.
Play the guitar, Tamao.
Anything is fine, just make some noise.
Payback against that pain in
the ass dad of yours.
Soga, you're such a sweetie!
I really appreciate you
coming all the way out.
I just can't bring myself to trust
digital communication, y'know?
I also prefer to see people
in person when I can myself.
I like being close enough to see them,
hear them.. and hit them if I need to.
If the way you looked wasn't enough,
talk like that'd make it hard
to believe you're a hero.
Well, I'm not one.
Oh, right. It's... Kuroiwa now, right?
So, what did you have for me today?
A list of customers from
a dealer in Hong Kong.
I highlighted the Japanese
citizens who are importing stuff.
And how certain can I be of this intel?
This guy's been in the biz for a long time.
If it got out that he'd been rolled over
by another operation, it'd kill his rep.
And when he realized it'd save him another
beating from someone posing as a customer,
he suddenly got real cooperative.
Makes sense.
Investigating it from
here is the police's job.
I'll be in contact if I find anything else.
Oh, hate to keep you when you're in a
hurry, but there was one other thing.
Mr. Kuroiwa, would you be familiar with
anyone who has a Quirk like O'Clock's?
No. Doesn't ring a bell.
But if you run into a villain like that,
shoot first and ask questions later.
One of our younger guys tried, believe me.
No warning shots. I'm talking about
shooting to subdue from the start.
The second he knows what's coming,
he'll be able to dodge.
We're kinda obligated not to
do that. Comes with the job.
He's a bad match for the cops, then.
Have someone else take care of it.
Taking down guys like that
is what I'm here for.
I figured. And I'll pretend
I didn't hear that.
Eraser isn't here today?!
He doesn't work here, y'know!
I'll call him now though, so chill out.
Cruller! Just keep circling around, okay?
Got it!
Huh?
Did you see Master over there just now?
Focus on running!
Did I imagine it?
He'd help if he was here!
I had something else to do today, didn't I?
Oh, right. A shave.
Something I came to understand
when trying to become a hero
is the fact that there's a limit
to what one person can accomplish.
Next time: Rain and Cloud.
A meeting like that had to have been fate.