Guess that's the last day
of middle school.
56TH GRADUATION CEREMONY
NISHI SHINJU MIDDLE SCHOOL
There wasn't anything
particularly interesting about it.
I don't really feel anything.
Miku-senpai, please
come hang out sometime.
Yup, yup.
Looks like it's different for her.
She keeps moving ahead
in life without me.
I bet she's the most popular
girl in school already.
Not that I really know.
Just how many people
are getting drawn to her?
Let's all sign our graduation albums.
GRADUATION
Time to head home.
Why would anyone scribble in something
as precious as a graduation album, anyway?
Way better to keep it clean.
Yukiya!
What happened?
What do you mean, "What happened"?!
This is the last time we're
taking this road in this uniform.
I wanted to spend
the last walk home with you.
Did that get you?
Hey, show me your graduation album.
Just give it!
Hey!
What are you doing?!
There.
- TRY TO BE MORE HONEST.
- KNOCK BEFORE YOU ENTER WAKANA'S ROOM
- FIX YOUR BEDHEAD BEFORE SCHOOL
DON'T BE STUCK UP IN HIGH SCHOOL. MAKE FRIENDS
LOOK PEOPLE IN THE EYE
WHEN YOU TALK TO THEM
She's just roasting the hell out of me!
Good for you.
You must have felt lonely,
having no one write in your album.
I never asked for this.
I wanted to end school with a slate
as clean as the driven snow.
Sure, sure.
You didn't have to
chase me down just to...
Wait, of course.
She chased me down just for this.
How can she even write so fast
in such a short time?
She's right, too.
I'm such a loser.
She's always by my side like this...
I can't stay like this forever.
Hey, wanna go by Uncle's?
He might treat us to cake
for our graduation.
Yeah.
I'm going to catch up
when I'm in high school!
Caught you blushing!
No, you!
EPISODE 3: CHILDHOOD FRIEND SEDUCTION
So, Nacchan and I were saying
we should go for a yummy lunch.
Yukiya, do you know any good places?
Fujiya Udon's pretty good, no?
Also your uncle's omurice.
Those are good, but...
I've been to Uncle's so many times.
I'm bored.
I want to go somewhere new and cute.
Uh-huh?
Sorry, I gotta go.
Oh, o-okay.
What's wrong?
You sound so sad.
Dummy.
Bye.
A little early, but good night.
Miku has lots of friends
both online and in IRL.
She must have promised
a call or something.
#MIKU'S ROOM - OFFLINE: 4
MIKU - REIJI - YUKIYA - NATSUKI
I never knew there was apple pie flavor.
Want half?
Yay.
KOI-KYUN
I wish we could be this way forever.
Talking with you makes my
heart race, Takanashi-kun.
Maybe, if I were like this guy,
I could have gotten more
out of that conversation earlier.
It isn't guaranteed that she's
going to stick around forever.
There's no telling how her feelings
are going to change going forward.
That's where you're at, huh?
HANABA HINAKO - THIRD YEAR UNIVERSITY
WORKS AT KANADE CAFE
You're living your youth, Yukki.
Oi.
So where is my beloved Miku?
She left. She said
she had something to do.
SHINONOME MASARU - MIKU'S UNCLE
OWNER OF CAFE KANADE
I'm done.
I don't want to work anymore.
Hinako-kun, time to close.
I want my hours, so nope.
What could a guy do to
make you happy, Hinako-san?
Money.
Is that even a valid answer
to my question?
High-quality bags, high-quality
cosmetics, high-quality necklaces.
I like it most when
a guy spends money on me.
THE RELATIONSHIP ENDS
WHEN THE MONEY ENDS
That's so brass tacks.
So cold.
Cold, huh?
You're so young, Yukki.
You know, all sorts of costs go
into enjoying expensive things.
Costs?
In most cases, you'll get something decent
if you just buy something online
with decent reviews.
But if you want something that'll
earn the most appreciation,
it's not just the price tag
of high-quality products.
The time it takes to choose,
to do research, to go to the store...
There's all sorts of costs involved.
Don't you put some extra thought into it
when you're buying something
a little nicer than usual?
I did have to think pretty hard
when I bought my PC.
I didn't want to mess it up, after all.
Exactly. That's what I mean.
The question is, can you do
the same thing for your special someone?
The more time and money you spend on it,
the more it comes across that you
put in an effort to make them happy.
Most people can see that.
The best way to make someone happy
is to pay those costs, I think.
You're surprisingly thoughtful
about these things.
Have you fallen for me?
You're welcome to try again
when you can earn your own money.
No, I definitely wouldn't
spend anything on you.
Thanks, though.
Costs, huh?
I did spend a lot
for my high school debut...
Okay.
MOM
INCOMING CALL
Mom?
Yeah, I'm making it now.
You are, huh?
No, it's fine.
I'll keep it in the fridge.
Be sure to eat it when you get home.
Yup, good luck.
YUKIYA
INCOMING CALL
Yeah?
What's up?
Oh, y'know...
Oh, I was just thinking,
you must have chosen somewhere half-assed
for your lunch with Nacchan-san.
I thought I'd just check
on Meshi Log before I go.
Ugh, you normies...
Let me guess, when you
say "somewhere cute,"
you mean somewhere grammable, don't you?
You know, the word "photogenic" overseas
is only used to described people.
In other words, it isn't
just what you're eating
but the synergy between
the people eating and the food
that contributes the
photogenicness to the synergy.
I'd appreciate if you didn't talk
about grammableness so casually
without even understanding what it means.
What's your point?
I'll show you how it's done.
Sunday, 9 o'clock, at the station.
Bye.
Huh?
Huh? What?
What?
What? What? What?
What?!
There's no turning back now.
#2: NISHIMAI AMUSEMENT PARK
A CLASSIC DATE VENUE!
Amusement parks, aquariums...
I've already been to all of them with
Miku with family or on field trips.
TOP 10 DATING DESTINATIONS FOR COUPLES
FROM THE COMMON TO THE BEST-KEPT SECRETS
She already goes to fancy places that
I wouldn't even know about all the time.
I'm going to put in the "cost"
that Hinako-san talks about
and make it a date
that Miku will never forget!
We've been playing the love game
pretty aggressively lately...
This has to be a date, right?
He makes it so obvious!
I can't remember the last time
I went out with Yukiya.
We used to go to the food court a lot.
Yukiya's so stingy,
sometimes he'd just have water.
And he'd never want to play
the crane catchers at the arcade.
But...
Here you go.
I want to catch big plushies
with him and stuff!
And stuff! And stuff! And stuff!
No...
I can't be getting too excited.
It's still Wednesday.
Asking me out on a date is like
walking willingly into my trap.
I'm gonna be all set for Sunday
and catch him off guard!
We live across from each other.
Why are we meeting up at the station?
Yukiya!
Did I keep you waiting?
You're here early.
TICKETS
No...
I just got here.
R-Really?
Err, what's with
that saucy voice just now?
Are you going dressed like that?
Huh?
What did he just say to me?
I spent three days and nights mulling
this over and three hours preparing today!
Did he just say "dressed like that"?
Come with me for a sec.
Huh? Wait, Yukiya!
SCUTTLE - SO FAST
He's so fast.
Umm...
I have a reservation under Asagi.
Oh, we've been waiting for you.
This lady here, correct?
This way, please.
FOR A SPECIAL CINDERELLA DAY
She came totally dressed up.
Should I really have had her get changed?
No, I planned this date
based on this shoujo manga!
I'm going to make it happen!
You can mess things up real bad
if you don't follow the instructions
when you're building a PC, too.
Trust in Hinako-san and the shoujo
manga filled with a girls' dreams!
MONEY - INVESTMENTS
Why is he making me get
changed right off the bat?
Is my outfit really that bad?
So you're on a date?
I thought you were attending a wedding.
Um, I haven't heard anything about this.
That's got to be difficult, huh?
What would you like to do?
Would you like to discuss it with him?
Umm...
I think he wanted to surprise you.
I answered his reservation call.
He sounded terribly nervous.
He was trying his best to tell me
which dress he picked out.
Yukiya picked this dress out for me?
Is this the kind of dress he likes?
Did he choose it because he
thought it'd look good on me?
I'll... take this one.
So this is the kind of thing
you wanted me to wear, huh?
Well? Happy?
I SEE. - MM-HM.
So joyful that you're
at a loss for words?
They sure know how to make
clothes that look good on anyone.
Huh?!
You know...
Okay, let's go.
Thank you.
Hey!
SLOW DOWN!
Slow down!
SCUTTLE
The appetizer:
salmon mi-cuit with dressing.
Are they high schoolers?
Y-Yukiya, are you sure about this?
This place looks expensive.
You see now?
The subject of a grammable scene
is meant to be the person
for whom such a venue and cuisine is apt.
You're dazzling right now.
Wait, wait, wait,
we really stand out here!
We're out of place!
Who cares what anyone else thinks?
Never mind that.
Just keep your eyes on me.
Uh-huh.
For sure.
For sure what?
Everyone else is a grown-up!
I'm so nervous being here!
Never mind the game!
It's good.
I've never had anything like this.
Y-Yeah?
He's off the mark,
but I can tell he's trying
his best to impress me.
He's going all-out.
It seems you're too distracted
to even speak now.
You know what this date is for, don't you?
We're just getting started!
Wh-What is he going to mess up next?!
Huh?
This is the most appropriate
decision yet today.
I like it!
I'm at Wonderland with Yukiya!
What should we ride first?
I can't decide.
Huh? Yukiya?
Huh?
Th-Thanks.
Did you feel anxious all on your own?
I was worried you might have gotten lost!
That line was so long, but it was so fun.
THIS IS ANOTHER COST
The ride ended instantly,
and we waited a whole 120 minutes.
My legs are getting pretty tired, though.
Yukiya, could I borrow your shoulder?
Wait, huh? What?!
No, err...
I thought I'd carry you if you're tired.
Y'know, like this.
Or are you too shy to take my offer?
Stop it with the hands, you pervert!
Why would I let you carry me here?!
Like...
He just keeps pulling weird acts.
And I feel like he's kinda pushing me.
Miku.
I'm going to get him back next!
Miku! Miku!
Don't you feel anything?
Here we go!
Dunno!
Look at my profile
shining in the nightscape.
Don't I look good?
Seriously?!
Are you asking me if you
made my heart skip a beat?
Heck if I know!
Really, though, what's up with that?
Oh, come on.
It does work.
Hey...
Do you still have more shenanigans?
Okay...
Could you close your eyes?
Wait!
Wait, are we actually doing this?
Just close your eyes.
Just for tonight...
You're my very own princess.
Wait, wait, wait!
This is too cringe!
Oh, what, do you have
feelings for me now, then?
No!
Not those kinds of feelings!
Relax.
No one else is around.
Just accept it and be happy.
You know, Yukiya...
You're honestly pretty sketchy today.
I mean, yeah...
I did feel pretty sketchy.
So you did.
But...
It left an impact on you, didn't it?
I doubt you'll forget such a sketchy date.
You'll never find another guy who
gives you a tiara in front of a castle.
I'm not...
I'm not letting anyone else
have your first.
Yukiya?
Yukiya!
This is going too far,
even if no one's watching!
Yukiya?
Yukiya, are you okay?
Yukiya?!
Aren't you embarrassed doing this?
You're one to talk.
Hey, are you really okay?
Should we go to the nurse's office?
I'm fine.
I'm just sleep deprived.
I just need some time to rest.
Sleep deprived?
Come to think of it,
your lights were on until late
last night and the night before.
You were gaming again, weren't you?
LEAVE A GOOD IMPRESSION ON YOUR DATE!
WHAT TO WATCH FOR IN YOUR OUTFIT
I guess.
I knew it.
You shouldn't be staying up so late
before you're going out.
And then you went way out of
your comfort zone today.
No wonder you're exhausted.
You'd normally refuse to wait
in line at an amusement park.
And you'd never waste money
on an expensive lunch or tiara.
You didn't need to push yourself so much.
HOT SPRING LOOKS FOR MEN
KOI-KYUN
But I have to.
Y-Yukiya...
Well?
Did I stun you?
Don't worry.
I had tons of fun today.
Yeah, I never stood a chance.
She acts so childish all the time.
But then she shows off her grown-up side.
I tried so hard to beat her.
You don't need to push yourself so much.
Don't worry.
I'm nowhere near her level.
I'm gonna go buy something to drink.
That startled me!
I never expected that surprise attack.
It seemed like something
was weighing on him.
I'm not letting anyone else
have your first.
What was that supposed to mean?
NO, I JUST GOT HERE.
WH-WHAT?
ARE YOU GOING DRESSED LIKE THAT?
COME WITH ME FOR A SEC.
Th-This is why!
This is why Yukiya was being so weird!
This one's full of sticky notes, too.
He's been reading like crazy.
I'm just sleep deprived.
He's such a goof.
He took it so far.
Went out of character.
He must have been super embarrassed, too.
He's that desperate to win against me?
Why is he trying so hard to win?
I... CAN'T HOLD BACK ANYMORE.
Huh? Wait.
Is this...
A kiss?
A kiss?!
TO BE CONTINUED
MY CHILDHOOD FRIEND WILL DO ANYTHING
At the coffee shop from Seattle
with the childhood friend!
At the library with the childhood friend!
In front of the janitor room
with the childhood friend!
And at the common stairs!
Hang on...
Sheesh, Onii! You've got
everything you could want!
Next episode: "My Childhood
Friend Will Do Anything!"
See you there!