Today's Menu
This Month's
Recommendations!
Hugh, why so deep in thought?
Las-kun.
Hey.
What's this? Torture studies?
Yeah.
You've been pretty
enthusiastic about it lately.
I was wondering what
to do about my report.
I see.
I'm not taking that course,
and none of our friends are in it, so...
Hey.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Modern Torture Studies I
Why don't you just ask
one of your senpai at work?
They're pros.
Oh.
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
The Next Day
Modern Torture Studies, huh?
So this is the kind of
stuff you're studying.
I was hoping I could talk to everyone
to get good references for my report.
What kind of stuff do they teach you?
Things like torture methods
and the importance of torture.
Really?
Is that any fun?
Yes!
Not only do we give villains
a taste of retribution,
but through the new information we
obtain, we destroy even more villains!
Torture saves the good in the world,
and its wonderful culture has such depth.
It's definitely worth studying!
What a nice smile.
Modern Torture Studies I
What's this? Modern Torture Studies?
Do you know this stuff?
To an extent.
I know some stuff about torture methods,
but nothing about the rest.
I only know what
I looked up out of interest.
That's how it is for both of you?
We leave the bothersome
details to others.
We just do the torturing.
They're definitely consistent.
I have national certifications, after all.
And thanks to Siu-san's threat—help,
I've got lots of certifications, too.
They're almost like
trading cards at this point.
Government, public, civil...
A full set looks something like this.
There are all kinds, huh?
Wow.
Siu-san, please stop trying to compete.
I'm not competing.
Still, they may be scum,
but this job does involve hurting people.
There are a lot of rules.
Even though these villains don't deserve
a single shred of such consideration.
Hugh, you scare me sometimes.
Modern Torture Studies I
I'd never looked into any of this in
detail before. It really is interesting!
Could be good to use this as an
opportunity to learn some of it.
Which brings us to...
the first-ever Heart-Pounding
Torture Quiz Tournament!
Heart-Pounding
Torture Quiz Tournament
Question 1
Question one!
It's a tool used to scratch skin!
Easy, right?
The name of this torture device is...
I know! Cat's claws!
However!
At what point is a
torturer allowed to use it?
That's the question?
When the torture target
is designated Class 2.
Correct
Correct!
But...
personally, I think that even
among Class 3 torture targets,
there are a mountain of villains more
than deserving of the cat's claws.
The current standards
seem too lenient in...
Don't add personal opinions
to a correct answer.
Torture Quiz Tournament
Question 2
Heart-Pounding
Okay, next...
is a question about water torture.
That's the kind I like!
The use of water torture
is permitted with...
Class 2! Class 2!
However...
given certain conditions,
it is not limited to that.
If it doesn't exceed thirty minutes,
its use is permitted at Class 3.
That's correct.
Correct
No fair!
Mike
Hugh
We have the results!
Mike
Hugh
With an overwhelming lead, Hugh wins!
Hugh, you're unbeatable!
And for the two who did their very best,
a gift of all-you-can-eat yakiniku!
Yay!
Prize
Yakiniku Ticket
Valid at whatever yakiniku place you like
Expiration date: None!
Hugh, you look so happy.
Is it because you beat me so badly?
N-No, it's not!
Before now, I never got
along with people very well,
but no one here gives me
special treatment.
I've been able to work and
have normal conversations...
So I was just thinking how happy I am
that I started torturing and met you all!
NUZZLE
Me, too!
Did this help with your report?
Nuzzle, nuzzle...
Yes.
I'd like a private room for four, please.
The Next Day
Your report was so good,
you got an award?
Award
It's thanks to all of you!
That's amazing!
He might change the torture biz one day.
What?
An urgent job?
We were just on our way out.
The request just came in,
and they want the information today.
I suppose I could do it.
Really?
But in exchange...
MWAH HA HA
you have to say,
"Sero-sama, I beg of you!"
Urk...
He came up with that stupid
request 'cause he thinks
he's the only one I can ask!
I'm sorry, I have a deadline.
And I have class work.
Sure. Good work today.
But for the company... For Hela-san...
Sero-sama!
You just had to go and
bring in this headache...
I guess I've got no choice.
I'll go change clothes.
Get everything ready for me.
That damn Sero... Why is he
always intent on humiliating me?
Why is the only one I can turn to,
and today of all days?
Plus, his handwriting sucks,
he always turns in his shift papers late,
and he's always picking fights with me!
Why do Hela-san and
Siu-san like him so much?
I mean, all he can do
is torture people, right?
I'm...
I'm jealous.
He should be...
in the... warehouse district...
He's not good with any kind of violence.
You know that Hela took Noe in, right?
Yes.
Before that, he wasn't
treated well by his parents.
Being with Hela helped
him get past all that,
but he still has an
understandable aversion to it.
I'm sure it bothers him that
he can't perform torture.
Is not being able to torture
really something to worry about?
...a-alone.
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
Could you say that again?
You're kidding me.
You're done?
Yeah.
What a horrible smell.
I got a bit rough because of the rush,
and I only just finished, so...
Oh, boy.
Ugh. This couldn't get any worse.
He really just puked on
me and then fainted...
Got his own clothes dirty, too.
Where am I?!
The nap room.
Why?
Because you barfed, duh.
GLOOM
You think I'm pathetic, don't you?
Yup.
Can you blame me? I mean,
I'll never react like you do.
What's it matter what I think, anyway?
There's no need for you to think
the same about yourself.
But since you puked on me
and made me take care of you
after making me work overtime,
you should be thanking me until you die.
Th-Thanks.
It's all about being the
right person for the job.
Don't stress over it
so much. It's annoying.
Hela-san and Siu-san
really care about you,
and everyone around you relies on you.
Really?
So you rely on me, too?
Oh, no, not me.
Well, you're always... always...
You glare at him every time you meet.
You should be able to
handle it better than that.
He's used to you guys,
so it doesn't matter,
but with other people, he's always
keeping his distance and cowering.
That's gotta be exhausting
for all parties.
That's why it's good to have
a guy like me around.
You really are a mean one, aren't you?
Sero-san, a lot of the criminals you two
handle committed horrific crimes, right?
Doesn't it ever make
you want to kill them?
Huh?
They're all revolting,
but it's not our place to kill them.
Personal feelings have
no place in torture.
Which one do you want to hear about?
The first one, the preschooler?
The second, the salaryman?
Or my third, the high school girl?
Oh, man.
Well, I did get the
necessary info, though.
Sorry. I messed up.
Again?! You—
Handle your job better.
I handle it fine.
How is this fine?
Huh?
I'll overlook it today and today only.
Now my debt's paid off.
Your debt?
Oh, you mean from when
you barfed all over me?
You are just so...
The Daily Life of a Part-Time Torturer
Hela-san, this is for you.
Thanks.
How about now?
Just a little more.
Is it good?
It is!
Papa, open wide!
Hey there! You boys!
We're just two lonely women over here.
Want to hang out with us?
Papa, who are these people?
No idea.
Papa, don't go with them!
"Papa"?
Kids?
Two papas?
S-Sorry for bothering you!
Nero-chan, you're so smart!
You make Papa very happy!
You don't get to call yourself that.
It's so cold!
It's great that those two
could come along, isn't it?
Hela was nice enough to
say to bring them along.
Both of you, say thank you to Hela.
Okay!
Thank you, Uncle Hela!
You mean "Big Sister."
Thanks, Uncle.
Thank you, Hela-san!
I will dock your pay.
Noe, you should go and have fun, too.
I'm having more than enough fun h—
We don't have enough people,
so get over here!
Damn that Sero...
Do your best out there!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Don't drag me down.
Same to you.
Here we go!
Okay!
Yay!
Wh-What are you doing?!
And what are you, a statue?!
Hugh is dangerous. We'll aim for Mike.
All right.
Sero!
Got it!
Sero-san!
Please don't hit the scary ball at me.
I'm weak against adorable
creatures, okay?!
I could hit thousands of balls
at full force against Noe, though!
You little...
Mike's Super Cutie Attack!
Yup! That's damn cute!
The kids sure are enjoying themselves.
Well, when someone who's enjoying
himself just as much says so...
I'm not enjoying anything.
You invited us all to hang out
like this out of nowhere.
You have some on you!
What's going on?
Why, nothing's going on.
You're not plotting anything, are you?
Stop saying things that
make me sound so awful!
When it was just us two,
it was good that way.
But it's not so bad having
everyone together like this, is it?
I'm happy for you!
Since Sero-kun and everyone came,
you seem like you're having fun!
Both Papa and Hela-chan!
Just wondering, but
why call me "Hela-chan"?
It's shorter than "Uncle Hela"!
I suppose I'll take it.
Papa, hurry up and light it!
Light it!
Stay back. This is dangerous.
Hugh
Look! Look!
They're getting all excited
like little kids. It's adorable.
Hey, Hugh!
If we changed the amount of powder,
do you think we could
use them for torture?
That might just work!
They're so cute.
Shall we start heading home?
All right.
Did everyone have fun?
It was tons of fun!
I had fun!
Thank you!
I'm glad to hear it.
Now you'll be able to do your best
at work tomorrow, right?
I've accepted a very important case.
What?!
I knew it.
Hela-san said it was
a very important case.
I'm sure none of it will come
to us, though, right?
Yeah, that's true.
We've got four torture targets this time.
So the four of us will take it on.
Cool! This is the first time all four
of us have worked at the same time!
Don't get so excited.
These guys have done abductions,
murder, human trafficking...
They're a hardcore criminal
organization that'll do anything!
And this time, we have core
members of their organization.
If we take them down,
we might get closer to their leader.
It's a big job.
If it's a big job, then...
do you think we'll get bonuses?
Probably.
Really?
I... want to give my mom
and dad a trip as a present.
What a good kid!
The one I'm in charge of says the
lead criminal is a man called Sakoru.
The one I'm in charge
of says it's Sakoru, too.
Same here.
Same.
All right! Everyone matches!
Which means...
they've all agreed on the
same story ahead of time.
Right?
I thought so.
And they keep babbling on
about stuff we never asked about.
It's likely that most of this
follows their script,
but there are small differences.
It's unskillfully done.
I'll try shaking them up
to trick them into spilling.
You haven't tortured yours
at all yet, have you?
The interrogation was
the important part, so...
There's no need to hold back.
I'll leave it to you.
Yes, sir.
Torture builds a sustainable society
Give the villains
the iron hammer
Okay, let's get back to it.
Let's give it our best!
I know what you said back there,
Yeah!
but you already got accurate
info out of yours, right?
Yeah.
The lead criminal's a guy named Try.
Right?
So you got that out of yours, too, huh?
Yup.
You gave those two the tougher
ones on purpose, didn't you?
Hela said to do it that way.
I see. In that case...
Wanna bet on whether
those two can do it or not?
You love this stuff, don't you? Fine.
They can.
This isn't even a bet!
Then you change yours.
What? I don't wanna!
Oh, you mean that lot?
Don't worry. We're getting the job done.
Me? Oh, no, no.
Siu, Sero, and our two rookies.
Rookies?
This is a big case for us, you know.
Yes, yes.
Leaving it to rookies is—
Oh, be quiet! Don't
underestimate our rookies!
The police inspector's griping again?
Yes.
He worries far too much.
I thought the task might be a
little too difficult for them, too.
It is, a little.
But if I know those two, they'll be fine.
Besides, they look so cute when they're
struggling over a tough challenge.
You're being mean.
This is just love!
I know that what he's saying is a lie,
but I can't get the truth out of him.
This is the first time
I've had this much trouble.
I never knew long torture
sessions were so exhausting.
I'm losing my strength and intensity.
I guess someone like me really
can't be like Sero-san and—
Mike-kun.
Hugh? What is it?
Sorry. I have blood on me right now.
It's all right.
When I started thinking of such
scum's blood as wastewater,
I got a little better with it.
That's a very Hugh-like
way of getting over it.
So, what's going on?
Well...
Mike-kun, is there
anything I can help with?
There is, but... they
entrusted this job to me.
Yeah. So...
won't you let me do it with you?
And then, I'd like it if you
helped me with mine.
We still can't do this like
Siu-san and the others can,
but with the two of us together,
we'll get a little closer!
All right! Let's get this
taken care of quick, together!
Let's do it!
You're done, too?
Yes, but we ended up working together.
I'm sorry.
What're you apologizing for?
You decided to work together
and made it through, right?
Job well done!
The way you two work so well
together is a powerful weapon.
You did good.
They were rough assignments
to handle alone.
What?!
Hela-san can be so mean.
It's a bad habit of his.
But Hela was sure that we'd be
able to handle this job now,
and that's why he took it.
Meaning you two are
counted as valuable assets.
So we've already become
splendid master torturers?
Hey, now.
Just a joke.
After all, we want to catch up
to Sero-san and Siu-san!
Right, Hugh?
Yeah!
As individuals, that's one thing,
but as a duo, I think you two
might have already beaten us.
You can't be serious!
We're the strongest team, aren't we?
Are we?
Please continue to mentor us!
Please do!
Sure thing!
I'll be counting on you!
Okay!
Seriously. I'm depending on you.
I'll work my very hardest.
Okay! Let's all grab something to eat!
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Elanor Sakamato
John Chandanais
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Becky Cottrill