Hurry it up, Koichi! Come on!
Nah. If I go too fast without
any gear, it's dangerous.
Man, it's cold today, huh?
Oh, get a move on!
Look lively!
Makoto and the Captain!
We're gonna start the
meeting without you!
Sorry, I was late getting out of school.
And I didn't get out of work on time.
I see.
Well, you want a lift?
Can we?!
Well, since you were
nice enough to offer...
Man, flying really is faster!
But... colder!
Freezing, actually!
Catastrophe
Great upheaval in society or the natural world.
Major change.
Can also refer to a tragic outcome in stories.
Often accompanied by destruction.
Farewell Party!
Captain!
Man, I'm still cold! Are you two okay?
We're fine.
I honestly don't see how you're not
cold without wearing a coat, Captain!
Not a problem, with the help of my Quirk!
The aerodynamic field that covers me
doesn't just propel me while I'm flying,
Aerodynamic Field
but also shuts down heat, cold,
and impacts from the outside!
So I just need to expand it,
and it protects my body!
And you only use it on girls?
Don't make it sound like that!
Say there was a single blanket right here.
Would you want to share
it with another guy?
I'd take that over freezing! You
really are a piece of work.
Make sure you keep all of
that off the record, Koichi.
I can see how it'd be bad
for his image, yeah.
Not that stuff.
I mean the specifics about his
Quirk and its weaknesses.
Better to keep that sort of thing secret.
Oh, I get you.
The kind of precaution a famous
hero would need to take.
Good morning!
Sorry about the delay!
Meeting Room B
And that'll cover our
review of the last event.
Which also completes our
Narufest run for the year!
You all did great.
And from this point on...
It's our Christmas party!
Leave this to us!
Fold, fold, fold...
Pizza's here!
Sup!
I can take that.
It's okay. I've got it.
It all looks so good!
Hello, everyone! Good to see you!
President!
Okay, here we go...
Ready and...
Merry Christmas!
Red nose, red nose!
Line up, everyone. Come get yours!
Gift certificates!
It's the color of my passion.
You're so dreamy.
The Captain's asleep.
He's been pretty busy lately,
from what I can tell.
I seem to remember you falling
asleep during the meeting.
Is the party already over?
Time for the next gig?
There's still time. Make
sure to rest while you can.
Your schedule through New Year's
Eve is full, after all.
Okay, sure, work me like
a horse if you must.
This year, the next, and beyond.
That's just life.
Actually, you'll be getting ready
to go home early next year,
so while you'll still be busy until
then, things should slow down after that.
Go home? But I thought those
lawsuits were all still...
Your excursion's just about over, boss.
All the cases that were still in dispute
should be wrapped up by
the end of the year.
Which also means the suspensions affecting
you throughout the States will be lifted.
The negotiations with the various people
who asked for restraining orders
on you are proceeding, as well.
I had no idea.
A big part of it is that a lot of
the cases that were against you
ended up being fraudulent.
They were?!
A whole cocktail tray of honey
traps and paparazzi collusion.
You made an easy mark for them.
Which did leave us with our
own options, thankfully.
Oh, Makoto, I hope we're
always good friends.
Because I sure wouldn't
want you as a foe.
That means you get to go home, Captain!
That's great!
Well, even if I go back to America,
I won't get to go home, per se.
Considering how my wife feels about me...
She's scheduled to give birth next month,
so the two of you can have a nice talk
about the future once you're with her.
Give birth? Pamela?
To my baby?
And I didn't know about this?!
She told me something when I met her.
"I know my husband is a good man,
but he's a little too trusting."
"I don't want to risk raising a
child in the middle of this mess."
"I intend to bring up
the baby on my own."
And Pamela said all that?
Well, if you want a direct quote,
it was more like "That idiot—"
Never mind! I believe you!
The summary will do.
I think the whole thing
would hurt my feelings.
What was it that made her
change her mind, then?
When she told me about the
baby, I told her something.
What was that?
To leave it to me!
Oh, then you'll be all good, Captain!
Congratulations!
I wanna see the baby!
Me too!
I see... I'll really get to
go back to the States...
To my home.
And to meet my baby...
I couldn't ask for a better
Christmas present!
H-Hang on! Wait, wait! I
didn't mean it like that!
You guys get that, right?!
He does tend to set himself up for
problems like this, doesn't he?
Yeah, I think I see it.
It's kind of late, so everyone
be careful on the way home.
Okay!
Marukane
See you all next time!
You kids are going back in a taxi, okay?
Okay!
Can you bring the change and the
receipt to our next meeting?
Yeah!
We had a lot of fun!
And there'll be more, next year!
Okay!
Driver, they're in your hands now.
Bye bye!
Children can be so adorable.
I'm picturing having three, back at home.
What do you think, Makoto?
I think you should discuss
it with your wife.
And I think if anyone overheard you now,
they could make problematic assumptions.
Oh, that'd be bad!
What?!
Something huge just flew by!
A villain?!
Oh, no! The girls' taxi!
This is bad! If it falls
from that height...
It's all right!
I can take down the villain
and save the kids in one go!
Captain!
All right, I made it—
Turns out, you didn't.
It blew up?!
Is the boss...?
Captain!
Are you all okay?! You're
not hurt, are you?!
Captain!
You okay, Captain?!
Oh, man, you're bleeding!
What was that explosion?!
Is that Captain Celebrity?
C.C.'s all torn up!
Excuse me! I work for
him! Let me through!
Stop it! No photos! Don't
post me looking bad!
Looking bad?
You've never looked
more impressive, boss!
Looks like using flight and explosions
together can be pretty effective.
Enough to put a dent in
Captain Celebrity...
Or is it?
It looked like he took some kind of
barrier and put it around those kids
right before the blast.
Which means he took the brunt of the hit.
And the only reason he seemed invincible
before was because of said barrier.
He's not actually immortal.
And that gives me plenty to play with.
Hell, another two or three hits
with the same kind of blast...
I oughta be able to take
him down easy, y'know?
Happy New Year.
Might Tower
Well, we might've been buried in work
all through the New Year's holiday...
But here's to working
together again this year.
Yes, likewise.
And I hate to spring this on you, but I
won't be able to drop by for a while.
Oh, really?
Well, I'm sure you've got more
to do than keep me company.
It's not that. Something urgent came up.
An outside tip came through
for a pre-existing matter,
and the investigation has
progressed somewhat as a result.
This case... is it the one with the
drug, where you ended up being shot?
That's worrying!
Put in a call for me when you do
something dangerous, all right?
You can even make it private,
and I'll come incognito!
I am here...
Incognito!
I appreciate the sentiment, at least.
Recycle Shop
Hoppers
And so that covers the individual
clients from the list,
who we've been investigating to
find a trail back to the source...
But we're still lacking
something definitive.
Not to mention, there's a chance
that while looking into this,
the Factory might catch on
and go into hiding again.
These guys are definitely
light on their feet.
Some more info to narrow down
the search would be handy.
Don't you think, Eraser?
Here, Tsukauchi.
It's a record of the Naruhata
Vigilantes' activities.
One week ago
Oh, wow.
You two have been really working hard!
Right! Well, not me, but...
Yeah, that's the Crawler...
He's amazing.
Either play dumb or act proud...
But pick a lane, kid.
It's all good, though.
Most of this falls under crime
prevention and civilian arrest laws.
There seem to have been more
injuries early on, but...
Some unrelated old guy was
responsible for those.
Okay, I'll note those as separate from
everything from summer and beyond.
And I'll be holding on to
these records you provided.
I appreciate your cooperation.
There's a good chance that
the Naruhata villain attacks
were arranged by a major crime syndicate.
This might even be a step
towards solving the case!
I'd like to thank you, too.
Having pictures like those out there had
me worried I'd get arrested some day.
And when we talked to Makoto about it,
she said we'd be better off asking
a hero we know than the police.
It's true that heroes are more considerate
about individual circumstance,
while still having the same
kind of access.
I'll treat you two as anonymous
tipsters, so don't worry.
Mr. Manager, I wanna thank y...
Or rather, give my regards
to our mysterious vigilante.
I think it was the...
Crawler.
His name is the Crawler!
What a farce.
Come on, man, play along.
Looks like a digital notebook
composed of photos and text
containing information about
incidents involving Naruhata villains...
There seems to be stuff here
on unreported incidents and events from
before the police arrived on scene.
Where'd it come from?
Not sure.
Midnight just asked me to pass it
along, so I don't really know.
Couldn't tell you anything about
the vigilantes' identities, either.
MOMENT OF EXPLOSION
RESCUE FROM THE SKY
Are you all okay?! You're
not hurt, are you?!
BREAKING NEWS: CAPTAIN CELEBRITY WRAPS UP DOMESTIC OPERATIONS, PREPARES TO HEAD HOME THIS YEAR
The American hero, Captain Celebrity,
who was the talk of the town after the
explosion at the end of the year,
intends on concluding his excursion in
Japan this year and returning to his homeland.
BREAKING NEWS: CAPTAIN CELEBRITY WRAPS UP DOMESTIC OPERATIONS, PREPARES TO HEAD HOME THIS YEAR
I hate to spring this on you all, but
it was always part of the schedule.
As much as I hate to leave you, my family
is waiting for me back in the States.
Captain Celebrity will remain in Japan
for the rest of the New Year's holiday.
It's believed that his time in Japan will
lead to a rise to even greater heights.
Wow! The video's gone
past 100 million hits!
That's even more than
the giant monster fight!
They say your approval rating is
skyrocketing, and nearing All Might's!
You're one of the most-talked
about tags on the internet, too!
#Celebrity, #Captain, #CCHomcoming,
#AerialExplosion, #LameHoodie...
There's a lot of buzz about people
wanting an official Captain hoodie
but there being none on sale.
His existing merch is all sold out, too...
We couldn't get more stock in time.
Aw, it's a shame that there's no
way to take advantage of the buzz.
Which is why... we'll create
another round of buzz.
The venue for the boss's farewell
party at the end of March...
is not going to be the Naruhata
Public Hall like I said previously,
but will instead be the 500-meter-tall,
50,000-person-capacity Tokyo Sky Egg!
The theme of the event will be
Japan/US hero collaboration,
and we're gonna make it a big event!
This sounds kinda sudden!
Hey Makoto, are you sure about this?
I kinda forced our way in! No way
am I letting this chance get away!
It'll be your last gig in Japan.
Let's make sure you go
out with a bang, boss!
Looks like there's no getting
out of this, Captain.
And if you're doing it,
let's make sure you can say your
time in Japan was a huge success!
And of course, the Narufest team
will be offering our full support!
Our support?! As in, performing
on stage, at the Sky Egg?!
Us?
We usually only have around 100
guests at Narufest, right?
And half of them are friends and
acquaintances, like Samazu...
So, more like fifty?
But the Sky Egg is...
Fifty thousand!
What do we do, what do we do?!
That's a three digit difference!
W-We train! We don't
have any other choice!
No, just perform like you usually do.
I'm a fan of the way you all
usually perform, anyway.
Captain!
But since it's a special occasion,
we'd love to show off!
Right?
Well, there's not a ton of
spare stage time anyway.
Enough for a CC-themed dance routine,
before coming in for a remix of our
standard, the Marukane theme, right?
I wanna bring in the cheer
team for C.C.'s agency,
along with the Naruhata
neighborhood squad,
so I'll need to talk to reps of
the band and dance club later.
Right!
Girls, we're gonna train
like crazy until the event.
No sour faces, either!
Right!
Everyone's back to normal!
Because we've gotta work hard.
I'll be rooting for you all.
The next day
Okay, let's start this practice!
Right!
You can do it! Fight on!
Final Event Coming Soon!!
That just leaves the guest heroes...
I'd like to assemble a who's-who
of the Japanese scene.
You need me for an event? Copy that!
I'd love to show up with my team.
Training
Ridiculous.
I'm not interested.
I'd love to come! You can't
keep me from a party!
You coming, Yamada?
Yeah!
Well, I'll show up if I get the chance.
Wash!
I want to thank you again for
agreeing to our sudden offer.
I'll send along a draft of the
contract in the next few days.
Should it go to the e-mail address
you sent me the other day?
Right! Thank you so much.
It's a pleasure to be working with you.
Got a pretty decent lineup, but
it could use a little more...
Maybe I should reach out to more regional
heroes from outside the metro area?
Getting All Might would be ideal, but...
Welcome home. You seem
to be working hard.
Oh, Nao...
You were actually home? That's rare.
Just to get a change of clothes.
I'm heading right back out.
You always keep busy, huh?
Look who's talking. You even
bring work home with you.
Just don't overdo it.
This is a big juncture for me!
I'd honestly appreciate you pushing me
more than trying to stop me right now.
Well, I am rooting for you.
I appreciate it, Nao.
Then, can you maybe hook me up with
your connection at All Might's agency?
Not happening.
Just a cell phone number will do!
No means no!
Just this one time!
Villainous hands reach out
for the Captain's final event...
To protect the Sky Egg from destruction,
the Captain engages in his most
desperate battle yet.
Next time: Zero Hour.
Watch Japan's pro heroes assemble!