Your Highness, I will not fail
to rescue you this time.
I, Louch Brittan, White Knight
of the Imperial First Legion!
White Knight of the
Imperial First Legion
Louch Brittan
Your Highness. Please wake up.
Your Highness.
I do apologize for leaving
you in here for so long.
It took some time to
develop my new spell.
That said, the magic
I've come up with is flawless!
A spell to prevent perception except
by those who are pure of heart!
Upon activating the spell,
for a set period of time, I become
imperceivable unless you're pure of heart.
Can't touch
Can't see
But it's not just limited to sight.
The impure of heart can neither touch
nor hear me at the moment.
Can't touch
Swoosh
Can't hear
Though it also means I cannot
touch anyone who's not pure of heart.
Also, it's a bit over-the-top
on how pure-hearted you have to be...
My troops who play video games too much.
Or secretly eat snacks ended
up being unable to notice me...
Sir Brittan?
Why, you...
Not that Her Highness would be affected!
Pardon me, Your Highness.
Please wake up.
Huh?
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Swoosh
I can't touch Her Highness...
This must mean...
The spell was a failure!
This spell is one where not even
the pure of heart can perceive me!
I should lift the spell
for now—wait, no!
There's no way to lift this spell
other than to let it run its course!
What are you doing out here?
You can see me?!
What a foolish question.
That night, we managed to see eye-to-eye,
thanks to Mobile Cavalry Soul Cross,
and we spent time after
that discussing our favorite anime.
I'd never forget
the sight of a dear friend.
Would I, Loutchi?
Gotchi!
I see.
Magic that prevents people outside
of the intended scope from perceiving you?
Yes. I spent a long time
creating that spell...
But it didn't work.
I did all sorts of tests to see
if I made a mistake with the scope,
but not a single person noticed me.
Well, I can see you.
That's true. I wonder why.
Perhaps it turned out
to be a spell that
only lets your friends perceive you.
Maybe so.
A spell that only lets Gotchi see me...
Is that useful for anything?
Oh right, Gotchi. What
brings you out here at night?
Ah, I remember now.
They're about to show
the Gazinder movie on Hell-X TV.
The Gazinder movie?!
I thought I'd watch it
in the Hellholm theater room.
How about it, Loutchi?
I'd love to!
Oh, but if anyone in Hellholm
spotted you with a human like me,
it would cause an uproar.
I'm sure it'd be fine.
Oh, and besides, Loutchi.
Right now, you've cast
the perfect spell on yourself, have you not?
That's right! The spell
that only lets Gotchi see me!
Right, off we go.
Go! Go!
Cosmic Supreme
Gazinder
Watching this on a giant screen rules!
That it does!
Gotchi, you turned my failure
into what will be a fond memory.
Thank you.
No need to thank me.
That's what friends are for.
Cosmic Supreme
Gazinder
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Many years have passed since the
Imperial Army and Hellhorde went to war.
The Princess and Commander
of the Imperial Third Legion
falls into the hands of the Hellhorde
in the midst of fierce battle,
and is subjected
to torture day in and day out.
The grand inquisitor Torture
Tortura's torture in particular...
is the very definition of merciless.
Looks yummy!
I definitely want it!
Princess, if you'd like to try some...
As brave and dashing
as the princess is...
You'll have to divulge
an imperial secret.
I'll talk!
She cannot stop herself
from confessing.
Delicious!
I see.
So the Royal Empire
has five neighborhood cats.
I've managed to obtain
a fantastic secret.
Today, let's take a peek into
a day in the life of this torturer.
So warm...
Oh, how shameful of me.
Visiting my parents after so long
has made me drop my guard.
I ordered it to the wrong address!
I'm just stopping by my parents' to fetch
the package I accidentally sent them.
I have a torture session after this,
so I need to snap out of it!
I'll do some cleaning in here
to wake myself up.
I found it.
This is the package, right?
I had the wrong idea,
so I'd brought it to my bedroom.
She's a total goner!
Leaving everything within arm's reach!
Folding a cushion over
to use as a pillow!
Sh-Sh-She's a total goner!
That's not it.
I was trying to clean up,
when I found some snacks...
Yuki no Ya
Kiratto-san
Came across some manga I used to like...
Found some photos which
got me nostalgic...
Which made me want to
dig up my yearbook...
Then I wanted to try on my
uniform to see if still fit...
And before I knew it...
I ended up like this.
So you did, huh?
You don't have to tell me.
I know I can't stay in here.
If I don't leave soon...
I won't make it in time
for today's torture...
Which is why...
The bananas being thrown
by the buff koala...
There!
If I want to catch them all
while standing on a stool...
Was I asleep just now?
I think so.
Oh no. I need to wake up...
I can't escape the warm kotatsu...
It bids me into the world of dreams!
Bear it, Torture!
Are you all right?
Uh oh. Mom's turned into Kiratto-san.
It feels like I'm wandering between
the real and dream world.
I know I need to wake up,
but I'm slowly getting sleepier...
Sleepy, sleepy, sleepy...
Oh, yeah. What's in this package?
The torture implement I was
going to use for today's torture.
I wanna be tortured with this!
Sleepy, sleepy, sleepy...
That's right, it's the torture implement
I picked out with the princess...
It should arrive on the 22nd.
Awesome! Thanks!
I can't wait!
Today's the day the princess was...
Looking forward to...
Looking forward to!
Sleepy!
If today's torture is canceled...
The princess would be so sad!
Making your torture target sad is...
Unthinkable for a torturer!
Have a safe trip back.
I'll be going!
You seem awfully chipper
today, Your Highness.
Yep.
I've been looking forward to
today's torture for ages!
A torture you've been
looking forward to for ages?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Princess.
There you are, Torture.
Without further ado...
'Tis time for torture!
Entrance
Ceremony
Boss? What's wrong? You seem down.
You see, I haven't been
able to see my daughter...
Sounds like it's something
pretty serious!
What?!
Totchan's coming home today?!
I want to see her!
Don't you have work, dear?
And she's only stopping
by to pick up a package.
I don't care how long! I want to see her!
Why are you so desperate to see her?
I haven't seen her for
three whole weeks now!
That's not that long
for a daughter who's moved out.
What?
Hurry up and leave already
or else you'll be late to work.
I'm supposed to be working
for the sake of my family...
So why must I sacrifice my family
for the sake of my work?!
Save the dramatics
for something more serious.
A photo!
At least get me a photo!
I want to see how much
my daughter's grown!
I don't think an adult woman's
got much growing to do.
I'd like that photo sooner rather than later...
Sure thing
Here's the photo
Okay! Time to work my butt off!
He cheered up.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
You're going out pretty far today, right?
Yep.
I saw a pancake place
that looked good in a magazine,
so I wanted to torture
the princess there.
You haven't been there yet,
have you, Vanilla-chan?
Will you be okay? You won't get lost?
Should we have our maid drive you two?
Nope, this is my torture.
I'll be one to escort the princess there!
Vanilla-chan!
I'm leaving!
You have fun now!
She's growing up so quickly.
Yes.
Before you know it,
our baby bird will be leaving the nest.
Indeed.
All right.
Let's disguise ourselves and follow her!
Get the car ready, Miss Kon!
Yes, sir
Kuroenji
Station
Oh, s-sorry I'm late.
No worries, I just got here myself.
That's a relief.
Should we get going?
Yeah! It's this way.
Helltrianon
phell
It's supposed to be a
five-minute walk from the station,
but they've been walking
for twenty minutes now.
Just as I feared, Vanilla-chan is lost!
This way, Princess!
Sure.
Oh.
My shoelaces came loose.
Mind if I tie them back up over there?
Go ahead.
Why won't the princess lead the way?!
Can't she see that
Vanilla-chan's in distress?!
No, dear. Didn't you notice?
What?
Just now, the princess,
while appearing to be walking naturally,
caught her shoelaces with her foot...
and untied them!
What?!
And the spot she chose
to tie them...
is next to a giant map!
You're right!
In addition, so far on their walk...
She took the outer side on narrow back
streets so Vanilla-chan's safe from cars,
subtly made sure that she
was hydrating regularly...
Kuroenji
Station
And what's more, she arrived ahead of
schedule to scope out a map of the area!
She did all that?!
The princess is well aware
of the fact that Vanilla-chan
has lost her way...
As well as...
Vanilla-chan's desire to
be the one to guide her!
Princess!
I figured it out, Princess!
It's this way!
Yeah!
We're here!
We made it!
Okay, Vanilla-chan.
Huh? Oh!
Time for your torture, Princess!
I won't give in so easily!
Welcome!
They look great!
Yeah!
Vanilla-chan, wanna try some of mine?
They were so tasty,
she forgot to ask for a secret
Oh, can I?
Here, open wide.
'Tis Time for "Torture,"
Princess
Is her playmate one of
her friends from preschool?
Nope, she just met him today.
Oh?
It's amazing that she can get along
with someone she met just now by chance.
I'm going to step away
to do some shopping.
Keep an eye on her.
See you later.
I suppose I should find somewhere to sit.
I believe there's a bench over here.
Oh, hello there.
Hello.
He must be that child's father.
Thank you for playing with my child.
Oh no, I should be thanking you.
What do I say to him?
I'm pretty good at talking to people
I've just met without getting nervous,
but the problem is I don't
know what to talk about.
If we were colleagues, we'd have
things in common I could bring up...
Work work work
But he's not part of the Hellhorde.
What do I even say to someone I've met
for the first time today?
"Do you live around here?"
Wait, is it okay to ask something
so personal right off the bat?
"Great weather we're having."
It'd be too obvious that
I'm at a loss for conversation.
"What anime are you
watching this season?"
There's no guarantee that he likes anime.
I've got nothing to talk about
other than work and anime!
I didn't have any problem
talking to Loutchi...
Gotchi...
My son's in first grade.
Is your daughter around his age?
I see.
To start a conversation, you should
first offer information about yourself.
No, she's still in preschool,
but I'm sad that she'll be moving up soon.
Oh, it really is so sad, isn't it?
I'm doing a good job talking to him!
How has school been?
I managed to expand on the topic!
Two combo!
Once the game of verbal
catch is underway,
I just need to keep
the conversation going!
It's not easy, that's for sure.
For a music recital we just had,
all the kids needed matching T-shirts,
but they only gave us five days' notice.
What? Only five days?
It had to be a solid yellow T-shirt, too.
It's like, you're really springing
that on us with five days?
That sure sounds rough.
I'm doing it!
Three combo!
As we continue to work in tandem...
Four combo!
We're building up a conversation combo!
He's so nice and easy to talk to!
Speaking of T-shirts, I can't wear them
with these horns on my shoulders.
Five combo!
Oh, that's true. They'd get all torn up.
That's right.
It's so sad that I can't wear
T-shirts of my favorite anime.
Bad!
I messed up!
Our lively conversation lowered my guard,
and I said the word "anime!"
He's a nice person.
Even if he's not very familiar...
I used to watch anime as a kid, too.
He's sure to change the topic
to cater to my hobbies, like so.
But that will lead to...
What? Recent anime?
Well...
Oh, I just watch what
my son does nowadays.
M-Makes sense...
Our different power levels will turn
the conversation hazy, like a cloud!
Just when it had gotten so lively, too!
Do you... like anime?
Oh, yes.
Wha...
What are you watching this season?
What?
Six c-c-c-c-combo!
Eh?
Oh...
Could it be that you...
I'm into anime.
Seven combo!
Eight combo! Nine combo!
Ten combo!
The Hell-Lord
talked