This is a story about a deranged world.
Who are you?
I just woke up.
Why did you instantly attack me?
What are the rules this time?
Answer me.
I just woke up, you know.
I don't know anything about this game.
Tell me what you know.
Did you really just wake up?
You're not with the girls in the entryway?
That's what I said. What entryway?
Tell me what's going on.
Sorry.
We can discuss those details later.
They'll find us if we stay here.
Will you come with me?
Who are you?
Nobody suspicious.
Where did you come from?
I'm just a humble—
Azuma-chan! I'm so glad you're alive!
Wait, dummy!
Don't open it until I'm finished!
Are you hurt?
Azuma!
Everyone...
Sorry.
We just came back for allies. Right?
I was... scared.
Seriously?
So, who is she?
That's Yuki-san. You're her, aren't you?
An incredibly skilled
ghost-like veteran player.
I've heard of her before.
Someone that incredible
is willing to help us?
Since everyone's here,
let's introduce ourselves.
My name is Yuki.
Nice to meet you.
This is an escape game.
The game's probably beaten
by using those to escape the bath.
But there's a limited number of tags.
Yeah.
Yuki-san, if you'd woken up sooner
and didn't have a tag,
what would you have done?
I'd start by looking for the exit.
And if you reached the entryway
and realized you needed a tag,
would you go back to look for one?
No. I'd wait at the exit
for a player with a tag.
Fighting every other player would
be inefficient, so I'd form a team.
That's how the entryway team formed, too.
We can't leave without
one tag for each person,
so both players and tags
accumulate in the entryway, but...
Thirty people is probably the cutoff.
How'd you come up with that number?
Judging by the number of shower stalls,
there are fifty participants.
Considering the average survival rate
and tags that have already been used,
about thirty more people can escape.
That's the upper limit to the size of a team.
Isn't that amazing?
Yeah.
The players still here are
the slow starters, aren't they?
Sorry.
How many tags do we have?
Nine, I think.
That's a lot. The entryway team
hasn't come for them?
Not yet.
I think it's hard for them to get us in here.
What do you mean?
That door we used earlier is the only exit,
and there's a wall back there.
They can't get behind us.
It's not a bad spot to defend.
Excuse me...
Go on.
That...
Sugiyama is our treasurer.
Could you give that to her?
Oh, right.
Here.
Mishiro-san, Mishiro-san.
Mishiro-san will praise me.
Mishiro-san!
I did it, I did it, I did it!
I got three!
They asked to join us now,
so I pummeled them!
Well done, Riko.
Could I get the usual for three?
Again?
Yes, please.
I love how cold your
right hand is, Mishiro-san.
All done.
What? But I brought back
enough for three people.
What should I do next?
Attack the enemy's position?
Let's wait and see a little longer.
Mishiro-san...
Our strategy is to hit and run.
Azuma and I will fight at the front.
I'd like the rest of you to support us.
We have roughly thirty enemies,
but it should end once we
defeat about half of them.
If every remaining player can use a tag,
the smart thing to do is to make a deal.
They must know that, too.
Let's prepare as much as we can
so we can all survive.
These are all the knives?
Yes.
Any mirrors nearby?
I think there are some around the large bath.
But getting lost would be dangerous.
Amon, we've got a job for you.
Take a left. Cross here and go right.
Then take another left.
That's impressive.
Right?
Thanks.
Huh? Oh, sure.
So that's how you smile, Amon-chan.
It's cute.
What is it?
Oh, did we go too far?
Yes. It's above us.
Huh?
This should be enough, right?
Yeah.
Huh? Where's Hiwada?
She went to powder her nose.
Oh.
Azuma.
Where did she go?
They were looking for someone.
Um...
Hiwada-san...
There she is!
Damn. Hey!
Shit. Wait!
Think, think, think.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
What?
Take a left. Cross here and go right.
Hey!
Then take another left.
This way!
Okay.
Damn!
So many! Now we can make
enough for everyone.
You're amazing, Amon-san.
Thanks, Amon.
I didn't do anything.
You're always so modest.
Apparently, her leg's not that bad off.
I know.
You're amazing, Amon.
You should be more confident.
That's good.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Stick your chest out. Yeah, that's it.
Think it's a hot spring?
This bath, I mean.
I don't think so.
No, it is.
I can feel it working.
If she was in that area,
she was probably collecting shards of
mirrors and things to use as weapons.
Did she tell you that?
Actually, um...
She got away.
Hey!
Sorry. A player we'd never seen
before came to her rescue.
That's right! Someone new
seems to have joined them.
She suddenly showed up
and then vanished like a ghost.
It's true. We looked for her
but couldn't find any trace of her.
A ghost?
They're all good girls, aren't they?
Yeah.
Why are you in this business?
To beat 99 games.
That's my goal.
What about you?
Huh? I, uh... For normal reasons.
Normal?
Sorry. I guess it's not normal.
You think a girl as masculine as me
does well in the real world?
I don't think there's anything wrong with it.
It's better than people who refer
to themselves in the third person.
Yeah, you're right.
I wonder why.
It's not like I can't wear
my uniform, act amiably,
and talk more like a girl.
It shouldn't cause me any pain.
But once I started thinking about it,
I struggled to talk to friends,
go to school, leave the house,
eat with my family,
or do anything at all.
Slitting someone's throat
and killing them is easier.
I'll release you from this game.
Huh?
I'll help you find a decent job so you
don't have to play this dangerous game.
What would you say if I proposed that?
Azuma, I—
I'd smack you.
Right.
They're here.
Azuma.
Good luck to us both.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
There are a bunch of people
on the other side of the wall!
Why?
Why didn't I notice?
Why didn't I check?
The game is set in a public bath.
Why didn't I even consider that possibility?
I could've noticed long before now.
I can't even use the Wall of Thirty
as an excuse.
I don't believe it.