It's been one week since
Ishino the Musician died.
To find out who was responsible,
we raided the lair of a Dark Lord,
the Count of Twin Pincers,
but all we got our hands
on were underlings.
And with not much intel to show for it.
It looks like I'm gonna need to
get a little more creative.
Scum of the Brave
Another bouquet of flowers.
A Brave's Legacy
Make them stop sending them here.
Dear "Reaper" Yashiro
This season is marked by clear skies and stars that dazzle more beautifully than the rest of the year.
To that end, I would like to invite you to a small affair
in which we will take full enjoyment of these long winter nights.
Vintage wine of the finest grade will be served as we discuss our various goals,
which I hope will make for a sublime evening.
Actually, this works.
A literal invitation. What a joke.
Good day! It's me!
Master! Why did you ignore the—
What is that bouquet?!
Is it for you?
Nope. For Ed.
I had no idea he was so popular!
More importantly, Master!
Why didn't you come to observe
the practical exam last week?!
Oh, right.
Well, I never intended to.
Where's the other one? Sara.
She has cleanup duty at school!
The daughter of King Arthur
cleaning the school grounds...
So, did you two pass that exam?
Sara and I did.
Aki got a draw and has
to take a makeup exam.
Yes! My opponent, Sakakibara
Helen, was a fearsome foe!
I struck, and she evaded, only for her
to strike, forcing me to evade!
It was a close-fought battle!
One could say it was a white-knuckled
battle of epic proportions!
Seriously?
I thought the opponent
was pretty average.
They were so evenly matched,
it devolved into a drag.
Yukine! I would appreciate it if you
embellished my exploits around Master!
If Indo says they were average,
they must've been half decent.
Looks like my lessons had an effect.
But if the fight dragged on that long,
you still haven't fixed
what I warned you about.
You were passive, aimed for counters,
and tried to win on points, right?
Yes! But I like to think that I
have taken your lessons to heart.
The technique for disarming
foes that you used...
I believe it's called a
kote-uchi in kendo.
I made good use of it.
Your nonlethal intentions...
are something I have inherited.
Look, I only used it because killing
them would've been a big headache.
Now, now, there's no need
for such modesty!
Listen to me, damn it!
You think I'm trying to not be lethal?
Next time you get a chance,
get a good read on my mind.
Read your mind, Master?!
No! I think we need to get to
know each other better first!
That sort of relationship...
would be inappropriate!
Somehow that was an even more
annoying reaction than I anticipated.
Instructor. When's my next lesson?
I'm kinda busy for the foreseeable future.
But you said you'd train me more.
You promised.
Did I, now?
You did. I know you did.
Fine, then.
You girls busy this Saturday?
No! We are in fact completely free!
What kind of lesson will this be?
Social studies?
Okay, we'll meet up at 6PM in
front of Ikebukuro Station.
I'll notify Sara.
Don't eat anything the day of.
There's a good chance
you'll puke if you do.
No, that wasn't what surprised me...
You're going to contact Sara?
How, exactly?
Uh, by text?
Texting?!
Master! Why do you have
Sara's contact info?!
Because we exchanged them?
An exchange?!
That's so cruel! We haven't
exchanged such information yet!
And I can't believe Sara had the gall to
do so ahead of me, the first apprentice!
Please, please shut up.
Instructor.
Unacceptable!
Me too. I want to exchange contact info.
Fine, but do you even have a phone?
Sometimes.
Sometimes...?
Master! Me as well!
Please, let us exchange
contact information!
With you, Jogamine?!
Master, I feel there is an undeniable bias
in the way you treat Yukine versus me...
Why wouldn't there be?
There we go.
Can you believe Ishino was sitting
on top of all this gunpowder?
Hope you don't mind me hogging it all.
It's fine. I wouldn't know
what to do with it, anyway.
More importantly, did you find it?
Yeah. It was a real treasure trove.
Joe! We're gonna play later,
winner takes all!
There's a Pantheon of Plagues
you can have for free.
Screw that card!
More importantly, what about Tidal
Wave? He would always use that—
Hey.
I showed up because you said
you needed a favor.
What is this?
If you two are just gonna play,
I'm heading out.
My bad. Don't sulk so hard.
I'm not sulking!
There's something I need
to confirm, actually.
Remember your last lesson?
Those two we ran into aren't involved
with the Round Table, are they?
I don't think so.
It's not like I know everybody, though.
What about your dad?
He mention anything?
I don't really like talking to him.
I can never tell what he's thinking.
There's a good chance he knows what
happened that night, though. I think.
Why's that?
I'm not sure.
Might have something to do
with his ether perception.
During the thing with the
Count of Amber Thorns,
he knew you rescued me without
me ever telling him, Sensei.
That it?
Nope. My favor involves this stuff.
It's a job only you can do.
These are all women's clothes...
Are they yours?!
Hell no.
It was something Ishino was into.
Like what?!
I wouldn't ask, if I were you.
I need you to pick dresses fit
for a party from this collection.
You'll use them in the next lesson.
For a party?
I take it I'm picking out what I wear?
Yeah. Choose something for
Jogamine and Indo, too.
I don't mind, but why me?
You really think having those two
pick their outfits would work out?
This is it!
Should we be going through
his stuff like this?
This happens all the time with Braves.
So, the Pincers raid
didn't turn anything up?
Out of the people Malta grabbed,
one of them had some intel.
Didn't know anything about
that woman, Levi.
But the guy, Ido, was a Brave who
raised hell in Kansai until last year.
He worked as a mercenary for Dark Lords
and stuck his nose into all
kinds of conflicts.
And he was famous for never
working with the losing side.
Might have to do with
his ether perception.
Seems likely.
He acted like he knew how
strong I was when he saw me.
Both of them are washed up
Braves who became outlaws.
And they were wandering
inside the academy...
Yeah. At first, I had them pegged as new
muscle for the Coffin Count of Storms.
He may be allied with the
man from yesterday.
He was fairly capable, wasn't he?
I don't think they knew who I was.
Then running into you was a coincidence?
Hard to say.
But we'll have to ask someone who's
more in-the-know than Pincers.
And since they went to the
trouble of inviting me...
And you're taking them along?
Sounds pretty complicated.
Taking you and Malta along
would be like declaring war.
I'm just going to talk.
Part of it has to do with
his last words...
The recorder Ishino always
had on him had some data.
Hello, Yashiro? Things have taken
a turn for the interesting.
I'm a bit busy at the moment,
so I'll make this brief.
Keep your eyes on your
three little friends.
I sincerely doubt he was worried
about the kids with his dying breath.
King Arthur's daughter.
My master's daughter.
And a girl who's weirdly used to killing.
There's gotta be something
connecting them to the Half Dragon.
I'm not a softie like Pincers.
If they insist on buzzing around me,
I'm gonna make use of them.
Scum of the Brave
Hey. You're early.
Not really. More like right on time.
And why didn't you give us
more of a heads-up to come armed?
You know how hard it is to find
something that matches a dress?
Her tastes are more girly than I figured.
What is it?
Nothing.
You seemed to have dressed
up pretty decent, is all.
Must be nice, being a rich girl.
Bet your maid helped you get all set up.
Uh, no! And getting them ready
was a real ordeal! Seriously!
It's hard to move in this.
Was there nothing shorter?
Or maybe something like
what you're wearing, Sara.
This is pretty hard to get
around in, too, trust me.
Really?
Really.
Plus, I picked a white dress
that I thought would suit you.
You like white, right?
I do!
Sara! How do you explain the
design of my dress, then?!
Look at how exposed I am!
For someone with my beauty to go around
in such... scantily clad fashion!
I'll be scouted as a model!
Let's go.
Why did you think this
dress would suit me?!
Explain yourself, Sara!
I mean, you ask why, but...
That's what Sensei picked out.
I see! As to be expected of Master!
He has an eye for quality!
I was in a sour mood before,
but I feel great now!
Sara and Indo's restraining clothing
will make for a better lesson.
Jogamine, you're kinda terrible,
so no handicap for you.
It'd be asking too much.
What are we doing for the lesson?
Last time you reacted to a surprise
attack with one-on-one matchups...
But it was a little too
straightforward and no fun, right?
Hey, we're not exactly doing
this for "fun."
This time, you'll fight
against multiple opponents,
and you know going in
that they're hostile.
It's gonna be really
exciting and educational
because you'll get to try
out all kinds of techniques.
A certain Dark Lord is throwing
a little party today.
The Coffin Count of Storms.
Arguably the strongest Dark
Overlord in western Tokyo.
You all know the Count of Twin Pincers.
He basically runs errands for them.
In other words,
this is gonna be real simple.
We're gonna make this a party to remember!
Yes, Master!
Dark Lords throw these kinds of
parties for the intimidation factor.
They put on a front of glitz and glamour
to show how powerful they are,
both internally and to the outside.
I'm pretty sure the the Coffin Count
of Storms will be there in person.
Ishino's death happened on their turf.
There's no denying they know something.
I'm hungry.
There's going to be food, right?
That's the last thing I'm worried about!
And Sensei, if it was gonna be like this,
you could've said something sooner!
Wait, Sara! Since when have you
referred to Master as Sensei?!
I normally don't overlook
that kind of thing!
Shut up!
We're going!
Master!
It's quite the lively venue, isn't it?
Quit gawking.
They're gonna think you're some bumpkin.
Welcome to the party.
May I have your name?
I am Ed Cyrus.
And I am here in the name of the
great martial supernova, King Rob!
I was sent to offer my lord's regards
to the Coffin Count of Storms.
One moment, please.
Master!
That man in the suit over there
seems... very blue, for some reason.
Is he a Dark Lord?
Do you seriously need to ask?!
I see! Then our aim is to subjugate
the various assembled Dark Lords?
Not at all, no.
But since we're here,
I may as well warn you about
which Dark Lords to avoid.
Don't stare too hard.
They'll take it personally.
Right!
That blue devil-looking guy is the
Judging Count of Silver String.
Part of the Three-String Alliance
that rules northern Tokyo.
Looks outgoing enough, but he's
a real dour, antisocial type.
Over by the stairs is the
Count of the Warped Garden.
An awful piece of work,
so if he talks to you, just ignore him.
The Counts of Mournful
Pulsation and Mournful Spray.
Just avoid them. Period.
What did I say about staring?!
If you knew these bigwigs
were gonna be here,
why didn't you warn us?!
Learning to improvise is
part of the lesson.
I'm sorry, sir, but the name Ed
Cyrus was not on the guest list.
Would it be all right if I checked
your identification or invitation?
Sure, one sec...
How's this?
I don't happen to have
my insurance card, so...
It's on. Go ahead and use E3.
Don't shoot! You might hit the guests!
They won't use guns in here.
Now, for the opening act.
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Lee Francis
Henry Lin
Gabriella Alabanza
Riley Dalton
Sho Stifler
Next Time
Do you know the saying
"lead with the edge"?
It means you can swing, but you won't
cut shit without a blade.
A lesson that seems actually applicable!
You're getting
the hang of this, Master!
Next time is Episode 10,
"A Brave's Instruction".
A Brave's Instruction
Go, go, Master!