I'm gonna kill every one of you fuckers!
Don't you dare hurt that lady!
Don't look, Kaeko-san!
Mistress, stop staring at the
back of his balls and flee!
Ogata! Stop laughing and grab him!
What's going on here?
Who are these people?
This isn't Yuusaku.
Who the hell are you?
Flee, Norabo!
I'll hold them off!
Run!
Kaeko-san!
Your clothes...
Just hurry!
Go! Go!
Wait.
That's Sergeant Kikuta.
I know what's going on here.
Sergeant Kikuta was, in fact, doing his job.
Hanazawa Yuusaku!
You're the man from before...
Where are your clothes?
Oh, Sergeant Kikuta.
Not him!
Golden Kamuy
Episode 58
Starting Gun of Resolve
Kikuta-san, who are those guys?
No idea.
It's possible Commander Hanazawa had
other people working for him besides me.
I thought this was your Plan B.
No, Plan B was to come up with a fake
Commander Hanazawa and his wife.
That's also horrible.
Will they come after Kaeko-san?
To stop what Lady Hanazawa
did from getting out.
There's no need for that anymore.
I want to marry you.
I'm homeless, and my parents are gone.
I have nothing.
My family has money!
I don't care!
We've lived in different
worlds our whole lives.
Well, you can get used to mine!
You can just live with me from now on.
If you don't have a home,
where are you going to live from now on?
I'll join the army, maybe.
I'm told they have white rice, at least.
Mistress, marriage is something
that binds two houses together.
Your family will never allow it.
You only care so much about how
much a man looks because you
want to get back at all your schoolmates
who got married before you, right?
The idea your school has that girls
who don't get married are leftovers
is bullshit.
You don't need to have a man next
to you to restore your self-respect.
You're capable of proving
your worth on your own.
Let's go, Hamako.
I'm sorry for deceiving you.
Thanks to you, I was able to get a brief
glimpse of a wonderful other world.
Farewell.
Please become a handsome soldier.
Kaneko Kaeko would go on to become a
financial titan known as the Empress.
But what's not as well known is that
during the Russo-Japanese war,
she spared no expense to aid war
widows and care for the wounded.
Choya Shimbun
Ow...
You're crazy, getting shot
protecting a guy like me!
I'm the one who got you
involved after all.
It's fine. And anyway...
I've got a first-class seat to hell.
Forget about me.
And all about Hanazawa Yuusaku, too.
What you said about joining the army...
You're not serious, right?
Thanks for everything.
Give me back that cap, please.
Hanazawa Yuusaku told me that
this was your brother's,
and that he died during
the Sino-Japanese war.
When you said you had a
first-class seat to hell...
Do you blame yourself for
your brother's death?
I'm the one who told him to join the army.
Our family was poor. I told him he
could at least make sure he was fed.
More people died of disease
than bullets during that war.
If I hadn't talked him into joining,
he wouldn't have suffered and died.
I basically murdered him.
It's true that you're the reason
I thought of joining the army.
But in the end, it's my call to make.
No matter what happens,
I'll never be angry with you.
Why don't you forgive
yourself, and move on?
And it won't be that easy
for anybody to kill me.
I'm immortal!
Keep the cap.
Tell Hanazawa Yuusaku about the lady!
He has the right to choose!
He's a problem for the whole army now.
And I'd get kicked out, too.
Forget this whole thing.
If we see each other in the army,
let's pretend we've never met.
See you around, Norabo.
Sergeant Kikuta, I'm sending you
to the 7th Division.
Come up with your own
reason for the transfer.
Get close to Lieutenant Tsurumi and
report to the central government.
Watch him and make sure he
doesn't get out of control.
Who's this?
He'll be doing the same thing.
But to make sure you're both not caught
at once, I want you to act separately.
Just don't get in each other's way.
1904: Hill 203
Yuusaku-dono! Yuusaku-dono! Yuusaku-dono!
So Norabo was a hero of
the Russo-Japanese war.
But I'm the one who got
him to join the army.
So I guess that's a win for me.
Next time we meet, I'll have
to fight Kikuta-san for real.
And this?
Ko.
Wait... This can't be...
I've got it.
This is the location of the gold?
At last...
At last, the war for
the gold will end, huh?
No, no.
It's only just beginning.
You know what this is, right,
Warrant Officer Kikuta?
Sapporo Nakajima Amusement Park
The dead drop.
An old method used by spies.
A technique for handing something
over without physically meeting.
Oh, I found a cigarette.
Hey, wait! You there!
I told them somebody would
pick up a cigarette.
You got careless in my absence.
Private Usami did well.
The copied skins... and this...
You're finished, Lieutenant Tsurumi.
You'll be killed.
I know what you want to say.
If they can't be sure you're alive,
the central government will come to
put a stop to me for good, right?
The gunshot that killed
Warrant Officer Kikuta
is a sign that we have just
destroyed our own line of retreat,
and have no choice but
to capture the gold!
It's the starting gun of our resolve!
I'm not talking about
the central government.
It'll be Norabo that takes you down.
Norabo?
I've got a first-class seat to hell.
And I'll make sure
there's room next to me.
Lieutenant Tsurumi only sits next to me.
Sugimoto.
I think we've got it.
Tell all our forces scattered
around the island!
Do whatever it takes to get
here as soon as possible!
Load your warhorses with weapons and ammo!
And come as fast as you can without rest!
The gold's here?
How do I read this?
This line.
The one that crosses the others.
Do you see it?
Fort Goryoukaku!
There, of all places.
This has gotten interesting, huh Gamushin?
The fact that the code could be
cracked without all the skins...
Resulted in both Hijikata
Toshizou and Lieutenant Tsurumi
solving it at almost the same time!
Wait a second.
Is that the copy of your skin?
It fits here perfectly.
We didn't need it at all!
Hakodate...
Golden Kamuy
Mt. Hakodate
Hakodate Station
Fort Goryoukaku
Hakodate!
The oldest port in Hokkaido
that was opened to the outside world
and a center of international trade.
There are many consulates
and churches here.
It's really shaped like a star?
It's so big I can't even imagine.
How big is it?
1.8 kilometers, if you
go along the outer moat.
Approximately 550 meters
from this side to this one.
What is Goryoukaku, anyway?
The remains of a castle.
The Hakodate Magistrate, a government
building run by the Edo Shogunate,
was located in its center.
Protecting Hokkaido from
Russian expansionism,
diplomacy with Europe and America...
It was created to be the
political center of Ezo.
The outer walls are all that's left.
And the last place we soldiers of the
Shogunate fought the revolutionary army.
Our last great stage.
It's said that Hijikata
Toshizou died at Hakodate.
"All that remains of soldiers' dreams."
Our dream ends at Goryoukaku.
And a new dream will
begin at Goryoukaku, too.
The army used it as a training
ground until 1897, I heard.
But now it's empty.
There are no homes near this place,
so normally nobody comes here.
So they hid it in a place where the
army once had a training ground?
I guess they thought the army'd
never bother to look there.
It's a bold choice.
Where did Nopperabo bring the gold from?
According to what Botaro the
Pirate heard from the old Ainu,
it was seven kilometers to the southwest.
The Russian consulate on Mt. Hakodate.
Kimuspu, this is where the gold is, right?
I was here when the gold was
carried into this building.
We'll go around the back and go inside.
The Russian ambassador who
lived here was a greedy man,
who tried to work with
members of their military
to sell us Ainu weapons and a warship.
But the ship got into an accident.
The ambassador, his family,
and the officers were all aboard,
and they all sank with it.
Since relations with Japan
were getting worse,
no new ambassador ever came.
This place has been locked up ever since.
This way.
The wall in the library in the back.
We put this wall up after he died.
Everyone but me who went down
into this basement is now dead.
Someone's outside!
Otonoshin will have to die.
What was that about?
Whatever it was,
this place isn't safe anymore.
Get the light closer.
Wenkamuy killed them all.
What's this?
Hey, Kimuspu.
What's going on here?
When cracking the code,
without Botaro the Pirate's
hint about Hakodate,
we wouldn't have thought of this
place's star shape so soon.
There's no time to waste.
We'll hurry and find it!
Old Man Nagakura, calm down.
We got here ahead of Lieutenant Tsurumi
and his men, thanks to Botaro.
It might take them days to crack the code.
Oh?
These guys...
Get down.
Any more soldiers' footsteps?
Nobody close.
They're carrying a telegram.
It's from... Lieutenant Tsurumi!
It came from Sapporo! One hour ago!
"Head to Goryoukaku, immediately!"
Oh no...
They solved the code, too...
How long before they're here?
There are two trains that travel
between Sapporo and Hakodate each day.
Sapporo
Otaru
Hakodate
Assuming he leaves in the morning,
that should give us a full day.
And a horse would take even longer.
I see!
No, Lieutenant Tsurumi might
hijack a waiting train.
That'd get him here in 12 hours.
No time to waste! Get digging!
Calm down, Shiraishi!
I'm pretty sure it's not there!
Then where is the gold?
The code didn't have any hints?
Gold
There wasn't the character
for "gold" anyway?
We need to dig it up and run!
There are several buildings inside.
That old storehouse
predates the Hakodate war.
And the smaller buildings
the Army put up...
the Ainu would've known about them, too.
It's likely they hid them under
the floors of one of them.
We should search there first.
I won't say you're wrong...
But wouldn't it be faster to toss
it all into one of the moats?
Gold dust won't rust
underwater, after all.
Then they may have hid it in a well.
It's not here!
Calm down!
Hey, where's Kadokura and Kirawus?
And Kantarou.
We need to find them.
We split up at the station.
They're getting a cart for us.
We've got another problem.
Assuming we find it,
how far can we get with it?
Mt. Hakodate
Aca and his friends must've made
that seven-kilometer journey many times.
How much gold can a cart carry?
If we assume a horse can pull
twice its weight, 800 kilograms.
Assume one bag weighs 60 kilograms.
That's 13 bags at most.
No problem, then, assuming
they can bring 90 carts.
That's not happening!
And what's that square on your head?
Hey, geezer, what was the plan here?
Did you even have one?
Nobody expected we'd have twelve
hours to get the gold out, obviously!
Even Wilk didn't assume two sides would
crack the code at almost the same time.
We're screwed, then.
We'll have to fight.
We can hole ourselves up here, and fight.
Indeed.
Fight the whole 7th
Division? By ourselves?
I've arranged things.
Though I didn't expect things
to be cutting it this close.
14 Hours Earlier
We came on this ship to follow Asirpa.
Friends are waiting in Otaru.
How many?
One hundred twenty.
Weapons, too.
I'd like you to bring your comrades
from Otaru via the afternoon train.
I'm shocked Sofia decided to
work with Hijikata Toshizou.
They've been fighting for the far
east Russian minorities, right?
Would they change their minds that easily?
That's right. Kiroranke
gave up his life for that.
Can we trust them?
They may steal all the gold.
If that happens, we deal with it.
We have little hope of
winning without them.
If Lieutenant Tsurumi gets the
gold, we get nothing.
I think we can trust Sofia.
We will migrate to this land, set
down roots, and gather strength.
This is the multicultural Hokkaido
that Comrade Wilk wanted.
And someday this will be our base
of operations against Russia.
That is the Far East Federation
that Comrade Yulbars wanted.
I won't deny either Wilk
nor Yulbars their dream.
That is my decision.
Now decide if you'll follow me.
What country are these gaijin from?
The going is easy,
but the way back is scary...
Sapporo Rail Yard
We thank you for your cooperation.
They've fought against the Russian army.
They're veteran guerrillas.
This won't be a hopeless fight.
And we have one other advantage.
I, Hijikata Toshizou, have
fought at Hakodate before.
I know exactly how to do it.
Next Time
Our Kamuy
Next Time: Our Kamuy!