CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
Why are you so restless?
We opened the Detective Agency,
but we don't have any clients!
That just means everything is peaceful!
That's true!
H-Help me!
A client! Get the tea!
A-Anyway, let's sit him down.
Where?
What am I gonna do?!
Hey! Everyone calm down!
Have some tea!
So, how can we help you?
The contents of my bag
turned into apples and potatoes!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
A brilliant inspiration
rinto hirameku
I'm sure we'll find it
We're Precure, after all
kitto mitsukeru
datte Precure
It's calling to us
watashitachi wo yondeiru
Where's the truth?
What will we discover?
shinjitsu wa doko?
hakken wa nani?
One mystery after another
nazo ga nazo wo yondeiru
Gather the pieces
From now to the past and future
Puzzle wo atsume
genzai kara kako, mirai e
Like evidence
Something shining across time
shouko mitai ni
toki wo koe kagayaku mono
How? How? Is it a trick?
nande? nande? Trick kana?
Why? Why? We'll face it
naze? naze? tachimukau
Look and feel
Figure out the secret
mitsumete kanjite
himitsu wo tokiakasu no
One brave step will lead to a miracle
yuuki no ippo ga kiseki made michibiku
The answer?!
Found when you notice the unnoticed
kotae!?
Kizuitenai mono ni kizuita toki
It's destiny, it's love
Whispered in a tiny voice
unmei ne tte daisuki yo tte
chicchana koe
Let's walk that road together!
issho ni aruite ikou!
Let's look for it
The hint is in the heart!
sagashi ni iku yo Heart ni Hint!
A brilliant inspiration
rinto hirameku
The jewel key connects us
Opening the link moving forward
Jewel no kagi ga tsunagaru
tsugi e no kizuna hiraku yo
Hey, us being born and having met
Is a wonderful mystery
nee umareta koto
meguri aeta koto no shinpi
Go on! Star Detective Precure!
susume! Meitantei Precure!
Exciting! Our First Client!
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
I'm Detective Anna Akechi!
I'm Mikuru Kobayashi!
Oh, okay. Nice to meet you.
I gave him my business card!
I feel like a detective!
That's great, Mikuru!
Sheesh!
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Junichi Komatsuzaki.
UNIVERSITY STUDENT
JUNICHI KOMATSUZAKI
You said there are apples
and potatoes in your bag?
Yeah! I suddenly noticed
the contents had changed!
Apples, potatoes, onions,
bread, and an apron.
What was in your bag originally?
My manga manuscript...
-And some clothes.
-Manga manuscript?!
You're a manga artist?
No, I'm just trying to be one.
I came to show
my manuscript to a publisher.
If they like it,
I could become a manga artist!
EDITORIAL DEPARTMENT
No, I will be one!
Wow!
Where did you notice
your manuscript was missing?
Huh?
Here?
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
I went for a walk to calm down before
going to the publisher, and ended up here.
I then noticed that my bag felt heavy.
P-Potatoes?!
Huh? Where's my manuscript?
My manuscript?!
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
D-Detective Agency?
Whoa! Help! Detective!
How could the contents of my bag change?
Hmm.
Isn't the strap too short?
But I don't remember making it shorter.
I got it!
It wasn't the contents,
but the whole bag that got switched!
No!
This is definitely my... huh?
It's dirty.
Did you drop it somewhere?
Now that you mention it!
In front of the station!
I see...
I've found the location of
another Makoto Jewel.
I'll steal it with grace.
No, I should go!
You can, like, stand down!
That's my line, baby!
There they go again.
Easy there!
Being passionate is great and all,
but you're barking up the wrong tree.
I, Goemon, will take it on!
There he is... what a pain.
Maestro Usonoir. Leave it to me.
You just want to go, don't you?
That's so totally wack!
No! It's for the newcomer!
I'll take her along and show her
the ropes of being a thief!
She can watch me and learn!
He doesn't need to do all that!
Go, Goemon.
Cure Arcana Shadow!
Lie lie, sir!
Yeah, it was here!
Someone ran toward me and we collided
and I dropped my bag!
Could it be?
When you two collided,
you happened to exchange bags,
and you took the wrong bag?
I see! That could be it!
What did that person look like?
I don't remember.
There was just someone here
with that same bag!
She was looking for a man
who took her bag.
Anna, your reasoning was right!
Yeah!
Where is that person now?
Not sure. She went that way.
What did she look like?
-A young woman with glasses.
-Hmm, I see.
Her hair was like this.
I'm done! It was this person, right?
This person?
Yeah, that's her!
What?!
-He recognized her!
-Amazing.
Let's go find her!
According to the Tome of Mirages,
the clue to finding the Makoto Jewel is,
"A square object, wrapped in purple
and stuffed with dreams."
Wrapped in purple? A purple cloth?
A bag.
Painting classes!
ATELIER PLENTY
PAINTING CLASSES
Now taking new students!
Please take one!
Painting classes!
I want to learn how to sketch faces.
Do you want me to teach you?
Hm? What's that?
I've never seen her.
-No?
-Sorry.
Still no information.
This might be impossible.
It's okay! We'll find her for sure!
Yeah!
I found it! Wrapped in purple!
You can leave that bag,
no, the Makoto Jewel with me!
A Makoto Jewel?
The Phantom Thieves' Guild?!
T-Thieves' guild?
We'll find the bag
with the manga manuscript!
And we won't give it to you!
You're passionate!
So hot you're boiling me up!
But you picked the wrong guy!
I'll take that!
Stop!
Open!
Pre-Kit Light!
I-It got big?
Yeah! A Jett-senpai invention!
We can draw what we want
with the light, and...
It takes shape!
A peanut?
No, a trampoline.
I see!
We'll get your bag back!
Wait up!
What do you think? This is a thief's work.
What about the Makoto Jewel?
Lemme sit down.
Um...
They're all round.
Here's a square!
Is this it?
It's just bread.
You drew a blank.
They were talking about finding a bag
that had a manga manuscript in it.
Hey!
Where are you going?
Newcomers these days!
G-Give it back!
We've got to look for the manuscript!
Gotcha.
I see now.
Whoa!
The Makoto Jewel must be
in the manga manuscript.
What?
Who'll find it first?
It's on, Star Detectives!
MAKOTO MIRAI
Why would a thieves' guild
want my manuscript?
We won't let them have it!
We'll find it first!
Just forget it.
I draw manga because
I want to make everyone smile.
But I don't want my manga
to put you detectives in danger!
We feel the same!
Detectives make people in trouble smile!
So we always gold-star solve our cases!
Leave it to us, the Star Detectives!
Detectives...
Wait for us at the agency!
Let me read your manga once we find it!
Sure!
Where is that woman?
She came this way, right?
Yeah.
By the way, in the bag were apples,
potatoes, onions, bread,
and an apron, right?
Yeah. Maybe it's someone from
a restaurant or a food store?
If it is...
PORK CUTLET
SETTING UP
There are way too many restaurants.
TAKOYAKI
Oh! Curry!
CURRY HOUSE
They say apples help
make the flavor smoother!
You have a point!
Hmm... I don't know her.
We thought for sure it was a curry shop.
Maybe a different one?
Oh, I know!
Have you seen this apron before?
Hang on! What's this?
Isn't it a ketchup stain?
Ketchup?
Hmm... Where is it?
Where's that bag with the manuscript?
Hmm... Cure Arcana Shadow, help me look!
I don't need to.
Yeah, she already
knows where it is, right?
Yeah.
W-What did you say?
So what foods use ketchup?
-Pasta!
-Omurice!
-Hamburgers!
-Fries!
You're both wrong!
These potatoes and onions are sprouting,
and the apples aren't fresh.
No restaurant would use these ingredients!
-Huh?
-Then what?
If you're stuck, go back to the beginning.
That's the detective's golden rule.
Yeah! Junichi bumped into her here,
and dropped his bag.
I thought it got dirty when he dropped it,
but it's paved here!
So it is!
WET PAINT!
Pochitan! That's wet paint!
Pochitan!
I hope we can get it off!
You dropped something!
I see!
This is the answer!
-The bag is surely...
-Over there!
ATELIER PLENTY
PAINTING CLASSES
Come in!
It's definitely her!
Oh! My bag!
There's Junichi's bag!
They're identical!
No wonder they got mixed up!
I can't believe you two found me!
The stain on the bag wasn't dirt.
Nor ketchup on the apron.
I got it when I saw
the paint on the handkerchief.
I thought the stains might be paint.
But!
The paper Anna dropped.
When I saw the flyer, I figured it out!
ATELIER PLENTY
NOW TAKING NEW STUDENTS!
The stains were paint!
The things in the bag weren't for eating.
They were for painting practice!
You're right! You really figured it out!
We're Star Detectives after all!
You call yourselves Star Detectives!
Hmm? This is a pretty neat manga.
I'll take it! I'm off!
Stop!
They came!
I won't let you escape!
So you caught up to me!
How did you know the manuscript
was at the painting school?
JUNJUN KOMATTSU
It was the bread.
Bread?
Yes, the newcomer figured it out.
Bread can be used like an eraser,
to erase the lines.
You knew just by looking in the bag!
That's my girl!
No biggie.
JUNJUN KOMATTSU
Here's a prize for catching up to me.
Lies, envelop!
Come on, Hanninda!
Hanninda!
Open!
Jewel Cure Watch!
Precure! Wake-up Time!
3! Discover!
6! And face one another!
9! We are the miraculous duo!
Spin around!
And finish off cutely!
Gold-star closing the case on any mystery!
Star Detective, Cure Answer!
Jumping towards smiles
with layered reasoning!
Star Detective, Cure Mystique!
Star Detective Precure!
I'll show you my answer!
Hanninda!
Kudos!
So this is a Hanninda! Maestro Usonoir
bestowed some incredible powers!
Usonoir?
Oh, yes.
He's the great boss of
the Phantom Thieves' Guild.
Maestro Usonoir!
I'll bring back the Makoto Jewel
for Maestro Usonoir!
So I must eliminate you two!
Hanninda!
Junichi just wants to make people happy.
You can't use his manga like this!
Who cares?
As long as Maestro Usonoir is happy,
that's all that matters!
Hanninda!
Mystique Reflection!
W-What?
Answer Attack!
Hanninda!
Huh... Not bad.
-The manga manuscript!
-And Junichi's smile!
We'll get them both back!
This is our answer!
CUREtto Case Closed!
Hanninda!
Pochi Pochi Cure Cure!
I had fun today, Precures!
Let's meet again!
CURETTO DETECTIVE AGENCY
T-Thank you detectives!
JUNJUN KOMATTSU
Junjun Komattsu?
Yeah! That's my pen name!
Oh! Uh, um, Mr. Junjun Komattsu?
You know him?
Yeah! I love his manga!
SOLVED BY THE CYBORG DETECTIVES!
You're going to become
a famous manga artist!
Huh? Really? Is that your deduction
as a Star Detective?
It's not a deduction, I just know!
How can I explain...
If he's such an amazing manga artist,
I want to read it too!
Me too!
-I want to read it!
-Hang on! Me first!
I'm first!
This calls for rock, paper, scissors!
Okay! Ready?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Again!
(NaNaNaNa why? Why? WHY?
NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER?!)
(NaNaNaNa naze? naze? WHY?
NaNaNaNa nazo? nazo! ANSWER?!)
Connect the dots, oh? Oh my!
ten to ten musundara ara? ara!
Could it be a "gold-star case closed!"?
Could it?
"hanamaru kaiketsu!" kana? kana?
Reasoning turns around riddles
Twists and turns, reverse
suiri to nazo wa uragaeshi
niten santen gyakuten
Even words and behavior are traps? Traps!
Don't just believe them! No!
kotoba ya shigusa sae wana? wana!
unomi ni shite wa dame! dame!
Pay attention, think and then
Take the first step!
yoku mite, kangaete, sorekara
fumidasu no yo ippo!
When I see someone in trouble
I immediately want to help
komatteiru hito mitara
sugu ni tasuketai
Cause I wanna, wanna do something
So I go running off
datte nantoka nantoka nantoka shitakute
kakedashiteiru
Na Na Na mystery! Mystery!
Na Na Na nazo! nazo!
Solving mysteries
Is what a Star Detective does
nazo wo toku no ga meitantei
See through lies and find truth
Find the answer for a smile
uso ka makoto ka mikiwamete
egao no kotae mitsukeru
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 100
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 100 bai
Working together, we can figure it out
Friends are a true miracle
chikara awasete norikoeru
tomo wa kiseki no katamari
Let's go! Star Detective
iku yo! Meitantei
Na Na Na why? Why?
Together, I've got courage times 1,000
Na Na Na naze? naze?
minna to iru to yuuki 1,000 bai
Hand in hand with my friends
Until everything's solved!
tomodachi to te ni te wo totte
banjikaiketsu suru made!
We're Precure, after all
(NaNaNaNa mystery? Mystery! ANSWER!)
DATTE Precure
(NaNaNaNa naze? nazo! ANSWER!)
There's another case!
But we're feeling conflicted!
Why didn't you ask me first?
Don't take on clients without asking!
No holding back with cases and friendship!
Star Detective Precure!
"Star Detectives in Trouble?"
That mystery! CUREtto Case Closed!