Thank goodness, bro...
Master Seiichiro!
Master Seiichiro, hold on!
But how? It didn't hit him!
Master Ist, what's going on?
Oh, I knew it. His barrier is gone.
Smooch.
No good, huh?
M-Master Ist!
What are you doing during an
emergency in our holy church?!
As I suspected, it's best
if it's the same person.
Priest, you have a lot of magical energy.
Wh-What are you saying?
We need to take him to the infirmary!
Oh, you can't.
If you take Kondu to
the infirmary, he'll die.
So won't you sleep with him?
Huh?
Well, didn't you just cast
a barrier on Kondu?
I did.
Um, you didn't know that Kondu
has no resistance to magical energy?
Right now, Kondu is experiencing
acute magic-sickness.
You need to acclimate him
to the magical energy
or it's going to go berserk inside of him.
Then that's why you...
Yeah.
But it looks like mouth-to-mouth
wasn't anywhere close to enough.
On top of that, it's better if
the caster does the acclimating,
so please infuse your
magical energy inside him.
Th-That's...
I understand.
No need!
ISEKAI OFFICE WORKER: THE OTHER WORLD'S
BOOKS DEPEND ON THE BEAN COUNTER
EPISODE 11: I GOT HOSPITALIZED
Aresh!
I'm the one who manages
everything for him.
Give him back to me.
"Give him back"?
Master Seiichiro isn't an object.
Moreover, he's very weak right now.
I won't hand him to you.
Aresh-sama?
Master Seiichiro! You're awake!
Seiichirou!
Oh, thank goodness.
You're safe...
Siegvold.
Your Highness...
Aresh normally sees to Kondou's health.
You can leave everything to him.
Relinquish the man.
I understand.
Will Master Seiichiro be all right?
Well, probably.
Aresh-san is used to taking care of him.
Huh?
Quellbus!
I'm going to use the back room.
We're not some cheap inn for quick flings.
He's definitely magic-sick,
but there's always a chance
it's something else.
It's better to have someone on hand
who can explain or respond appropriately.
Explain, huh?
Aresh...
How many magical energy recovery
tonics have you had today?
One.
Don't lie.
You probably drank one to acclimate
Kondu on your way here, too.
In your current state
of relying on medication,
using enough magical energy to treat
him will take too much out of you.
I know.
That's why I came here.
Don't worry about me.
I know my magical energy limits best.
Please don't do anything too reckless.
It's so hot...
My head and my whole body hurt.
It reminds me of that time I had the flu.
MEDICINE
I didn't get any rest until
I collapsed from the fever.
I was still getting work files
while I couldn't go into the office,
and my fever spiked to 40 degrees Celsius.
I feel like my consciousness is
more faded than it was back then,
but I'm not uncomfortable.
In fact, I'm nice and warm...
It's soothing,
like soaking in a hot spring.
I remember this feeling...
Aresh-sama?
You finally woke up...
Good grief.
It's still going to take some time.
You're such a reckless fool.
When did you get back?
This morning.
The instant I returned,
I found out you went to the church,
so I immediately headed there.
I barely made it in time.
I swear, you're so...
You never listen to anyone, and you
have no regard for your own well-being.
This is what happens the second
I take my eyes off of you.
On top of that, you didn't
send me a single letter
and wound up collapsing
into another man's arms!
Honestly, if it weren't for that,
I might not forgive you.
Aresh-sama...
Welcome back.
I'm home.
Yes, he seems to be fine now.
I'm heading back to the estate.
Keep an eye on Seiichirou
once he wakes up.
Keep an eye on him?
Wait, Aresh!
After that, I was ordered to stay
hospitalized for three days.
It's now the second day.
I haven't seen Aresh-sama since.
Seriously, I was so shocked
when I heard you collapsed!
Never mind that.
Where are the documents?
Huh?
I came to visit you, but now it looks
like I only came to make you work...
Speaking of visitors,
immediately after I awoke...
Master Seiichiro, I offer you
my sincerest apologies!
Oh, no... There's no need
for you to apologize.
Please raise your head.
No. I knew you had no
resistance to magical energy,
yet I still exposed you to such danger.
It's my fault that I wasn't doing well
that day due to lack of sleep,
and going to the chapel
was entirely my decision.
Besides, I probably
would have died instantly
if you hadn't cast that barrier on me.
Thank you very much for saving me.
Actually, about that...
Kondu, you have a visitor.
Then I'll take my leave.
Please don't overexert yourself.
Valtom-san...
How are you doing, Kondu-sama?
Thanks to Aresh-sama,
I've already made a full recovery,
but I was told to take every
precaution and rest until tomorrow.
That's excellent news.
Aresh-sama has informed me that he will
fetch you when it is time to return home.
I see...
The young master is currently
recuperating at the estate.
Huh?
To be precise, he has fallen ill from an
excessive amount of recovery tonics.
The purification expedition,
the magic beast subjugation,
and then immediately acclimating
magical energy upon his return
placed considerable strain
on even the young master,
whose magic reserves are vast.
So that's what happened...
I thought it was strange.
He treated me at the infirmary
instead of at home.
Usually, Aresh-sama would have taken
me there to keep an eye on me himself.
Kondu-sama.
I have known the young master,
Aresh-sama, since he was a child,
and have had the privilege
of attending to his needs all these years.
It may be presumptuous of a mere
steward like myself to say as much,
but I harbor feelings for him
akin to those of a parent.
Therefore, Kondu-sama...
I know that what I am about to ask runs
contrary to the young master's wishes.
My top priority is safeguarding
the young master's health.
Right.
Since meeting you,
the young master has changed.
He has shed his former lethargy
and became more vibrant than
I have ever seen him before.
It brings me joy that the young
master has fallen in love,
and in my eyes, you are the savior
who has given him the vitality to live.
However...
That is all contingent on
the young master's health.
Though I believe the young master's
feelings are important,
I desire that he see to his
well-being above all else.
Perhaps that is merely the
sentiment of an old man.
No, you're absolutely right.
I've been too dependent on Aresh-sama.
I have a habit of prioritizing work
while neglecting my own health.
Now I've compromised
Aresh-sama's health, as well.
The monster subjugation
is a perfect example.
The very one putting Aresh in peril is me.
I'm sorry. This is all
a failure on my part.
There is no need to apologize to me.
After all, I'm sure the young
master decided on his own
to subjugate the magic beasts
purely to impress you.
However, even if it means
incurring his resentment,
I wish to protect the
young master's health.
Please remember one thing.
Many of us would be at a loss
if you were to fall ill.
Well? How are you feeling?
I'm doing great, thanks to you.
I was able to get some proper rest.
Didn't you have your subordinates
bring you documents to work on?
I haven't done much of it.
Now, regarding my bill...
Oh, don't worry about that.
You're a civil servant, Kondu.
So this is one of the perks of
working at the royal palace!
You look a lot better.
You got here pretty early.
He looks like his regular self.
If Valtom-san hadn't told me, I might
have never known that he was bedridden.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
Indeed.
I'm guessing one of the reasons
he wanted me hospitalized here was
so I wouldn't see him in that state.
You feel hot. Do you still have a fever?
No, I'm fine.
Hey, why don't you save all that
affection for when you get home?
Really?
Really.
You're not pushing
yourself again, are you?
How many times must I tell you
the infirmary isn't the place for that?
Oh, Kondu, you're going home already?
Ist-san and... Sigma-kun?
G-Good morning.
Who is that?
The child who made my abacus.
Why are the two of you together?
Ist-san invited me to see
the sorcery department.
We got to talking about a magic
tool when we met at the church,
and he asked me to make
one together with him.
Huh?!
I love woodworking, but I've
always admired magic tools...
But crafting them costs a fortune.
I thought the only people
who got to make them
were artisans working under nobles.
I thought I'd never get a chance
to be involved! I'm so happy!
He beat me to the punch.
Given Sigma-kun's ingenuity and drive,
I hoped he'd attend the private school
and eventually work at the palace.
Ideally, I wanted him for
the accounting department!
Kondu, we made something amazing!
It's based on Sigma's idea.
It's only a prototype,
but we can actually measure
magical energy with this!
Please tell me the details.
Hey. You were hospitalized in the
infirmary until your discharge just now.
What's with the sudden burst
of motivation to work?!
Huh? B-But, I mean...
We're going home.
Okay...
Ist-san, please write up a...
Yeah, not happening.
U-Um, I wrote a simple summary of
the mechanism and materials we used.
Sigma-kun, you're the best!
What? It's nothing, really.
I always saw these kinds of
documents at my boss's place.
He's so brilliant. How wonderful.
I want him for the accounting
department after all.
Wait, if he went into the sorcery
department, my life would be a lot easier.
What a dilemma!
Do you remember what I just said?
Yes, of course.
Let's go home.
I'll take my time to go over it there...
Ow, ow, ow!
Excuse me.
Wh-What are you doing to Master
Seiichiro after he just recovered?!
This is nothing, Siegvold-sama.
Please don't worry about it.
Aresh-sama, I'm the one at fault.
Please let me go...
That's enough, Aresh!
Master Seiichiro,
are you in better health?
Yes, thank you very much.
Siegvold-sama?
I came because I heard you
were being discharged.
Please let me know if I can be of any help
regarding what we spoke of the other day.
I'll be on my way.
What we spoke of the other day...
Actually, about that...
The ball of magical energy that flew our
way that day wasn't just an accident.
Huh?
I learned of the situation
from Prince Yurius
after Commander Indolark carried you away.
A child present at the time remarked
that the prayer and incantation
were notably different from usual.
I foolishly failed to notice it
while I was talking with you.
However, Master Ist remembered
every word of it and informed me.
It wasn't the normal prayer we use,
but one that consumes far
more magic than necessary.
I tried to stop it, but someone
intentionally triggered an explosive surge
from the child who lost control
and shot it at Kondu.
The only one capable of such a thing...
Now, let us begin the prayer.
Cipriano...
Is he trying to cover up the embezzlement?
Even so, his methods...
However, there isn't any definitive proof,
so we've been quietly
conducting an investigation.
Master Seiichiro.
I promise you that I will testify fully
and truthfully, no matter the situation.
Then, while I was hospitalized,
Cipriano submitted the
income and expenses report,
bringing my temporary assignment
to the church to an end.
Welcome home, Aresh-sama and Kondu-sama.
It's good to be back.
We were so worried!
I'll make sure to bring
you back to full health!
Thank you very much.
I knew it. There's no similarity at all.
There's nothing left for me
to do at the church.
As for the private school,
Her Holiness and His Highness
are heading the project with my support.
As for the finances,
all I had to do was submit the
paperwork to Prime Mister Camile.
So why was I the one targeted?
Something doesn't sit right...
Seiichirou, are you all right?
Not to worry. I'm perfectly fine.
You've lost a little weight.
Have I?
I feel like you're the one
who's lost some weight.
It tends to happen when
an expedition runs long.
You're already thin to begin with,
so you really need to take
better care of your health.
Okay.
Really? You're quick to lie.
I really did take my time
and rest properly.
Aren't you the one who isn't
properly resting, Aresh-sama?
I'm fine now.
Sorry for worrying you.
I was pretty worried when Aresh-sama
immediately went to hunt magic beasts
right after the purification expedition,
but does he realize that?
Um, Aresh-sama...
What is it?
Is there anything you wish for?
Huh?
It'd have to be something
I can provide, though.
Is there anything you'd like
me to do or get for you?
I'd like to thank you
for saving my life again.
But you won't take monetary
compensation, right?
Of course not.
That's why I want to do something
to pay you back in a different way.
It could be anything.
You're my savior, so I'm willing
to do just about anything for you.
Anything, you say?
Anything.
Not that I'll quit my job, though.
In that case, change the
way you speak to me.
Huh?
Have I said something rude to you?
No, that's not it.
I'm telling you to change
your tone with me.
My tone?
I want you to speak to me
like you do that boy.
Huh?
Oh, do you mean Sigma-kun?
He's a stall vendor
and I hire him for work,
so the dynamic is completely different.
So what?
I'm closer to you than a child like that!
In other words, this noble who has a face
as beautiful as a sculpted masterpiece
and is the strongest knight
in the kingdom is jealous
of a little boy barely
over ten years of age?
My chest hurts...
Where? How does it hurt?! Let me see!
That's not it...
It's just that it's been a while since
my heartstrings were tugged like this.
It's not an illness or anything...
This is too much.
EPISODE 12
WE CORNERED HIM. AND THEN...