Episode 6
That's basically it.
You all should have felt the
various changes in your bodies.
As for me, apart from the collection,
another purpose of this trip
is to witness your transformation.
These valleys...
...are transforming us?
Zhou Tian? Qi?
What on earth is this place?
I remember now.
Qi. That's right, qi.
Nash is a telekinetic.
I know what sect Honda comes from.
Vista can use the power of runes.
I'm not sure about Chanon yet.
Miss Basha, I hold no prejudice
against your worldview,
but we're not the chosen ones.
According to Liu, we're all
Outcasts who can use qi.
And you...
You're a voodoo priestess, right?
Who are you people?
Don't worry about us.
Liu, Judy,
are you two also Outcasts?
That's right.
But in a fight, our abilities
won't be much use.
Especially Judy,
so you'll need to protect her.
Those inside, please let us through!
Go back! This isn't where you belong!
The things here
don't belong to you either!
A woman?
May I ask whether you're from the
Company or the Quan Xing Sect?
None of your business!
Get out of here!
No, it is my business.
If you're from the Company,
then we need to talk.
Wu Gensheng's collection
doesn't belong to us,
nor does it belong to the Company.
If you're from the Quan Xing Sect,
who knows how much of this
stuff you've seized by force!
All right, everyone heard that.
Neither side has any moral
qualms about the collection,
but the opposition is formidable.
Pressing ahead is extremely dangerous,
but you'll have a chance
of becoming an Outcast.
Of course, you can also give up.
You can keep the deposit.
Keep going!
Keep going! Keep going!
All right. Since it's decided,
there's no point hanging around here.
Chanon, you're with me.
Honda, Nash, Basha,
you guys stay with the group.
Liu and Judy, stay in the
center of the formation!
This is...
These are the symbols of the God of War.
They can unleash your potential.
All right, guys!
Let's rush in!
Ben...
What do you think?
I have absolutely no
interest in the reward now.
It's not just me. Everyone who
came here feels the same.
If the collection in this cave
really has something to do
with these magical powers,
then we won't let Liu
take it away so easily!
Everyone, ultimately this is
Jinfeng's and my business!
Those foreign Outcasts aren't pushovers,
and it looks like they can work together!
If you guys wanna leave,
then hurry!
If you're not leaving,
then I, Xia Liuqing, owe you a big favor!
Everyone, get ready to fight to the death!
Why?!
Why didn't Aimolu react
when that girl attacked?
Damn it!
What kind of lung capacity is that?
Mr. Honda, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Those intense flames...
only caused minor burns to his skin!
Chanon! Don't chase after her!
What's wrong, Kate?
Nothing.
I just thought this would
be more comfortable.
Your... Your face...
I'm perfectly fine!
Ever since we entered the valley,
this power has been flowing within me.
If I channel it, it grows
stronger and stronger!
You felt it too, right, Ben?
Yeah...
Let them advance further!
Ben, I have a feeling that
we can become the chosen ones!
They're retreating! Everyone advance!
Wait!
Don't!
Idiots!
The difference in skill is too great!
If it weren't for their numbers,
do you really think these
wood-choppers could stop me?!
Besides that black girl,
they can control them too?
As long as I can circulate the power
within my body faster and faster,
you'll see that Aimolu's power
is actually connected to mine!
Got him!
Keep firing!
Aimolu will regenerate anyway!
These tiny tunnels are so annoying!
Let me seal them all!
One down...
Damn it, he's equipped with something!
There's no doubt about it!
That bastard is connected to Ma Xianhong!
Judging by his reaction,
he's a weakling!
Liu...
I'm fine.
Watch yourself!
Just finish your own mission.
Judy, you're the main character this time!
Don't slow down! Keep advancing!
Are you scared, Fatty Liu?
Good... very good... excellent!
Want me to give you another little push?
Something's wrong!
These people are acting way too weird.
Elijah!
Here's the rest of your payment.
From now on, your only
mission is to protect Judy!
Everyone, if those humanoid
branches are bothering you,
leave them to me to sort out.
Aimolu!
What happened to my Aimolu?
Superhuman strength...
I need to find out
what this guy did to Aimolu.
Honda! Saliva!
Watch out for that guy's saliva!
Are you afraid I'll digest
you with my saliva?
You're overreacting.
This saliva is the power of a sage.
As I haven't reached the level of a sage,
I still have the limitations of a human.
Humans... don't eat humans.
This guy... is too dangerous...
The large intestines,
small intestines, stomach,
San Jiao, gall bladder, and bladder,
collectively known as the "Six Fu Organs."
My ability is called the Sage Thief,
or rather,
the Six Viscera's Borrowed Immortality.
It's based on the Six Fu Organs,
creating a perfect digestive system.
It instantly decomposes matter,
transforming absorbed nutrients into qi.
Next, it extracts moisture from the air,
mixing it with super-powered saliva,
creating a corrosive
agent lethal to anything!
My saliva is mixed with my qi,
and unless this qi is completely depleted,
it will continue to consume the object.
If I don't get into any accidents,
my life will be very long,
and very boring.
It feels like...
I'm becoming less and less human.
I can no longer feel my arms...
What are you doing? Idiot!
I'm not your burden!
I... am already like you now!
This power is amazing!
It's like the whole
world has been renewed!
That freak Elijah is so strong
because they entered this world long ago!
Now I'm here too!
I want more! More power!
The treasure here is
connected to this power,
so it must be mine!
Move!
Wait for me! Guys!
Don't leave me behind!
I don't want to die here.
I also want to see the treasure!
Everyone gained mysterious powers
after entering this place.
But why have you all changed
so much more than me?
Nothing.
I just thought this would be...
That's right.
Do I do this?
Lower my center of gravity like an animal?
Yes...
The power in my back can
flow more easily now.
That's right. Maybe this is
what we were originally like.
As long as we can harness this power,
it doesn't matter what we become!
The timing is about right.
If it doesn't take too long,
I should still be able
to do whatever it takes.
I hope Bao'er hasn't forgotten
what I told her to do.
It's almost time... to make my move!
I've never seen this before.
There are others lying in wait
in these little tunnels!
You...
Liu Mingyuan, right?
Damn this terrain!
Guess we'll have to work harder.
Someone's there!
Over here!
Charge!
This woman was always with Fatty Liu...
Xia, Granny, cover me!
He's retreating! That guy's retreating!
Not yet.
Still not yet!
Qiu! Help me!
Zhang Chulan? Where are you?
I've been keeping an eye
on everyone from behind!
Come help me!
Baldy Liu is trying to escape!
You kept me behind to stop
him from running away, right?
That guy must know someone
from Biyou Village!
You're helping Xia because you want to
find Ma Xianhong's kidnappers, right?
Baldy Liu is an important lead!
If you know everything, then you
could've taken down Baldy Liu!
Sorry, I was recently injured...
Zhang Chulan...
Such an important matter...
Why didn't you say something sooner?
My bad.
Internal injuries, pretty bad...
He wants to mess with me,
yet he also wants to do his job.
This guy is so greedy...
Hurry up and go, otherwise
Baldy Liu will actually escape.
Bye!
You guys can take your time and fight!
My bad, Zhang Chulan!
I shouldn't have been so indecisive!
Damn it!
Abandoning your job to mess with me?
Wang Zhenqiu, what the
hell is wrong with you?
Take the main road, my darling!
Bao'er!
Cover me!
Zhang Chulan, you...
Fire again!
Xia, we can't stop them all!
Deal with these Outcasts first!
We'll handle the rest later!
No way! I won't let anyone's filthy
hands touch the Sect Leader's things!
Hey, Jinfeng! There's no choice!
Listen to him.
As for Zhang Chulan...
Let me keep you company!
Up until we entered the valley,
Wang Zhenqiu, you were indeed
the perfect troublemaker for me.
But you should've focused on your job.
If you wanted to target me,
you shouldn't have let me learn
your ulterior motives.
Your true objective was to
find leads about Ma Xianhong
by engaging with these intruders...
All right! Let's move out
according to the plan, everyone.
What people desire is also their weakness.
Don't tell me you're just
playing the Monkey King.
Even if you really were the Monkey King,
as long as the headband incantation
is recited, you'd be screwed.
Monkey King...
Damn it, not a single one of these
Part Timers is easy to deal with...
What if that monkey becomes angry?
Bao'er!
I need to tell you something.
If you see me charging
in during the operation,
stop anyone who tries to stop me!
Especially Wang Zhenqiu!
Got it!
The small tunnels on both sides are gone.
The terrain has changed.
What... What is this place?
Am I nearly there?
Hold on! I must hold on!
Bao'er, you have to hold on too!
Is this the place?
Translation & Timing: Henry Lin
Editing: Alicia Ashby
QC: William Haggard
FQC: Sriram Gurunathan
"He who steals a hook is executed,
he who steals a state becomes a prince."
Cutting Open Satchels...
You know about this despite
being a foreigner!
Do you know this saying?
"Robbers will not vanish
till the death of the sages."
Yes...
It's also from Zhuangzi's
Cutting Open Satchels.
The entire section reflects Zhuangzi's
view on the chaotic times.
Self-cultivation, family management,
state governance, and world peace.
From the perspective of bringing
world peace, it's correct.
But I'm just a humble cultivator.
I have my own perspective.
A petty thief steals a pearl,
a prince steals a kingdom.
If one reaches the level of a sage,
what do you think would be
worthy for him to steal?
Only one thing:
the vitality of this world.
This is the technique of
my sect, the Sage Thief!
It has another name:
the Six Viscera's Borrowed Immortality!