It's too quiet.
And too dark.
What are you doing? There isn't
a single guard in the museum!
Over.
Oh, come on. You're the one who told me to
focus on the search for Mr. Yelle, sir.
Over.
That doesn't mean you can neglect
your guard duties, dummy!
Over.
Fine.
I'll start heading back now, so stand
guard for me until I get there, sir.
Over.
Stand guard for him, he says? Damn him.
The most marvelous of them all
has made her entrance!
And tonight, I am too marvelous to believe!
L-Little Red Phantom Thief!
Oh dear. Are you here
all on your lonesome, Mister Director?
Even if it's just another worthless guard,
I deserve a bigger audience than this.
Q-Quit playing games!
What have you come to steal this time?!
An unannounced theft wouldn't
be marvelous at all. I wouldn't do that.
So today, I come with a warning.
"On the night of the full moon,
I shall marvelously help myself
to the jeweler Yelle's latest work,
the Blue Heart!"
What? What? What? What? What?!
It's only fitting for the most marvelous
one of all to possess that marvelous item.
Goodbye. Until the next full moon.
THE CASE OF LITTLE RED PHANTOM THIEF
AND THE BLUE HEART
THE CASEBOOK OF ARNE
So that's the situation I'm in.
This is the kind of warning
Little Red Phantom Thief leaves, huh?
PART 7: EATING WHETS THE APPETITE
Lord Arne, we are going to
accept the case, aren't we?
No.
Huh?
Did you already forget
about the Hotel Pithos case?
The Hotel Pithos Robbery?
Of course I remember that.
It was the case where Little Red
Phantom Thief dressed up as you.
The heart we were supposed
to be guarding got stolen,
and we were attacked by werewolves.
You're welcome, by the way.
If I hadn't been there,
you would all have ended up in hell.
I already told you it all went
according to plan.
Regardless, nothing good ever comes
from getting involved with Little Red.
Please! I really need your help!
You're rumored to be
the only one capable of protecting
the Blue Heart from
Little Red Phantom Thief.
That's why I came to you.
That's our Lord Arne.
As his assistant, I can hold my head high.
Well, actually, all those rumors came
from my boomerang security guard.
I've brought you another client, kiddo—
Detective! Detective! Detective! Detective!
My man has disappeared!
My beloved one and only!
Please find him for me!
Without him by my side,
life is no longer worth living!
Are you sure he disappeared?
Maybe he ran away.
Love is fleeting, after all.
Don't say that.
There's no way that's true!
He and I are in love!
Whoa!
He even promised to make me his bride!
Wh-What the hell is this lady's problem?!
Fine. I'll go to the art museum.
Thank you very much.
Lord Arne, what about this woman?
Save me!
I'll leave her to you, Lynn Reinweiß.
I think it's about time
you accepted a case on your own.
Zwei, you're just taking advantage of Lynn.
Lord Arne.
You really trust me
with something like that?
I promise to do my very best.
Oh gosh.
A-dor-a-ble.
Come. We're going with him.
Huh? Why?
Lynn wishes to do this on her own.
I do not want to get in her way.
So, uh...
At a time like this, Lynn,
some chamomile tea can come in handy.
It helps to take the edge off
the sadness and confusion.
Oh, thanks, Zisye.
Throw in some tasty sweets
and you're all set.
I'm sorry for losing
my composure like that.
I don't blame you.
Someone very dear to you is missing.
He's not the type of person
to just leave without saying anything.
With the Arne Detective Agency on the case,
you have nothing to worry about.
I can't thank you enough.
I brought ya even more clients, kiddo.
Hope ya appreciate it, kiddo.
Please find my boyfriend! He's gone missing!
She's beautiful.
Looks tasty.
A leannán sídhe?
You're very well informed.
A leannán sídhe is a fairy that's said
to grant talent to artists she loves
in exchange for their lives.
The first director of the museum
was fond of the following saying:
"Artists sacrifice their own vitality
to bring their work to life."
"The enduring radiance of that vitality
is what stirs the viewer's emotions."
In other words,
that crest is a symbol of art itself.
And we have many other wonderful
works of art on display inside.
This way, please.
We'll go do some sightseeing.
We're in a city of art, after all.
Later.
Huh?
But this is the number one
tourist spot in town.
The four statues in this room
are by an emerging sculptor who's
already heralded as a leading talent.
According to that sculptor,
"True art does not emerge
from a complete form."
"Only when a work is incomplete can
the imagination of the viewer fulfill it,
and allow it to reach
a state of perfect beauty."
That one's by a talented painter
with a very promising future ahead.
Mr. Yelle's talents have truly
been flourishing recently.
Please take a look
at these stunning examples.
So this is what humans consider beautiful.
I don't get it at all.
Little Red Phantom Thief
sure has odd taste.
Actually, regarding that,
I should tell you...
You don't even have the new piece?
Mr. Yelle went missing about a week ago,
and so did the Blue Heart
he was supposed to lend to us.
Meaning there's nothing for Little Red
Phantom Thief to steal in the first place.
Right.
Then, the case is closed. I'm leaving.
Ah, please don't go!
If the item you want me to protect
isn't even here, why would I stay?
If we can't locate Mr. Yelle,
the museum will be in dire straits.
Also, the next full moon is tomorrow.
Once Little Red Phantom Thief finds out,
there's no telling what she might do.
I'm begging you! Please at least come
and protect the museum tomorrow night.
This truly is a city of art.
Would you like your portrait painted?
How about a painting to remember
your visit to the city of art?
Why not? Maybe we should
have our portraits done.
No way. If there's a permanent record
of me in this form,
I'll be a laughingstock
among vampires.
Aren't you already?
What a beautiful young lady.
Oh, I think I'll go with you.
Hey!
Couldn't you have tried
to look a little less mean?
Shaddap.
Amy! Nach!
It's Lynn.
You got three clients?
Seriously? Is going missing
some kind of new fad?
It's actually very strange.
All three men who disappeared
had links to the art museum.
The first was employed by a shipping
company that transports artworks.
The second was a curator
who quit just last month.
The third was an interpreter
who helped out with museum tours.
That is indeed strange.
Then, there's the warning Little Red
Phantom Thief left at the museum.
All of these mysteries are
connected to the museum!
It's just like you said, Lynn.
The museum seems to
hold some sort of secret.
Right?
Lord Arne, I'd like to join you
at the museum tomorrow.
No, Lynn Reinweiß. Tomorrow,
you'll investigate this Yelle fellow.
But the full moon's tomorrow.
I'll be devastated if I'm not there
for the showdown
between you and the marvelous
Little Red Phantom Thief!
I was planning to be there
to cheer you on.
Cheer on?
Absolutely do not come to
the art museum. That's an order.
You're so selfish, Lord Arne!
Who's the selfish one?
You demon! You devil!
Well, yes, not far off.
I am a vampire, after all.
Did Mr. Yelle have any family?
When I first rented this place out
to him, he said he had no one.
I see.
This must be him.
He looked much healthier back then.
He'd lost a lot of weight recently, you see.
I was worried he may have
been working too hard.
He said he was working on his magnum opus.
He sure seemed excited about it.
His magnum opus, you say?
I also think he said he was
making it for someone special.
For someone special?
I thought maybe he'd fallen
in love with someone.
But where would he have run off to?
He'd lost weight?
So much so, the landlord had
started worrying about him.
For living creatures,
humans sure are weaklings.
"Weaklings," huh?
Weak... Ill...
A hospital!
If Mr. Yelle actually was sick,
maybe he went to a hospital.
Excellent reasoning, Lynn.
We'll ask about the other three men, too.
Well, that was a waste of time.
No, it wasn't a waste.
Huh?
At least we've ruled out
a few places they didn't go.
Look.
Huh?
This would look nice on you.
Aw, it's so cute. I love these.
Huh. Looks like it has paint inside.
What a pretty color.
Find something you like?
Those are said to ward off evil, miss.
Ward off evil?
Hey, Nach.
It really does ward off evil.
N-No, you dummy!
It just surprised me a little!
A little?
Having something shoved in your face
would surprise anyone!
I'll take it.
Hey!
Excellent choice.
I smell something sweet.
It's very faint, though.
Zisye?
What's up, Little Red?
The only person you saw here
was the jeweler, right?
Yeah. After I heard you were
gonna steal the Blue Heart,
I peeked in every once in a while,
but Yelle was always alone.
Or at least, he was the only person
reflected in the mirror.
He could have been living
with a vampire or something.
But vampires smell like blood,
and it doesn't smell like blood in here.
There's a faintly sweet smell
in the air instead.
So what are you planning to do tonight?
You won't find anything at the museum.
That's true.
But I believe Mister Vampire will be
waiting for me at the museum all the same.
He did say that in front of me,
so I think he intended for you to find out.
Then, I guess it'd be rude
to stand him up, wouldn't it?
It might be a trap, though.
A trap?
Miss, want your portrait painted?
I'm sorry, but no thank you.
Want a portrait?
Ah, I'm in a hurry, but maybe next time.
It's Mr. Yelle!
Do you know him, miss?
Oh, uh, yes.
Then, would you mind taking that to him?
Huh?
He commissioned me to draw his portrait
about three weeks ago.
A little to your left, please.
No, I think I'm fine here.
He paid quite a lot of money for it, too.
I asked him to come and
pick it up in a few weeks.
Isn't it a lovely expression?
Yes, he appears very happy.
But he hasn't come to get it yet,
so I don't know what to do.
It's odd he never came to pick up
this painting he commissioned.
Something very strange is going on.
Perhaps there is more to
his disappearance than it seems.
Anyway, we still have work to do
to find the missing men.
Come on out, Little Red Phantom Thief!
Do you really think she'll show?
You can bet on it!
This sort of thrilling situation is right up
Little Red Phantom Thief's alley!
She's over there!
She got me!
Little Red Phantom Thief
has made her marvelous entrance.
Freeze!
Did you witness my marvelous jump
just now, Mister Vampire?
Little Red! What have you done
with the director?
The museum director is right over there.
Sir!
Now, turn your attention to this.
N-No, it can't be.
Is that the Blue Heart?!
If it is, what are you gonna do about it?
Yes, you are about the only person capable
of joining me in a marvelous dance.
Dance, you say?
Ridiculous. Now, hand it over.
I'm not giving it to you.
Give it here.
If you want it, you're gonna
have to take it from me.
Tch. Uh, wait. Now how did I...
Oh, like this.
Lord Arne!
I thought I told you
to stay away, Lynn Rein—
I'm rooting for you, Lord Arne!
Evilly! Bloody! Fantastic! Neuntöte!
I've suddenly lost interest.
It seems our marvelous dance has ended.
This is but an imitation.
Actually, I came here today to deliver
another marvelous warning.
Unfortunately for you,
I've had to change my plans.
I will locate the missing Mister Yelle
before you even have a chance,
and take the Blue Heart for myself!
And on that note, Mister Vampire,
I bid you a marvelous farewell.
I have located the missing humans.
Huh?
Or more accurately, I have located
the corpses of the missing humans.
The corpses?
They're here.
Huh?
Mere statues would not
be able to move like this.
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
TIMING: HENRY LIN
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: ELISABETH CRIST
TRANSLATION CHECK: ELIZABETH ELLIS