Nei
Shushu
Miss Shushu!
We received a report from the commander.
She said the Azuma Banquet is over!
And?
Miss Himari's mother was the winner.
Well, she is the commander
of the 9th Squadron.
It is what it is.
Did Himari give 'em
the 7th Squadron special?
Apparently, she made up
with the other Azumas.
They acknowledged how strong she is!
Seriously? That's awesome!
Yeah! There's nothing better
than a happy family!
Wow, I'm so glad to hear it!
Yukki's spent the past five days
glued to Himarin's side for training.
I haven't been able
to approach him at all.
But now, it's my turn!
My plan is foolproof!
This time, I'm gonna win Yukki over
no matter what!
Giving men and women
that extra confidence boost...
Kawabata
That's right!
With the magic of summer!
Magic?
My heart sunk and I no longer feel hope for the future
It felt like time froze and now it's all over
Brooding and silent
The umbrella of my heart began to open
Still, I kept my chin up and went on
I won't ask you to comfort me
I want to grow strong and focus on what's ahead
But weakness crushes me
Meeting you is what filled my world with light
I didn't have an ounce of hope, and yet I could laugh
Ordinary conversations always brought me a smile
I won't say thanks 'cause you'll blush and laugh
But I'm thinking it
Can I move forward from here?
O light, come to me
Late Summer Slave
Episode 7
The Azuma Banquet participants spent
the night at the Azuma estate.
It was time to relax and unwind.
Baths at home are the best!
Today was a wonderful day!
Hey, it just occurred to me...
What?
When we were kids, it felt like
you were constantly by my side.
Yeah.
Aw, how cute! You don't even know that?
I guess you could say that.
Was it 'cause...
you were protecting me from Homare?
Not really.
You were a handful
when you were little, that's all.
Thanks...
Big...
Big Sis.
You're in an awfully good mood, Yachiho.
Maia?!
Come wash your big sister's back
like old times.
Excuse me?
"The Great One."
Wild God of Extremities
The Great One
An ability that controls a massive,
sturdy pair of hands individually.
The hands can be invisible.
I won't take "no" for an answer.
Why the hell are you using your ability
in the bath?!
I haven't lost to Himari yet.
I'll sneak into Yuuki's room
to seduce him,
put him under my spell...
and steal him for myself!
Y'know, this is actually
kind of embarrassing.
Let's get this over with!
He's gone!
You're a little too late.
Himari and the boy
went to the other dimension with Fubuki.
To go over what happened at the Banquet.
They're working hard.
Lady Tovera!
I came here
to mess with Yuuki Wakura, too.
How disappointing.
Yeah, well...
Head to toe, you look like a kid.
"Ephemeral," Tovera's ability,
Ephemeral
Azuma Years
allows her to suck
the life force out of others.
Tovera absorbs the life force from flowers
to restore her youth.
By sharing the excess life force
she has stored with others,
she can also
accelerate growth and healing.
Talk about a freakish ability...
You were thinking something rude just now,
weren't you?
No, of course not!
Still, damn that Fubuki.
Getting the jump on us like that.
And those...
are the inadequacies
that I noticed during the Banquet.
You're especially lacking in awareness
of your periphery.
I'll keep that in mind.
Thank you for the valuable lesson.
You're welcome.
Let's practice that again
once we get home.
You got it!
Moving on.
Try Heavenward this time.
Uh...
Oh no! Did you just borrow him?!
Oops.
Well, as long as we're here...
perhaps I should ride him.
What?!
Wait a minute.
I was in the middle
of using Yuuki just now.
I loaned him to her right afterwards,
so his reward...
My mother-
Will Fubuki and I have to reward him
at the same time?!
Eternal Chains: Slave
Human Bullet
My whole body feels heavy.
This is what loaning him is like.
I guess it can happen by accident.
All right then.
Show me what you've got.
Roger!
Himari, can you handle
a light sparring match?
Bring it on!
Here goes!
I'm not quite as strong or fast...
But...
I bounced off?!
It's like you're made of rubber.
Can you leap into the air
and destroy that boulder?
I'm on it.
So high!
For the last part,
consolidate your power into your arms.
That's insanely strong!
If we leverage your body's flexibility,
it becomes a versatile tool.
Ugh, I'm exhaused.
I could really go
for something sweet right now.
Okay.
I guess we're doing this.
I wondered why my body led me
straight to the kitchen.
So this is your reward.
You're all worn out, aren't you?
Mwah!
Be grateful I'm feeding you!
Come here.
It's your reward...
so there's no need to hold back.
Besides, if I don't do it,
the reward won't end!
Your training is going to become
more grueling from here on out.
Drop by the Azuma house
every now and then.
I'll help you relieve some tension.
Oh, come on! It's still going?!
That's the spirit, Himari!
How indecent can you get?!
Now, Himari.
Where's your sense of compassion?
Miss Kawabata,
you have a magazine interview and
photoshoot on your schedule tomorrow.
I'll send you the details again.
'Kay. Thanks a bunch.
Shiki Kawabata
Styling Outfits for Maximum Happiness
10 Habits for Enhancing Beauty
I wonder what they'll ask
at the interview.
My goodness, you're stunning!
You passed the first round
of prey auditions!
Whoopsies!
Big Sis Shikoku would say
that making a scene is a big no-no!
The summer season has arrived!
Arrived?
Summer's nearly over.
Non, non!
My summer starts right now!
It's not often we get time off.
Let's kick back
and enjoy a day in the normal world.
Too bad Himari couldn't join us.
Well, we can't afford
to leave the dorm empty.
And you...
You haven't forgotten
which squad you're in, have you?
I'm merely stopping by on my break.
I finished the floatie!
All right!
Let's go swim, Nei!
Okay!
They've got perfect figures!
I saw Commander Ezo that one time.
She was gorgeous, too.
Let's get out there with them, Yukki!
S-sure!
The commanders have me beat
in combat power,
but I'll make up for it with skill
and a proactive attitude!
No backing down!
Well, it's time I get back to work.
Okay. Good luck out there!
That was fun!
I can't wait to get Big Sis back to normal
so we can have a blast like we did today.
Guess who!
Shushu?
Ya knew it was me right away, huh?
What's the matter?
Now to hit him with my new technique!
Selective Paradigm Shift!
Only my boobs get bigger!
I was waiting for the shower...
but you were taking too long.
S-sorry for making you wait!
It's all yours!
It's working!
The vacation's loosening him up!
Summer magic is incredible!
I came up with a whole bunch of
romantic plans in preparation for today!
I won't let him escape!
Great view, huh?
Shushu.
Everything in Mato looks the same,
so it hits even harder.
So true!
Y'know, us two watching
the sunset like this...
It's like we're a couple.
Your collection of romance manga
in your room got bigger.
Been reading too much?
Huh? You noticed that?
You mentioned before that you
weren't really into romance manga.
Oh, well...
Guess you could say I'm at that age!
That makes sense.
It does?
You've gotten even cuter lately, Shushu.
Oops, time's up.
I'd better head to practice.
All my plans went down the drain!
Yukki!
I get the feeling
this has happened before!
Yukki! You dangerous, dangerous man!
I gotta get stronger...
at my ability and at playing mind games!
All right, let's start our session.
Miss Kyouka, let's practice Heavenward!
Heavenward, huh?
That form is less efficient
and takes too much of a toll on you.
Think of it as a last resort.
This form is your baseline.
But-
The way I see it...
Heavenward didn't lose to Fubuki
because you lack experience with it.
It's too powerful, and you
couldn't control it on your own.
Oh...
Which is why you'll be able move
effortlessly with more training,
even in Heavenward form.
Got it!
For now, I want to practice
different kinds of long-range attacks.
Long-range?
One of the Eight Thunder Gods had wings.
We should anticipate
our enemy being able to fly.
Ah.
All I can do right now
is throw rocks at them.
I have an idea. We'll test it out.
First, we get warmed up!
Yes, ma'am!
Were you always this fast
in your normal form?
I got faster 'cause of training!
No, it seems like more than that.
I've been transforming
into my Whirlwind form a lot lately,
so my body feels lighter for some reason.
Wait a minute...
Whirlwind.
Shining Star.
Iwatooshi.
Phoenix Wings.
Killer Fang.
Human Bullet.
The more I loan him to the others,
the stronger his normal Slave form gets?!
My normal Slave form
gets stronger when you lend me out?
Reward in
Progress
Exactly.
Your muscles are retaining the benefits
of the various forms
you take on with the others.
Which makes it
an even more valuable approach.
That being said, if you're against it-
In that case...
it might be a good idea to loan me
to the others more often!
Yeah, probably.
Miss Kyouka-
I didn't mean to cut her off like that.
I wonder what she was going to say.
In retrospect...
it was the same
when she slayed the Unihorn.
During important battles,
Miss Kyouka always uses this katana
to attack the enemy herself.
You're one hundred percent
dedicated to your master.
I ought to be more like you!
And if that means
working with the others...
Let's do this!
Now then...
Today, we'll be taking turns
riding Yuuki Wakura.
What?!
Yuuki Wakura, lie down over there.
Yes, ma'am!
Well, here I go...
Flex your abs.
L-like this?
Yay!
It doesn't hurt
when I sit like this, right?
Just relax.
I'll teach you a lesson, Yuuki Wakura.
Aw c'mon, don't be a lazy bum!
That's it, well done.
Um, am I too heavy?
Am I doing this right?
Hey, are you listening to Miss Yakumo?
Are you okay? I'm sorry!
Hm, how's this, Yuuki?
What a horrible dream...
Why?
What's with this awful ache in my chest?
Yuuki?
Miss Kyouka!
Perfect timing!
For what?
About the whole "lending me out" thing...
I...
changed my mind!
Emergencies are a different story,
but I don't want our baseline to change!
I want to keep working with you!
Earlier, I...
I thought I had no choice
if I wanted to get stronger.
But it bothered me...
Patrols or battles or whatever else,
I want to do it with you!
The reason my life
looks the way it does is because of you!
Besides, there's barely even a difference
after one of the others borrows me!
I didn't notice until you said something!
Yuuki...
But more importantly, my training sessions
with you are usually way more-
Yuuki!
It's about time!
That's exactly why you're my slave!
Yeah!
All right, let's get training!
To come up with a new technique!
These chains exist as part of my ability.
I should be able to extend them
now that I'm more familiar with Yuuki.
Let's make it happen.
Got it!
Yuuki!
Okay!
This light...
That could come in handy
for all sorts of things.
Reward in
Progress
You did a fantastic job tonight, Yuuki.
We have more options in combat now.
I'll keep up the good work!
Was that a conch?!
I think one blow means
there's an emergency of some sort.
Three blows?!
That signal...
The Eight Thunder Gods!
Store this one, too.
Just a few more 'til we hit our goal!
And boy, am I starving...
Love beam!
Wanna know and wanna do, wanna touch
These feelings pouring out of me just won't stop
Sweet, so sweet, let me in with your body darling
I'll domesticate you, time for a reward
With the heat from skin on skin overlapping
It's fully charged
Now ready to launch!
Shoot from my hand now, love love beam
Aim for your heart now, love love beam
Bridging the gap between us
And firing from point blank
Yay! Yay! Yay! Yay!
You won't escape my love love beam
To the ends of the Earth, love love beam
Yeah, love is what changes the world
Dye it all heart-colored, even the darkness
The Commander of the 2nd Squadron
Episode 8
Next time, Episode 8:
"The Commander of the 2nd Squadron"
For today's bonus... Ta-da!
Aw, our Himarin's grown up so much,
hasn't she?
Nei will do her best, too!
At what?