Thanks for bringing me that message from
Cecilia even on your day off, Teal.
Oh, don't worry about me.
I wanted to visit the guardian
deity, and it was on my way.
I... see.
Anyway, I'm gonna go. Get some rest.
Take care out there.
Teal was acting awfully docile.
Oh, my guardian deity!
I stayed respectful of the time and place
and controlled myself, just like you said!
Don't get all excited!
You'll collapse again!
Look! I have some of the
magicite you love so much!
You found such fine ore for me?
I'll work my very hardest,
so please eat all you like!
Don't hold back!
I'd like you to think carefully
about what you just said.
So Gar's basically just a
gigolo at this point, huh?
You mustn't laugh.
But it's clear how much Teal
genuinely loves Gar, isn't it?
Yoki?
Oh... This tea's really good.
Maybe all my practice
is starting to pay off.
Today was fun, as always...
but do I really want
things to stay this way?
And...
why did you call me over for this?
There's no one else I can
turn to for love advice!
Please!
Well, Captain... you have
no friends, after all.
Rude! I have friends!
And? What did you do this time?
I told you, I just want some love advice!
Look, you know how I can use Vanish
Wave to turn invisible, right?
So after saying goodbye to Cecilia,
I was wondering what she
might be doing, so...
Not good enough!
I'm not done yet!
I had no idea Cecilia was
putting in that much effort.
And that made me worry that maybe
I really don't know the girl
I love that well at all.
That's incredibly creepy.
Huh?
Can I arrest you for unlawful
entry and stalking?
I just came here for some love advice!
I swear...
Well, I don't think things
are going too badly.
But for all your hollering
that you love Cecilia so much,
you're not aggressive enough!
From my perspective, you're a coward!
Wha?!
Do you just want to be her
teatime companion forever?
W-Well...
You can't make any progress if you
barely know anything about her.
That's true...
Thanks, Duke.
Just one thing:
don't be a stalker.
Right.
A stalker?
So... are you actually a
criminal, not an ordinary civilian?
Er, no, it's not like that...
You showed up at just the right time.
I'm leaving the rest to someone
who knows Cecilia well.
Huh?!
S-So...
Please tell me everything
you know about Cecilia.
Gross. Zero points.
DUKE ASKED ME TO COME.
Also, would you just use your voice?
You were talking last time.
"No. That was a special exception."
NO. THAT WAS A SPECIAL EXCEPTION.
Jeez, I'm sorry, okay?!
Okay, I guess I can't make you
talk if you don't want to.
Anyway, you want to know about Cecilia?
I do owe you for the advice
you gave me before,
so I'll tell you.
Please do!
Okay, let's see...
I don't think the hero's party
would exist without Cecilia.
Did you guys get hurt that often?
That's not what I mean. But first...
there's the problem of all
the women who flock to Yuga.
Hi!
CHILL OUT.
The swordsman's written
notes didn't stop them,
Cut it out already!
and when I stepped in, things
just got more heated.
Move it!
Out of our way!
Everyone, please calm down.
But Cecilia always calmed
the storm for us.
"She did almost all of
the background work."
Uh, you should all be sharing that.
W-We do things when we can!
WE DIVIDED UP THE TASKS WE COULD DIVIDE UP.
I WAS THE COOK.
"We divided up the tasks
we could divide up.
I was the cook." Really?
Well, you know I can't cook!
And what about Yuga?
He can, but whenever he goes
out to gather ingredients,
he always finds trouble to get into.
Cecilia and I were in
charge of gathering intel.
Since our swordsman's so useless, y'know.
Cecilia managed our money, too.
So Yuga contributed nothing at all?!
Maybe not, but the incidents he caused
always ended up helping someone somehow.
I'm glad Yuga was our hero.
His kindness is the real deal.
I see. I feel like I understand
Yuga a little better now.
But that's not what I want!
I was asking about Cecilia!
Was there anything else?
Oh, right. She had that nickname.
What nickname?
You don't know? Oh, it was brilliant!
Cecilia was...
You seem to be having a fun conversation.
Cecilia?!
What are you doing here?
I was looking for you, Mikana.
I wanted to talk to you.
We were just... talking
about old memories...
I want to talk about old
memories with you, too.
At length, I assure you.
Yoki, Raven,
we'll be taking our leave for today.
What?!
Why only me?!
Yoki, I'm sorry, but it's not my
place to tell you Cecilia's nickname.
I-It's okay.
Mikana's noble sacrifice taught
me one of Cecilia's landmines.
Yoki, do you still have some time?
This is the orphanage where Cecilia
does a lot of volunteer work.
Huh...
Oh! It's the Cold-blooded Swordsman!
Cold-blooded Swordsman!
Cold-blooded Swordsman?
THAT'S MY NICKNAME.
Ah.
Cold-blooded Swordsman!
He has no blood or tears!
You guys don't even know
what that expression means.
Hey, where's the Holy Mother?
Holy Mother?
Isn't the Holy Mother coming today?
I wanna eat the Holy Mother's desserts!
Thank you, Cold-blooded Swordsman!
Since I don't speak when I fight,
people seem to see me as a cold-blooded
man who sheds no blood or tears.
So that's why you're the
Cold-blooded Swordsman.
Yuga's nickname is "the Wandering Hero."
Mikana's is "the Guardian,"
or "the Eternal Friend."
I'm kinda curious
where those came from...
But Cecilia...
Why doesn't she like being
called the Holy Mother?
It's not my place to tell you.
But you can just learn
more about it from now on.
I'm sure you'll have opportunities.
I guess so.
But if you don't know what
to do once you find out...
Never mind. Anyway, what
are you going to do now?
Yeah, that's the question, huh?
It'd be best if I could get to know
Cecilia better and get closer to her...
Why don't you take on a quest with her?
I mean... thanks to you, I...
That's it!
When the heroine is in a tight spot,
the protagonist gallantly saves her!
And from there, love is inevitably born!
"Operation I'm a Protagonist,
Too" begins now!
I managed to get Cecilia to agree.
Today's the day I show her what I can do!
And then...
Good morning.
Why are you here?
The swordsman asked me to accompany you.
Something else came up, apparently.
Raven!
So what are we doing?
You want to show Cecilia
what you can do, right?
I do have a plan.
Let's hear it. I'll score it for you.
Score it?
The quest is to get rid of some undead
that have made their den in a mansion.
That'll be a great chance
for Cecilia to shine.
Huh?
Uh, won't it?
Well, I was thinking...
Just leave this to me!
Yoki, you're the best!
So... my dream was that I'd mow
down all the undead myself...
Thirty points.
Harsh!
Are you dumb?! Cecilia is a priestess!
Dealing with undead is her specialty!
Oh.
Your problem is that you base
all your plans around yourself!
Your priority should be
what Cecilia will think!
I-I'm sorry...
Well, you and Cecilia can
be the main fighters today.
I'll be on support.
You two need to work together
to defeat the enemy.
You want to form a relationship
of trust, don't you?
I-I get it. I think I can do that.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Huh? Mikana?
I'll be tagging along on this quest.
Oh, that's very reassuring!
Actually, I brought someone else, too.
Happiness!
Hi.
Thanks for your help the other day.
Thanks.
Okay, shall we get going?
This is it.
All right! Let's take out those undead!
Yay.
Hold it right there!
Did you forget the plan already?
Oh, yeah!
So anyway, Cecilia and I
will take the front line.
Mikana and Happiness, you're
the rear guard. Okay?
She's not giving the slightest
hint of being afraid of ghosts.
I guess that's to be expected.
And there they are already.
Holy Circle!
Wow, that was quick.
That's Cecilia for you.
I'll take these.
Holy Circle!
Are you tired, Cecilia?
I'm just fine.
Holy Circle is an essential
spell for any priest.
I've boosted my magic efficiency for it.
Okay.
I think it's still a good idea
to stay hydrated, though.
Thank you.
Well, that was thoughtful.
Our captain is like that.
Yeah, I guess he's the type to
take off in weird directions
when he overthinks things.
This is the last room.
You never see this many undead
packed into such a small space.
It's clear they have a leader.
In other words...
This is where we'll find the boss.
That's...
an Undead King.
Sure looks important with
that crown on its head.
Are they strong?
An Undead King's strength isn't much
different from that of normal undead.
They just have a bit more intelligence.
Wimp.
It doesn't live up to
its name at all, then.
Now, dead one who has taken up
residence in someone else's house
without consent!
We will return you to the afterlife!
Pathetic.
Just who are you people?
Hey! We have intruders!
Your buddies won't be coming.
What?!
The only undead left in here is you!
And now you're just an ordinary skeleton!
Huh?
Yoki...
You are...
...scum.
Wait, uh... It was just a little prank...
Fiend.
Again, I didn't—
Brute.
Give me a chance to explain myself!
How dare you... How dare you...
How dare you?! How dare you?!
I'm sorry, okay?!
In that case...
How about this one?!
I lose.
How very honorable of you.
You won't resist anymore?
I've lost.
I have lost.
Cecilia, it sounds like
he's resigned himself.
Use Holy Circle to put
a quick end to this.
Why are you so attached to that crown?
This crown was important to me.
I don't know why.
It was just very important.
It was important to you?
Maybe you were the king of some
nation when you were alive.
All right.
I'll send you to the afterlife
along with your crown.
The way she's handling this...
Heaven's Rondo.
I feel so nostalgic...
I hear a voice.
The voice of...
Cecilia! You shouldn't
use such advanced magic!
Well, we've gotten rid of all the undead.
That's mission complete.
True. Shall we go home, then?
But Mikana and Happiness, since
you didn't do any work here,
why don't you go check around the mansion?
Oh, fine!
We'll work.
We'll meet back at the carriage.
So, Cecilia, can I lend you my shoulder?
Or carry you on my back?
I'm sorry...
I'll take that shoulder.
You used too much magic, huh?
I wasn't sure if he'd be able
to take his crown with him.
He sure looked happy, though.
Looks like she can't make it.
Yoki?!
Th-This is embarrassing...
Don't worry.
I'll move as fast as I can so
the other two don't see us.
Why...
are you guys so far apart?
Trouble?
Well, this is our stop.
Okay. Good work today.
Bye.
Well? What's my score?
Oh, you remembered, huh?
Just tell me.
No score.
Huh?
Sorry, but I'm not going
to score that one.
Huh?! You mean it wasn't even scorable?!
No, it's not that.
But that's for the best.
Don't overthink everything. Just
do the best at what you can do.
That sounds kinda noncommittal.
Not at all. It's the
best advice I can give.
Well, I'm going home.
Okay. Thanks for today.
I'll have to work hard, too.
By the way,
I heard you visited the orphanage.
The kids told me.
If you found out my nickname,
I have to ask you...
Please don't ever call me that.
Oh, sure. I won't do
anything you don't like.
But... can I ask why?
Well...
Of course, if you don't
want to, that's fine.
It's just... it really suits you, I think.
The way you spoke to the Undead King...
You just had this air of sanctity.
It reminded me of that time
in the Demon King's castle.
Back then, you really
reminded me of a saint.
Yeah. I felt like a saint
was reaching out to me.
A... saint?
I mean... er...
All right.
I'll tell you why they
call me Holy Mother.
It's a famous story, so it's better than
letting you hear it from someone else.
You're so amazing, Cecilia!
You're good at cooking and sewing,
and at gathering intel and
handling our money, too!
You're...
just like a mom!
From then on, he started calling me
"Mom" in front of people all the time.
Stop laughing!
For crying out loud! I couldn't
have a child as big as him!
Sorry...
Come on, Yoki!