Boy, I have a favor to ask.
I wish to work.
You want to... work?!
I cannot simply remain here
as a freeloader any longer!
What brought this on?
I'm sure you know
that every time Teal visits
me, she brings me magicite.
Here you go, guardian deity!
Just how much of her paycheck
is she spending on me?
So you don't want to be a gigolo anymore.
Please.
Well, it seems like you're
prepared for this.
Okay, then, let's begin...
Gar's great reformation!
I am Gar. I wish to
register as an adventurer.
Will this suffice for my paperwork?
U-Um...
This is a friend of the Magic
Swordsman of Black Lightning.
He may look a bit shady,
but he can be trusted.
Kramen! Kramen!
What is it? I'm busy, you know.
Don't bother lying!
I know you were just admiring the lunch
your wife packed for you and grinning!
Hey! Not so loud!
I can't be bothered to comment on this
spectacle, so I'll just ask.
So what's up?
I wish to register as an adventurer.
Okay.
That's okay?!
The Magic Swordsman here
will be responsible for him.
Indeed! I guarantee it!
There you go. You're registered.
I thank you.
Now, we will return tomorrow
to accept a quest.
Find us one that you deem
suitable for a beginner.
Farewell!
Why did we not accept a quest today?
You need to prepare a weapon and stuff.
I can use my magic—
Oh.
Exactly.
The moment you use dark magic,
everyone will know you're a demon.
You gotta be careful.
Also, you don't know anything
about Minerva, right?
I'll spend today showing you around.
I appreciate the trouble.
What are you talking about? You're...
going to be the Magic Swordsman
of Black Lightning's partner!
I would rather not.
We're here to take a quest!
Must you be so loud first
thing in the morning?
Oh, someone's here looking for you.
For the Magic Swordsman
of Black Lightning?
Has something happened?
She's waiting behind the guild.
Don't make her wait too long.
I've been waiting for you...
Magic Swordsman of Black Lightning.
Cecilia?!
So it really is you, Yoki!
Huh?!
N-No, this is, um... How do I put it...
My name is not Yoki! It is "Magic
Swordsman of Black Lightning"!
Yoki.
I'm sorry. I know what
I'm doing is stupid.
You do?
But how did you know?
Sophia told me.
She said the Magic Swordsman of
Black Lightning showed up again.
I had heard rumors about him before,
but the more I heard, the
more it sounded like you.
I was worried some kind of uproar
might ensue, so I came to find out.
Kramen leaked my identity, didn't he?
So that's what's going on!
Are you dressed as the Magic Swordsman
so that Gar won't be conspicuous?
Yeah, something like that!
According to my plans, this
look is the way to go!
I'll help, too.
Huh?!
I'd be too worried to let
you handle this alone.
Right...
Now, let's start with a
beginner-friendly quest.
We are here from the adventurers' guild
about the quest to find your pet!
Tell us your story!
Hey. The clients appear to have frozen.
Hah! I guess they were
captivated by my appearance.
Magic Swordsman, would you please
keep your mouth shut for the moment?
For starters, please tell us
how we can identify your cat.
Can you describe its color,
size, and tail shape?
He's taking care to watch and learn.
This is the description
of their missing kitten.
It's very clever and always came
back home after going outside,
but this time, it's been
missing since last week.
How shall we search for it?
We should start by asking around.
It's standard practice to ask the
neighbors and any patrolling knights.
However...
I will go above and beyond that!
Hup!
My enhanced sense of smell picked
up the cat's scent from its owners!
And now I'll use Instant
Lightning to run faster
and run all over town
looking for that cat!
I found you.
Hah! You've instinctively sensed
my strength and put up your guard?
Relax. The Magic Swordsman of
Black Lightning is your friend.
I see I have no choice
but to put you to sleep.
Holy Bell.
Thank you so much!
But... where'd this cat come from?
It was with your cat.
I've healed its wounds, so please
look after it as well, if you can.
Now, farewell!
So our quest is complete now?
Yes.
Now we just need to inform the
guild that we've finished it,
and we'll receive our reward money.
I see.
All right! On to the next quest!
Wait a minute!
No one can do things the way
you do, Magic Swordsman.
This won't give Gar any experience.
Sorry.
This time, we'll put Gar up front
and have him do as much
as he can on his own.
A-All right. But I will still
depend on you to show me the way.
I don't know the land.
You have nothing to worry about!
You have me, the Magic Swordsman
of Black Lightning, behind you!
This must be the herb.
Listen up, Gar.
Gathering herbs is a path all
adventurers must walk at some point.
Don't take any more than you need,
or there won't be enough left for others.
Yes, I understand.
Will this suffice?
Yeah, looks good.
Now you, too, have taken a step
toward even greater heigh—
Good. Let's move on to the next quest.
The next quest is taking out some goblins.
This will probably be Gar's first battle.
We'll have to support him...
I don't think there'll
be any need for that.
It's all thanks to the power of love!
I mean, the power of
escaping the gigolo life!
I'm not a gigolo!
Yep, you've completed
the quest, all right.
Here's your reward.
So this is what it means to work.
Teal has been working all this time
and making money, despite
her weak constitution...
I will work even more!
And I will repay the debt I owe Teal!
That's the spirit!
We're rooting for you, Gar!
We'll back you up with all
we've got tomorrow, too!
I'm sorry, but could you allow
me to do this myself from now on?
What?!
But it's too soon for you to...
Don't worry. I won't cause any problems.
I have a good idea of how
to carry out quests now.
You'd better come back strong enough
to be the Magic Swordsman of
Black Lightning's right-hand man!
I'll be looking forward to your return!
Anyway, the sun's going down.
Time to part ways for now.
Do you have plans after this?
Since I'm the Magic Swordsman
of Black Lightning now,
I'm going on a Rank A quest.
I'll go with you.
Wut?!
But, um... most Rank A quests
require a few days' travel time.
And you're, well... busy, aren't you?
That's not a problem right now!
Or... would I be a burden?
Of course I'd be happy to have you!
But this won't be so much
a quest as a journey!
Before now, we've had tea together
and traveled with friends, but...
several days of just the two of us?!
B-But you'd be uncomfortable
camping out in those clothes.
And you don't have gear
for long journeys, do you?
Very well.
Then please wait here for a little while.
Huh?
Sorry I kept you waiting!
Cecily the adventurer at your service!
Cecily?
I'm all set for a long journey now,
and in this outfit, no one will know
I'm Cecilia from the hero's party.
So now there's no problem, right?
Kramen sure was happy, wasn't he?
He said we were taking care of a
real pain-in-the-ass quest for him,
but we're just inspecting some ruins.
How hard can that be?
Rank A quests aren't just about
fighting strong monsters.
Also, there are no villages we can
rest in on the way to these ruins.
Yeah, and no real road,
either. Kinda inconvenient.
Verifying our route to the
ruins will be dangerous.
On top of that, we have to search
inside without ransacking them.
Assume we won't be able to use
attack magic as a general rule.
But what if monsters show up?
We do everything we can to avoid combat.
Studying the monsters that live
in the ruins is part of the quest.
They're sure asking a lot...
The client is an archaeologist
from a research institution.
This quest is probably very
important to the guild.
They must really trust
you, Magic Swordsman.
Well, I'll have to give it my all, then.
Shall we start preparing to make camp?
We're camping out together!
We're spending the night alone together!
Any other time, I'd probably
panic and get all nervous,
but now, it's no problem!
Because...
I can play it all off by
going into chuuni mode!
I am the Magic Swordsman
of Black Lightning.
I will make even camping out
a comfortable experience!
I've assured that our
surroundings are safe.
And...
I've gathered fruits and vegetables
for our rations, as well!
You certainly are efficient.
No one else is around. Why
don't you take the mask off?
That I cannot do!
Until this quest is over, I am the
Magic Swordsman of Black Lightning!
To show my true identity
would be inexcusable!
Incidentally...
I've made it so I can
still eat with it on!
That's bad manners!
I'm sorry! I'll take it off!
Well, then, I'll dish up the soup.
Here you go. It's very simple, but...
Thanks.
That's good!
I mean, there's no way anything
you cook wouldn't be good!
You're exaggerating.
I-It's the truth!
Thanks for dinner! Mask on!
Be still, my soul!
You seem quite flustered to me!
R-Really? Well... that won't do!
We should sleep for
our early start tomorrow!
You want to go to sleep already?
She's so cute!
But... somehow, she seems
different from usual today.
But Cecilia, you—
It's Cecily!
Sorry. You've been questing since this
morning, Cecily. You must be tired.
Just who do you think I am?
I have completed more quests
than you, Magic Swordsman.
I am one of those chosen
to slay the Demon King
as a member of the hero's party!
I was just trying to imitate you.
That freaked me out...
I'm sorry to go against your
wishes, but I must refuse.
I am still inexperienced.
I have no intention of marrying anyone.
What, so that funny guy dumped you, then?
He has nothing to do with this!
Uh-huh.
But this is not a man you can
turn down for a reason like that.
The heir to an influential
neighboring domain lord
has requested your hand in marriage.
Now, let us away, Cecily!
An adventure yet unseen awaits us!
You mustn't yell so
loudly, Magic Swordsman.
If there are monsters nearby,
you'll provoke them.
Sorry.
I'll take the front line today.
Huh? Shouldn't it be the other way around?
Your magic is powerful.
It could damage the ruins.
I can restrain monsters with
Saint Chains if necessary.
No, let me handle this.
I can tell where monsters are.
Plus, I still have plenty of
magic I haven't shown you yet.
There are monsters up ahead.
Around thirteen of them.
What?
Incredible! You even got the number right!
But there are too many
for me to restrain them.
I want to avoid combat whenever
possible, so let's go around.
No. Leave this to me.
Illusion Sphere.
I can't see anything...
We're going to keep moving.
Keep your eyes shut.
So... what kind of spell did you use?
An intermediate dark spell
called Illusion Sphere.
It shows targets an illusion.
When they look at it, they see the
one thing they find most attractive
and can't tear their eyes away.
Attractive?
The thing they like most, basically.
In my case...
I'd see Cecilia. No doubt.
And Raven would see Happiness.
I wonder what I'd see if I looked at it.
Well... it'd be whatever
you like the most...
In that case...
I guess it'd be cake!
That's where you went?!
I mean, uh... n-nothing!
That's a convenient spell.
It's amazing how many different
types of spells you have.
That's not all there is to my magic!
Just follow me, and you
needn't worry about a thing!
It looks like this is where the ruins end.
Cecily... is it normal for ruins
to be so full of nothing?!
Well, there is an unusual mushroom.
No matter how far we go,
it's just monsters, plants,
monsters, plants, and mushrooms!
There's gotta be more to it than this!
Like an android
dormant for millennia,
a sealed magic sword, relics, treasures...
I'll even take the most
clichéd boss monster!
Just give me something!
Not so loud!
R-Right...
All right, let's head outside.
This is amazing.
Okay.
I guess that's the end of that quest.
It'll be nighttime soon. Let's
camp where we did last night.
R-Right...
Just the two of us again...
I definitely can't take off the mask now!
The quest is complete!
For the Magic Swordsman of Black Lightning
and Cecily, the Guide of Love
and Mercy, it was no prob—
Ow!
I don't need a nickname.
But it's so cool...
And? Anything to report?
Here you are.
A... written report?
Wow, this is fantastic!
Isn't a verbal report enough?
That kind of laziness is exactly why
I can't give a quest like
this to just anyone.
That's milady—I mean, Cecily for you!
I can submit this as is,
so it's a huge help!
Here's your reward.
That's Rank A for you. The reward's huge.
Let's use it to throw a big after-party!
That sounds great! But first...
you should change clothes.
Huh?
Hm? It's unlocked?
Where is the guardian deity?
I've been coming here every
day for the past four days,
and he isn't here.
I beg of you... if you know
where he is, please tell me.
Where has the guardian deity gone?
Ah, boy, you've returned.
Gar!
That voice... The guardian deity?
Yes. It's me.
Guardian deity!
You were away for so long!
I was worried about you!
I'm sorry I didn't inform you.
The truth is, I've rented
a room near here.
I've become an adventurer.
I can make my own living now.
So you no longer need to overtax
yourself to buy me magicite.
I'm not overtaxing myself!
Serving you is my greatest
happiness in life!
Please let me continue to serve you!
Very well.
Thank you!
But I will still repay my debt to you.
But there's no need! As long
as I'm by your side, I'm happy!
Um... we're still here, you know...
Teal didn't say a word about
the Magic Swordsman and Cecily.
She only had eyes for Gar.
Man, for some reason, I'm exhausted.
Yoki?!
I-I'm done for!
Four days' worth of embarrassment
just hits too hard!
I'm sealing this away!
Wait, please!
It's true that the Magic
Swordsman is out of control,
he draws a lot of negative attention,
and he causes trouble
more often than not...
But we came through this quest
in one piece thanks to his magic.
Cecily the adventurer would be
happy to team up with him again.
Well, Adventurer Cecily, there's
still much more to my magic!
If you've taken an interest,
I will show you even greater
power on our next quest!
I look forward to it!