FUTURE AFTER REVENGE
- Am I... alive?
Kyoya?
Siren!
You were found near
Shinjuku, which disappeared.
Oh, yeah.
You charged into the Mirage, didn't you?
To try and fight it on your own.
Looks like I'm alive, somehow.
Why would you do something so dangerous?!
There's no way you can
stop the Mirage like this!
Don't you understand
the condition you're in?!
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
It's Show Time
The price of living in the time of freedom
"So, what do you want to do?"
Just standing there with my empty body
Like a calling to protect the world
I craved an unequaled gift
Lost in night's darkness
Until a voice called out to me
Like the light that declares the dawn
I'll take you with me at
any cost (I pray and wish)
Just being with you makes me strong
It's not an exaggeration
That encounter was a supernova
(Our eyes were locked)
Will be changed forever (Just to be)
Destiny is Calling us now
Just to be who we are
Just to be by your side
Good.
Now we're connected
to servers around the world.
All that's left to do is to upload
the information from Metis, right?
Tears of Idea are forming
all around the world right now.
Everything that has disappeared from
this world as if they never existed...
The information on it will spill out
from those tears and flood the world.
Now it's all up to how people
will handle that information.
Believe it and cause panic
or laugh it off as a conspiracy
theory and get invaded.
It'll be hell either way.
It doesn't get
any more exciting than this.
Are we... Are we really sure
we can trust Medea-san?
We followed her judgment,
and we almost lost Siren-san.
She threw herself into the Mirage,
knowing what it really was.
Is that not called "suicide"
in the language of Earth?
That idiot has shined so brightly at
the core of the Mirage many times before!
Her song has saved the world
no matter how bleak the situation was!
Until Lukos beat her, that is.
You should have protected her.
You shouldn't have given her free rein
because of her past power.
But I understand that what happened
might have damaged your trust in me.
If you do not wish for this,
then let us stop this plan.
We'll move forward with the plan.
The world will be united,
even if it causes an unprecedented panic.
Everything's changed overnight.
We're getting backlash
from all over the world.
I wish our world debut
had been more positive.
It is what it is, for now.
Cruel truth like this is hard to accept.
But as Medea-san predicted,
the tears are starting to form.
I saw it!
My town, my family, it all disappeared!
Right in front of my eyes!
That footage from Japan wasn't fake!
He's come to the world of nightmares, too.
From this moment, everyone on Earth
will have to choose how to face XENOS.
Yo.
Long time no see.
Kyoya-kun? Soji-kun?
How did you get in?!
Press must have been staking out outside!
We know how to handle the press.
As such, we will leave Earth
and head to the XENOS stronghold.
We'll kick their asses with our
performance and snap them out of it!
I don't know if we'll come back alive.
This may be the last
conversation we'll have.
But I will... SI-VIS is...
Haven't you learned to relax?
You sound like a committee chair.
Or worse, a teacher.
What?
See how everyone's put off?
This dead air is your fault!
Huh? What?
I know, right?
He insisted that he do the talking,
so I let him, and this is what we got.
Your words are too emotional
and baseless!
You're right.
A cross between you and
I would be perfect.
Then you finish the speech.
Okay.
So... this is goodbye for a while.
We've been putting our lives on the line.
While I enjoyed it, I was scared, too.
So I think I just need to do
this tour like all the other ones.
But I still feel I'll be crushed
by fear I've never felt before.
Because the person I love, the people
I love, count on me to protect them.
No, that's not all.
I want to save those I've yet to meet.
Because Medea-san showed me...
What Yosuke-kun was trying to do.
His big wish for the people of Earth.
Everyone singing, dancing,
and laughing together.
The future where earthlings
and XENOS get along with each other.
The future Yosuke-kun dreamed of.
I won't give up on them until the end.
I see.
This Yosuke-kun must be
very special to you, Kyoya.
That's right.
So I have to go, Grammy.
Kenji, Yoshikazu, and Satomi!
You know, it may be cold over there.
Don't forget to bring your sweater.
O-Okay.
Don't you worry, Grandma.
I'll make sure that he does.
I'm counting on you, Soji-kun.
That boy always sleeps with his tummy out.
I'm hanging up, Grammy!
Sorry, guys. You can go ahead.
THIS IS NAGI'S MASTERPIECE!
WRITE SOME AWESOME MUSIC FOR IT!
You ready to go, Kyoya?
Siren.
Let's show XENOS how awesome
SI-VIS's performances are.
Siren.
And when Nagi comes back, we can all—
Siren!
Remember what Medea-san said?
Your Idea can't be returned
to normal with human power.
It was a strong curse XENOS cast
in exchange for your life.
That doesn't work on me.
I don't like this.
Don't leave me here.
I won't leave you!
We'll reconcile with XENOS, ask them how
to turn you back to normal, and come back.
So please wait until then.
Root for us from here.
Do you know how cruel that is?
I was born only to sing, nothing else.
I wasn't born to envy
other people singing.
I don't care if I disappear.
This can be the end of me.
I still want to—
No!
I don't want a world without you!
I'm doing this to protect
the world you're in!
You, Nagi, everyone in SI-VIS, everyone
at Harmonia, my friends and family...
I'm going, so I can protect this world
where people I love live!
I appreciate that.
But no matter what happens to me
or what results we get, I will sing.
No one can stop my song.
I know.
I want to hear your song...
one more time, too.
Bring Nagi back no
matter what, you hear me?
Thank you for the case, Vice President.
If that can be your good
luck charm, it's no big deal.
Come back alive.
We will!
Was it summer the last time
we came to Tatekashi island?
It feels like it was such a long time ago.
Well, a lot has happened since then.
This island is connected
to the planet of XENOS?
When Orphe escaped to Earth, he used
Metis to connect this place to XENOS.
It's like that one door
that goes anywhere.
It's the power Lord Archon gave us
to have Earth in our hands.
Orphe used it in a completely
opposite way.
Samael sealed the gate
I created, but here...
This gate allows one
to supply Idea remotely.
Even if you leave this planet.
However, it won't be as strong as
your live concerts, so do be careful.
This road leads to the planet of XENOS.
There may only be a few of us left,
but Apollo, who defeated you alone,
awaits at the end.
Are you still—
Of course we'll go.
It's what you, other XENOS,
and most importantly,
Yosuke-kun set out
to achieve more than ten years ago.
Everyone, follow me.
You think I'll just let you go like that?
Krios.
It's been a while, June.
You're going to our planet, aren't you?
You're going to destroy us
before we take Earth from you.
Krios, listen to me. We are—
It's pointless.
Your voice will not reach Krios.
That's not true!
Krios is...
He's more kind than anyone. He's the
purest, most innocent last child of XENOS.
He went slightly off track. That's all.
If I talk to him—
That's not the problem, Medea-san.
He doesn't hate you.
That's why your voice doesn't reach him.
What?
The only words that will reach him
are those of the person he hates.
My words only.
Yes, that's fine.
I only need to get revenge on June.
Kyoya-kun, you heard me.
Please go ahead.
June-kun.
This is vengeance only I have
the right to take on.
You have to join us later, June-kun.
With Krios, if you can.
You're helpless,
yet you're so selfish, Kyoya-kun.
Wha...
Stop it, June. Don't speak the truth.
Sometimes truth hurts people.
That's that. Medea-san, please lead us.
But without me, he can't open this gate—
Didn't you hear me? Krios will help him.
I believe you.
Krios!
A stage?
It's the place where Lady Eden
gave the blessing to the people of XENOS.
The Diva sang the melody of blessing
and continued to give Idea to the people.
From this place to the whole planet,
to every single person.
Beyond time and age,
for generations before Lady Eden.
But it was interrupted?
The cause was unknown.
Did the Idea of the stars get depleted
or did the Diva's blood get thinner?
Or perhaps Lady Eden's body
has reached its limit?
This is the Diva's stage.
The sacred place to give blessings
to XENOS, to people.
Right here.
Was that Lady Eden?
The Diva with my blood.
Oh, it is her.
This is my mother.
Lady Eden.
Finally, the time for revenge has come.
You for Junne.
And I for Lukos.
What are the rules?
Do you want us to kill each other?
Hit each other?
Or... do you want to sing together?
Rules?
I need no such thing!
The world is heading
in the direction we want!
XENOS and the earthlings
taking hate out on each other
and crushing each other
for their own survival.
Nothing can stop this!
That's not true.
That's not the direction I want.
And not the direction you want either!
But you hated me!
Back then, you showed hatred toward me!
I finally got to where you are,
how you feel!
So why do you deny my feelings?!
We're the same, Krios.
You're who I was back then.
Loneliness, sadness, and frustration
all turned into hatred
and became out of control.
Actually, that hatred
still lives inside me.
Let me go.
But still, I... we choose to sing.
About our families, our friends,
and about the people we hold dear!
Release me!
No, not just them!
People who aren't family!
Who aren't friends!
Even those I hated!
Because someday,
we'll understand each other.
It may not happen right now.
There may be a long way to go.
S-Stop it.
But eventually, for sure...
Stop it.
SI-VIS's song will make it happen!
Please stop!
Why? Why didn't you dodge?
Were you going to let me kill you?
Is that your way of making
amends for your sins?
No, you're wrong.
I believed in it.
Believed in what?
Your true kindness.
What I saw wasn't an illusion.
It wasn't an assumption
I conveniently came up with.
I'm deflated, unable to accept the bad end
It was actually you who saved us.
- It was actually you who saved us.
- I bet you're shaking your head at me
I bet you're shaking your head at me
- Thank you, Krios.
Thanks to you, Earth
and its people have survived.
But always by my side
The city has lost its colors
- The city has lost its colors
- Why? Why did I?
Why? Why did I?
You... You're the ones
who erased Lukos, and yet...
Yes. And you were the ones
who erased Junne.
So there could've been a
future where we kill each other.
Or a future where we hate each other.
But it didn't turn out like that.
- Doesn't that answer why?
- Let me cry, elegy
Let me cry, elegy
Let's live together, Krios.
Two of us together, for Junne and Lukos.
Is too painful and impossibly long
It's unbearable
Of course. There was no way...
I could have killed you.
- I could have killed you.
-Better yet, just take me to where you are
Better yet, just take me to where you are
- I couldn't even leave you to die.
Yosuke-kun, I'm going to your homeland.
To the planet you tried to
save along with Earth.
In the musical stave
WOW, I let my feelings play
My bright future
WOW, started to shine
Unparalleled
With a smile on my face
I feel like I can even change
the world with you
(3, 2, 1, Singing over)
Intertwining harmony (Harmony)
I wouldn't have believed in miracles alone
This breathless heartbeat (Heart Beat)
I'll let it resonate in
the night sky with my voice
Our dream at full blast
Singing over, forever
Lan lan la la la