Why does Goryoukaku take
the shape of a star?
The answer is: for war.
It was based on the design
of the bastion fort,
which was invented in Europe while
Japan was in the Muromachi period.
The place we're standing
on is the bastion.
From this location, for instance,
we have a clear view of that bridge
and the stone wall behind it,
along with the bridge
and the bastion wall.
The bastion wall on the right, as well.
We can strike approaching enemies
from the side and eliminate them.
I see.
By deploying troops in each bastion,
we can attack our foes in any
direction, without any blind spots.
The shape of the fortress
is specialized for war.
But we can't use it like this.
We need trenches.
Indeed.
Those who have experienced the new
age of war understand such things.
While we wait for Sofia
and her men to arrive,
we will search for the gold
and prepare for combat.
Golden Kamuy
Episode Fifty-Nine
Our Kamuy
I found something!
A rock, huh?
I'm exhausted.
I'm pretty sure they hid it
in the moat, not a building.
But the old man said, "Dig here, doggy."
You've got something that makes
you think it's here, right?
You're still hiding things
from us at this point?
I'm not one of your soldiers, you know!
I found a lot of sandbags in a storehouse.
Huh?
They're here!
God
The character for god on my tattoo.
When we laid out the code, it landed
right on the storehouses here.
There must be something buried here.
Another rock, huh?
Does the god character
really mean anything?
No idea...
God
But the fact is,
there's no other character with a
similar reading, like shin or jin.
3:30 AM
It's not a rock!
I found something!
Just this box?
There must be more buried below
it, obviously! You idiot!
Open it up already! Hurry!
What's this? Soil? Sand?
Cietoi.
Powdered diatomaceous earth.
That can't be all that's here!
What's this?
Paper?
An animal stomach.
We use them for holding
oils and other things.
So they've done everything they can
to make sure the contents stayed dry.
A book?
What does it say?
Let the old men read it!
What's this?
Land deeds.
About the time our deal with
the Russian navy broke down,
a government called the
"Ezo Republic" existed in Hakodate.
They needed money to fight.
So we met with a Nispa named Enomoto
Takeaki from the Ezo Republic,
and traded gold for a treaty
recognizing Ainu land rights.
Land deeds bought with the gold?
Where's the land? How big is it?
Look at this.
Vast tracts of land,
spread all throughout Hokkaido.
There's no way Hijikata Toshizou
wouldn't know about this.
I didn't, actually.
About the time this treaty was
made, I was busy fighting.
I spent very little time at Goryoukaku.
Just as we were about to hand over the
gold, the Hakodate War came to an end,
and the Ezo Republic ceased to exist.
But Enomoto-san worked with the
Meiji government to ensure the treaty
with the Ainu would remain enforced.
The Meiji government wanted
the gold too, so they agreed.
They assumed, foolishly,
that they could abrogate it later.
But Enomoto-san had actually
had the ambassadors
Netherlands
France
England
of six countries be
present for its signing.
America
Italy
Prussia
It was clearly made out to
be an international treaty,
one that could not be easily abandoned.
Perhaps this was his way of repaying
the Ainu for their support of him,
or perhaps he knew the war was lost,
and only wanted to make one last
problem for the government.
The deed book contains a detailed
record of its own history,
and entrusts the landowners,
the Ainu, to decide how the land is used.
The Meiji government wouldn't
want this getting out.
Wait, does this mean the gold is gone?!
Wonderful.
My daughter will live as an Ainu, and
this is the greatest gift I can give her.
I thought that this was
all we could do, too.
That the only thing we could do with
the gold was buy forested land.
That this was the only way to
protect the Ainu without fighting.
If we protect the forests,
we can protect the kamuy.
Our culture can't exist
without the kamuy.
The thing I had finally figured out,
what I could do for the Ainu...
The old Ainu had already accomplished it!
The golden kamuy that I was
told would bring disaster...
was the kamuy we really needed!
I'm so disappointed I can't even stand.
But why'd Wilk hide the deed book here?
He could've taken it with him.
Perhaps someone was after it.
Kiroranke, maybe?
But stealing the book wouldn't...
Wilk's code led me to the deed book.
But there was nothing in our
discussion about protecting forests.
Did the Ainu make the land treaty to
protect their forests in the first place?
Leaving behind the Kamuy wouldn't
make the Ezo Republic more powerful.
Don't you think Wilk left
this behind because he wanted
the land's resources to be developed?
Asirpa...
What Wilk said... What Yulbars said...
Forget it all.
Sofia.
There's nothing left for us here.
We have two hours until Lieutenant
Tsurumi and his men arrive.
We need to get out of here now!
We need to tell the ones
working on our defenses!
Hurry! Kantarou, head
to the east entrance!
I'm crying so much I can't see.
I can't walk.
Hang in there, Shiraishi.
Hijikata Nispa. I'll take the book.
Hijikata Nispa?
Only half was used!
It says that 37,125 kilograms of
gold were given to Enomoto Takeaki.
Nopperabo told me there
was 75,000 kilograms.
So a bit over half of
it's still out there?
Half the gold's still out there somewhere!
Calm down, Shiraishi!
Get to the trenches!
Lieutenant Tsurumi's men?
But it's too soon!
Look out at the sea.
Something's in the sky.
Military air balloons!
They're watching us?
So that was gunfire from a ship?!
They came in their destroyers!
The minute Lieutenant Tsurumi
began to crack the code,
he also contacted Ominato
naval base in Aomori,
where Koito's father was located,
Ominato
so that he could quickly get to
the gold no matter where it was.
Sapporo
Sugimoto Route (Hakodate Line)
He went from Sapporo Station
to Muroran station,
Muroran
Tsurumi Muroran Line)
and took a destroyer waiting
at the port to Hakodate port!
Hakodate
Ominato
Yes!
Good morning!
Golden Kamuy
What's he doing?
Kadokura! Take care of the rest!
Where's he going?
Somebody's here.
Don't shoot! I want to
talk to Lieutenant Tsurumi.
Did he go to surrender on his own?
Of course not!
Probably not.
Anyway, it's too late to retreat.
We'll have to fight as best we can.
Let's go, Kirawus.
Is their plan to use those big
cannons to flatten Goryoukaku?
We need to get out of here.
They're lying in wait to attack
anyone who runs from the cannons.
This place has three exits,
and I'm sure they have lots of
soldiers hidden beyond the bridges.
Only 16 army soldiers can
ride along on a destroyer.
Even if they brought all four
destroyers that we saw at Abashiri,
that's 64 people.
They may not have many stationed
except at the exits!
All the more reason to leave now, then.
No, wait!
Wilk said the prisoners
would get half the gold!
Let's figure out if the other half
is in Goryoukaku before we run!
Indeed... after all these
complicated riddles,
he can't have hidden it
somewhere else in Hokkaido.
I can't die before I see
the gold for myself!
Calm down, Shiraishi!
The cannon fire stopped.
There was no gold.
I wondered what the famous Nagakura
Shinpachi was going to say.
Do you expect me to say,
"Oh, too bad, then," and just go home?
I can simply use my destroyers'
cannons to blow you all to pieces,
sweep aside the pile of gore,
and see for myself whether it's there.
We found the deed to land in Hokkaido,
which the Ainu bought with gold.
The result of a treaty between
the Ainu and Ezo Republic.
If you were an intelligence officer,
you should know something about this.
Ministry of Finance          Home Ministry
About how the Meiji government
seemed to have a lot of extra
money after the Battle of Hakodate.
Or something that didn't make
sense about the huge cost of the
Russo-Japanese War.
The deed book says that the
Ainu have the right to use
their land as they see fit.
It has the rights to a huge
expanse of Hokkaido land.
The forests can be turned into
fertile land, perfect for farming,
and vast mineral resources
sleep beneath them...
And the name on the deed?
None.
It simply says the Ainu have the right
to use the land, and no one else.
But it's worth something to you, as well.
The 7th has many Ainu soldiers,
like Ariko Ipopte, right?
Please, spare the lives of everyone
in exchange for the deed book.
Hijikata Toshizou is driven
by one thing: battle.
As the second in command
of the Shinsengumi,
he's looking for a place to have
one last grand battle and die.
He was lucky enough to survive
the hopeless Battle of Hakodate.
But now he's eager to find a place to die.
I promise I'll go back to Goryoukaku
and persuade him to surrender.
Nagakura-san, please, get off the ground.
You're hoping to use the deed book
to get me to stop firing the cannons,
then go back to Goryoukaku and fight
alongside Hijikata Toshizou, right?
You cunning old man.
You, Nagakura Shinpachi, are more eager
to have one last fight than anyone!
You're a survivor of
those crazy Shinsengumi!
Stop with the bad acting.
I'm good at seeing through people's lies.
Then did you figure out how
much of what I said was true?
Lieutenant Tsurumi's men who couldn't
fit on the destroyers
will be coming here by train, right?
They should be here any minute.
The cannon fire's stopped.
Why don't we at least get
the young lady out of here?
She can take the deed book, too.
Sounds good to me.
That book's not going to
do me a damn bit of good.
Don't you all agree?
We've finally made it all this way,
and the gold might be beneath our feet!
I can't just give up!
I'll stay here too.
I want to be useful to everyone,
and I have to see this to the end.
Young lady.
If it looks bad, I'll get
Asirpa-san somewhere safe.
Hijikata-san!
Nagakura-san let himself be caught!
He told me to "take care of the rest"!
It might be thanks to him
that the attacks stopped.
Anyway, I'll follow the plan.
Okay, hurry and go.
Please, stay safe.
Let's go, Kirawus! Mansur!
If you sent Kadokura on
that suicide mission,
then it means we're staying
here to fight, right?
Why?
Asirpa, staying will teach
you what your father felt.
A wind of fortune brought
to us by a very lucky man
is about to bring us victory.
Wow, lots of flies today.
Those aren't flies, Kadokura!
The soldiers who came by train!
A minute later and we'd have
been completely surrounded.
So it was thanks to you
that the cannons stopped.
I don't know how long it will last.
But I've left a seed that will
make Lieutenant Tsurumi hesitate about
doing any large-scale attacks.
We brought Onuma dumplings, the famous
snack from Onuma Park Station.
A deed book?
You believe this?
It's a bluff!
We can't be so sure.
The Meiji government should have been
flat broke after the Battle of Hakodate,
but they immediately began the grand
redevelopment of Tokyo, the new capital.
A water and sewage system. The large-scale
railways. The brick town of Ginza.
And the huge beer factories
built in Yokohama, Sapporo,
Tokyo, and Osaka, one after another.
They say the liquor tax alone was enough
to pay for the Sino-Japanese War.
The Russo-Japanese War was
also supposedly paid for with huge
loans from foreign countries.
But who knows if that's true.
Before the war, not a single
country expected Japan to win.
But there's no way General Okuda
wouldn't have known about it.
Does this mean his goal was to get rid of
this unfortunate contract with the Ainu,
and he simply used the
gold as bait for us?
Well, I'll see for myself if
the deed book is even real.
I'll give Hijikata Toshizou
the fight he wants.
It's time for the Battle of Goryoukaku.
Dig around here.
Why here?
Kadokura's tattoos had an
important clue that led us here.
It was so long ago that even
I'd forgotten about it.
They can't see us from
those balloons, right?
The pine trees hide us perfectly.
Hurry!
A lid?
Open it, now! Now!
A well for horses.
I'm probably the only man
alive today who remembers it.
It's dangerous! Calm down!
Calm down, Shiraishi! You're crazy!
Asirpa-san, let's go down together.
Yeah.
Well?
There are bags everywhere!
Let's open one in front of everyone!
Okay, pull it up, Ushiyama!
Gold!
I told you, that's dangerous!
Just wait up there, fool!
Ow...
Asirpa-san...
Looks like we found the gold, huh?
Next Time
The Battle of Goryoukaku
Next Time: The Battle of Goryoukaku!