Saegusa Hospital
Wishes and Songs Will Be Heard
What's up, Soji?
Something's off at Harmonia.
No one's picking up the phone.
Maybe they all went home?
No cell phone, no land line, nothing.
That's not normal.
Okay, I'll go back and check.
June is here, too.
Let's meet up in front of the office.
Here we go.
Is this your doing?
Nope. It was a lady who's
much scarier than me.
I see. So XENOS isn't playing around.
It's more like we've been
going easy on you until now.
Can I leave here if I defeat you?
I told you, I didn't create this space.
But maybe...
you could get a tip or two if you do?
That's more than enough.
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
It's Show Time
The price of living in the time of freedom
"So, what do you want to do?"
Just standing there with my empty body
Like a calling to protect the world
I craved an unequaled gift
Lost in night's darkness
Until a voice called out to me
Like the light that declares the dawn
I'll take you with me at
any cost (I pray and wish)
Beyond the Echo-verse (To the future)
Just being with you makes me strong
It's not an exaggeration
That encounter was a supernova
(Our eyes were locked)
In an instant, everything that I am
(In an instant)
Will be changed forever (Just to be)
A calling arises from deep
within in my burning heart
Destiny is Calling us now
Just to be who we are
Just to be by your side
No one's at the front desk.
Where's Nagi? Was she inside?
I don't know.
But we can't get in touch with μ, either.
It's highly likely that Nagi
was inside with her.
Hey, Kyoya!
Off I go!
Whoa?!
What are you doing?!
What's going on?!
Nagi, this way.
What's happening here?
What the heck is this?
How's it going over there?
It's no good.
I can't take back control.
Looks like they have
us right where they want us.
Watch it, Nono-Ken!
What're you doing over there?
Well, just in case
when XENOS charges in...
You won't stop XENOS with that.
Please don't say that like we're doomed!
We'll just do everything we can.
Whoa?!
You aren't half bad, miss.
You're called Rui-san, am I right?
I'm surprised you know about
the manager. I'm not even the talent.
I don't think there's anyone else
among XENOS who knows
more about Harmonia Entertainment than me.
Still, I'm what you call a "noob."
I only got into it a few days ago.
I won't let you mess with my talent.
Wow, you think you're going to stall me?
Don't underestimate a former SI-VIS!
Damn it, this doesn't make sense.
They're not even attacking us.
XENOS, what are you trying to do?
μ...
Don't worry!
Stick together, and there's
nothing to be scared of!
So we'll go home together, Nagi.
Back to Kyoya!
Well, I'm afraid it won't be that easy.
Because our objective is—
Whoa, there!
This takes me back, old man!
No one attacked us, so I felt lonely.
Hey, now! SI-VIS girls
are quick to lose their temper—
I guess the secondary form has its limits.
μ! I'll help you now!
Now, Medea.
What?! Nagi!
Hey! Oh, boy.
I might get yelled at for this later.
Hmm.
Front and back entrances,
second-floor window,
underground parking lot, it's all bust.
We get tossed out.
Does this mean the whole building
is covered in the Mirage?
It's a different type of
application than we've seen,
but I'm sure it's similar technology.
Wait, aren't they...?
How do we get inside?
To connect with the Mirage,
we need the backstage stuff and the staff.
Both are inside the building.
And Metis as well.
Which means that right now, we have
no way of connecting with the Mirage.
Hmm...
Oh, how about what we did when we jumped
out of the helicopter the other day?
That wasn't your power.
Hayama-san said it was Nagi-chan's power.
Oh, that's right!
If Nagi's also trapped
in here, we can't use it.
No, we can use it!
She was inside and I was
outside of the Mirage back then.
So we just need to do the same.
But you were able to touch
Nagi directly at back then.
This time, we don't
even know where she is.
Then there's nothing we...
We just need to deliver it.
Our location to her!
Tell me, what is your purpose?
I can't even start to guess
what kind of technology you use,
but I can tell the difference
in its strength.
So I hate to admit it, but I can tell
that you're holding back on me, too.
Oh no, I did go all-out.
When I'm running multiple
applications, this is my limit.
That said, it's true that I'm personally
not interested in killing you right away.
Because that'd be
boring, you know?
Huh? Isn't this...
the server room?
I was only going to lure in the diva.
But I guess this is within
the margin of error.
Attacking without even
hearing what I have to say?
You're so barbaric!
You're the invader
who attacked out of nowhere,
so I don't want to hear it!
μ!
You weren't invited here
in the first place.
Please sit there and be quiet.
Nagi... run.
You're the one with the blood
of Eden the Diva.
What?
I am Medea.
I came to this planet
to tell you the truth.
This is the record
your friend left behind.
Wait, a video?
Yosuke and Nagi? What is this?
I see you're not surprised.
Nagi?
Somehow... Somehow I knew it.
That I wasn't like Kyoya and μ.
Yes. You are one of us.
You're a member of the tribe
those around you shun as "invaders."
And Orphe is as well.
He's the XENOS you all called "Yosuke."
He's the one who betrayed us, kidnapped
you, and brought Earth into this war.
He's the main culprit.
You named the diva "Nagi,"
and you never told her who she was.
You never told the members
of SI-VIS who Orphe was.
Because you were afraid
that it would sever their bond,
and SI-VIS would fall apart.
I was only looking for
the right time to tell them.
More importantly, they were too young
and immature to bear this secret.
You're right.
It's a sensitive subject.
So I get where you're coming from.
But right now, your indecisiveness
will be our advantage.
The diva will probably feel that
you betrayed her, you know?
And SI-VIS won't be able to accept
the truth about Orphe, you know?
Diva, you have a power
that no earthling possesses.
No, not just the earthlings.
Even amongst us, your power
to share and give Idea is very special.
It's a power that can single-handedly
change the fate of a planet.
I've come here to return
your power to its rightful place.
We need y—
It's Kyoya.
Hey! This is Kyoya! Right, Nagi?
What?
Wait, what's going on?
Nagi, you met Kyoya when you were a kid?!
Y-Yes, I remembered it at that cave.
Oh, right! The cave on the island!
Will you shut up?
Woo, we can so use this!
A friend you've met as a child
but was somehow forgotten!
Not to mention you saved his life!
This is like an ultra-top-class
Goddess of Fortune stuff!
Y-You think so?
Man, what an awesome material!
Now we can teach Kyoya a le—
I mean, get his attention, Nagi!
D-Do you really think it'll be that easy?
Huh? Why not?
B-Because the diva is XENOS.
And therefore incompatible with you...
The adversity is exactly why
their romance will heat up!
Can't XENOS understand
something so simple?
Wh-What are y—
I can't believe how dumb you are.
That silly boy Kyoya
will never have a change of heart over
something trivial like Nagi being XENOS!
μ, you were mad just a second ago
that Kyoya had a change of heart.
Whose side are you on?!
Right now, I'm trying to tear down
this old hag, so work with me here!
"Old hag"?
Why don't you give it a try?
Test the bond of SI-VIS right now.
Challenge how much
they care for each other!
And if SI-VIS collapses
from internal disunity,
then it's on us, the management team,
for failing to foster them.
We'll take responsibility.
But do you really think
it will work out so smoothly?
Hey, Medea. What do we do?
Looks like our win isn't guaranteed.
You're beyond my understanding.
The reality I forced you to face
isn't something to take lightly.
That should've been more than enough
for your trust and love to waver—
Let's go, μ.
Roger that.
Where do you think you're going?
You think I'd let you just walk away?!
I can go anywhere.
I can hear Idea...
No, I can hear a song.
Kyoya's... everyone's song.
Oh, wow!
An impromptu concert?
Just the three of us?
That's right!
It's just the same as the normal battle!
But we're outside of the Mirage.
Even if we sing out here,
we can't save anyone,
let alone fight XENOS.
We can.
The Idea will reach Nagi!
Wishes and songs will be heard.
I just know that we can
tell her we're here!
The song that succumbed
and vanished that day
Braver dreamer
Dreamer...
In the driving meteor shower
This planet is like a dystopia
An ode to freedom, devoted over and over
Wow!
Where do the voices drop out
and disappear to?
What are they singing?
Warning sirens
Well... Is it "Braver Dreamer"?
Of revival will sound
Damn it! I'm the only one
who can't hear it.
Burning down whimpers and fuss
I see. Then let me bring it to you.
Flickering in blue and inextinguishable
Ignite the flame
Run faster and stronger
Far away, to the end of the world
This is...
In these muddy shoes
Metis... it's responding!
Someday, somewhere,
someone without a doubt
For real... It's not all,
but some commands do go through!
An ode to freedom, devoted over and over,
that succumbed and vanished
Could it be that Nagi-chan did this?
No.
SI-VIS did this.
We'll pick it up and pass it on
Put everything into restoring the system.
We'll drive XENOS away
and take back our office!
Yes, ma'am!
Oh, man. They'll want to
know who's responsible.
Seabirds fly in the dawning sky
Look up and you'll find a utopia
Any comment?
That's what I'd like to see.
Reading the flowing breeze
I'm looking forward to seeing
you struggle some more.
Show us the path that we should take
I'm counting on you.
He really didn't kill me.
The prologue will
What does he want?
Announce the beginning
As if to slash open hesitation
Leaving the traces
on the ground I tread on
Keep on pushing toward the future
You're too careless, June.
Sing higher and stronger
Let the morning wind
carry the endless wishes
Stepping firmly on the ground
Why...?
The dream I raised to the sky far away
I can crush the pests now.
An ode to freedom, devoted over and over,
that succumbed and vanished
I can get my revenge, but...
We promise to protect it to the end
Let there be light
for the withering flowers
Let there be future
for the faltering present
I'll never let go
Of your hand
Sing higher and stronger
Let the morning wind
carry the endless wishes
Stepping firmly on the ground
The dream I raised to the sky far away
With our hearts racing,
we'll face tomorrow together
We're Braver Dreamers
Run faster and stronger
Far away, to the end of the world
(We're dreamers)
How are they doing that?
In these muddy shoes
Look!
So cool!
Someday, somewhere,
someone without a doubt
An ode to freedom, devoted over and over,
that succumbed and vanished
The fans are watching.
We'll pick it up and pass it on
Do it later. Later!
So those are earthlings.
Medea. Long time no see.
Orphe.
The view outside is back to normal.
We escaped from the Mirage!
What?!
I-I'm so relieved!
95% of Metis's control has returned.
Three more minutes
and we can restore it completely.
Good.
Metis might be restored completely, but...
What the heck is going on here?
Nonomiya-kun! Shioriko-chan!
Huh?
Yes?
Get ready and be on standby.
The second wave is coming!
In this data you just unlocked,
everything Apollo did
is archived as a record.
It's the information that's already
been erased on our planet.
He was trying to create
an heir to Lady Eden.
Was it a clone, an artificial child,
or a mix of both?
Anyhow, that's what gave birth to Nagi.
She's altered, but still a child of hope
who has the blood of Lady Eden.
When I found out that truth,
he pointed his blade at me
and hid everything away.
Medea. Do you remember
what I said back then?
Doubt everything.
Do not believe everything easily.
Doubt, doubt, and doubt it even more.
And only believe in the truth
that's left in the end.
I hope that the truth you arrive at
will be the same one I found.
Don't let Apollo steal Nagi away.
She may be able
to save both of my homes.
Your wish...
I was finally able to receive it.
But... if possible, please be aliv—
Oh, man. Well, that was a failure.
They totally gave me the slip.
You had no choice.
We misjudged SI-VIS's...
no, humans' relationships of trust.
Let us retreat.
Hurry back and ask
for instructions from Lord Apollo—
Nope, wrong answer.
Operation Recapture Diva
is now in its second phase.
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Tomoko Takedani Sater
Krzysztof Kunc
Salem Alabanza
Gabriella Alabanza
Michelle Tymon
In the musical stave
WOW, I hid my feelings
My pitiful past
WOW, started to shine
Challenges ahead but
I'll embrace them
I feel like I can even change
the world with you
(3, 2, 1, Singing over)
Intertwining harmony (Harmony)
I wouldn't have believed in miracles alone
This breathless heartbeat (Heart Beat)
I'll let it resonate in
the night sky with my voice
My... our dream at full blast
Singing over, forever
Lan lan la la la