Adapted from the story of the same title
by author Ku Xuan
from Chinese Qidian Website of Yuewen
Group The Daily Life of the Immortal King
The Daily Life of the Immortal King 5
Episode 10: Heavenly Dao's Secret
Lord Spirit Emperor, finally, you're back.
We all believed that you
wouldn't be caught so easily.
I'm so sorry, your Lord
Spirit Emperor is now mine.
Just a little more
Spiritual Energy, it'd be enough
to open the Dao Ancestor's Treasure.
No matter how great these gifted
children's Spiritual Roots are,
they can't compare to the big shots
of the cultivation world.
Of course, that little
girl is an exception.
Sooner or later, I'll
devour that girl, too.
Ah, you're finally here.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Hahaha.
It was a pleasure working with you.
The Ascension Technique was a success.
And Earth-Moon Passage is now open.
Here I come, Heavenly Dao!
Elite Class
Instructor Pan is here.
Quiet, everyone.
Come on, don't be so serious.
It makes me look like a strict teacher.
What's gotten into Instructor Pan today?
First of all, let's welcome
Wang Ling back to our school.
What are you staring at?
Give him a round of applause.
Hehehe.
The story starts before
morning class today.
It's nice to see you siblings
getting along so well.
It seems like Nuan doesn't
want Ling to leave her side.
Since Nuan wants Ling to stay.
How about you take her with you, Ling?
Your mom and I could enjoy ourselves.
That's just how things are.
Wang Ling wants to bring his little sister
to study at school for a day.
What?
I disagree.
Ascension Technique Lesson Plan
Such a young child, who'd take
responsibility if something happens?
But...
No buts.
I don't agree.
Ah! So bright!
What is this?
Since Instructor Wang has
come to plead for you,
we'll let little Wang Nuan
become our one-day student.
Ah?
Now that you've joined our 60th High,
you'll need to change into
these training clothes.
Hey, when did you even prepare these?
Wang Ling was surprised
that his little sister
would win the hearts of
both head instructors
with just one glance.
There's a story that the
Primordial Cultivator,
also known as the Ancestor of Cultivation,
created the Heavenly Dao.
To prevent the Heavenly Dao
from falling into the wrong hands,
he sealed its secrets on the Moon.
Instructor Pan, how'd
the Primordial Cultivator get to the Moon?
That's what we're going to learn today,
Ascension Technique.
Theoretically, if you've
got enough Spiritual Power,
you can open an Earth-Moon Passage
and go to the Moon
using the Ascension Technique.
How much Spiritual Power would that take?
It's an amount you can't
even put a number on.
With your capabilities, you can't
open a very long spatial passage,
but Ascension Technique is
the foundation of spatial techniques.
It's a key skill.
Everyone, please give it a try.
Pervert!
Alas!
You're still learning,
so it's normal to have
some inaccurate passage positioning.
Sun Rong, where did you position it?
Instructor's Office.
Instructor Pan, I've brought
the graded talisman papers.
Hmm, as expected of Sun Rong,
accurate passage positioning.
You're a good learner.
Oh dear, little Wang Nuan,
do you understand it?
Ah, our little Wang Nuan is the best!
You're so young,
and you're so talented at drawing.
What's that?
Let me see.
How odd, that part of the sky
looks unusually bright.
It seems to be some kind of passage.
I think this must be a cosmic phenomenon
caused by a cultivator
undergoing tribulation.
No need to worry.
I never expected it to go so smoothly.
Now, only the last step to go.
Who dares open
the Heavenly Dao's Gate without asking?
I just need to break through this gate,
the secret treasures left by
the Dao Ancestor will all be mine.
Guo Hao, hit the 8-ring.
Exam Passed.
Strange...
Why is there a pink target?
Hehehe.
Little Wang Nuan, I prepared a
pink target just for you, do you like it?
You're always welcome
to visit the 60th High, hahaha!
Ahem.
Next up, Sun Rong.
Senior Wang Ling
and Little Wang Nuan are both watching.
I'd better give my best shot.
Looks like Little Wang Nuan
is eager to give it a try too.
You combined it with
your spiritual root attributes
to improve accuracy.
You're always great, Sun Rong.
Excellent
Next up, Chen Chao.
Exam
Hmph.
Junior Sun is skilled.
But as the monitor,
I don't even need help to hit the target.
Make-up Exam
The Hundred-Step Flying Sword Exam
is about precision,
not who can throw the farthest.
Chen Chao, you'll take
the make-up exam next time.
Wang Nuan, do you also
want to give it a try?
Your turn, Wang Ling.
Let me show you how it's done.
Hmm.
Here I come, Heavenly Dao!
Oh no.
I can't move my body.
Wang Ling.
Missed the target.
Failed
Failed.
That's great, Senior Wang!
The school building is safe.
How can you be so happy about failing?
Alas, I really don't understand
young people these days.
Oh? Little Wang Nuan is
also taking the exam?
Wang Nuan is so young,
but she's learning quite well.
Yeah, though she didn't manifest Sword Qi,
I can tell her learning ability
is impressive, hahaha.
Oh no.
What?
Where did this sudden gust come from?
Wang Nuan's shot is far
stronger than I thought.
I can't deflect it perfectly,
then I'll have to...
What?!
This Sword Qi, what's happening?
No matter who you are,
once I step through this gate,
I'll become invincible!