JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES, PARTY OF NONE
EPISODE 7: THE JACK-OF-ALL-TRADES
FOLLOWS HIS FEELINGS
That's... a teleportation light!
Hey, what happened?
We were suddenly transported
out of the dungeon!
What's that?
Let's go see.
Excuse me! Coming through!
The Black Dragon...!
Wait!
Something's wrong.
W-What?
It's already been defeated!
What's going on here?
Th-That's...
Orhun!
Luna?
You fought the Black Dragon?!
You need healing!
Orhun?
Take care of... the clean up...
Why is Orhun the only
one who looks injured?
Don't tell me...
He fought it himself?
You beat it?
That's impossible! What's going on?
Don't you dare ignore me!
Enough!
What?!
It's clear that Orhun was the
one who beat the Black Dragon.
Why don't you accept your
own weakness already?
What?
You always try to tell us what to do!
Pixie, take care of him.
M-My body won't move...
The fight's over already.
Stop it, both of you.
Damn it!
My report on the expedition's going
to be about nothing but Orhun!
He gave me courage,
and helped me cast my
first advanced spell.
He taught me about
Parallel Construction...
And...
He defeated the infamous
Black Dragon all by himself!
He saved my life again...
He was so cool when he fought.
He always has such a
kind expression, too...
Is that what they call a gap?
I'm back...
S-Sister, welcome... home...
Her face is a mess.
It's been forever since
I've seen her this tired.
At least take a shower before bed.
Later...
Let's go to the baths together, then!
You need to take a bath
when you're tired, huh?
Thank you, Sophia!
I'm so glad you were safe today.
It was thanks to Orhun.
He was so cool today, huh?
Hey, Sophia.
How did the fight between Orhun
and the Black Dragon feel to you?
Huh? Well, he was really strong.
Yeah, that's the normal reaction.
He's so much more powerful than us
that I can't even understand him.
I understood him.
What?
Tell me what you understood!
Calm down, S-Sister!
Sorry...
His movements and magic were amazing,
but I think the rest was all just basics.
Basics?
Yeah.
It was exactly what he taught us about
how rear attackers and defenders fight.
So I learned a lot!
It's amazing that he can do
all that by himself, huh?
I thought that I could never understand
the bottomless well of strength
I saw in Orhun's fighting,
but Sophia was different.
She understood what she
saw in her own way.
You're amazing, Sophia.
I'm not...
That's not true.
You're way more amazing, Sister!
Sophia...
I respect you the most of all.
You walk on your own two feet.
You're so cool and a lot
of people rely on you!
I want to be like you!
But don't push yourself too hard, Sis!
Ow...
Relieve Pain!
My whole body aches...
I guess it's close to noon.
I pushed myself to my limits
yesterday, after all.
I'm lucky there are no bad aftereffects
after all that magic I used.
Selma?
I'm sorry to bother you today.
How are you feeling?
As you can see, I'm fine.
Thanks for coming all this way.
We finished the teaching expedition
with no casualties, thanks to you.
You have our thanks.
Stop bowing!
Somebody like you shouldn't be...
My position isn't what's important.
You saved me, and our new recruits.
I cannot thank you enough.
Selma...
Actually...
Could you come to our clan right now?
Our leader wants to meet you.
Sure. I'm not doing anything today.
I'll make this quick.
Would you like to join the
Night Sky Silver Rabbits?
We want you to serve
as a front-line attacker
for Unit 1,
our clan's most powerful party.
And I want to recommend you
as a lieutenant of our clan.
Lieutenant?
I'm far too young...
You've got more than enough
experience and power.
And you're educated,
serious, and a hard worker.
You have what it takes to
be one of our lieutenants.
You agree, right, Selma?
Yes.
I would like to work with
you to support our clan.
Normally, anybody would jump
at an offer like this, but...
Sorry.
Could you give me some time?
Of course. Take your time.
Thank you.
I'll take my leave, then.
Oh, and the Adventurer's
Guild wants to see you.
All right. I'll head there.
I can't believe the Night Sky Silver
Rabbits want to recruit me...
So I'd have comrades, again?
It's not that funny, Old Man.
Sorry.
You always seem like such a grown-up.
It's nice to see you
acting your age for once.
I'm serious about this, you know.
It's true that they seem
to think highly of me.
But...
You might end up used
and thrown away, again.
Yes.
"Used" may not be a nice word,
but I think that supporting each other
and making up for our weaknesses
is how people grow.
I agree. But...
Think about it some more, then.
I came at the worst time...
So the Black Dragon appeared on Floor 50,
and you defeated it alone, I'm told.
Yes, that's true.
Alone? Nah.
We'd already weakened it, and you were
lucky enough to land the killing blow.
Lucky for you. We saved your life.
Shut up. You're not a part of this.
What?
Derick.
Guild master, if I may?
Oliver, why did you head straight
to Floor 92 with your new Enchanter?
Did you think it would be easy because
you'd been there so many times before?
I'm right, huh?
I told you numerous times
that it was dangerous to go ahead
before you got stronger.
There were a lot of times in the deep
floors where someone almost died.
And that's why we got a new Enchanter.
With someone whose support magic
was more powerful than yours,
I assumed we could go deeper.
And that's why you fired me.
That, I'm not mad about.
What makes me mad is how little
you seem to think of Enchanters.
I know exactly how much they're worth!
An Enchanter's important,
which is why I got a new one!
Then why did you start
with the deep floors?
Do you know how much
concentration it takes
for an Enchanter when
they're dungeon-delving?
All an Enchanter has to
do is sit where it's safe
and cast another buff when
the first one runs out.
It's simple!
Are you serious?
Of course I am. It's the truth!
I can't believe you.
Oliver, 61 seconds.
Anneli, 134 seconds.
Derick, 186 seconds.
That's how long each of your buffs last.
An Enchanter has to keep track of
all those to refresh the buffs,
and also give commands
to the rest of the party.
How is that easy? Tell me, Oliver!
Sophia, did you hear anything
about what Orhun will do next?
No, nothing.
We never did get a chance
to talk to him yesterday.
Do you think he'll join the
Night Sky Silver Rabbits?
You feel the same, huh?
We were just saying that!
Right, Sophia?
Y-Yeah.
Then why don't we ask him together?
Great idea!
But where is he?
My sister might know!
Orhun Dura...
I'd love to have him join us.
But is he ever going
to want comrades again?
He can get by without them.
And...
My magic won't work?
I don't need your buffs!
They'll throw me off
from what I'm used to!
He doesn't need my help.
He's someone far, far more
powerful than I am right now.
And I told him I'd like to
"work with him to support the clan," huh?
Sister!
What is it, Sophia?
Do you know where Orhun lives?
We're going to meet with him and
ask him to join the Rabbits!
Are you serious?
I want him to join, too, but...
But with his power, he doesn't need us.
If anything, at our level,
we'll just slow him down.
We know that.
But I want him to join us anyway!
Just being with him will show me
what I need to learn, I think!
Yes!
It's fun because when he teaches
you, you can get a lot stronger!
I-I'd love to have him with us more...
You guys...
Right now, we may be
slowing him down, yes.
But someday we'll get stronger
and make him recognize us as comrades!
That's right.
I can just learn from
him and get stronger!
It looks like I was thinking
about it too much.
He went to the Adventurer's
Guild. If you hurry...
Got it! Thanks!
Thank you!
Let's go!
So now they're going to talk about the
penalty for the force teleportation, huh?
Sucks to be them, I guess.
I feel tired.
Is that them?
What are they doing here?
That's him!
Orhun!
Mister!
Damn it...
The damage from yesterday
is catching up with me.
But why am I even running?
Orhun?
We want to talk!
Where are you?
This way!
No!
Orhun!
Where'd he go?
Let's look that way!
Yeah.
Orhun!
Whew.
Huh?
He's not here.
That's strange.
I know he went this way...
Why are you avoiding them?
I decided I wasn't going
to join another party.
But that would make them sad.
So you're avoiding them?
Seems like they matter a lot to you.
That's odd.
Why is he avoiding us?
Maybe he doesn't want to join
the Night Sky Silver Rabbits.
And that's why we're all
going to ask him, right?
B-But what if he actually says no?
Then I'll quit the Rabbits
and become his apprentice!
No fair! Me too, then!
And of course, Sophia will too, right?
Um...
I don't want to say goodbye to him.
They seem to look up to you a lot.
Stop it, Old Man.
I...
When you ran in here, you looked
like you were kind of enjoying it.
I know you're looking
for a place to belong.
But I think that you
don't have to be alone.
You can find your place alongside others.
Where I belong?
Orhun?
Sophia!
Um, thank you for saving us yesterday!
Oh, no...
We've been looking for you all day!
Where have you been?
Um... I've been going around town.
What are you doing out here at this hour?
It's close to our clan HQ.
It's one of my favorite spots.
Favorite spots?
Yes.
The moon here is beautiful.
You know how even when it's totally dark,
the moon still shines bright?
So I feel like when I look at
the moon, it gives me strength.
Do you know where the name of the
Night Sky Silver Rabbits comes from?
No...
The moon is also called
"the guide of the night."
And...
The Night Sky Silver Rabbits want
to be a guide for adventurers.
That's where the name comes from.
A guide...
I talked with someone about that, once...
U-Um... Orhun!
Would you please join the
Night Sky Silver Rabbits?!
I want to stay with you!
Hey, Sophia.
What kind of place is the
Night Sky Silver Rabbits to you?
T-To me?
Yeah.
Well...
They've taught me so many things,
given me so many smiles...
I can be proud to say that it's my home!
To me, it's the place where I belong!
The place where you belong...
Looks like you have your answer, then.
Yes, Vince...
No, Leader.
Please let me join the
Night Sky Silver Rabbits.
We're glad to have you.
Congratulations, Orhun!
Here's your guild uniform!
Try it on!
Sophia, is that true?
Yeah!
Hooray!
From now on, I'm a part of
the Night Sky Silver Rabbits.
I look forward to working with you.