I don't like this.
I really don't like this.
I very much do not like this.
I know I have to deliver the new weapon
to the fortress city of Scudet,
but that means going
to the field of battle again.
I'm so bummed out.
Lord Van, look.
That's the city closest to Scudet.
It looks like a normal city at a glance,
but I see an awful lot of soldiers.
Post-defeat, our Scuderian army probably
started using it to reorganize the troops.
Yelenetta Kingdom's new weapon
was incredible, wasn't it?
It's been a long time...
Van.
EPISODE 11: THE ULTIMATE SQUAD'S
PROUD COUNTERATTACK
It's been a long time, Father.
Van. I hear you have been made a baron.
Yes, I have.
I hear you defeated a dragon.
Oh, it was only a forest dragon, though.
A-A forest dragon?!
How did you do it?
Even I can't defeat dragons
of that class on my own.
I have to mobilize the full force
of my knights to face one.
Um, I defeated it with ballistae.
Ballistae, you say?
Impossible.
There is no way you could have done that.
Even if I were totally honest,
he probably wouldn't believe me.
Young man.
Panamera.
Oh? Am I interrupting
a father-son reunion?
No.
Is His Majesty here, too?
Yes. He's been eagerly awaiting you.
He was wondering if you'd prepared
something interesting again.
Well then.
Father.
Shall I show you my ballistae
after I've met with His Majesty?
Good idea.
Seeing is believing, as they say.
Though if you have some bolts to hand,
I could show him my own right now.
No, I have something better now.
I figured you might.
Will you sell me the new ones?
Okay, I'll prepare some for you soon.
We can talk prices later.
Listen to you, already touting it.
I'm Viscountess Cayenne.
I have brought Baron Van Nei Fertio.
Please enter.
Whoa!
Impressed by His Majesty's royal guards?
They're really intense.
They're strong, right?
Yeah.
Since His Majesty values military feats,
his guards are all superb warriors.
Although with your gear, you might
still stand a chance of beating them.
Damn, Panamera. That was on purpose.
Okay, let's go.
Now, regarding our strategy
going forward,
we'll gather Scuderia's elites together
and retake the fortress city of Scudet.
Any objections?
COUNT BARIATT SHIROCCO FERDINATTO
That's Count Ferdinatto. Arte's father.
He does kind of resemble her.
Aperta. Is there anything we should
be wary of for the upcoming battle?
Yes.
Yelenetta's army has laid siege to Scudet
in vain many times over the years,
but this time, they took it
in the blink of an eye.
The number one reason for this appears
to be their wyverns and those black balls.
Black balls?
Their new weapons, huh?
In other words, we can't win
without doing something about them?
Yes. However, they use
the wyverns to attack from above.
It will prove difficult to take them down.
Marquis Fertio, they attacked your men
with those black balls, yes?
Yes.
Scuderia's reinforcements are here!
Take this!
What's that weapon?
Lord Jalpa! Our forces
have nearly been wiped out!
Wh-What?
They delivered tremendous force
and decimated our army.
Baron, have you come up
with a potential strategy?
Well...
We just need to defeat
those wyverns quickly,
before they can attack
with those black balls, right?
Hmph. A ridiculous notion.
Such childish drivel.
It'd be no problem
if we could just do that.
Normally, I would say
it's out of the question, but...
It's strange, but I think
the baron could do it.
Then, could we have you on the front lines
of the operation to retake Scudet?
Oh, I'm sorry. I have no intention
of going to the front lines.
Talking back to His Majesty?
I can't believe it.
What's he thinking?
The gall of it—
You don't want to go to the front lines?
You could earn yourself glory.
I know, but could I please act
in a support capacity?
Why?
Um...
Because I don't want to get hurt.
What?
How selfish can you get?
What an impudent brat.
What kind of upbringing
did he get at House Fertio?
You may be a child,
but you're out of line.
You're just the lord
of a small, remote village.
You should know your place.
Father, I understand that well.
However, none of you higher nobles have
even imagined what it's like to be a lord
earnestly defending such a small village.
What?
Marquis.
Baron, continue.
Right. In the beginning,
I was made the lord of a tiny village
that could easily be wiped out.
I was accompanied there by fine allies,
but I didn't receive
any support from my family.
Despite that, I've worked hard
to greatly develop my patch.
Even so, the village remains small.
If Yelenetta Kingdom were
to attack it while I'm away,
they'd stand little chance of victory.
But would Yelenetta even bother
to attack such a small village?
Yes. They actually sent
a reconnaissance force to take Seatoh.
Yelenetta is serious
about crushing us this time.
So they will likely try to conquer
all the other domains on their borders.
Right. And it'd be all too simple
to burn down such a small place.
No way.
Do we have a way to counter this?
I'll need to strengthen my defenses.
I just want to protect the village
my citizens have built together.
So I can't afford to let myself get hurt.
I understand now.
Still, you make it sound like you can
counter the Yelenetta army, baron.
Yes, I believe I can.
Impossible.
They're using wyverns
and those black balls.
Those won't be a problem, either.
Your Majesty, I plan to do more
than just support from the rear.
In return for that, I'll prepare
my new ballistae and catapults.
Is that so?
How reassuring.
Then, let's go make these ballistae
and catapults at once.
You're going to start on them now?
Van, you really don't
understand the situation.
We're in a race against time—
Father, allow me to show you
in person like I promised.
H-How can this be?
What in the world is this?
So quickly?
Wh-What's going on here?
What do you think, Father?
Pointless. I'm sure they're just for show
and not all that impressive.
I'm heading back to reorganize my army.
Still, this is incredible.
So this is the baron's new weapon?
You've created another
sensational piece of equipment.
These catapults are capable of launching
specially made shuriken to down wyverns.
You think we can win
with weapons like this?
I won't say it's guaranteed.
But we've done everything we can.
Unless the enemy surpasses my predictions,
we have a good chance of victory.
I'll be counting on you, baron.
Yes, sir.
You're all dismissed for today.
Go organize your armies.
Yes, sir.
Good work today, Lord Van.
Thanks. Did you come to pick me up?
Yes.
Lady Arte is with me, too.
Arte?
F-Father.
You bring me such grief!
I-Is Mother doing well?
Yes, she's spending her time
in my domain as usual.
I'm glad to hear that.
Well, I'm busy preparing for war.
Let's have a longer chat
when things settle down.
All right. I look forward to it.
Arte, are you okay?
If you're not feeling well,
maybe you should rest.
I'm sorry.
Till, stay with her.
Right.
Lady Arte, this way.
All right. Can I entrust you
with our artillery squad, Khamsin?
Sure. I have no doubt that your weapons
are the strongest, Lord Van.
I'll go prove that to everyone.
Thank you.
For now, we'll just have to use
the catapults to defeat those wyverns.
Then, the Seatoh Chivalric Order
will defend Khamsin's squad.
We'll help out, too.
Okay. That's reassuring to hear.
So it's finally time
for the decisive battle.
Yelenetta easily took
the impregnable fortress city of Scudet
with the help of wyverns
and their new weapons.
That means...
the age of battles being decided by the
strength of elemental mages is at an end.
So you believe Yelenetta possesses
the greatest military might at present?
Or perhaps...
this boy does, with the many
weapons he makes.
We will now commence
the operation to retake Scudet!
Yeah!
Charge!
Split into two and advance,
just as we planned!
Our top goal in this operation to retake
Scudet is to defeat the wyverns.
Let's ensure we seize victory!
Right!
Yeah!
Kusala! Pluriel!
We'll act as a mobile unit and support
where our ranks are thinnest!
Right!
Okay!
Seatoh Chivalric Order!
Our role is to defend the artillery!
Advance with caution!
Yes, sir!
Okay. They should be coming out soon.
Damn Scuderian army.
They plan to split up
and destroy the ramparts?
I thought they'd concentrate on the gate
and destroy that, but whatever.
We'll just crush them.
Ready!
Fire!
All right! Commence the operation!
Ready shields!
They blocked all of them?
I hastily made them using wood blocks,
but they work fairly well.
Impudent brat.
Mages, get ready!
Fire!
That's it! Destroy those shields!
Th-The shields won't hold much longer!
Sir Dee?
No shield can withstand
the assault of Yelenetta's army.
What?
The north gate?
Where did that come from?
What? A detached force?
Keep going and destroy the gate!
Storm Ruler!
Ice Field!
Fire Javelin!
Oh no. They were planning this
from the start?
I'm glad you fell for it so fully.
We're forcing it open!
Right.
Ice Storm!
Flame Lance!
Wh-What the hell?
My father and Count Ferdinatto
are both really strong, aren't they?
Now! Onward into Scudet Fortress!
Go stop them!
Wipe out the Scuderian army!
So this is the Yelenetta army
that's full of elites?
This is bad.
Surround them!
Take this!
Lady Panamera!
Don't waste this opportunity!
Leave this area to us.
What?
I won't be beaten in close combat.
Be careful of attacks from range, too.
Are you all Van's people?
Yes, we are.
In that case...
Hey! Tell them it's time!
Yes, sir.
Damn. I didn't think
we'd struggle this much.
Wyverns!
There's that many of them?
They're finished now!
Come, drop the black balls!
Khamsin, you're up!
Catapults, prepare to fire!
Yes, sir.
Fire!
Good. Just as we planned.
There's still one alive!
It's enormous.
Let's go, Kusala!
Got it!
I-It's not working?
Good. We have it pinned down.
Ballistae, fire!
Leave it to me!
Burn the foes before me to ash.
Vermilion!
Rejoice! The enemy's main forces,
the wyverns, have been destroyed!
We did it!
I never expected the baron's power
would be this great.
We've lost. Our only choice is to run.
Oh dearie me.
Where do you think you're going?
Just come quietly, okay?
Father.
Are you really okay
leaving without seeing Van?
Perhaps my beliefs were wrong.
We fended off and defeated Yelenetta
Kingdom's wyverns and black balls.
This glory is all yours, Lord Van.
All I did was issue commands
from the rear.
It was thanks to all of your efforts.
I'm really glad everyone came to no harm.
Yeah.
Lord Van.
We captured Yelenetta's commander.
He should know all kinds
of confidential information.
Well now, maybe you could enlighten us.
What was your goal here?
In short, their commander says Yelenetta
Kingdom's plan was a three-pronged attack.
Seatoh and Scudet
were two of those prongs.
And the last one is...
Ferdinatto County.
Arte's homeland.
TRANSLATION: JOHN PICKETT
TIMING: ANDY ELLIS
EDITING: SMR
QUALITY CONTROL: RILEY DALTON
TRANSLATION CHECK: REI MIYASAKA
NEXT EPISODE: EASYGOING TERRITORY DEFENSE
BY THE OPTIMISTIC LORD