WHOOSH
MY CHILDHOOD FRIEND IS JUST TOO CUTE
ALL CHILDHOOD FRIEND LOVERS REJOICE!!
YOU CAN'T BE IN A ROM-COM WITH
YOUR CHILDHOOD FRIENDS!
MY CHILDHOOD FRIEND IS JUST TOO CUTE
ALL CHILDHOOD FRIEND LOVERS REJOICE!!
MY CHILDHOOD FRIEND IS JUST TOO CUTE!
OUT OF BATTERY!
PLEASE EAT HAMBURG STEAK FOR DINNER
TONIGHT! / I'M SORRY AS ALWAYS.
MY CHILDHOOD FRIEND IS JUST TOO CUTE
ALL CHILDHOOD FRIEND LOVERS REJOICE!!
EIYU / I'M GONNA CHECK THE GYM
OKAY, I'LL CHECK THE PARK
LOVE CONFESSION
TRUTH
WAIT FOR ME, OKAY?
DON'T LEAVE
ME ALONE, OKAY?
WAIT FOR ME!
TRANSLATOR: SACHIKO TAKAHASHI
TIMER: MARIANA MARTINEZ
EDITOR: GABRIELLA ALABANZA
QUALITY CONTROL: S BILYEU
FINAL QUALITY CONTROL: REI MIYASAKA
EPISODE 3 / ADMIRING THEM? LONELY? SCHOOL
AT NIGHT? STILL WON'T START A ROM-COM