YEAR 2 CLASS 7
CULTURE FESTIVAL PLANS
WHAAAAAAAAT?
OOOOOOOH!
THE ELITES CALLED
INTO ACTION
(THE GOING-
HOME CLUB)
BUZZ
I'VE NEVER HAD A PART-TIME JOB BEFORE,
BUT ONCE I GO TO UNIVERSITY,
I THINK I MIGHT LIKE TO TRY
WORKING PART-TIME AT A BOOKSHOP.
READ
REALLY?
YOU CAN'T
HELP IT, THOUGH
WANT TO TALK
ON A CALL?
SORRY. I'M OUT
RIGHT NOW
READ
OKAY!
RESISTANCE
TO MALES: 0
OF COURSE
HE HAD
NO IDEA
CURIOUS
ABOUT
(LIKES...?)
FEW
CHANCES
TO
INTERACT
LIKES
JUST
FINE
GET
ALONG
WELL
TOGETHER
HAS
EXPERIENCE
DATING
ONE-SIDED
LOVE RETURN
RATE: 0%
BUT IN THEIR OWN WAY, THOSE ARE GOOD MEMORIES...
YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
OUT SHOPPING BECAUSE THEY
LOST AT ROCK-PAPER-SCISSORS
TRAUMA RESPONSE TO GIRLS WHISPERING
GIRLS WHO COULDN'T CARE LESS
SURPRISE!!
BOOM
NONSPECIFIC!!
MEAT
CULTURE FESTIVAL, DAY 1
(STUDENTS AND STAFF ONLY)
CULTURE FESTIVAL
YOU WIN
SOLD OUT! THANK YOU!
CULTURE FESTIVAL, DAY 2
(VISITORS ALLOWED)
DOKKIRI BINKEY
BUT
NORMALLY
THAT'S...
COZY CAFE
JAPANESE-STYLE
FOOD STALL
REST AREA
When we get tired, we'll get tea and
baked sweets at the PTA's place.
GLOBAL WARMING
PHOTOGRAPHY
CLUB
EXHIBITION
WELCOME TO
OUR EXHIBITION!!
TAKE YOUR TIME
LOOKING AROUND
SELF-CONFIDENCE (A TINY BIT) UP
HE READS AS
"POPULAR WITH
THE LADIES"...
MIDDLE SCHOOL
YEAR 3
CAN'T SAY
IT WAS A JOKE IN
THIS ATMOSPHERE...
WENT
WITH
THE
FLOW
NONCOMMITTAL
HALF-
HEARTED
MOVES
DOES
NOT
KNOW
THIS IS WHY I LOVE
MY MIDDLE SCHOOL FAM...
RIBBIT
I AM
YOUR
"NOW"!
DROOP
LET'S HAVE
THE BEST,
FUNNEST DAY!
-S
THEN WHY
DOES HE
STILL CALL
HER BY HER
FIRST NAME?
IF THERE'S A
GET-TOGETHER,
WILL SHE SEE
HIM THERE?
STRESS
SUDAKEN
DEMURE
TYPES ?
TO SUZUKI-SAN,
I LOOK FORWARD TO
OUR CONTINUED RELATIONSHIP
-TANI
TELL ME ALL KINDS
OF STORIES AGAIN SOMETIME
-REINA
ME TOO
-NA
ME TOO!
-YAMA
DOESN'T
KNOW
ANYTHING
YOUR VOICE
IS TOO LOUD
YOU TALK
TOO MUCH