The Best Things About
Being a Villain!
Starting down a
villain's path from
zero
By Bertia
This is how different
your income can be!
Using Regular Means
Using Underhanded Means
This doting
parent...
An Observation Log of My
Fiancée Who Calls Herself a Villainess
Chapter 2
An Observation Log of the Self-Proclaimed
Villainess's Debut into Society.
The Day of Her Social Debut
Six Months Later, Halm Academy
Six Months Later
Courtgain Deles Mardan
Two Weeks Later
Reverse\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\hHarem?
Example of a Reverse Harem
Heronia Inderon
Chapter 3
An Observation Log of a Self-Proclaimed
Villainess and Entering School.