POPURI
BOOM
YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
(TANI'S BIRTHDAY EVE)
NOVEMBER
1ST
TANI'S BIRTHDAY!
QUIET...
*ACTUALLY GRATEFUL
reactions
reactions that make
reactions that make people
reactions that make people happy
YAY
TAIRA'S
BIRTHDAY!
YOU...
TANI'S NIGHTS
END EARLY
INCOMING CALL
SUZUKI MIYU
ASLEEP
ZZZ...
WOO-HOO
BAM
THUNDER
CHOCOLATE
POPURI
SHREWDLY, HAS HER OWN PORTION
OVEREXCITED
THUD
KISS...
WHERE
I WANT
TO GO
WHAT
I WANT
TO DO
LACKS A DESIRE TO SIGHTSEE
CUTESY...
MOVIE
TIME REQUIRED:
2 HOURS 30 MINUTES
ZOO
TIME REQUIRED:
2-3 HOURS
AQUARIUM
TIME REQUIRED:
1-2 HOURS
MUSEUM
TIME REQUIRED:
3-4 HOURS
SPECIAL
EXHIBIT
A
WORLD
OF
TREASURES
MINUTES
LATER
THAT WAS
A MOTH
WHEW
TEMPORARILY
CLOSED
WAIT
TIME
EATING
ARRIVE
HOME...
SU
I WANT TO GO OVER THERE!
OVER
THERE
HMMM
TIME
SCHEDULE
WHAT?
"BASH"
MEANING
"HUGE
BIRTHDAY
PARTY"