Advanced Class
Jan. 14th (Tues.)
Class Duty: Minazuki
Episode 6
The Misanthrope and the Light of Dawn
Jan. 17th (Fri.)
Class Duty: Usami
Final Assignment
Kyoka Minazuki
Jan. 24th (Fri.)
Class Duty: Minazuki
Jan. 31st (Fri.)
Class Duty: Ohgami
Feb. 7th (Fri.)
Class Duty: Minazuki
Feb. 14th (Fri.)
Class Duty: Usami
Signature Book
Sui Usami
Feb. 21st (Fri.)
Class Duty: Haneda
Final Assignment
Kyoka Minazuki
Final Assignment   Problem 2
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Try and remember!
The very first class!
And when you trace them in order...?
Final Assignment   Problem 1
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Solve the
crossword puzzle!
Hiragana Table
Ko
Ha
Hiragana Table
Te
Ko
N
Science Prep Room
Final Assignment
Kyoka Minazuki
Office
Final Assignment
Kyoka Minazuki
Advanced class student
Teacher
Location from a dream
A certain
love story
Final Assignment   Problem 3
m 0 0 l 230 0 l 230 215 l 0 215
Where was the confession?
Next Episode:
The Misanthrope and the Fruitless Love Fortune