Well?
I've checked a million times.
The transmission from the
colony fleet is the real deal.
We did it, Jessica!
Hey!
Broadcasting a message to Earth
for over a hundred years really paid off!
It's a miracle.
A fleet that left Earth a century
or a century and a half ago
just happened to be
headed in our direction
and just happened to pick up
the transmission from our home.
Miracles are meant to be seized
with your own hands!
Where is the fleet now?
About 0.15 light years away
from Noman's Land.
Can we communicate with them?
If you can wait two months per relay.
Real-time communication won't be possible
until they're just about to arrive.
Still, what a relief. Now we're saved.
No.
We can't say for sure
that we'll be saved.
Don't let your guard down.
But for sure, there is hope.
Hope gives us the courage
to live on to the next day.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
Yeah!
Run!
Get to the shelter!
Here they come!
Brad, I'm staying, too!
What're you gonna do
against those monsters?
But—
We don't stand a chance!
You go and bring him back to us!
There's a tracker in his prosthetic arm
that gives us his location.
Granted, it's from two
and a half years ago.
But it's all we have.
But...
We'll hold out until he gets here!
Now go!
Vash...
Oh, you helped me?
Um... Thank you.
Where did you...
No, that's not important.
Um! I'm looking for someone!
He should be nearby.
Have you seen this man?
Um...
Come with me.
I must have twisted my leg
when I collapsed.
Th-Thank you so much, um...
Mister Hoppered.
In here?
Vash!
I'm so glad! Thank goodness!
Listen... Listen, I...
Vash?
Eriks has been that way for a long while.
He has? And... "Eriks"?
I found Eriks some time after that day.
What day?
Lost JuLai.
He seems to have lost his memory.
It's only natural. He must have
gone through a lot in JuLai.
I think.
You've taken care
of Vash this whole time.
Thank you...
Thank you.
Say, Mister Hoppered, why "Eriks"?
Have you remembered anything? Vash—
No, don't push yourself too hard.
It's all right...
Eriks.
Are you sure?
We knew Vash survived,
but we couldn't go after him.
We had no idea how much he was suffering.
Maybe it's best that we
leave him the way he is.
Now go!
But, our home...
I'm sorry. You have no idea what
I'm talking about, do you? But, um...
I...
I kill the girl at sundown.
I'll be waiting at Moonseeing Hill.
Eriks... No.
Vash the Stampede.
I talked to them.
Don't worry.
They'll never bother you again.
In fact, they promised.
It looks good on you.
It's so dark.
If darkness had a bottom,
it must be like this.
This is all she saw for the longest time.
I've spent too long struggling
in a lightless world.
The darkness is crushing me.
The girl is just sleeping—for now.
Fight me or she dies.
If you lose, I'll kill her.
You must kill me in order to save her.
It's time to wake up!
You like it? Good.
Don't worry. I'm not hungry.
You can have it all.
Shoot!
I like your hair.
What's wrong?!
Do it like you did in JuLai!
That distorted space...
The electrified air...
The unending despair...
That was the moment!
What you took from me...
was half of my entire being!
I...
I've been in a long dream.
In it, Hoppered, you were kind to me.
You could have killed me at any time.
Why didn't you?
I could accept death at your hands.
I may have been thinking that,
somewhere in my mind.
But not now. Not anymore.
I can't let you kill Jessica.
Then kill me.
That's enough, Hoppered.
Please, I can't...
I'm sorry.
Jessica?
Jessica. Jessica.
Vash?
Now hurry up and send me off.
I can't do that.
Vash?
Stop, Hoppered.
Please, stop!
You... live to suffer.
I won't kill you.
You must survive in this cesspool
of a world, all the while coughing...
blood.
Hoppered.
Eriks...
Rem...
Would everything have been better
if I never existed?
Our home is under attack?
I'm sorry, Vash.
I wanted to leave you be.
It's fine. That's all right.
But the only one who knows
the location of our home is...
That's what Luida and Brad think.
Nai is alive?
Let's go, Jessica.
Two and a half years after
the tragedy known as Lost JuLai,
a material witness, the Humanoid
Typhoon known as Vash the Stampede
with a $$60 billion bounty
on his head, has been sighted.
Authorities are working to verify...
I hope it really is Vash!
Milly, as a journalist, you can't trust
outside information right away.
You have to see it with your own eyes.
Yes, ma'am!
Also, in order to see
the truth behind something,
Uh-huh.
you can't just look dead ahead.
You need a wide field of vision—
Yeah, but you still gotta
look forward, too.
Vash the Stampede!