[YUKI] Why are you dressed
like that, like a Stump?
I prefer loose, comfortable
clothing, that's why.
Aren't you embarrassed to walk
around in that skimpy outfit?
Oh.
Did you see my friend
in the maze?
Her name is Moegi.
Yeah, but she's dead.
Is she?
Why'd you go
and kill everyone?
I hoped you'd understand.
You've played
death games before,
so you've had the chance
to kill before, right?
Or if not, hmm.
Have you ever kicked
a chair out of frustration?
I've vented like that before.
And you feel better?
At the time, yeah.
And now you know why.
[YUKI] She ended up like
this because you were
venting your frustrations?
Well, obviously.
She was on her way
to clear 96 games.
She was a veteran!
She was weak, and her body
moved weird for some reason.
Huh?
Go on.
Look closer.
[unsettling tune]
There's something
strange about her guts.
She already made
a ton of money.
So why didn't she quit?
Was she addicted?
Who knows?
[gasp]
[KYARA] Hey.
[gasping]
[gun cocks]
[gunshots]
[gasps]
[thud]
[gun cocking]
[dramatic music, knife swoosh]
[grunting, panting]
Armored.
That's against the rules.
I don't know how
you can play death games
with a defenseless body.
If you can pay to give yourself
an edge, why wouldn't you?
Don't bother.
My whole body is armor-plated.
[gunshots, swooshing]
[body thud]
[swish, gasp]
[gasping]
Well done.
Aiming for the artery
in my neck?
You're good.
Way better at killing than
these other weaklings.
[YUKI] Stop enjoying this.
I mean, get a life.
Battle junkies
are so last year.
That's funny coming from you.
You don't know
anything about me.
Oh, I can tell who you
are with just one look.
You're like me.
You feel comfortable in this
world of death games.
[chuckle]
This place is great, isn't it?
There are no silly rules.
You can kill
whoever disgusts you.
Nobody even cares
that you kill.
And if you're vicious enough,
you'll attract
your very own groupies.
This is the only place for us.
What you want is to die here.
That's how you feel.
Go on, admit it.
[YUKI] She wished she could
say the psycho girl was wrong.
But...
she'd be lying.
And Yuki didn't have
what it took to lie.
[theme music]
Finally, it was time
for her to leave here.
As for regrets,
she didn't really have any.
[HAKUSHI] You never told me
why you play these games.
[YUKI] I don't know.
Does it matter anymore?
Where'd I come from?
Where am I going?
Who am I?
I'm a ghost.
I was never even born.
I will never die.
I just drift around.
And one day, I'll wander
off somewhere else.
And then...
I'll disappear.
[gentle piano music]
[gasps]
This flavor.
It's yummy.
Thank you.
This flavor.
It's yummy.
Thank you.
Aoi!
[KINKO] Like I said before,
if you're going to survive,
you need to be ruthless.
Don't sacrifice
yourself for others.
Do what's right for you.
Besides, a little shiftiness
can only give you
more depth as a person.
[YUKI] You think it will?
Yeah.
I think it will.
[crying]
Kinko.
[sob] Kinko.
[SUMIYAKA] My next game,
I hit the wall of 30.
Oh, come on.
You don't believe
it's a curse, do you?
I didn't think stuff
like that bothered you.
It's cute.
Momono.
[MOMONO] Beniya.
Beniya.
Momono.
Beniya, please--
--I won't ask you
to live or anything else.
I don't want to die.
I won't ask for anything.
Hey, congrats
on surviving the game.
So what do you
want to eat today?
[SHIORI] Oh, hey.
Like, I always wondered,
why is my name Shiori?
I bet my folks were inspired by
those Turkish rugs they saw
and wanted me to grow up
to speak thoughtfully
and care about others.
I guess I did in the end.
I don't think
there's anything wrong
with being that way.
It's better than folks
who refer to themselves
in the third person.
[chuckles] Yeah, that is lame.
Shouldn't you try to stop me?
'Cuz if you let me
kill myself like this,
you won't fulfill
your purpose for her.
Reiko.
Thank you, Reiko.
Mishiro.
Thank you, Mishiro.
Honestly, I'm glad I met you.
Because at that moment,
I was prettier than anyone.
And weren't you as well?
[REIKO] What about me?
[YUKI] You were, too.
[MOEGI]
The Nighthawk star burned on
and continued to burn.
It kept burning
and burning and burning.
And still to this day,
it burns.
I was so--
[MOEGI] And still
to this day, it burns.
I was so jealous of Moegi.
[MOEGI] And still
to this day it burns.
[YUKI] I was jealous
of all the girls
I met in death games
who lived in this world.
[VOICES] And still
to this day, it burns.
And still to this day,
it burns.
[YUKI] This story--
[VOICES] And still
to this day, it burns.
[YUKI] --is about a world
that's gone insane.
[VOICES] And still
to this day, it burns.
[YUKI] But--
[VOICES] And still
to this day, it burns.
[YUKI] It's also the story
of a world where at one point,
all these girls lived.
[VOICES] And still
to this day it burns.
It's a world where I also--
[HAKUSHI] Oh, you cry too much.
Well, you figure out why
you play these games yet?
[buzzing]
You know now, don't you?
Hakushi was my mentor.
I'll inherit her will,
her goal.
I'll clear 99 games,
and won't stop till I do.
From now on, I am going
to live in this world!
All right.
Let's go.
[HAKUSHI] You need
something to believe in.
That's how you'll survive.
[YUKI] Huh?
[HAKUSHI] What happened
to practicing denial?
[clanking, gasping, clashing]
If you want to keep
playing longer than me,
you need something more.
There's a limit
to my style of playing.
You're a master skeptic,
but you need to get
just as good at trusting.
That's something I know
you'd be good at.
[YUKI] She wondered,
"How did Hakushi could she feel
when she hid this for her?"
Her nose stung.
Her chest felt hot!
[gunshots, gasping]
[yelling]
[gentle music]
[MOEGI] Welcome home.
[KYARA] I love you.
You want to fight?
[knife clanks]
No.
I killed five.
I've had enough.
I don't ever want to play
a death game ever again.
[YUKI] Yeah, I bet.
[gentle music]
[YUKI] It was 5:00 PM.
A little too early to start
my usual routine,
so I just sat there.
I thought to myself,
now that I've taken on
my mentor's goal,
what do I have
to do to survive 99 games?
One step at a time.
I started small
and cleaned my place.
When I was done,
there was one last step.
As far as age goes, I can still
pass as a high school student.
But for some reason,
I still felt weird.
Since graduating
middle school,
I've been floating
through life.
I was ashamed
of being seen outside,
so I stopped going
out in the daytime.
[children laughing in distance]
I smelled
the osmanthus blooming.
The sun was setting, and I felt
its fading warmth on my back.
I walked and kept walking.
From now on, I'm going to live
in this world as a player
full time.
From now on,
my goal is to survive
99 of these games.
From now on, I play death
games to put food on the table.
[gentle music, paper ruffling]
[HAKUSHI'S AGENT]
I'm here to take you home.
The game's over.
Let's go.
You can stop pretending
you're dead now.
[HAKUSHI] Over already?