Klutzy
The Klutzy Class Monitor and
the Girl with the Short Skirt
The Klutzy Class Monitor and the Library Assistant
Class Monitor
Library Assistant
Tsukishima Seiichi
Is that so?!
It's definitely not him
Grumble
Grumble Grumble
Lion at Home
Lion at the Library
Snore Snore
Wide Open
Snoring
Princess
Blah blah blah
Camera 1
Camera 2
Camera 3
Out of the Library
Squeak Squeak Squeak
Beam
m 0 0 l 115.5 0 l 115.5 108 l 0 108
The Klutzy
Class Monitor and
the Girl with
the Short Skirt
m 0 0 l 115.5 0 l 115.5 108 l 0 108
The Klutzy
Class Monitor and
the Girl with
the Short Skirt
The Time She Spent Lunch With the Klutz
Health (And Dignity) Representative
Checkout
Desk
Return Slot
Squeak Squeak Squeak
Po-chan ♥