Episode 13
Barrier Day
Rigarden Magical Academy
The Day Before the Final Day of Graduation Exams
Rigarden Magical Academy, Faculty Room
Rigarden Magical Academy Professor
Edward Serfence
Written Magizoology
Will Serfort: Perfect Score
Rigarden Magical Academy Professor
Workner Norgram
Eliza Nosferat
Rigarden Magical Academy
Study Room
Familiar
Kiki
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Will Serfort
Colette Loire
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Rosty Nowman
Rigarden Magical Academy
Headmistress's Office
Julius Reinberg
Rigarden Magical Academy
Sion Ulster
Rigarden Magical Academy Headmistress
Caldron Anouve
Rigarden Magical Academy
Breezeway
Rigarden Magical Academy, Sixth Year
Wignall Lindor
Lihanna Owenzaus
Elfaria Albis Serfort
Ice Faction Aide-de-Camp
Sarissa Alfeld
Ellenor Ljos Alf
Zeo Thorzeus Reinbolt
History of Magic Final Exam
The List of Failed Students
Will Serfort
Rigarden
Officially Urbus Rigarden, the capital of magic. It is the capital city of the Rhizanth,
the inhabitants of paradise. A great metropolis that stands at the center of the world of magic.
Mercedes Caulis, the Wizard's Tower, welcomes the five most powerful wizards, the Magia Vander.
Rigarden Magical Academy boasts the world's best magic education program.
The Abyss Gate is the first gate leading into the dungeon.
The city's many important facilities bring in talented fledgling mages from all over the world.
The city is also called the Land of Legend, or the Land of Beginning, for driving off the Celestial Host.
Terminalia, The Barrier Festival
Do not ever leave this undone. It must always be built.
Whatever it may take, send the barrier to the edge of the sky.
That is why the Magia Vander exist.
-The words of a certain mage queen.
Clairie Serah
The Wizard's Tower Watcher
Iris Churchill
Fire Faction
Rodge Holland
Vandes Terminalia
Supreme Spell: The Five Wands' Great Barrier Partitioning Paradise
Episode 14
The Party from Hell Begins