FREEZE...
TRUDGE TRUDGE TRUDGE
CLASS TRIP
OBJECTIVES
BROADEN
YOUR
EXPERIENCE
ABIDE BY THE RULES
OF LIVING IN A GROUP
STUDY
HISTORY
DAY 1
KYOTO
GROUP ACTIVITIES
NARA
DAY 2
DAY 3
OSAKA
CLASS TRIP
OBJECTIVES
YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
CLASS TRIP GUIDE
YEAR 2 CLASS
KYOTO
EVERYONE IN THE
GOING-HOME CLUB
KONEKO PREFECTURAL
HIGH SCHOOL
CLASS TRIP GUIDE
YEAR 2 CLASS
QUIET FOCUS...
DEAD-END
PIECE
MUTTER MUTTER MUTTER
2-8 CLASS REPS
CRACKLE...
HEE HEE...
JOLT
WAAAAAAH
Day 1
Day 2
QUICK QUICK QUICK
SHFF...
THUD THUD THUD THUD
"I AM JUST BACKGROUND" MODE
THUD THUD
FWIP FWIP FWIP
CONTRADICTORY
SHFF...
IT'S NOT LIKE I HAVE ABSOLUTELY NO IDEA
AWKWARD
TRAIN-TO-SCHOOL GROUP
CLASS TRIP
PICKING GROUPS
ARGHHHH
HANG OUT A LOT
HANG-OUT GROUP
(+SUZUKI)
ALWAYS TOGETHER
GLANCE GLANCE GLANCE
(I'LL GO TO A DIFFERENT GROUP)
(GOT IT!)
DID SHE UNDERSTAND...?
IF IT GETS DONE,
ANYTHING'S FINE.
IN THE END...
YAY!
SIGH...
TABIPPLE
FALL
BAM
FWIP FWIP FWIP
...HUH?
YEAR 1, SPRING
1. KAWASAKI
YEAR 2, SPRING
2. SUZUKI
CLASS TRIP
PICKING GROUPS
SILENCE...
SENSE OF ANXIETY
TABIPPLE
FALL
NO SENSE OF ANXIETY
TEA
FOR SALE AT THE HOTEL SHOP
TAIYAKI
O D E N
DAY 1: HANDS-ON LEARNING
EVERYONE SPLITS UP TO TAKE
THE COURSE THEY CHOSE
PAINTING 1
PAINTING 2
TRIP GUIDE
MAKING
JAPANESE
SWEETS
CERAMICS
KUMIHIMO BRAIDING
CERAMICS GROUP
PAINTING GROUP
JAPANESE SWEETS
GROUP
MAKING VENUE
SMILE
(NEUTRAL ATTITUDE)
GRIN...
I'D LOVE
TO...!!!!
BIG ROOM
EXAMPLE
SQUEE SQUEE
YAY YAY
I WOULD LIKE
TO HUG...
STARE...
BA-DUMP
GURGLE
NOT DENYING IT
SMOOCH...
I'M NOT A
GOOD EXAMPLE...
TINTED
COLORED LIP BALM
MINERAL
FOUNDATION
SNEAK...
THUMP
THUMP THUMP THUMP
OH NO...!!
CHANGING THE SUBJECT
TO HIDE EMBARRASSMENT
OH...?
SOLITARY