[crackling]
[RIKO] Why did I decide
to play death games?
Is it because I don't
care if I live or die,
or care about anything anymore?
[footsteps]
Hm.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
Riko, I'm curious.
How would
you define your "self"?
Think.
Of all the things in the world,
what makes up
a person's "self"?
Lilies are poisonous.
At least, that's what I heard.
If I plant a lily seed
and it blooms,
and the poison from it
ends up killing someone,
then it was me
who killed them.
That's my perspective
on it, anyway.
I gave it life.
I nurtured it, guided it,
I gave it a reason to live--
a purpose.
Say I did the same
for a person.
Nurtured them, guided
them, gave them purpose.
Their accomplishments would
also be mine, wouldn't they?
♪ ♪
That person would be part
of myself then, wouldn't they?
Riko...
you have a hollow soul.
I will fill it with purpose.
[rainfall]
[angelic music]
[RIKO]
Mishiro?
♪ ♪
I left her for you.
[MISHIRO]
Good job.
Do we have enough keys now?
Yep!
I got yours right here!
[MISHIRO]
You can leave without me.
♪ ♪
[RIKO]
She's not the girl you want.
♪ ♪
[MISHIRO]
I'll go see for myself.
♪ ♪
[dripping]
[YUKI]
Wow, you're looking good.
What do you say?
How about this time
you spare my life?
[running footsteps]
[groans]
[fist pounding]
[grunting]
[MISHIRO]
You're a disgrace!
You're a disgrace.
You hear me?
[panting]
[exhales]
[whimper]
[running footsteps]
[tinkling music]
♪ ♪
This score must be
settled more dramatically
on a much grander scale.
With me, having risen
from rock bottom,
and her more
superhuman than ever.
♪ ♪
We'd throw everything
we had at each other
in a battle for the ages.
And in the end,
I would be victorious.
And that's how it had to be.
40 games,
I've played 40 of them,
and none of them
were easy to survive.
I used every trick I knew
to keep my broken body going.
I never stopped looking
forward to the day
I could finally
fight her again.
[breathing heavily]
How dare she run away?
[water sloshing]
[splashing footsteps]
Where are you?
Come out and fight me!
Do you have any
idea how I felt?
You have no right
to act this pathetic!
Coward! You're acting
the same as I did back then!
After losing to you,
I addressed my weaknesses.
I rejected every last
thing about my old self.
Do you know what it
took to get here?
[coughing]
[breathing heavily]
[water sloshing]
♪ ♪
[YUKI grunts]
[MISHIRO]
Look.
Look!
♪ ♪
That girl in the mirror?
I didn't come this far to see
how pathetic she's become!
♪ ♪
[YUKI] Well, I guess I thought
I had a knack for death games.
I knew if I keep
playing, the day will
come when my luck runs out.
But like, when I die, and I
can be a ghost for real,
if that happens,
I'm cool with it.
♪ ♪
But now--
Now--
what about "now"?
I was ready to die any time.
[whooshing]
[melancholy music]
When I started playing death
games, I didn't care if I died.
But then, I never
cared about dying.
♪ ♪
Mishiro.
The last time we met, she was
a pathetic, garbage player
who I got the better of.
This time, she
managed to trip me up.
Now I'm good as dead.
♪ ♪
But--
if I have to die, I don't
want to go like this.
Killed by a sucky person like--
Oh, wait.
That's how she felt.
♪ ♪
[water sloshing]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
Die! Die!
Die already!
♪ ♪
[gulping]
[struggling]
♪ ♪
[screaming]
[YUKI]
I don't want to die.
I don't want to die!
I refuse to die!
[thud]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
[yelling]
[clang]
[splash]
♪ ♪
[gasping]
[crunch]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
[gasping]
♪ ♪
[water sloshing]
[slow footsteps]
[angelic music]
♪ ♪
[MISHIRO] I'll give
you your first mission.
[RIKO]
Mishiro?
[MISHIRO] She's pale.
[RIKO] Mishiro?
[MISHIRO] With a lifeless face.
[MISHIRO] She's surrounded
by an aura of death.
[RIKO]
Mishiro?
[MISHIRO]
Like a ghost.
[RIKO] Mishiro!
♪ ♪
[MISHIRO]
Riko.
If the day comes when
that girl kills me,
I want you to take my place.
♪ ♪
Yeah.
That's my purpose.
♪ ♪
Hold it.
[soft dramatic music]
Stop.
Mishiro gave me an order.
♪ ♪
She said I have to kill you.
Do it, then.
[fist thump]
[grunting]
[thud]
♪ ♪
[RIKO] Did Mishiro
tell you about me?
Huh?
Did she?
[thump]
[music intensifies]
Well?
Did she mention
me to you at all?
Did she?
Come on, say something!
Oh, wait.
You didn't kill her.
You ran away from her, right?
That's it, right?
[rainfall]
[YUKI] When they say the
W all of Thirty's a curse,
they're right.
It is.
Not only was it a shit game,
but I also played like shit.
It was bad.
I had no shot at winning.
My body was mostly wounds,
and hers was mostly metal--
like a killer robot.
I only won because I got lucky.
[pounding]
[punches landing]
It's like all the luck I'd
been saving for months was used
up during that last fight.
Every ounce of it.
[alarm]
Where are you going?
You'll die.
I see.
That makes sense.
Dying like that'll be
a lot less painful.
Shouldn't you try to stop me?
Cause if you let me
kill myself like this,
you won't fulfill
your purpose for her.
[MISHIRO]
Riko.
[RIKO]
No.
Wait! Don't go!
- [MISHIRO] Riko.
- [RIKO] Don't go, don't go!
- [RIKO] Don't go!
- Don't go!
- [MISHIRO] Riko.
- Riko.
- Don't go!
[RIKO]
Please.
Please don't go!
[MISHIRO]
Riko.
[angelic music]
♪ ♪
Thank you,
Riko.
[gunshot]
[mechanical whirring]
[alarm sounds]
[clang]
[alarm continues]
[footsteps]
[alarm stops]
[whirring]
[AGENT]
Excuse the bumps.
[YUKI]
Oh.
Uh.
Mm.
[AGENT]
Sorry about your fingers.
They were lost down
one of the drains.
That was your 30th game.
Congratulations.
Only 69 more to go.
[YUKI] Mind if I
ask you something?
[AGENT]
Go ahead.
[YUKI] In this game, I was
the last player to wake up.
[AGENT]
Yeah, you usually are.
[YUKI] Was being
last a penalty?
[AGENT] I'm sorry about
the unnecessary stress
you were put through this game.
But don't you worry.
That won't ever happen again.
I won't let it.
[YUKI] What do you
mean you won't?
[AGENT] I can't go into too
much detail about it.
But what I can say
is us agents support
you girls with all our hearts.
The way you sacrifice
everything in order
to complete the game and
your desperation to survive,
you won't believe how
many people there are
who wish they had that drive.
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[YUKI] Kiritani, Ochiba,
Funabara, Hagakure,
Shizukawa, Arabi,
Karin, Mizunata, Aman,
Sugiyama, Hiwata,
Asuma,
Riko.
♪ ♪
[gasping]
[squelch]
[splash]
[gulping]
♪ ♪
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
♪ ♪
[YUKI] Honestly,
I'm glad I met her.
♪ ♪
I wish time would
stop right now.
♪ ♪
Because right now,
no one's prettier than me.
[splash]
♪ ♪
[MISHIRO]
It's so warm.
So warm.
[alarm beeping]
[YUKI] Good game.