YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
BIBIMBAP
PIBIMPAP
HEH
PAP
PIBIMPAP
HEY!
HO! HO!
NO.
FULLY EQUIPPED AIR CONDITIONING
(READ: THE LIBRARY)
WORLD HISTORY
EIGHT INNER GATES
YEAH...
PIBIMPAP
BIBIMBAP
YUP. THIS IS GOOD.
EITHER KIND WORKS...
*SUZUKI
GRAND OPENING SALE
FIRST 3 DAYS ONLY
I'M IN THE MOOD FOR ICE CREAM
AFTER DINNER THIS TIME OF YEAR -S
CIGARETTES
POPURI
WE HAD THE
SAME THOUGHT
UMMM...
YOU NOTICED
HEADING HOME FROM CRAM SCHOOL...
NOT GETTING TEASED LEADS
TO ITS OWN KIND OF ANXIETY
DISMISSED
HUH?
I'M UNDERSTANDING MORE AND MORE...
HANG ON...
LET'S RIDE VEHICLES
CORRECTLY AND SAFELY, OKAY?
EVERYONE SAFELY ESCAPED REMEDIAL LESSONS
KONEKO-MACHI SUMMER FESTIVAL
SO EXCITED
I'LL BE THERE SOON!
I'M IN FRONT OF THE STATUE
ROGER THAT!
ROGER
NERVOUS
SWEATING
BEAUTIFUL
SUZUKI, THAT'S SO CUTE!
*BEING TEASED
THIS HAS HAPPENED, THOUGH:
BEAUTIFULLY DONE
HAPPY
"LIKE A COUPLE"?
ONLY STRANGERS AROUND
JUST THE TWO OF US OUT TOGETHER
PUT EXTRA EFFORT INTO THIS OUTFIT
OKONOMIYAKI
YAKISOBA
TOPPED WITH EVERY FLAVOR OF SYRUP
KONEKO-MACHI FESTIVAL
SUPER BALL
GET THIS MANY, KEEP THIS MANY
WORDLESS PRESSURE
TWO BALLS ACQUIRED!
LIST OF HANDY STUFF TO HAVE