JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Episode 56
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 3
Um... Well...
Uh... See...
Guaranteed-Hit,
Guaranteed-Kill
Guaranteed-Hit
You'll lose if you
go out of bounds.
Same if anything but your
soles touches the ground.
Huh?
Seriously?
Silence
Confession
Denial
Itadori "No!"
Itadori "I just borrowed their bathroom."
Higuruma "So you did enter it, then!"
Itadori "Y-Yes..."
Itadori "I regret it..."
"Guilty."
"Confiscation."
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Higuruma Law Office
"Guilty."
"Confiscation."
"Death Penalty."
"Executioner's Sword"
9: Players shall be able to view the
following information on other players:
name, points, number of
rules added, current Colony.
Rule 10: Players are able to
transfer a number of points
of their choosing to other Players.
Next Episode
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 4