3 MILLION CHANNEL SUBSCRIBERS
CELEBRATION EVENT
SUMERAGI IKON
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT
THIS STREAM HAS ENDED
SUMERAGI IKON CHAT STREAM!
SUMERAGI IKON - 32.2K SUBSCRIBERS
MOMOTOSE AO - 3 MILLION SUBSCRIBERS
PIANO STREAM!
VTUBER TACKLES CENTRALIZED COLLEGE ENTRANCE EXAM
MUNDEY
COOKING STREAM!
SUMERAGI IKON
WHAT DO I WATCH?
WHERE'S THE HANDCAM?
THIS LIVESTREAM HAS ENDED
SUGAR UNPACKING STREAM
F FOR STREAM
HOME EC. ROOM
CHOOSEDEY
WHENSDEY
THIRSTDEY
FRYDEY
MOMOTOSE AO NEW OUTFIT
KINDA SEXY
FEW DAYS LATER
IKON NEW OUTFIT DEBUT!
NEW OUTFIT DEBUT
VIEWERS
WOW, IKON!
I COULD WATCH THIS FOREVER.
JUMP FOR US!
[SURPRISE COLLAB] TAKOYAKI PARTY!
I'LL DM THE VTUBERS I WANT FOR THAT ONE EVENT! PLEASE DON'T IGNORE IT!
RESULTS
I'LL SHOW YOU SOMEDAY
ONE WEEK LATER
SUMERAGI IKON STREAM COMPILATION - 270K VIEWS
ROOKIE VTUBER WETS HERSELF FROM FEAR
MOMOTOSE AO COLLAB INVITATION
A BOLT FROM THE BLUE
FEW DEYS LATER
SUMERAGI IKON - 4TH PLACE OUT OF 4
MOMOTOSE AO
CALL ENDED
WE'LL MAKE DIRECT CONTACT
Translation:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hTiming:
\h\h\h\h\h\h\hEditing:
\h\hSriram Gurunathan
Mariana Martinez
William Haggard\h
\h\h\h\h\hQuality Check:
Translation Check:
S Bilyeu\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h\h
Michelle Tymon