EPISODE 18: WORLD WITH A FUTURE
AFTER DISEMBARKING, SQ LIVED WITH JINA.
AFTER SPENDING SOME TIME AT SCHOOL,
SHE BECAME A PRIVATE DETECTIVE FOR SOME REASON.
AFTER SELLING HER "SLIME" TO A BLACK MARKET DEALER
THAT CHIPIE INTRODUCED HER TO, COMET WAS ABLE TO BUY
THE SHIP OF HER DREAMS. ON A PLANET NOW COVERED IN SLIME,
THE BLACK MARKET DEALER'S ADVENTURE BEGINS...
"I'M TELLING YOU, BUD! I'M A LITTLE GREY!"
WITH THOSE MYSTERIOUS PARTING WORDS,
SHIGEMICHI WAS NEVER HEARD FROM AGAIN.
AFTER RETURNING TO GLYZE WITH RACIO,
REMNAN BECAME THE LEADER OF A GROUP OF REBELS.
HIS ENEMIES FEARED HIS UNDYING TENACITY AND UNWILLINGNESS
TO PROVIDE EITHER QUARTER OR FORGIVENESS.
SHA-MING WENT ON TO BECOME A FAMOUS ZOOLOGIST.
THE ANIMAL COMMUNITY HE CREATED, AND HIS AMAZINGLY
INTRUSIVE METHODS OF "EXAMINING" HIS SUBJECTS DREW
EXTREMELY MIXED REACTIONS FROM THE SCIENTIFIC COMMUNITY.
JONAS CONTINUED TO WANDER THE GALAXY. HE DIED ALONE.
AFTER GIVING JONAS HIS LAST RITES,
STELLA ENTERED A SLEEP OF HER OWN,
TOGETHER WITH THE SHIP.
SHE AWAITS THE KISS THAT WILL AWAKEN HER...
AFTER RETURNING TO GLYZE, RACIO GREW DISILLUSIONED WITH
THE AUTHORITARIAN GOVERNMENT AND STARTED A REVOLUTION
TOGETHER WITH REMNAN. THE GLORIOUSLY NUDE STATUE
OF RACIO NOW STANDING IN THE GLYZE REVOLUTION MEMORIAL
PLAZA SERVES AS A POPULAR MEETING SPOT.
AFTER LANDING, JINA RETURNED TO HER JOB AS
A SPACE TRAFFIC CONTROLLER. SHE LIVED A SIMPLE,
HONEST LIFE AND WAS LOVED BY MANY.
CHIPIE UNDERWENT FELINIFICATION, COMPLETING HIS TRANSITION
INTO A CAT. IT IS SAID THAT THE ADVENTURER COMET ALWAYS
HAD A BLACK CAT BY HER SIDE WHEREVER SHE WENT.
AFTER RETURNING TO NADA, OTOME PARTICIPATED IN
MANY RESEARCH PROJECTS. KNOWN AS
THE "MOTHER OF INTELLECTUALIZATION,"
SHE BECAME A SYMBOL OF HUMAN AND ANIMAL INTEGRATION.
KUKRUSHKA WENT WITH OTOME TO NADA.
AFTER SPENDING SOME TIME THERE, SHE SUDDENLY DISAPPEARED.
NO ONE KNOWS WHERE SHE ENDED UP.
UNKNOWN.