Hell's Paradise
A faint flower was blooming
unnoticed by anyone
Not a burning red,
but flickering serenely in red
I've been pausing for a long time
dragging my past at my feet
If I break free from this ambivalence,
will I be able to bloom by its side?
The future is slipping away
between my fingers
What mistake did I make
to pay this price?
Always hurting myself
and hesitant even to a small joy
I want to stop now
The flower just bloomed in dignity
and that was all I needed to be happy
I just wanted to protect this one flower
Wishing to be strong, I
picked up the vulnerability
I had once cast away
Can't break free from the ambivalence
In ambivalence, I become myself
Like rooting strongly into the soil
like swaying ephemerally to the wind
I'm slowly loosening myself to bloom
Hell's Paradise
Love and Karma
Yamada Asaemon Toma
Several Moments Earlier
Yamada Asaemon Shion
Nurugai
On the other side, even today
Someone is unraveling,
yet they still stand
A stab to the chest, this loneliness
Points and lines,
breaking off and vanishing
My shattered mask
It's more than I can bear
But I must keep on living
Tomorrow awaits to greet me
It's endless
And so fragile
Is it better to believe
hearts don't exist at all?
Radiant and soft
Was the hand
I squeezed back on that day