OH?
CONTRACT / KOHAKU ICHIMURA (WHO WILL BE
REFERRED TO AS "KI") AND YOI TAKIGUICHI
ONE, KI AND YT SHALL ESTABLISH A
ROMANTIC RELATIONSHIP ON AN
TWO, KI AND YT MUST KEEP THEIR ROMANTIC
RELATIONSHIP CONCEALED AND NOT DISCLOSE
THREE, KI SHALL NOT ENGAGE IN ANY
PHYSICAL CONTACT WITH YT, INCLUDING
GOOD EVENING. / THIS IS MY FIRST TIME
MESSAGING. / IT'S TAKIGUICHI.
GOT IT.
GRAB
BROWN SUGAR WARABI MOCHI
APRICOT JAM
BEAN DAIFUKU / LEMON DAIFUKU
MOON VIEWING
RABBIT MANJU
FLOWER GARDEN
GOT IT.
NASU OYAJI CURRY
GREEN TEA
UNAWARENESS
TRANSLATION: YUKARI MURASE-LOUDEN
TIMING: ANDY ELLIS
EDITING: GABRIELLA ALABANZA
QUALITY CONTROL: SALEM ALABANZA
FINAL QUALITY CONTROL: ELIZABETH ELLIS