You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
CRACK
Smooch Smooch
Octopus Rice Crackers
So Good,
You'd Want to Kiss It!
M
ME
MEN
MENA
MENAC
MENACI
MENACING
ribbit
wriggle
Bye
See ya!
Kisu
ANGEL'S
KISS
Kiss
A girl friend kissed me
A Girl Suddenly Kissed You?!
The Psychology Behind It and How to Handle It
Sports Day
Executive
Committee
Team
clap
ba-dump
hesitating
This Kiss
Calm
Eiyu
Tension
Sports Day
Event Selection
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
Episode 10
Feeling the Afterglow Kiss After Kiss? Become a Sports Day
Committee Member? Still Won't Start a Rom-Com