EEEK
FULL POWER
VISUALIZATION
PREPARING WORDS...
YAY YAY YAY
SIGH...
NOT THIS AGAIN...
WORDS AND THOUGHTS
COMMUNICATION SKILLS
ARGHHHHH...
AND REALLY, YOU SHOULD
LISTEN TO THE LECTURE.
BOW
STAAAAARE...
BREAD FESTIVAL
30 PTS IS GUARANTEED A PRIZE!
EVERY DAY, BREAD
GASP
AAAAAAAA...
IN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
YAY YAY YAY
YAMADA (AGE 9)
ZIIIIING
IN MIDDLE SCHOOL
HA HA HA
ATHLETIC, NOISY
BOOKISH, QUIET
SENSE OF HUMOR
"THIS IS FUN!", "THIS IS FUNNY!"
DAAAAAZED...
TRA LA LA
LIBRARY
HA HA HA
AAAAAAAAA...
HAPPY
ANGRY
SAD
FUN
* SHE HAS SUCKED HER LIPS ENTIRELY
INSIDE HER MOUTH TO KEEP FROM GRINNING.
NISHI-SAN LIKES BREAD
NISHI-SAN IS COLLECTING BREAD STICKERS
NISHI-SAN, YOU CAN HAVE THIS
TH-THANK YOU
YAMADA
HONDA'S GRANDPA
JUST LISTENING IS FUN...
NOTICE ALREADY...
YAY YAY
〇〇 MIDDLE SCHOOL 3-〇 GROUP (2)
▢▢▢ HAS LEFT THE GROUP, XXX HAS LEFT
THE GROUP, △△△ HAS LEFT THE GROUP
SERIOUSLY, YOU...
REALLY...?
HUH?
STAAAARE...
30 PTS IS GUARANTEED A PRIZE!
OLDER BROTHER'S ROOM
BUT SHE WANTS TO TALK ON THE PHONE
FATHER = GOLF
GRANDMA = GRAND GOLF
KONEKO-MACHI LIBRARY
KONEKO-MACHI COMMUNITY CENTER
THUD THUD
TANI
FATHER, MOTHER
WHAT?
THUD THUD THUD
THUD THUD THUD THUD
"THERE'S NO ONE HOME RIGHT NOW."
* DINING ROOM
* STUDYING SERIOUSLY
GROWL...
GROWL
MOTHER
COULD PROBABLY TELL HER...?
FATHER
HMMM...
BROTHER
DEFINITE NO
THANK YOU FOR THE MEAL
"HIS ROOM"
DESK MAT
SHOCK ABSORBING
DISCOUNTED SET
SHE COULDN'T FIND A MORE
NATURAL WAY TO BRING IT UP
GRADUATION
TANI
OHHHHH
ADOOOOOORABLE
GRIN...
"FRIEND"?
"GIRLFRIEND"?
SO VERY AVANT-GARDE...!!!
FIDGET FIDGET FIDGET