STUDENT COUNCIL OFFICE
PREPARING FOR SPORTS DAY
ADDITIVE-FREE COUGH DROP
ALL ALONE WITH YOU UNTIL DARK
LIBRARY
STUDENT COUNCIL
FOR SPORTS DAY
SORRY, I'M RUNNING A TEMPERATURE
ARE YOU OKAY? REST UP TODAY.
BROADCASTING ROOM (TEMP)
BROADCASTING CLUB - CONFESSION
PROXY CONFESSION SERVICE
RED TEAM - WHITE TEAM
PERSON YOU RELY ON MOST
PERSON WHOSE VOICE YOU LIKE THE MOST
BROADCASTING ROOM (TEMP) | CONFESSION
BROADCASTING ROOM (TEMP)
PROXY CONFESSION SERVICE
BROADCASTING CLUB ADVISOR
ANDO LEMON (27)
THE ADVISOR'S CALLED LEMON-CHAN
TRANSLATION: SRIRAM GURUNATHAN
TIMING: MARIANA MARTINEZ
EDITING: WILLIAM HAGGARD
QUALITY CHECK: S BILYEU
TRANSLATION CHECK: MICHELLE TYMON