Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 9: People Who Can See Them Aren't Scary?
Punishment Room
I won't say mean things
\h\h\h\hto my friends anymore.
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
I truly regret what I did, and hope I can
make up with my friends. I understand this
is home to others who each have their own...
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
I feel profound remorse when looking back on who I was until yesterday.
I understand that my actions and words caused distress and harm to others
at the facility, and I deeply regret that. Moving forward, I am determined
to make a fresh start and become a better person.
First, I would like to sincerely apologize for repeatedly making careless
remarks towards my friends who live at the same care facility, and for
causing them harm as a result. I regret allowing my own anxiety and painful
experience turn into anger in my words. Moving forward, I want to focus on
respecting others' feelings and building relationships where we understand
one another.
I further express my deep remorse for repeatedly behaving and speaking
in ways that caused fear among the staff and fellow residents. They are here
to support us and deserve our respect. Going forward, I will remember this,
work cooperatively, and make an effort to build a safe and mutually
supportive environment.
I fully acknowledge that my past actions resulted in my isolation from those
around me. From now on, I will actively engage in communication, cooperate
with others, and strive to create a community filled with mutual support
and smiles. I sincerely pledge to become someone who brings positive
influence to others through my words and actions, and who treats everyone
with respect. I am truly sorry for
truly
sorry
for
I, the psychic Mob Osamu,
will protect you, Namu-san.
Execute
at once
Up until he said that, I thought I was
the only one who saw a different world.
Execute
\hat once
Purify
Chie-sensei Isn't Scary
You can't just say "No" to everything.
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
discarding whatever doesn't suit them.
Hasumi Chie
She's so amazing
I can't contain myself
Kaya-sama is supreme
I, the psychic Mob Osamu,
will protect you, Namu-san.
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary