Unread Messages
Kukuru and Wagari are fighting near
the hot springs!
Little Mine Book
Mixed Martial Artist
Futo Ryuno
Lame
Sticky Love Bomb
Land Mine Connection
Beautician
Shota Ryuha
Land Mine Connection
Sumo Wrestler
Gintakewaka
Land Mine Connection
Digital Artist
Ginpei Ishiyama
Freak
Stay out of school
Go back to your ivory tower
Get lost
Milk
Kiyomi Urusugawa
Eru Kusaba
Out of the fight
Enflame
Eye
Shoulder
Dei Surugi  To: atggldq
HOLY SHIT UR UGLY LOLOLOL GUESS THEY
LET ANYONE BE AN IDOL THESE DAYS
WHAT ARE YOU A BEHEMOTH
Mayolar To: sO.nWpYzU
Reported
Sayaka-chan stan To: sO.nWpYzU
Who the hell is this guy?
Pretty sad to get your kicks riling people up online
Pavlov-san To: sO.nWpYzU
Nobody likes you
Five Minutes Earlier
Order
Attack Kukuru Kasubata
Dance to death