Tokyo Police
2nd District Police Station
Nao Kanzaki
Ms. Nao Kanzaki,
Congratulations.
You have beaten the 1-in-100,000 odds
to participate in the Liar Game Tournament.
The Legendary Con Artist
100 Million Yen Battle
Mitsuo Tanimura Law Office
Progress Report
Kazuo Fujisawa
Nao Kanzaki
You are currently losing. The game will end in 29 days.
Fujisawa-sensei
Progress Report
Kazuo Fujisawa
Nao Kanzaki
You are currently losing. The game will end in 29 days.
The Latest on Massive Scam
Genius Con Artist to Be Released Soon
Shinichi Akiyama, soon to be released
Izakaya Yocchan
Japanese Sake,
Shochu, Craft Beer
Izakaya Yocchan
Strawberry au Lait
Umeboshi Rice Ball
Coarse Red Bean Bun
Game Ends
Next Time
Shockwave