SUMMER FESTIVAL!
GIRL'S HEART
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
snug
Cold
Hotel
In bed
Morning After
Missed bus
Not Against It
Friend
Spent the Night
INARI FIREWORKS
INARI
FIREWORKS
INARI FIREWORKS
SUMMER KISS
Shio has always been so generous.
INARI
FIREWORKS
My Childhood Friend
Is Just Too Cute
All childhood friend lovers rejoice!!
"You maggots! Do you wanna go out
with your childhood friend?!"
Lid
COLD
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
Episode 7
Relationship Talk? Sharing Half?
Festival Vibes? Still Won't Start a Rom-Com