Top Secret
Me
Hirose
Plan to Become Hirose's Friend!
Walk home after school together
Walk to school in the morning together
Eat lunch together
Listen to our favorite songs together
Help each other study
Exchange contact information
Hang out after school
Hang out on the weekend
Call each other by our given names
Plan to Become Hirose's Friend!
Walk home after school together
Walk to school in the morning together
Top Secret
Plan to Become Hirose's Friend!
Walk home after school together
Walk to school in the morning together
Eat lunch together
Listen to our favorite songs together
Help each other study
Exchange contact information
Hang out after school
Call each other by our given names
Hang out on the weekend
Hang out after school
Exchange contact information
Help each other study
Listen to our favorite songs together
Eat lunch
together
Top Secret
Vexing! Are They an Item?!
RIP
Friend
SEETHE
Sentenced
to Baldness
Easy to Drink!
Gigant Protein
For a Healthy Body and Mind
Gigant Balance!
Avocado Flavor
Gigant Protein
*Follow the recommended serving size
Nurse's Office
At the extracurricular lesson
in Yokohama...