JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Seriously?
Kenjaku's Objective
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
Idle Transfiguration
Insufficient Cursed Energy
Kenjaku's Objective
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
How?
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Why?
Unknown
How?
Assimilate Mankind With {}Tengen
Tengen
Star Plasma Vessel
Ordinary Person
Assimilation Possible
Assimilation Impossible
Star Plasma Vessel's Death
Assimilation With the Star Plasma Vessel Prevented
Tengen
Tengen's Evolution
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Out of Control
Kenjaku's Objective
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
How?
Why?
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Unknown
Kenjaku's Objective
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
How?
Why?
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Unknown
Why?
Suguru Geto's Death
Obtained Cursed Spirit Manipulation
Obtained Idle Transfiguration
Star Plasma Vessel's Death
Tengen's Evolution
Obtain Tengen
Assimilation With Star Plasma Vessel Prevented
Tengen's Evolution
Obtain Tengen
Assimilation With Star Plasma Vessel Prevented
Tengen's Evolution
Obtain Tengen
Tengen
Star Plasma Vessel
Six Eyes
Kenjaku's Objective
Stop Tengen's Assimilation
Unpredicted Event
Toji Zen'in Intervenes
Kenjaku's Objective
Zen'in Toji Intervenes
Star Plasma Vessel's Death
Cursed Spirit Manipulation
Prison Realm
The Culling Game
Mankind
Tengen
Assimilation
Incomplete
The Culling Game
Mankind
Tengen
The Culling Game
Warm-Up
Assimilation
Success
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
The Culling Game
Mankind
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
Tengen
The Culling Game
Details
7: The Game Master must approve any additional rules
requested under Rule 6 above, except when
the Rule would significantly hinder
the continuation of the Culling Game.
7: The Game Master must
hinder the continuation
6: By spending 100 points, not counting the initial point value assigned to them,
Players may negotiate with the Game Master to add an additional Rule to the Culling Game.
By spending 100 points
add an additional Rule
Create a Rule to Escape the Culling Game
Free Satoru Gojo
Tell us.
Prison Realm
Satoru Gojo
Prison Realm Back
Inverted Spear of Heaven
Black Rope
They said it's all gone.
Prison Realm Back
Inverted Spear of Heaven
Black Rope
Angel
Hana Kurusu
Episode 50
About the Culling Game
Satoru Gojo
Prison Realm
Prison Realm Back
Angel
Yasohachi Bridge's River
Other Side
Colonies' Barriers
*"The Challenging Land"
The catchphrase issued in '99 by
the Hokkaido Government Office.
The Culling Game
Warm-Up
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
Warm-Up Complete
The Culling Game
1: After awakening their Cursed Technique,
players must go to a Colony of their choice within 19 days
and pledge their participation in the Culling Game.
Remaining Time Until Tsumiki
Must Enter the Culling Game
Obtain 100 points and add a rule
allowing people to escape.
2: Players breaching the first rule shall be
stripped of their technique.
3: Non-Players shall become Players upon
entering a Colony, and their entry shall be taken
as pledging to participate in the Culling Game.
upon entering
4: Players will receive points upon
ending the life of another Player.
ending the life
5: Points shall be designated based on the value
that the Game Master gives their life,
and fundamentally, a sorcerer will be worth
5 points while non-sorcerers will be worth 1 point.
fundamentally
a sorcerer will be worth 5 points
non-sorcerers will be worth 1 point.
Game Master
Kogane
Not the Game Master
5: Points shall be designated based on the value
that the Game Master gives their life,
and fundamentally, a sorcerer will be worth
5 points while non-sorcerers will be worth 1 point.
6: By spending 100 points, not counting
the initial point value assigned to them,
Players may negotiate with the Game Master
to add an additional Rule to the Culling Game.
100 points
add an additional Rule
6: By spending 100 points, not counting
the initial point value assigned to them,
Players may negotiate with the Game Master
to add an additional Rule to the culling game.
7: The Game Master must approve any additional rules
requested under Rule 6 above, except when
the Rule would significantly hinder
the continuation of the Culling Game.
7: The Game Master must approve any additional rules
requested under Rule 6 above, except when
the Rule would significantly hinder
the continuation of the culling game.
8: Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days of
joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
do not show
a change
8: Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days of
joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
The Culling Game
Future Actions
Choso
Yuki Tsukumo
Guard Tengen
Maki Zen'in
Retrieve Cursed Tools from the Zen'in Clan
Juzo Kumiya's Atelier
Maki Zen'in
Retrieve Cursed Tools From the Zen'in Clan
Okkotsu
Participate in the Culling Game
Meet Up With Panda
They're thinking that having Okkotsu near
Itadori would keep Fushiguro safe, but it
would be a more efficient use of their
forces for Okkotsu to act alone.
Megumi Fushiguro
Yuji Itadori
Meet Up With Kinji Hakari
Kinji Hakari
Kenjaku's Objective (Road Map)
1 Year Ago
Suguru Geto's Death
Obtained Cursed Spirit Manipulation
Absorbed Mahito
Obtained Idle Transfiguration
Turn Mankind Throughout All Japan
Into Sorcerers With Idle Transfiguration
Insufficient Cursed Energy
12 Years Ago
Toji Zen'in Intervenes
Amanai Riko Murdered
6 Years Ago
Obtained Prison Realm
Assimilate
Star Plasma
Vessel
Tengen
October 31st
Satoru Gojo Sealed
Guard   Fate
Six Eyes
Assimilation Failed
Tengen's Evolution
Becomes a Target for
Cursed Spirit Manipulation
Assimilation With People Aside from
the Star Plasma Vessel Becomes Possible
Goal: Warm-Up for Assimilation
Absorb Tengen With Cursed Spirit Manipulation
The Culling Game
Make Modern Sorcerers and Sorcerers Awakened
or Incarnated Through Idle Transfiguration Fight
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
The Culling Game's Objective
Colony
Idle Transfiguration
Modern Sorcerers
Incarnated Sorcerers
Those Whose Cursed
Techniques Awakened
Fight
The Culling Game: Rules
Stock Up Cursed Energy
Rule Forcing Them to Fight
Use Stocked-Up
Cursed Energy
to Move the Barriers
Designed to Ferry
the People of Japan
to the Other Side
10 Colonies Throughout Japan
Forced to Cross to the Other Side (= Cursed)
Warm-Up
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Itadori's Friends' Mission
1. Free Satoru Gojo
Tengen Possesses
Open Prison Realm Back
Obtain Prison Realm
Kenjaku Possess
Can't Do Without
the Front Gate
To Force It Open...
Inverted Spear
of Heaven
Black Rope
Angel
Culling Game Player
Satoru Gojo Destroyed
Miguel and Okkotsu Failed to Find
Technique That Extinguishes
All Cursed Techniques
In the Colony on the East Side of Tokyo
2. Rescue Tsumiki and
Reluctant Players
Consume 100 Points (Per Rules 6 and 7) to Add a Rule
7. ~Add a Rule Allowing Escape from the Culling Game
Persuade Players With 100 Points
and No Intention of Adding a Rule
Each Person's Actions
Maki
Go Retrieve Juzo Kumiya's Cursed Tools
Fushiguro Has Become
the Head of the Zen'in Clan
Go to the Zen'in Clan's Forbidden Vault
Meet Up With Panda
Okkotsu
Go On
Ahead Alone
Gather Information
Itadori    Fushiguro
Recruit Help
Recruit Kinji Hakari
Tsukumo      Choso
Guard Tengen
Participate in the Culling Game
Remain in the Tombs of the Star
50-50...
Culling Game Player
Fumihiko Takaba
Next Episode
Perfect Preparation