MIDDLE SCHOOL
ALUMNI GATHERING
AH HA HA
HEE HEE
POUT
FLASHBACK TO
THE PREVIOUS EPISODE...
DON'T LEAVE ME
BEHIND, TANI...
YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
(BECAUSE
I'D
FEEL
CONFLICTED
ABOUT
IT)
STAND-IN COMMENTATOR
SILENCE . . .
Thank goodness
WHAT?!
RIHITO
INCOMING CALL
THINKING
ABOUT IT
MOUTHING
FLAP
OTHERWISE THERE'S
NO POINT IN MY
GETTING TRICKED...
BA-DUMP
GLOOM...
SAVE
BA-DUMP...
I'VE SEEN IT...
I'VE SEEN IT BEFORE...
Urk....
BACK TO THE START AGAIN
THAT WAS
"BEING SHY"
HEART POUNDING...
AN "EVEN THE GOING-HOME
CLUB WANTS TO EXERCISE!"  GATHERING
(HELD IRREGULARLY)
GOT SWEPT ALONG INTO GOING HOME TOGETHER PART OF THE WAY
BA-DUMP
PANIC
WORRY
HEH
HNGH....
HE NOTICED...
BA-DUMP
THUMP
PSHHHHH
WHABAM-THUMP
BA-DUMP
THMP
THUMP...
WHEW
BA-DUMPPPPP ! !
FWOOSH
SILENCE
SHOPPING AT THE SCHOOL LUNCH COUNTER
WHAT...?
YAY
*THIS IS
TAIRA'S
SENSE OF
FAIRNESS
BA-DUMP
SHOCK
PANT
GASP
GASP...
PANT
GASP
GASP...
PANT
AFTER SCHOOL
YEEEEEEAH
BAAAAAM
MISCELLANEOUS SHELF-WORN TOYS
CLEARANCE SALE!
WOW
YAY
WHOA
WOW
YAY
WORRY
REQUEST
ABSOLUTELY
DOES NOT APPLY
DOES NOT
QUITE APPLY
NEITHER
APPLIES
SOMEWHAT
ABSOLUTELY
APPLIES
MENTAL SURVEY SHEET
ANXIOUS
WORRY
BA-DUMP
Squeeze
INFORMATION ON
THE GIRL GLEANED FROM
CONVERSATIONS UP TO NOW
SAME SCHOOL
DIFFERENT CLASS
SHY
MATCHES THE PROFILE
THUMP
FWOOSH
EMBARRASSED