IN OUR
UNIFORMS...
FLOWERS IN A MIRROR,
MOON ON THE WATER
THIS IS...
GROWTH(?)
PHOTO
STICKER
YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
COMPREHENSION
HOW FUNNY
BOOM
SWEET POTATO!!
PRETEND
GOURMET REPORTING
MELTYYYY...
CHOMP...
CUTESY...
BOOM
STICKER HIDING SPOT
SHOCK
BECAUSE HE
HAS GLASSES...
THE PROCESSING
RAMEN
NO ANSWER
UNREAD MESSAGES BELOW
HOW'VE YOU BEEN? LOL
Commentary
NO ANSWER
UNREAD MESSAGES BELOW
HOW'VE YOU BEEN? LOL
Doin' Good!
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
GLOOM...
WEEKEND
HO-DON
TAIRAZUMA
SHUDDER...
I <3 OUR
NEIGHBORHOOD
WHOOSH
EX
Doesn't count
WAS
THAT
JAPANESE?
EX
SO IT'S
NOT REALLY
ALL THAT DIRE...
UNREAD MESSAGES BELOW
YOU WENT BOWLING
TODAY, RIGHT? LOL
EX (1)
AAAAAAAA...
YESTERDAY'S BAD MOOD TAIRA
OH, IT'S TAYLAZUMA
GLOOM...
SNEAK
SNEAK...
MORNING!
WHISPER...
SANDLOT BASEBALL
BROTHER
SLEEPOVER
DAD
HERE
YAY
SUZUKI'S
OLDER
BROTHER
AND HIS
HOMIES FROM
THE HOOD
THE YOUNG MEN SHE'S SEEN UP UNTIL NOW
GULP...
SILENCE...
BA-DUMP
POOF
WHOA...
DISTRACTING
THOUGHTS
ARE YOU
DYING...?!
YAY
DAD'S VERSION OF STYLISH
AND HIS CLOTHES SEEM TIGHT
FOR SOME REASON...
SUZUKI MIYU
WOBBLE...