Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 8: Reversed Isn't Scary
Family
Fall
Festival
October 24th (Sat)
Central Shopping Street - Station Front Street
Family
Fall
Festival
October 24th (Sat)
Central Shopping Street - Station Front Street
Mob Osamu
Voice Call
Mob-san
Did something come up?
Is it something related
to Kaya-chan's aunt?
Her name is Nana-san
Canceled
Civic Park
I have something important to tell you. Come alone.
I'm here. Where can we meet?
Where are you?
Hey
tsohG
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
The Sandbox Isn't Scary
Staff Room
Injury Log
Tamura Asuka — Playground
Collided head-on during tag and got a nosebleed.
Applied ice to stop the bleeding.
Sakurai Rihito — Same as above
Bump on forehead. Applied ice.
Nakahashi Yuki — Sandbox
Unexplained bruise on right arm. Applied ice.
Nice People Aren't Scary?
Family Fall Festival
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka