Exhibition
Takeru
Shiratori
This Week's Top Events
Groveling
on Your Feet
S Dog
(5) Revised Edition
Mixy-Mix
Mixy-
Mix
Takeru
Shiratori
Critters
Bodies
Takeru
Shiratori
Critters
Bodies
Takeru
Shiratori
Critters
Bodies
My Girl, She's Like the Sun, Yeah?
The Dark Nav
Login
Register
Calling all rescue specialists!
Client: Kenichi Kitami
Reward
yen
Client History
Job Description
Payment Details
Client Information
Job Description
Rescue our kidnapped leader.
If you're a master of armed and unarmed combat
with the athletic ability to sneak into any secret base,
wouldn't you like to put your skills to the test?
Experienced applicants welcome! Inexperienced ones, too!
What Is "Charm," Anyway?
No Unauthorized Personnel
Beyond This Point
Modified Bloodline
Curse?
My company's business suit
DUN DUN DUUUN
SIGH
My First