Ext.
Select
Hold
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 11: Mommy's House Isn't Scary
Origami
Manabi-ya\h\h\h\h\hCrayons
I'm sleeping all day,
— Shizuo
Ebisumori
Let every curse
be laid upon
Ebisumori Mutsu
Let every curse
be laid upon
Ebisumori Nana
Let every curse be laid
upon Ebisumori Mutsu
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Little Sisters Aren't Scary?
Nana
Mirai
Ebisumori
She's spending the day with your older sister
The Ebisumori Family Isn't Scary?
Chicke-Men
Rockin'
delish
Umashibo
Seaside
Grill\h\h
Gumi Tree
Neri Neri Neri-ne
Mix until fluffy
Chicke-Men
Rockin'
delish
Umashibo
Seaside
Grill\h\h
Gumi Tree
Neri Neri Neri-ne
Mix until fluffy
Chicke-Men
Rockin'
delish
Umashibo
Seaside
Grill\h\h
Gumi Tree
Neri Neri Neri-ne
Mix until fluffy
Funeral of
Ebisumori Yoshie-sama
The Curse of Ebisumori Mirai!
Her target is K-kun
from
Class 3!
Photo Order Form
Ebisumori Mirai
Curse
Begone,
evil
spirits
Infant and Early
Childhood Health
New Edition
Childcare Studies
Ebisumori
Mother's name:
Ebisumori Yoshie
Child's name:
Municipality:
Maternal and
Child Health Notebook
Facility or
Provider Name
eaten it when I had the chance...
That's my only regret.
But I need to help
the baby grow,
so Mommy's gonna
do her best
Doctor’s Notes
(Rest, Leave from Work etc)
Weight
Additional Tests
(Including Hemoglobin)
Blood Type Test
Record
Questions to Ask
If you have bleeding, your water breaks, or feel strong tightening
in your abdomen, see a doctor immediately.
Unlike normal childbirth, I hear it happens in an instant, so there's no pain or suffering.
I used to think a lot about the afterlife, but my sister said she would guide me as the shrine maiden.
Questions to Ask
If you have bleeding, your water breaks, or feel strong tightening
in your abdomen, see a doctor immediately.
Unlike normal childbirth, I hear it happens in an instant, so there's no pain or suffering.
I used to think a lot about the afterlife, but my sister said she would guide me as the shrine maiden.
So I'm not worried.
I've spent my life being protected by my sister.
But the day I can finally serve her and the Ebisumori family is almost here.
It's been moving a lot inside my belly
lately. I can feel the power to destroy
our enemy growing stronger.
Looks like my sister hasn't properly educated Mirai-chan.
It seems she doesn't understand the difference
between shrine maidens and Ohara-sama.
If Mirai-chan doesn't get educated, the one
who'll have a hard time later will be
Nana-chan as the shrine maiden
It seems she doesn't understand the difference
between shrine maidens and Ohara-sama.
If Mirai-chan doesn't get educated, the one
who'll have a hard time later will be
Nana-chan as the shrine maiden.
It's Mirai-chan's life, after all.
It seems she doesn't understand the difference
between shrine maidens and Ohara-sama.
If Mirai-chan doesn't get educated, the one
who'll have a hard time later will be
Nana-chan as the shrine maiden.
It's Mirai-chan's life, after all.
We should make sure it ends in a way
I'll leave in this notebook the things Mirai-chan
needs to know as the next Ohara-sama.
May she honorably fulfill her duty
as an Ohara-sama.
Ohara-sama's Role
Maternal and
Child Health Notebook
Ebisumori Yoshie
Sato Mirai