JUJUTSU KAISEN
THE CULLING GAME PART 1
SATORU GOJO HAS BEEN DEEMED
AN ACCOMPLICE IN THE SHIBUYA INCIDENT
AND IS HEREBY EXPELLED
FROM JUJUTSU SOCIETY.
IN ADDITION, ANY ATTEMPT TO FREE HIM
FROM HIS SEAL WILL BE DEEMED A CRIME.
JUZO KUMIYA'S MASTERPIECE,
THE CURSED TOOL "DRAGON BONE"
SECRET ART: FALLING BLOSSOM EMOTION
TECHNIQUE RELEASE - BLAZING COURAGE
EPISODE 51
PERFECT PREPARATION
JUJUTSU KAISEN
KUKURU UNIT CAPTAIN, NOBUAKI ZEN'IN
"HEI"
HEAD OF THE HEI, NAOYA ZEN'IN
THE SIX MEMBERS OF THE HEI,
THE NINE MEMBERS OF THE AKASHI,
AND THE 21 MEMBERS OF THE
KUKURU UNIT WHO WERE ABSENT
FROM THE ZEN'IN CLAN'S HOME
THAT DAY ALL MET UNTIMELY DEATHS.
AT PRESENT, NO RESIDUALS
HAVE BEEN DETECTED,
AND AUTOPSIES REVEALED FAINT TRACES
OF CURSED ENERGY IN THE CORPSES' WOUNDS
THAT ARE BELIEVED TO COME FROM THE
CURSED TOOL USED AS THE MURDER WEAPON.
SEVERAL DAYS LATER, BOTH THE
GOJO CLAN AND KAMO CLAN
MOTIONED FOR HEADQUARTERS TO REMOVE THE
ZEN'IN CLAN FROM THE BIG THREE FAMILIES.
HEADQUARTERS HAS TABLED THIS MOTION.
NEXT EPISODE
PASSION