Sato
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Episode 7: Hospitals Aren't Scary
Kids'
Room
Bye, Daddy.
In Surgery
Postmortem
Examination
Report
Hemorrhagic Shock
Placental
Abruption
weeks pregnant
Hemorrhagic Shock
Placental Abruption
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Sato Shizuo-sama
I sincerely apologize for showing up
so suddenly that day. I hope Kaya-chan
and Mirai are both doing well.
Please feel free to contact me if there's
anything you need.
Ebisumori Nana
Ebisumori
Nana
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Kaya-chan
\h\h\hIsn't
Scary
Playground Equipment
Isn't Scary
Mori-no-Oka Park
Let's follow the rules and play nicely
Let's wait our turn
Sit down before sliding
Don't climb from
the opposite side
Do not
jump off
Let's follow the rules and play nicely
Sit down before sliding
Staying Home Alone Isn't Scary?
Hanamugi Kindergarten
Guardian ID
For: Sato Kaya
Hanamugi Kindergarten
Sato
Kaya
How could you say something
like that to a child?!
Demon
Strong
Execute
at once
Incoming
Playback
Monitor
Indoor Call
Menu
Talk
End
Thank you very much
for picking her up.
I'm on my way to see Mirai, so I probably
won't be able to get home until around 6.
There's food I bought in the fridge,
so please have dinner with Kaya.
♫ Long Cat ♫
Long Cat
♫ Long, long, meow ♫
♫ Cat, cat, meow ♫
♫ Long Cat, meow, meow ♫
♫ Let's play, let's play together! ♫
♫ Long, long cat. Let's play together ♫
♫ Long, long, meow ♫
♫ Cat, cat, meow ♫
♫ Long Cat, Long Cat! Meow, meow ♫
Note-
book
Incoming Call
Hasumi Chie
Call Ended
Translation
Timing
Editing
Quality Control
Translation Check
Naomi Suda
Krzysztof Kunc
SMR
Gabriella Alabanza
Rei Miyasaka
Kaya-chan Isn't Scary
Mori-no-Oka Park