[HAKUSHI]
Wrong.
[YUKI struggling]
Kill him first?
[HAKUSHI]
Wrong.
[YUKI grunting, panting]
Play dead, then?
[HAKUSHI]
Wrong.
[YUKI grunting, panting]
[confused gasp]
[cries out]
[struggling]
[HAKUSHI] The right answer is
"avoid psychos," always.
[YUKI]
I'm confused.
Every game I played
so far, I killed people,
and I'm not talking
just one or two.
So doesn't that
make me a psycho?
I'm pretty sure folks out in
society would see it that way.
[HAKUSHI] Winning one
of these death games
doesn't depend on killing.
It depends on surviving
to the end.
And that's the reason
I've been pushing you
so hard to be
a pro at surviving.
But a homicidal
maniac's different.
They don't play death
games to win
and get paid,
so don't fight 'em.
Avoid 'em.
[YUKI] What if
I don't have a choice?
What if the only way to win
is to go head-to-head
with a psycho killer?
How am I supposed
to handle that?
[HAKUSHI] You'll have
to figure that out.
Your training's over now.
[distant struggling, gasping]
[YUKI] The psycho
Hakushi just warned
us about was probably the one
that threw the pine cone.
But then, that means
the killer followed
her all the way back here.
No way.
She'd never screw up like that.
Or did she?
Was there any other
way to explain it?
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
No.
The why and how of it
didn't matter anymore.
Right now, the one thing
I needed to focus on,
the only thing,
was surviving.
[static]
[pensive music]
♪ ♪
[gasps softly]
A-chan?
[laughs]
[YOUNG AIRI] What'll happen
to me if I don't become a swan?
[AIRI'S MOM]
What?
[YOUNG AIRI]
I'm a duck now,
but when I grow up,
and I don't get
to be a swan,
what do I do if
I'm still a duck then?
[gasps softly]
Hm.
I don't know.
What do you think
you should do?
[YOUNG AIRI]
If I stay a duck?
Mmm.
I don't know.
I think swans
are pretty neat,
but I like ducks more.
[chuckles] Oh, yeah?
Then don't worry.
Even if you stay
a duck, you'll be fine.
[chuckles]
Even if I don't grow
up to be a swan,
and even if...
I can't change
that fact,
still,
what else is there?
[sniffling, crying]
[distant banging]
I have to keep
trying and fighting.
[pleasant but distorted music]
♪ ♪
[ANNOUNCER]
Everyone, time to head back.
It's almost 5:00 PM,
which means
day one is just about over.
♪ ♪
Everyone, time to head back.
It's almost 5:00 PM,
which means
day one is just about over.
♪ ♪
[MOEGI] He couldn't
get closer to the Sun,
no matter how far
or high he flew.
[gunshots]
The Sun just seemed
to grow smaller
and get further away.
Then the Sun said,
"You are a Night hawk, yes?"
Ah, this must be hard for you.
Wait for night.
Then fly up to the stars
and speak with them.
After all, you are
not a daytime bird."
[pants, grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[HIKAWA]
Moegi!
[ANNOUNCER] Everyone,
time to head back.
You're alive.
Thank goodness.
There's a serial
killer on Team Bunny,
so now there's more to worry
about than our kill quota.
Are you heading back?
No.
I'm, like, lucky
I ran into you.
I was all alone.
Let's stick together
from now on.
That way, we can survive.
'Kay.
By the way, I hate to ask,
but I need a favor, sort of.
I'm, like, all out
of ammo for this thing.
If you have a bullet or two
to spare, I'd appreciate it.
Sure.
[HIKAWA]
You're a lifesaver.
[MOEGI]
I can spare one bullet.
[synthesized clock chiming]
[ANNOUNCER]
It's 5:00 PM now.
The gates will open again
for everyone at 6:00 AM.
It's 5:00 PM now.
The gates will open again
for everyone at 6:00 AM.
♪ ♪
[MOEGI]
I ran into a rabbit.
She was pale, like a ghost.
[cacophonous music]
♪ ♪
[static]
[frantic flapping, chittering]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
[cawing]
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[flapping fades out]
[flapping, chittering]
♪ ♪
[exhales nervously]
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
[gasps softly]
[gasps]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
What?
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[struggling]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[gunshot]
[gasping]
[kicking]
[grunting]
[cries out]
[panting]
[MOEGI screaming angrily]
[tumbling, panting]
[growls]
[gunshot]
♪ ♪
She had way more
experience than me.
No matter what I did, the ghost
was always one step ahead.
And now I'm her target!
[cawing]
I thought if I
killed my folks--
[somber music]
♪ ♪
I thought if I could just kill
my folks, then--
then--
[sobs]
I could be strong, like Kyara.
[gunshots]
♪ ♪
I knew it was impossible,
a nighthawk becoming a whale.
Yeah, right.
That's not--
[sobs]
I could never be.
[crying]
[KYARA exhales]
I love you.
[inhales]
[MOEGI] That's what
she thought Kyara
meant with each deep
breath she took.
[KYARA]
I love you.
[MOEGI] No one ever
held her like that
or made her feel
like that before.
So she didn't really
understand what it was then.
[KYARA]
I love you.
[MOEGI]
But that warm feeling she got
was the only reason she
needed to keep on living.
[deep breathing]
Like that nighthawk
trying to reach that star.
I--
I have to keep
trying and fighting.
I refuse to die here.
I refuse to die
because Kyara is my teacher!
[clattering]
[smoke releases]
[gasps softly]
[gasping nervously]
[gunshots]
[gasps]
[MOEGI] A white-hot pain burned
through every nerve in my body.
[soft piano music]
I took a shot
to my stomach, my shoulder,
and maybe one other place.
I didn't know exactly
where anymore.
♪ ♪
That ghostly girl made a face.
I couldn't tell if she liked
killing me or hated it.
[gun cocks]
I guess it didn't matter.
I was done either way.
And if this was
the end for me,
it meant I didn't
have to pretend
to be strong anymore.
I haven't felt like this
since I killed my folks.
I forget.
At the end of that story, what
happened to that nighthawk?
Did it become a star?
[sighs]
Oh, well.
I'll ask Kyara to read
it to me again.
Anyway, until my last breath,
I, Moegi--
[flapping]
[chirping]
spent my very last moments--
[crying]
Crying in frustration.
[cawing]
♪ ♪
[chirping]
"The nighthawk's star burned
on and continued to burn.
It kept burning
and burning and burning."
[flapping, chirping]
"And still,
to this day, it burns."
[water flowing]
[YUKI] That Stump
wasn't even a threat.
She had no talent for this.
That's all there was to say.
It seems the psycho
killer was her mentor.
[chuckles] She wasn't a very
good student, honestly.
Even if they'd done this
over and over a hundred times,
that Stump would have
lost every single time.
She was that hopeless.
[footsteps]
Still, she saw it clear as day.
The look on her
face as she died--
she looked like
someone who poured
her heart and soul
into something
and still, somehow, failed.
Here's this poor girl
who lived life as best
she could and still lost.
What does she get
for that when it's over?
[scoffs]
Nothing-- that's what.
The Stump girl's expression
was a mystery to Yuki.
Even if you told her
what it was about,
she still wouldn't be
able to sympathize.
Still, there was
something there.
It was different from
Yuki's weak reasons
for playing death games.
Stump girl wasn't one of those
"one-and-done type" players.
She played because
she was reaching
for something bigger than her,
something she thought
she could achieve.
She had a goal.
[lights clicking on]
And Yuki...
she killed it dead.
A girl, drifting through life--
killed it.
No, not someone alive.
Someone dead, a ghost.
A ghost stopped it
from happening
with her skills,
her instincts.
♪ ♪
Hakushi taught her how
to avoid taking responsibility
for what she did in games.
Deep inhale, deep
exhale, repeat.
[breathing]
But in the end,
that technique wasn't
enough to clear her mind.
No matter how
many breaths she took,
no matter how deep,
she couldn't shake it off.
Yuki's heartbeat
started to feel strange,
like something was stuck in it,
something sharp, like a needle.
There was a part
of Yuki that couldn't
accept the reality
of that Stump girl dying
while she was
allowed to live.
And she knew, if she
thought like that,
and bumped into the psycho,
she was dead.
[footsteps]
But her legs didn't stop.
She kept walking,
one foot after another.
If I really am a ghost...
why do I still have legs?
[footsteps continue]
[birds chirping]
[eerie musical note]
[KYARA]
Incredible, isn't it?
[theme music]
♪ ♪
Welcome back, bunny.