Campus Store
EXTRA EXTRA HOT
LIMITED EDITION
3CURRY BREAD
CURRY BREAD
You Can't Be in a Rom-Com with
Your Childhood Friends!
LIMITED EDITION
EXTRA EXTRA HOT
CURRY BREAD
Haunted House
Microwaved It
EXTRA EXTRA HOT
Watch me...
finish it!
Don't die, Akari!
Distracting Thought 1
Distracting Thought 2
swim
bounce
Enjoy the views of the ocean
and the highlands all to yourself
bump
drag
blush
We've Got This!
Please be quiet in the library
English
Translator:
Timer:
Editor:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Sachiko Takahashi
Mariana Martinez
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Rei Miyasaka
Episode 5
Extra Extra Hot? Finals Done? Bath Episode?
Things Will Never Change? Still Won't Start a Rom-Com