Nasu Oyaji Curry
Please select payment method
Cash
Credit Card
QR Payment
Point Payment
IC Card
Go Back
Call Clerk
m 0 0 l 185 0 185 80 0 80
What?
What's wrong?
Sorry. I'm getting distracted
because you're here.
It feels like a parent
classroom observation day.
Stop making me laugh
Hey
Today after school, would
you like to go somewhere?
It feels like a parent
classroom observation day.
Stop making me laugh
Hey
Today after school, would
you like to go somewhere?
I'm sorry.
I have work today
Okay, got it
I'm Just Jealous Is All
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis