My legs hurt...
My glasses are missing...
November 1, 06:02, Sendai Colony
Episode 54
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 1
JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Screw it,
I'll use it where I can.
The Next Day,
The Zen'in Clan Is Exterminated
He's actually a human who really existed,
though it was over a thousand years ago.
Sukuna?
Searching
Hajime Kashimo
Points
Rule Added
Current Colony: Tokyo No. 2
Hiromi Higuruma
Points
Rules Added
Current Colony: Tokyo No. 1
8: Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days
of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
Day
"Players may expend
points to leave the Culling Game."
Angel
Persuade Players with 100 Points
and No Intention of Adding a Rule
Hunt Down Hajime Kashimo
Hunt Down Hiromi Higuruma
November 12th 12:00 Tokyo
(Remaining Time Until Tsumiki
Must Enter the Culling Game:
7 Days 12 Hours)
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Boo...
Split Ahead
Next Episode
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 2