[birds chirping]
[Fujisawa gasps]
[NAO] Mr. Fujisawa, you're not
getting away with this.
[Fujisawa gasps softly]
[NAO] From now on,
I'm taking
the Liar Game seriously.
Also...
I'm not only getting back
my 100 million yen.
I'm going to steal yours
as well.
By the end,
I'll be declared the winner!
[♪ opening theme song playing]
SHOCKWAVE
[Fujisawa groans]
[NAO] I'd made up my mind
to fight back.
Moping and crying
wouldn't get me anywhere.
I needed to do something,
and I'd found
the perfect ally to help me.
I have a plan.
[NAO] Somehow,
a brilliant con artist
who brought down
a corrupt corporation
was standing in my corner.
He was bound to know
the right thing to do.
Your plan... What is it?
We only need to do two things.
Follow these steps,
and I guarantee
we'll get the money back.
Step one, tell him that
you're playing the Liar Game,
and be sure
to make it sound convincing.
As for the second step,
keep him under
constant surveillance.
Is that all?
That's the whole plan?
Yes. Trust me.
[NAO] That's why
I confronted Mr. Fujisawa
and told him my intentions
to win the game.
And why I began to monitor him.
Still, is this really enough
to get me the 200 million yen?
[Fujisawa gasps]
It's you.
Hello again.
I just want to let you know
that I'll be playing too,
on Ms. Kanzaki's behalf,
of course, in case
there was any doubt.
Which means that I'll soon be
taking 200 million yen from you.
That understood?
[grunts] Ha!
You're never going to get it!
-Are you sure?
-[gasps]
Believe it or not,
I have a perfect plan
to steal the money for her.
[Fujisawa exclaims]
[Fujisawa pants]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Fujisawa groans]
Good evening.
Is this the police?
A suspicious vehicle
has been parked
outside my house for a while.
[NAO] Huh?
No way! The police?
[chuckles] Wait, you let
the cops scare you off?
How was I supposed to react?
-You're right. Sorry.
-[Nao gasps]
[AKIYAMA] I figured something
like that might happen.
With that in mind,
I've leased this apartment
for a month.
-Have a look out the window.
-Huh?
Oh, it's my teacher's house!
Now we can watch him from here
without having to worry
about the cops bothering us.
[NAO] Thank you, Mr. Akiyama.
You're a good person.
At first, I thought you were
scary and intimidating.
But you've been
nothing but kind,
scheduling our shifts
so I can visit my father
in the hospital.
You even went through
the trouble to rent this place.
Please tell me, what reason
do you have to help me
right after your release?
Money, obviously.
Companies would be
out of their mind
to hire an ex-conman
as an employee after what I did.
If I steal the full 200 million
for you,
then I get a quarter of it.
Fifty million
for a month's work?
I'd be crazy to pass that up.
ONE WEEK LATER
[NAO] This was all assuming
that we would successfully
steal the money.
Why was he so confident
that we could actually do it?
-[door opens]
-[AKIYAMA] Time to switch out.
Anything out of the ordinary
today?
Doesn't look like it.
Early on, he'd go
to the pachinko parlor
or pick up his groceries.
But he hasn't even left
the house these past few days,
so it's been quiet.
Interesting.
-[NAO] Um...
-[AKIYAMA] Hm?
Can you tell me
what the point of all this is,
if you don't mind me asking?
-[AKIYAMA] Hm?
-So far,
we've spent the entire week
doing nothing
but staring at his house.
I don't mean to doubt you.
I just don't know
what we're trying to accomplish.
[AKIYAMA] What we're doing
is conman 101.
"Before springing your trap,
try to rattle your target."
Weaken them.
For example, bank transfer
scams against the elderly.
The scammers will impersonate
a loved one
panicking about money
over the phone.
So old people freak out
and open up the floodgates
to their finances.
You could be as level-headed
as they come,
but as soon as you lose
your composure
and start to waver,
you become a much easier mark.
In short, your former teacher...
We're going to drive him
to the brink mentally
until he cracks.
[Nao gasps]
Imagine if you were
in his situation.
His opponent declared
that she would win to his face,
then I told him that
I had the perfect plan
to steal the 200 million.
But he has no idea
what the plan is,
and on top of that
is under 24-hour surveillance.
-See for yourself.
-Uh?
They say they've got a plan,
but that would require
getting the money
from where I've got it stashed.
So what the hell
could they have up their sleeve?
Downright impossible,
there's no way they can do it.
Besides, I've got
a perfect plan of my own.
[Fujisawa gasps]
[exclaims]
Well then?
He definitely looks like
he's flustered and more on edge.
[Akiyama chuckles]
Yeah, knowing someone's
watching you all day
and all night is bound
to take its toll on a person.
The psychological pressure
keeps building up
with each passing second.
[NAO] All right,
now I understand
that the goal is
to break him down.
However...
How is that supposed
to get us the money?
He's got it stashed away
in a safe deposit box,
which means
we won't get anywhere
till we figure out
which bank he's using!
And even if we knew,
we only have a two-day window
to steal it from him
before the game ends!
He may not be keeping the money
in a bank in the first place.
[NAO] Huh?
I'll get right to the point.
The 200 million yen,
it's in his house.
[Nao gasps]
Really? What makes you say that?
Just think about it.
Imagine you've got 200 million
you want to hold onto,
so you go to the bank and put it
in a safe deposit box.
Meanwhile, your enemies
are spying on you and your home
during all hours of the day,
waiting for the perfect
opportunity to make their move.
What's your move?
I'd leave my house immediately,
and stay far away.
Why's that?
Because I couldn't bear
the thought of always
being watched.
The stress would overwhelm me.
The money's in the bank already,
so I'm better off staying
mentally and physically sharp
for the end of the game.
That makes sense.
But what if you chose
not to hide
the 200 million in a bank?
What if you hid it
in some bushes instead?
[gasps] Then I definitely
wouldn't just sit around
at my place!
I'd want to be in a spot where
I could always watch it!
That so?
Out there, it's vulnerable
to getting stolen
if someone finds out
where it is.
It doesn't even
have to be an opponent.
Some stranger could randomly
come across the money
and take it for themselves.
How strange then.
He claims the money's sitting
safe in a bank somewhere,
yet he's at home?
[Nao gasps]
[AKIYAMA] He knows he's under
constant surveillance,
so much so that
he's unraveling.
If the money's actually safe,
why put himself through this?
There's only one explanation.
The 200 million
never actually left his house,
and he's worried
that we might steal it.
Wait, you're right!
If the money's just been hidden
in his house all this time,
he wouldn't dare leave it
unattended,
not when he knows we're tracking
everything he's doing!
[chuckles] Say...
Might be time we turn up
the heat even more
with our surveillance tactics,
to keep him on his toes.
We'll make it abundantly clear
we know where the money's
been hidden this entire time.
Okay!
♪
LIAR GAME ENDS IN 16 DAYS
[NAO] The pressure
must have gotten to him.
Mr. Fujisawa's anxiety
was right on his face.
He moved around the house
even less than he did before.
♪
He hasn't moved.
I don't think he's even shifted
more than an inch.
Oh. That helps
narrow down the location.
[birds chirping]
[NAO] Which room could he have
stashed the money in?
Technically, he could've split
the 200 million up across
different rooms.
If he really wanted to,
he could've even split it up
thousands of times
across his whole house!
[Nao groans]
Nao, is everything all right?
[NAO] Yes!
Don't worry about a thing!
[NAO] I have to win this game.
Not for me, but for Father!
LIAR GAME ENDS IN 10 DAYS
Just look at him.
Not looking good, is he?
A perfect time
to mess with him even more.
[gas hissing]
[Fujisawa gasps]
It smells like
something is burning.
Where is all the smoke
coming from?
-[explosion]
-[Fujisawa gasps]
Was that an explosion?
What's going on?
Did something catch on fire
in the kitchen?
Is it the stove?
Maybe the tub?
Or the water heater?
[Fujisawa exclaims]
Damn it all.
-[dial tone]
-[Fujisawa groans]
Hey, Tanaka.
Yeah, it's Fujisawa.
Something's burning in my house,
and I need you to drop
whatever you're doing
and come help me find out what.
And hurry,
there's smoke everywhere.
Why would I call a fire truck?
I called you!
-[laughter]
-[Fujisawa gasps]
[AKIYAMA] You should listen
to your friend.
The whole point
of the fire department
is to call them
when there's a fire.
Granted, the "fire" you heard
was my new toy here.
The smoke was real, though.
It was coming through
your outside vent,
if you're still curious.
Gotta say, I'm more curious
about how you reacted.
Instead of racing
around the house
and calling
the fire department,
you stayed put
and called a friend.
It's almost like
you'd rather be burned alive
than take one step
outside this room.
But that's just crazy, right?
[Fujisawa groans]
[Akiyama chuckles]
Unless, of course,
you've got all of the game money
stashed in there.
[FUJISAWA] You can't know that!
Oh, we knew you hid it
somewhere in the house.
Finding exactly where
was trickier, but not by much.
We knew if you thought
the money was in danger,
you'd rush to your hiding spot
to make sure it was all right.
[Fujisawa grunts]
[FUJISAWA]
And I stayed right here.
Congratulations, young man.
You got me,
and I was none the wiser.
-[Nao gasps]
-Thank you.
But that's not all, I'm sure.
[Fujisawa laughs]
Oh, you haven't
the faintest idea, young man.
[chuckles]
See, it doesn't matter.
Even if you know where it is,
there's no way this game ends
with you getting
your grubby mitts on it!
My secret weapon!
-[Nao gasps]
-[Fujisawa laughs]
You're as close
as you'll ever get to the money.
Sure, it's not fancy,
but you can't go wrong
with cold, hard steel.
You'd need some
heavy-duty equipment
to get through this.
Why, you'd need a forklift
just to get it out of this room!
So, great job
wasting all that time
getting me
to reveal something
that doesn't change
a damn thing!
But you lost a long time ago!
[laughs]
[Nao cries softly]
It's all over?
It can't be.
It's time you quit
this pointless harassment
campaign against me
and start thinking about
how you'll pay back
the 100 million yen debt
you'll have by next week!
[Fujisawa laughs]
[Akiyama chuckles]
You're that sure
you've won, huh?
[FUJISAWA] Huh?
[AKIYAMA]
Was flashing your safe
supposed to break
our spirits or something?
Then what? Finally get
a good night's sleep?
That's funny.
-Let me be clear.
-[Fujisawa gasps]
This is nothing.
I can easily empty that safe
right from under your nose.
[Fujisawa gasps]
[Nao gasps]
[FUJISAWA] You... You think
you can rattle me
by spouting
some stupid nonsense?
Well, think again!
There's no way
that you can win!
[Akiyama chuckles]
[AKIYAMA]
Except that there is, though.
And it's really easy, too.
[Fujisawa gasps]
[grunts]
[Fujisawa growls]
[AKIYAMA] You see
how he crumbled
when I pushed back on him?
He was so sure
that we'd give up
the moment we laid eyes
on his safe.
All I had to do was not react
and watch his panic-addled brain
completely shatter.
Just goes to show
how easily we fall
to bias and dissonance.
I know what a bias is,
but what's dissonance?
I've never heard of it.
[AKIYAMA] Let's say you're
asked an A or B question,
and you think A is the answer,
but everyone else thinks it's B.
The stress of being
the odd one out
is a kind of dissonance,
and stress is something
people will do
anything to avoid.
Fujisawa was so sure of himself,
his bias made him think
he could break us.
Yet by not reacting
to seeing the safe,
I contradicted that bias.
The stress
of that contradiction
put him into a state
of cognitive dissonance.
To deal with that stress,
he changed his bias
to align with my reaction.
[FUJISAWA] He has
another trick up his sleeve!
It's the only thing
that makes sense!
People can be quite malleable
if you give them
the right push.
Do you really know
how to get the money
from the safe?
Because it's starting
to feel like
everything we've been doing
was just to get him to believe
that you had some master plan.
Oh, ye of little faith.
I do, in fact,
have a master plan.
And I know exactly how
to get the money from that safe.
I just can't tell you quite yet.
[NAO] I was still worried,
but trusting him
was my only option.
So, we waited and watched
as Mr. Fujisawa's paranoia
grew and festered.
His occasional odd behaviors
became more frequent
and more odd.
[FUJISAWA]
I know he has a plan.
But what the hell
could it possibly be?
Don't tell me. Could he have
gotten the combination
to the safe somehow?
No, no, no, that can't be it!
Where would he have learned it?
Besides, even if he had,
it wouldn't help him.
This safe needs
both a combination
and a key to open it.
And he'll only get that
if he pries it from my corpse.
There's no conceivable way
for him to open this safe.
Unless he breaks it open
by force!
[gasps] That must be it!
But how is he gonna
pull that off?
He can't pry it open.
It's far too thick
and sturdy for that.
But then,
if he'd gotten a hold
of a powerful enough
cutting torch,
it wouldn't matter how thick
the safe was.
He has a cutting torch!
I'm finished!
He can just wait
until I fall asleep,
sneak in with his torch,
burn through the safe door,
and walk away
with my 200 million!
Well, not on my watch!
[Nao gasps]
[Fujisawa grunting]
[FUJISAWA] Come on and try me,
young blood.
You want to cut open my safe?
Then I'll cut you open
with my kitchen knives!
[Nao breathes uneasily]
[chuckles] What the hell?
[FUJISAWA] Wait a second.
Even if he had some
industrial grade cutting torch,
at the very least,
it'll take him
the better part of an hour
to get that safe open.
It would be a lot faster
and more practical
to simply carry it off somewhere
and destroy it!
So that's his game!
[Akiyama chuckles]
What unhinged thing is your
paranoia telling you to do now?
[Fujisawa grunting]
What's going on over there?
Pretty sure
he's securing the safe
so we can't carry it off.
I'm afraid it's too little,
too late.
[NAO] There was still
a lot of uncertainty,
but I was grateful
for Akiyama's confidence.
If not for that,
I know I would've fallen apart
like Mr. Fujisawa by that point.
That was day 25.
LIAR GAME ENDS IN 4 DAYS
Only four more left until
the game was over.
[lock clicks]
[Fujisawa grunts]
[Fujisawa panting]
[Fujisawa gasps]
WE WILL COLLECT THE MONEY
AT 5:00 PM ON JUNE 14TH.
[FUJISAWA] We've reached
the beginning of the end.
[Fujisawa chuckles]
If I can hold it together
for just 90 more hours,
I'll win 100 million yen!
[NAO] I saw this
in the mail today.
No doubt they sent him
the same announcement.
In four days, at 5:00 p.m.
What now?
I can't just keep watching him,
can I?
You're doing exactly
what you need to.
By watching Fujisawa,
you're pushing him
in the right direction.
Am I?
Stop worrying.
You see, I've already cast
a spell on that safe.
And when the time comes,
it's gonna swing wide open.
[NAO] Huh?
LIAR GAME ENDS IN 3 DAYS
[FUJISAWA]
Only three days to go.
Just 72 hours
between me and millions.
LIAR GAME ENDS IN 2 DAYS
LIAR GAME ENDS IN 23 HOURS
LIAR GAME ENDS IN 12 HOURS
Twelve hours before the end.
Was Akiyama telling the truth?
Will it really open?
LIAR GAME ENDS IN 5 HOURS
Not much longer now.
I can't drop the ball here.
Nothing is going to keep me
from getting what's mine.
LIAR GAME ENDS IN...
...55 MINUTES
It's too late!
I'm going to lose!
[Fujisawa gasps]
[NAO] Akiyama, where are you?
I need your help!
The game is almost over!
Please, I don't know what to do!
Akiyama, you said
the safe would open,
but it still hasn't!
[Fujisawa gasps]
[Fujisawa chuckles]
[Nao gasps]
[Fujisawa laughs]
I knew you were bluffing!
You were just trying to trick me
into thinking
you could open the safe!
Please, Mr. Fujisawa...
I know I've been spying on you
and scaring you this whole time,
and I'm sorry,
but you don't have to do this!
We'll both be safe
if you give me
my 100 million back.
[cries] Please, Mr. Fujisawa.
Don't do this.
Please, Mr. Fujisawa.
You can save me
and my family,
-if you just help me!
-[grunts] Shut up!
[Nao grunts]
Mr. Fujisawa!
[Fujisawa scoffs]
[Nao cries]
[NAO] No, open the door!
Open the door! Open the door!
Please, Mr. Fujisawa!
Don't do this to me.
-[chuckles]
-There's still time!
Forty-five minutes left
and counting!
Help me! Please, help me!
Mr. Fujisawa, help me!
You're better than this! Please!
[FUJISAWA] Thirty minutes
and counting!
[clock ticking]
[FUJISAWA] Ten minutes!
[NAO] Please...
There's still time.
Don't do this.
[FUJISAWA] One minute left!
[ticking continues]
[FUJISAWA]
Eight, seven, six, five, four,
three, two, one!
I did it!
-I won the game!
-[Nao screams] No!
[doorbell rings]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
NEXT TIME
RESOLUTION