Yoi-chan!
You have a new message.
School
Motto
Steady progress towards your goal,
with sober and irreproachable conduct.
Regarding future
relationship plans.
-As a basic rule, plans should be discussed and
decided more than a week in advance.
-Avoid areas where the school staff can see us
together.
-Be mindful to behave appropriately and maintain
proper manners as a high school student.
(Avoid excessive physical contact.)
m 0 0 l 258 0 258 50 0 50
Regarding future
relationship plans.
Kya!
Nasu Oyaji Curry
You have a new message.
Shark Park
D-Dash
That's right!!
Stare
Yoi on trip
Earring
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis