Is our promise still on?
Hey.
What should we do about the summer festival tomorrow?
For meeting up and such
Wh
What
What time
What time did
No Smoking
Due to the
summer
festival,
vehicles
prohibited.
Under
Surveillance
Nature's Blessing Rice
Fortune Telling
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Is our promise still on?
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Is our promise still on?
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Is our promise still on?
I'm sorry. I have work today.
Okay, got it.
Is our promise still on?
Today
Manga Encyclopedia
You on the Night of the Festival
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis