[IMORI] Why, Moegi?
[MOEGI] I need you
on the other squad, that's why.
But--
[MOEGI] But?
But what?
- Nothing.
She'll go.
Right?
Yeah.
Sorry.
[whimsical music]
♪ ♪
No one here.
Yeah.
[rustle, gasps]
[rustling]
[hollow ringing]
[playing scales]
[groans]
Stupid bunny.
Hey, Kozue, look
at what I found.
Kozue?
Nishida?
Guys?
Where'd you all go?
Come on.
This isn't funny.
[rustling]
[groans]
[grunts, static]
[hysterical laughing]
What the hell are
they doing to her?
Interrogating.
Huh?
So, where's your team
hiding your weapons?
[YUKI] I mean, we were told
not to use violence, so.
I don't--
She'd talk quicker if they
broke a few of her fingers.
With a team as big as ours is,
that would cause problems.
Hm?
It's about morals.
Without them, there's no way we
can keep this group together.
And Hakushi put me here
to keep these newbies in line.
Huh.
[YUKI]
She says her name's Kushieda,
and there's about 30
on her team.
Their leader's
called Moegi,
and she's using fear
and intimidation
to keep everyone in line.
[SUMIYAKA] Yikes.
I guess our team's the better
one to be on, then.
Oh, yeah.
Here it comes.
Tickle!
Tickle, tickle,
tickle, tickle, tickle!
Hee hee!
Looks like playing instead
of, you know, torturing.
And weirdly enough,
it gets results.
Like, have you ever been
tickled by that many people?
Oh, hell no.
Never.
Tell us where
your weapons are.
Tickle!
Hey! [laughter] Don't.
[grunts, pants]
Oh, yeah.
I'm down with this technique.
What?
[grunts]
Nice try.
Don't!
[laughter]
Huh?
Hm?
[panting, gasping]
Sheesh.
What's your problem?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
My next game,
I hit the wall of 30.
[sighs]
Oh, come on.
You don't believe
it's a curse, do you?
I didn't think stuff
like that bothered you.
It's cute.
♪ ♪
[groans]
I'm gonna hug you a bit longer.
♪ ♪
[footsteps falling, panting]
Hey, stop!
Huh?
[hollow ringing]
[playing scales]
[yelps, grunts]
[scoffs]
[whimpers]
[chuckles]
[gasps, gunshots]
[frantic music]
Damn it!
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[laughs]
[panting, grunting]
♪ ♪
[struggling]
[screams]
♪ ♪
[gunshot pops, grunts]
[casing clatters]
[panting]
[grunts, thuds]
[static]
[footsteps echoing]
[MOEGI] Thanks
for saving my life.
[playing scales]
[AIRI] Of course.
We're teammates.
[MOEGI sighs]
I know, but thanks anyway.
[playing scales]
[static]
[KANON] [gasping]
[RECORDING] The tutorial
stage is over.
Go forth and figure out
the rest for yourselves.
The tutorial stage is--
Hey, quit doing that.
[RECORDING] Go forth and figure
out the rest for yourselves.
The tutorial stage is over.
I said quit doing that.
What the heck's wrong with you?
[curtain flutters]
[startles, gasps]
We-- we went out,
like you ordered.
But our squad was
killed, and, like--
there was nowhere else to go.
[stammers] I didn't
run away, I swear.
[RECORDING] --stage is over.
Go forth--
[MOEGI] I'm not mad.
I ran away, too.
Huh?
You did?
What happened out there?
You're OK?
[RECORDING] The tutorial
stage is over.
Are you hurt?
[RECORDING] Go forth and figure
out the rest for yourself.
It's OK.
Really.
How many Stumps
are still alive?
[RECORDING] Go forth and figure
out the rest for yourself.
I don't know.
[RECORDING] The tutorial
stage is over.
Go forth--
And what if
Team Bunny finds us?
I don't know.
[RECORDING] The tutorial
stage is over.
Go forth and figure out
the rest for yourselves.
[floor creaks]
[groans]
[clacks]
The tutorial stage is over.
Go forth and figure out
the rest for yourselves.
[gunshot pops]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[MOEGI] The night hawk
is an ugly, ugly bird.
It has splotches like flecks
of miso all over its face.
♪ ♪
Uh.
Huh?
[gasps]
♪ ♪
Hm.
[KYARA] Thanks for waiting.
Y-- you are so cool,
the way you killed her,
like it was nothing.
Please make me your student.
[whimsical music]
♪ ♪
[KYARA] Do you like animals?
Like dogs and cats?
I don't hate them, I guess.
[KYARA] Do you like
people who keep pets?
Uh.
♪ ♪
I-- I don't like how
superior they think
they are to, like, animals.
[KYARA] Do you mind
screaming babies on the bus?
Yeah, I think
they're annoying.
[KYARA] Are your mom
and dad still alive?
[groans]
They are.
[KYARA] Do you love them?
♪ ♪
[MOEGI] I'd like
to kill both of them.
♪ ♪
Oh?
If you have any
questions, ask Shion.
Uh, OK.
[bag thuds]
[sighs]
[crashing]
[whirring]
[groans]
[MOEGI] Hi, Shion.
I'm Moegi.
It's, um, nice to meet you.
[grumbles]
[crash]
Do you know what's
breaking all the glass?
[crashing]
Shut up!
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[creaks]
[whirring, thudding]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[water running,
dishes clinking]
♪ ♪
[MOEGI] I think your clothes
are cute, Kyara.
[KYARA] Do you?
Yeah.
Do you prefer loose clothing?
[KYARA] I do.
You'd look awesome
in something formfitting, too.
You got the body for it,
not like me.
♪ ♪
[KYARA] I can't stand
wearing tight clothes.
[gasps]
Sorry.
I didn't know.
♪ ♪
Hey.
I feel like going out
and killing someone.
Care to join?
[whimpers]
[KYARA] Well?
I--
We'll take the car.
[whimpers]
[clicks, water stops]
♪ ♪
I will teach you how to kill.
"'Well,' he said, 'the king did
decree that on cloudy days,
we could stop
playing our flutes.
We were only playing now
because it's so much fun.'
Then Pose stopped his
playing and spoke.
'But I don't think the king
would give us permission
to go off on some journey.
Why, the clouds could
clear any time now.'
The comet said, 'Oh,
don't you worry.
I spoke with the king
just the other day,
and he said it would be fine.
He told me I would have no
problem if the twins went
on a journey one cloudy night.
Let's go.
You know, I'm lots of fun.
I even have a fun nickname.
The Whale of the Sky.
Did you know that?
All those frail stars
that are like sardines
and pitch-black meteors
that are like killifish--
[rumbling, bubbling]
I gobble all of them up."
[cracking, crunching]
[thuds]
[gasps]
[cracking, crunching]
Have you killed
your parents yet?
[inhales]
No.
Not yet.
I see.
This is good.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
"The fern frond drank
the morning mist
and swayed to and fro,
green and cold.
[elevator dings]
The night hawk squeaked, cheep,
cheep cheep, high and loud.
Then he tidied up
his nest as best he could,
preened his down
and every single one
of his feathers,
and once again
flew away from his nest.
♪ ♪
The mist began to clear,
and at that moment,
the sun rose in the east.
The night hawk flew toward it,
enduring the dizzying
bright light,
flying straight and true,
like an arrow shot from a bow."
♪ ♪
[KYARA & MOEGI] "Sun!
Oh, sun!
Please, please,
take me up to you.
I don't care if I
burn to death.
Even a body as ugly as mine
will glimmer some
as it burns in your flame."
♪ ♪
[breathes shakily]
"The fern frond drank
the morning mist
and swayed to and fro,
green and cold.
[sobbing]
♪ ♪
The night hawk--"
[sobbing]
♪ ♪
[grunts, punches landing]
[choking]
[rasping, straining]
♪ ♪
[gasping]
[deeply inhales]
♪ ♪
[slowly exhales]
[gasping]
[deeply inhales]
♪ ♪
[slowly exhales]
[breathing steadies]
[deeply inhales]
[slowly exhales]
♪ ♪
[deeply inhales]
[slowly exhales]
♪ ♪
[deeply inhales]
[slowly exhales]
♪ ♪
[deeply inhales]
[slowly exhales]
♪ ♪
[deeply inhales]
[both exhaling]
[both inhaling]
"Sun, Oh, sun.
Please.
Please, take me up to you.
Please turn a weakling like me
into someone as strong as you."
[AIRI] Moegi.
Um, one of the girls
told me she found
one of ours, dead, naked.
She said her body
was all torn up.
Yuki.
Did you see that chick
with the caramel hair,
one of the ticklers?
Why?
Something up with her?
Don't know.
We can't find her.
Last I saw her, she was--
[HAKUSHI] Everyone!
[panting] Listen up!
Oh, no.
She's not gonna leave
enough for our quota.
What was that?
I'm sorry.
I-- I don't know
how to handle this.
Forget the plan.
Run, now!
Like a shipwrecked sailor who
can't stop drinking seawater,
she can't stop killing
once she starts.
The teams don't matter.
She'll kill everyone.
[HAKUSHI] There's
a bloodthirsty psycho
with caramel colored
hair on our team.
[gasps]
♪ ♪
[clatters softly]
[smoke whooshes]
♪ ♪